All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen
and were held captive, confined in a cage,
by Caesar Clown who rules the island
and were exposed to Shinokuni,
a weapon of mass destruction.
But they broke out of
the cage thanks to their ally ---
a Warlord - Trafalgar Law's tactful maneuvers
and were reunited with their crew.
Now, outside of this laboratory
is filled with the poison gas
but there is one passage
that could lead you directly to
the sea bypassing the air outside!
There is a big door marked
"R-66" that is an entrance
to the passage to the sea.
I'd rather not have to create a massacre
but I can only give you two hours.
Those of you who stay longer than that,
I can't guarantee your safety.
There are children who were kidnapped
two years ago in this laboratory!
Retrieve them and head for the "R-66" door!
Wait for me, Momonosuke!
I'll save you at any cost!
Hey, Luffy!
Get a grip!
This is just the beginning of the New World!
Yeah, sorry! I won't drop my guard again!
With Luffy in the lead, they start to move
to rescue the children and kidnap Caesar!
Gum-Gum...
...UFO!
"Tashigi's Tears! G-5's
Desperate Breakthrough Plan!"
Why?!
Why are they inside of the building?!
The brokers are watching this!
Damn! What humiliation!
The Straw Hats and the
group of Navy soldiers are...
...running toward the passage to escape!
What should I do? What should I do?
What should I do?!
The Master! He's like a devil!
But looks like everybody's okay! I'm so glad!
DON'T DO ANYTHING
I don't know who gave me this paper.
Did he or she mean Luffy and the
others can escape on their own?!
How did they break out of that cage?
Who gave me this?
Who cares about those things now?
I'm a doctor!
I have to save those children!
I found out the formula of the
drug and I got the sedatives!
Wait for me, kids!
I will heal you at any cost!
But come to think of it,
which way should I go?!
What are my soldiers doing?
Troops have mobilized
against them in A Building!
The main unit is preparing to make a
stand at the post in the back of B Building!
I'm sure what they want is
to escape from the island.
Then, they must be heading for...
...the path going directly
to R Building - Gate 66!
I won't let them do that!
Block off the passage
between Building A and B!
Close the gate there and isolate Building A!
And then, destroy Building A
and let Shinokuni flow in!
What?! But if you do such a thing,
it will also kill our guards...
Just do it!
Don't forget to place a
Surveillance Transponder Snail!
What?! M-Master...
Let's restart this open
experiment for the brokers.
I haven't fully shown them
my scientific mastery yet!
Just go already!
Y-Yes, sir!
Humph! How useless!
And what will you do, Vergo?
Only idiots will fall for such a trap.
You're not the only one who
will lose face if we let
Law and Smoker get away, Caesar.
I can't trust you to handle this.
I will cut everything up!
Oh? That's strange.
I can't find my sword.
You're not a swordsman.
Oh yeah, I'm not a swordsman.
Alright, I'll go strike down those squirts.
Where are you, Caesar?!
LABORATORY BUILDING A
I won't let you pass through here, Straw Hat!
I'm a gatekeeper of B Building
and a former pirate!
People call me "Machete" Run!
In the name of Master Caesar,
the scientist of love!
You don't have animal legs!
I'm not a fan!
What kind of centaur you are?!
Spider...
...desu.
Outta my way!
THE PASSAGE BETWEEN BUILDING A AND B
It's a huge tunnel!
Law! What's this buzzer?
It warns people that a gate
in this building will close.
And that's the only passage to Building B.
What?!
I guess he's trying to keep us out.
You better tell your men to move faster.
I don't know what Trafalgar Law meant
when he said he can only give us two hours
but we won't let you guys
get away, Straw Hats!
You have nowhere to run!
What is this buzzer?
Don't do it!
Don't stand in our way!
Ouch!
It's hot!
It's cold!
So dependable!
You three swordsmen!
Alright, let's go!
Th-They're coming!
I think we can make it to the
children pretty easily like this.
Thank you for carrying us, Brownbeard.
Don't mention it. But, guys,
why did you bring the dragon with you?
Well...
We thought that we could get away
from the gas by flying on him
but he didn't fly at all.
He doesn't fly now because
he got injected with sedatives.
But it wasn't a great idea
to let him in the laboratory.
Is he dangerous?
He's kind of cute...
This is a rare opportunity for us!
Take them down!
I'll take the credit!
Didn't I say "Don't do it"?!
C-Captain-chan?!
Wow, you became a Captain, Copy-cat?
But you have no fighting spirit.
That's right. Just go ahead.
Oh, yes, yes!
Thank you so much!
Wait!
G-5! This is no time for fight!
Go to the passage at the back now!
What?!
The only gate in this
building is now closing.
Caesar is trying to fence us in.
If we can't make it to the
other side of the gate,
we can't escape from Punk Hazard!
Just go!
What?!
Oh no!
Hurry up, you guys!
Do as Tashigi-chan says!
Carry the injured!
Hurry up!
Go straight to the gate!
How awful!
Robin, where were you?
Robin-chan!
Luffy asked me to do something.
Anyway, did you hear what the Navy girl said?
Come on, Brownbeard-cchi!
Go faster!
That's impossible.
This is the fastest I can run.
I'm sick of running!
No!
I'm not a samurai so I'll just say it!
Enough already!
Hey, why is Brownbeard with those pirates?!
That bastard!
Is he betraying the Master?!
The Master is our great savior!
Let's just run for now!
We're in danger, too!
Come on, G-5!
The gate is right there!
Hurry up!
It's really gonna close soon!
Come on, come on!
Experiment cannon, stand by!
OUTSIDE THE LABORATORY
Take aim at the outer wall of
Building A of the Third Laboratory!
Fire!
The wall's been broken!
H-Hey, don't tell me...
You've got to be kidding!
Run! Run!
No!
What is it?
Shut up!
Brownbeard-cchi! Faster, faster!
Help those fools escape.
The children, too.
Don't look back and keep running!
I'll handle it!
Tashigi-chan!
Oh, help...
Come on!
Get inside the gate!
If you can't make it, you're gonna die!
Faster! Faster! Faster!
Hang on tight!
Yes, we made it!
We did!
Barely!
Hey, where's Tashigi-chan?!
Tashigi-chan told us to go head!
What?!
Don't stop and go straight through the gate!
Come on! Hurry!
Hurry!
What're you doing?!
Hurry up!
Get me down!
Tashigi-chan! That's enough!
You have to survive!
Goodbye!
What?! Captain-chan flew in!
What's going on?!
I'm glad!
But why were you flying...
Move out of my way!
There are still many Navy soldiers outside!
No! It's filled with gas out there!
Move!
I said "No"!
The gate is gonna...
Let go of me! There are still...
There are...
--But the gate is already...
--There are... Let go of me!
Smoker-san told me...
...to help them!
So, move out of my way!
--No, Captain-chan, it's too late!
--There's... There's no time!
Don't be ridiculous!
Your colleagues
are still outside of the gate!
Outta my way!
No means no! Captain Tashigi!
Well done, guys!
We certainly got our beloved
Captain-chan in our hands!
Those scum!
I can't believe that many of them survived.
But I won't let anyone...
...get away!
Despite successfully getting through the gate,
the Navy G-5 are attacked by Vergo.
When Tashigi is in tears as she
witnesses her trusted superior
take down her comrades one after another,
a certain man from the Straw Hats appears!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Treacherous Vice Admiral!
Demon Bamboo Vergo!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!