Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and on their way
to the next stage—the New World—
they reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
But they have yet to gather
and are stirring things up as a fragmented crew!
We're gonna restore his dream!
We're the New Fishman Pirates!
Shark Grip!
No! I tell you this is no good!
What should we do?!
Nami-chin?
Camie, do me a favor!
What?
Zoro! The water is rising!
I have a favor to ask!
Let those two get out of here!
What about you?
No one can get away
with that guy chasing after them!
Don't stand in my way of conquering this country!
Um... Well, uh...
You found me!
She's big!
Don't tell me that that is...
Oh, no.
They kidnapped the Mermaid Princess!
No, Sanji!
Don't turn around at any cost!
Huh? What's going on?
If you do, you're gonna die, Sanji!
Protect Shirahoshi
Decken's Pursuit
I'm coming!
To wherever my Shirahoshi is!
It's death or marriage!
P-Princess Shirahoshi has...
really been...
kidnapped!
Hey, Wimpy!
Why'd you come out of Shark?!
I-I'm sorry!
Luffy-sama, please don't get mad at me!
He made Princess-sama cry!
What an evil pirate!
I feel terrible... Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
Princess...
He said "Princess"!
Don't tell me that's...
No, Sanji!
No matter what, don't turn around!
Hey, could it be
that the Mermaid Princess is behind me...
if I turn around?
Yes, she's there!
That's why I don't want you turning around, Sanji!
You almost died
after seeing some regular Mermaids!
So if you see the Mermaid Princess,
you'll lose all of your blood and it's over for you!
The Mermaid Princess...
It's said the most beautiful woman in the world—
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock—pales in comparison.
She is the most gorgeous of all Mermaids. And now, she's behind my back...
No! I beg you!
Don't turn around!
Chopper.
Rather than live a day longer
without grasping the dream within my reach,
I will live out my dream...
and choose to die!
What?! I thought your dream was to go to the All Blue!
No!
Sanji!
Huh?
Th-Th-That is...
Now I know how poor my imagination is!
She's magnificent!
That's quite simply...
the embodiment of absolute beauty!
He turned to stone!
Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
We gotta rescue her!
But they're the Straw Hats
who are strong enough to occupy the palace!
I thought he'd die from a nosebleed.
But he turned to stone!
That's new.
Maybe because of his blood donors!
L-Luffy-sama, I don't know... what to do...
Hey, are you okay?!
In any case, Hachi, who did this to you?!
Hey, what do you guys want?!
We caught them!
The Straw Hats! We did it!
We are sea hunters who risk our lives
catching Sea Kings everyday!
Pirates are no match for us!
Don't mess with the sea hunters!
The sea hunters did it!
Great!
You guys are fishermen?! We're not fish!
I remember you, too!
You're the punk who used to be in Arlong's crew!
You're safe now, Princess-sama!
Turn them over to the Ammo Knights so they can cut their heads off!
Um... It's not like that, everybody.
Luffy-sama was not...
Hey guys!
Something's flying towards us! There!
Huh? It's no use—we're not gonna be fooled!
What?!
Hey, something's really flying!
Is it just some coral?
No, somebody's on it.
Oh no! That's...
Vander Decken!
I found you! I suspect!
Shirahoshi!
Vander Decken-sama!
He must've been hiding for a long time and now he's finally shown himself!
Princess-sama, run!
We'll handle this!
I want your answer, Shirahoshi!
If it's "Yes," you can escape death!
You have to...
marry me!
You've been throwing weapons at her
for ten years in order to kill her
and now you wanna marry her?!
Stop messing around, Vander Decken!
The Princess must've been deathly afraid
for ten years because of you!
How dare you propose to her!
I want your answer, Shirahoshi!
I suspect it's "Yes"!
Um...
What do you wanna say?! "Yes"?!
Y...
You're not my type!
What?
Noooooo!
What?! That's the reason?!
Y... Y... Y... Y...
You bitch!
You trampled on my feelings
of ten years and now who will you marry?!
If you don't love me,
your very existence irritates me!
Drop dead, Shirahoshi!
Run, Princess Shirahoshi!
Hurry up!
We'll stop him here with our lives!
Don't go anywhere!
Stay there, Wimpy!
What are you saying?!
We can't trust you pirates!
You're Decken's accomplice, aren't you?
You want her to die?!
If you run somewhere, I can't keep you safe!
O-Okay, I'll stay!
Princess-sama!
How dare you scare her!
You evil pirate!
Sorry guys.
I have nothing against you but you're...
in my way!
Gear 2!
Luffy!
He did it with his hands tied!
Why do you wanna interfere
with mine and Shirahoshi's business?!
Are you the one who took Shirahoshi?
Are you the one...
that's been throwing things at Wimpy?!
I'll kill you both! Let me put you two together
and cut you into quarters!
Just try it!
L-Let me go!
Gum-Gum...
Jet...
Hammer!
Th...
That guy...
beat Vander Decken!
He's still moving but we can catch him now!
Shark! Wake up!
Sanji!
You alright?!
He turned to stone a while ago
but he looks happy now. He's conscious!
Okay, got it.
Mermaid Princess... Am I in heaven or paradise?
My dream came true!
I can die now!
Again, your dream was to go
to the All Blue, wasn't it?
Hurry up, Wimpy!
O-Okay!
Please don't yell at me.
It makes me really anxious.
The people on this island don't like us for some reason.
We've got to get away from here!
Thank you!
Wimpy! Let's go!
Okay!
P-Princess-sama, why did you untie him?
That evil pirate must've scared her again!
I am sorry, everybody!
I will be back by dinner!
What?
Go Shark!
Get away, you shits!
Don't let them get away!
Wadatsumi!
He looks familiar.
He's the Sea Spirit who attacked the Sunny!
He works for Decken!
I-It's the Great Monk!
Wadatsumi!
Stop them!
I got it!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
Jet...
Pistol!
My front tooth...
It cracked!
It hurts! It hurts!
That oversized brat!
Alright!
Wimpy, let's get to the Sea Forest!
Yes!
"Dragon"
Boss Hody! A pirate girl and a Mermaid
just exited Ryugu Palace!
Who cares?
If I can get rid of him,
there'll only be an old fool and his mob to take care of!
Shark Arrows!
Nami-chin, was it okay
to leave Zoro-chin and the others behind?
We couldn't escape with everyone.
That's true, but...
Don't worry!
They always make it through!
I know they're all tough.
But Hatchin said Hody is not only strong
but his ideas are dangerous, too.
They've gotten much stronger in last two years.
That aside, what kind of person is Jinbe, the former Warlord?
Huh?
Even though he is a pirate,
people on the island trust him
so he's allowed to enter Ryugu Palace.
I see. But he was in the same pirate group
as Arlong, wasn't he?
That guy—Hody—is a follower of Arlong.
Jinbe's message to Luffy was "Don't fight against Hody."
I know what he meant.
Isn't it because it's dangerous?
I hope Zoro and the others won't make Hody mad
as they get more involved.
In any case, I wanna see Jinbe!
He'll be waiting for Luffy at the Sea Forest, right?
The events happening now have deep roots in history.
They could shake up the whole kingdom!
I think he knows everything about what's going on.
Boss Jinbe does?
Camie.
Take me to the Sea Forest!
Uh-huh!
Listen, soldiers!
Yes, sir! We'll get rid of Hody and his crew immediately!
No-jamon!
Since I can't fight at full power,
you'd be sacrificing your lives for nothing.
We shall give up the palace for now
and meet up with Fukaboshi and the others
and wait for a chance to fight back!
Give up the palace?
Are you serious, Neptune-sama?!
Damn Zoro!
He thinks he can beat a Fishman in the water?
Usopp-san, I keep losing my strength and I'm going to drown soon...
You're dead already.
That's true...
Are you starting to suffer?
Humans are so disadvantaged underwater!
Zoro's gonna pass out!
Is that what Hody's up to?
I'm passing out!
Zoro...
That swordsman's dead!
How stupid is he?
Thinking a human can fight a Fishman in water!
What a pain in the ass.
But this is it!
Drop dead, you lowly creature!
Zoro!
Boss!
One-Sword Style, Draw...
Lion Song!
Zoro's group must escape Ryugu Palace
before it fills with water,
but the Fishmen take Energy Steroids
to enhance their strength
and gain the upper hand again.
Meanwhile, Luffy's group
has finally reached Jinbe in the Sea Forest
and he tells them of the shocking past events
involving Nami and Arlong.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Straw Hats Defeated?!
Hody Takes Control of Ryugu Palace"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Straw Hats Defeated?!
Hody Takes Control of Ryugu Palace