Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the Paramount War against the Navy,
Luffy made it to Maiden Island
where he was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
Luffy has been left with Dadan -
the mountain bandit of Mt. Corvo
and met 2 precocious kids named Ace and Sabo
with whom he pledged to be brothers forever.
Our brotherhood will always be with us!
So from now on,
we're brothers!
Yeah!!
I'm gonna become a pirate before
you do so just forget it.
That's not fair! I'm gonna
become a pirate first!
You're still saying a crap like that?!
Can't you both understand that
you must become Navy soldiers?!
"We will stand on our feet."
This is nice!
Yeah, it's great!
This is our hideout!
Here they are!
Luffy Becomes an Apprentice?!
The Man Who Fought the Pirate King!
Seasons come and go and now it's winter.
Sabo! He's coming to you!
Don't let him get away!
Okay! I won't!
Yes! We drove him to the bay!
Luffy! Get ready!
Here he is!
Let's go!
You can't get away!
Yes! I got him!
Good job, Luffy!
We got two of them today!
We can have a lot of danpa soup!
Yeah!
I did it! I did it! I did it!
I made a kill for the first time! Yeah!
Hey, look!
Luffy, watch your back!
My back?
A big tiger!
He caught wind of our prey!
Luffy, get away from there!
He just wants the danpa!
That's my prize! I'm not gonna let you...
...h-h-have it!
He's too tough for you! Get away now!
No! Go away, stupid!
Otherwise, I'm gonna beat you up!
--That fool!
--Luffy!
You bastard! Gum-Gum...
You bastard...
Gum-Gum...
Wait, wait, wait!
Let's run while he's distracted!
Okay!
I'll get even with you!
Sorry about your first prize.
Leave him alone. We had no
chance against that tiger.
But that was my prize!
He can't just steal it!
Y-Y-You fool! Don't shake it!
--You little...!
--Stop, Luffy!
Sabo! Pull us up now!
I-I got it!
Sorry!
We're home finally! Let's just
go to bed on such a bad day
Go to bed on a bad day?
Oh, I'm starving!
--It's your fault!
--Ouch!
But if someone steals the prize you
caught by yourself for the first time,
I can see why someone would get angry.
--But it's reckless to fight such a big tiger...
--That's something you would do!
Humph! Shut up!
It's great to have brothers!
If they come aboard my ship...
Captain, you keep out of this!
Leave it to us!
No, I'll fight too because I'm a captain!
Why are you laughing?
That's not gonna make your stomach full.
I made up my mind!
Ace! Sabo! You guys gotta come
aboard my ship! Okay? Say yes!
That's so sudden!
We decided to leave it to the future.
But it'd be fun to be with each other
and you'll need my help, won't you?
You're the one who needs help, aren't you?
Yeah.
No!
I'm gonna help you!
You guys are welcome to come aboard my ship.
--No, my ship!
Then, this is not gonna work.
--Are you sure about it?
--Yeah.
Sabo?
I'm not gonna work for anyone. Forget it.
Come on! It's gonna be fun!
Oh yeah! How about this?
The one who beats the big
tiger can be the captain!
The big tiger? Are you serious?
The chances of you becoming
a captain are pretty low.
That's not true! None of us
can compete against him now!
--Good idea!
Yeah! Let's do it!
--Alright!
Are you ready?
Yeah!
We went through so much to
catch these. What a waste!
Don't complain. We caught
these to use them as bait.
Oh? There he comes!
What a greedy bastard!
He can't have them today!
He's here!
Is that the tiger?
What?! It's a bear!
That's not what we expected!
Go away! Shoo! Shoo!
Wait, it seems like he's
as strong as the tiger.
We can't beat the tiger if we can't beat him.
I see! So he's perfect for practice.
--I go first!
--That's not fair!
That's cheating!
Oh no! He's not cooling off!
He's gonna kill us!
W-Who is it?!
He better run - that old man!
That's Naguri from Gray Terminal!
Run! He's coming to you!
What're you doing, old man?!
You know that you don't belong here!
Go back to the forest now!
Cool!
It's like that time before!
What?! You were a pirate
and a captain, Naguri?!
Yes, indeed.
I knew it! Only a pirate
captain could do that!
"That"?
You made the big bear turn away
just by staring at him like Shanks!
You're cool, old man!
You think so?
I can't believe that Naguri
was a pirate because...
He's always collecting junk, hammering
away at them all day long,
making weird stuff,
and getting teased by the people
at Gray Terminal and by Bluejam's crew.
He looked pathetic.
You know nothing, Sabo!
That's how pirates are!
You don't know anything, either!
What do you know about pirates?!
I know pirates! Shanks doesn't
do needless killings!
Shanks, again.
Hey, it's cooked.
--Ow, ow, ow...!
--Ouch!
Oh, you got more than me!
You got to pay attention.
Have some, Naguri. You helped us.
Oh, thank you.
So, what is a pirate captain
doing in a place like this?
How could you ask me that?
You don't have to answer
if you don't want to.
No, I'll tell you.
Do you guys know Gold Roger?
Roger?
I know him! He was the Pirate King!
We challenged Roger, the Pirate King, to a fight!
Really?!
But we lost the fight and split up.
And everything just went downhill after that
and I ended up like this.
That's basically what happened.
But you fought with the Pirate King, right? That's cool!
No, no, we were no match for him.
We got beaten badly.
Oh really? Even you were no
match - that's how much he...
Yes. And not just Roger, his
crew was also very strong!
Most importantly, their teamwork
was in perfect coordination!
It was our honor to fight with them.
I see! I still have a long
way to go to become a pirate.
Are you interested in pirates?
--I'm gonna become one!
--Become a pirate?
Yes, a pirate! Oh yeah, old pirate
man, could you give me some tips?!
I want to get stronger!
I have to become a captain
to lead Ace and Sabo!
A captain?
Hey, say yes! You're a pirate master!
--Okay!
--Okay?!
Yeah! Then, let's start from tomorrow!
Where did Ace go?!
Yeah, about that...
What?!
The Pirate King is his father?!
Yeah. But you can't tell anybody.
Don't mention it to Ace. He's gonna kill you.
Why?
I don't know why but he
doesn't like Roger for sure.
But that's his father, right?
So what?
I'm sorry for both of you but I was
all by myself even if I had parents!
Oh yeah. Your parents...
Children don't always get
along with their parents.
But, what a shame! He's
the Pirate King!
I can understand that you
wanna ask him about Roger
but just don't, okay?
Uh-huh! I got it!
And... you too, Naguri.
Okay, I got it.
But I can't believe that
that boy is Roger's son...
There he is. Hey, just act casually.
Yeah.
--Don't mention...
--I know! Don't worry!
Oh, Ace! I didn't know that you were home!
Oh, Ace! I didn't know that
your father was Roger!
I knew he'd say it!
You idiot, Luffy! I told
you to not to mention it!
--Luffy!
--Yeah!
Who told you that?
Sabo told me!
Hey Ace, what was Roger like?!
No!
How stupid are you? Don't
just say it casually!
Let me go! I am acting casually.
--Ouch!
Don't you ever mention
that name when I'm around!
Why did you hit me?!
Don't be mean - just tell me!
Give people a chance to explain first!
Shut up!
Tell us about him! You're so mean!
He's right! You can't have
a secret from your brothers!
Shut up! I don't care about my brothers!
Roger, Roger, Roger! Ace's father
is the Pirate King!
Shut up! Don't provoke him!
When you get down to it, it's
your fault for being a bigmouth!
Ouch! What did you say?!
What are you doing?!
We're no longer brothers from today!
--That's what I was gonna say!
Alright, I'm counting on you.
Yes, I'll leave no stone unturned.
You know what you should do.
We'll get to it!
Yeah, but if you find him,
don't do anything yet.
What?
Can't you see? We have to make
his father feel indebted to us.
The longer he worries, the more he'll
appreciate us when we find Sabo.
I see.
Until the time comes, don't do
anything - just monitor him.
"We will have a visit this spring"?
Dogra! Magra! Where is
the country called Goa?!
Mt. Corvo, Gray Terminal,
and Windmill Village
are part of Goa Kingdom supposedly.
That's what I thought.
Easy, easy, boss.
It's rare to see you reading a
newspaper. Hell must be freezing over.
Ouch!
Somebody's gonna visit the Kingdom?!
It's making the headlines...
What's going on here?
Are they that big a deal?
"Celestial Dragon Visiting"
These Celestial Dragons?
Curious after Luffy is taken in as an
apprentice, Ace and Sabo visit Naguri again.
Seeing that the boys only care about
getting strong enough to beat a tiger,
Naguri tells them that they can't become
pirate captains just by being strong.
What does it really take
to be a pirate captain?!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Battle Against the Big Tiger!
Who's Going to be Captain?!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Battle Against the Big Tiger!
Who's Going to be Captain?!