Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
-- the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
Luffy learned about the hideous experiments
performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
and headed off to investigate.
So the clan split up. However...
What are they?
They are footprints, aren't they?
Is it an animal? If it's a human, he must be a Giant.
I sense something.
Two beast-looking creatures.
What're we gonna do?!
Where are they?!
Law? The Master?
No, we're on a snow-capped mountain so it must be them!
The Snowy Mountain Assassins - stalking out from deep in the snowstorm!
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
Your name is also on our kill list.
You guys, you didn't harm my friends, did you?!
Oh? Where did he go?!
They took Nami with them!
Save Nami!
Luffy's Struggle on the Snowy Mountain
They kidnapped Nami?!
It was my fault.
Even though they were very big,
I didn't notice they were there until
they appeared in front of my eyes.
First, it was centaurs and now, beast men?!
There are a bunch of strange creatures here!
Maybe they were waiting for their chance to attack us somewhere.
They didn't come here to save Brown-gator?!
It seemed like their main purpose was to kill us and take the kids.
But first, they killed Brownbeard at the Master's command.
They were supposed to be on the same side.
Brownbeard admired him so much.
The Master was our warm-hearted savior!
Luffy!
This Master guy is a very twisted person.
I can't let these kids go back to such an evil person!
I can't help worrying about Nami in Franky's body, too!
We don't know what they're gonna do to her!
Yes, I'll get her back at any cost!
You guys, look after those kids!
Wait, Luffy!
It's my body that they took!
Chopper, I can't fight like this!
Give me the bean that you eat when you transform
yourself into a monster!
It's not a bean!
The Rumble Ball is a power drug!
I don't think you can control it.
I can handle it with my super spirit!
Just give it to me! There's no time to argue!
I have no choice.
What?
Just one, okay?
Really?! It was in this pocket the whole time?!
Of course it was. It's Chopper's.
Listen. You can become a monster for just three minutes.
You can't fight after that.
So if possible, transform into Kung Fu Point like I did earlier and...
What?!
Buber!
That's way too early!
Let's go, Franky! This way!
Why're you attacking me?!
Oh no! He's out of control as I thought!
So is there much point to Franky going?
After running wild, he won't be able to move for a while
so he's not gonna be helpful at all.
Instead, he's going to be in the way.
Caesar's Research Institute
I don't know where he got it but this "Cyborg" Franky guy has...
...Vegapunk's laser weapon mounted in his body.
I'll make good use of Vegapunk's invention.
After I chop his body up and take the laser system out,
he will be useless. Get the incinerator ready!
Yes, sir.
What's going on with the Navy idiots who came to steal the ship?
Ah, yes.
We ambushed them successfully but...
--What are they?! --Humans?! No, horses?!
Kill them all!
We won't get beaten that easily!
Look behind you!
What?!
Here we come!
There are more!
--This is no good! --Nowhere to go!
We have to change tactics!
Let's try to seize the ship in full force!
Captain-chan... I mean, Smoker-san!
The battle is out of control now.
You mean...
...we're having a hard fight.
I mean...
I have an idea!
M-Master?
We're dealing with the Navy.
It's the perfect opportunity to test it!
Yeah, that's great! Let's do that!
Contact the centaurs who are on patrol now.
Yes, sir!
Tell all the other soldiers evacuate if they want to survive.
The mountain behind the institute
Let me go! Let me go, you fools!
What's wrong with you guys?! You perverts!
What're you gonna do to me?!
I know I'm pretty and have a good figure
so you couldn't help kidnapping me!
What is this guy talking about?
He must be a queer. That's cool.
You're gonna pay for this! Luffy won't tolerate it!
I hope you two get your asses kicked!
Be quiet for a moment. Noisy people like you are...
...Not cool.
But the weapons that are mounted in your body are...
...Cool.
If we give them to the Master, our reward will be...
...So cool!
Rock
It's cold today as always.
Scotch
My body's cool!
Yeti Cool Brothers
The Snowy Mountain Assassins
Then put some clothes on!
Our rifles are like cannons to you people.
We have poison gas canisters, too.
Nobody can beat us because we don't show ourselves.
You said your friend will come?
I'm sure he'll come. We set a trap to lure him.
People can't help following footprints in the snow.
Footprints! Footprints! How helpful!
They are pretty easy to follow!
Hey, Franky, I said stop!
Oh?
The footprints end there...
Huh?
Luffy and Chopper... No, Franky?!
Nami!
Watch out! They're around!
Shall we, Scotch?
Okay! He didn't notice there was a cliff. He is so careless!
There are spikes at the bottom!
--Die in vain. --Get skewered by the Ice Spikes!
Armament; Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
I see. He's a little trickier than the others.
Those two from before!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Pistol!
Jet...
...Stamp!
They're gone, again!
Fool. We know these mountains like our own backyard.
There are so many places that we can hide ourselves!
Burning Lands
It must be around here.
The place that the Master mentioned.
It's a huge building.
Is it a warehouse?
It's kind of eerie.
This door is the one, right? Okay, let me open it.
It's tight! Guys, give me a hand!
I think I heard something.
I didn't hear a thing.
Hey, we've been told not to go anywhere near here, haven't we?
Is it really okay to open it?
The Master was the one who told us that and he wants us to open it.
You don't trust the Master?
N-No, that's not what I meant!
Then stop complaining and lend a hand!
They move so fast even though they're so big.
Oh yeah!
Gum-Gum...
It's a dead-end for you!
...Balloon!
It's a waste to use this power only
defensively just letting the bullets bounce randomly.
That's what Rayleigh said.
He said I should focus on redirecting
every single one of them back with twice the force!
Gum-Gum...
...Fire Salute!
Rock!
He did it!
Stop, Franky!
Why are you struggling with him more?!
My body's hot.
Are they having a falling out now? Screw them!
Stop!
Just see if you don't!
Icy mountains are filled with potential weapons.
Watch out! The tip of an icy mountain is gonna fall!
Luffy! Franky! Look up!
You can't get away from it!
The other one is right there, too!
Choke on this KYP gas canister that will make you drunk in a second
and drop dead like your friends!
He did something useful!
All right! That was great, Franky!
Hey, enough already!
Gear 3:
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
He used one of his most daring attack there?!
No!
Luffy!
Oh no!
Sorry, Franky and Chopper!
I'll ask Chopper to treat you later!
Wait!
I told you. We know these mountains like our own backyard.
You can't catch up with me!
Help me!
Nami!
You just won't give up!
But I can reach way farther than you!
Whoa! He's like a monkey.
Alright!
Damn! Since it's a huge mountain range, it'd be a pain if I lose them!
He's...
Oh, you're the free-loader--- Trafalgar Law, aren't you?
I'm glad to see you here.
I was chased by Straw Hat Luffy and...
Room.
What?
You bastard! What are you doing?!
Counter Shock.
Thank you!
No! Hey you, give me back my body!
Nami!
Luffy!
Oh, Tra-guy!
Did you save Nami?
I've been thinking.
And I came here to talk to you about something, Straw Hatter.
I think you arrived on this island by accident.
But there is an important key lying somewhere on this island
that can wreak havoc in the New World.
There are only two ways to survive in the New World.
Either by living under the Four Emperors
or going against them.
And I guess you're not a kind of person who wants to work under someone.
Yeah, I want to stay as a captain.
Then, we have to form an alliance!
What?
An alliance?
If you and I join forces, maybe we can do it.
I have a plan...
...to bring down one of the Four Emperors!
Law declares to defeat the Four Emperors.
Nami and the others can't help but be hesitant by the frightening details...
But Luffy's answer surprises not only his crew,
but Law, as well.
Meanwhile, Caesar was also setting
a terrible plan in motion.
Next time, on One Piece:
"It's Formed!
Luffy and Law's Pirate Alliance!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
It's Formed!
Luffy and Law's Pirate Alliance!