Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be Pirate King!
Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
BON
VO
Let that shred of courage grow
YAGE!
YAGE!
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
YAGE!
BON
VO
YAGE!
shi
ga
ra
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve your dreams aren't for naught
cious
in
my
life
i
pre
cious
in
my
life
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
I'm sure it was right around here...
Found it!
If things are going as planned,
Luffy and the others
should be headed back to the dock with our gold in hand.
I'm sorry, I really did forget about this!
I didn't realize it before, but this
Waver works in the Blue Sea, too!
All right! Now we just gotta hurry back!
Sanji-kun! Hold on tight!
Onto you?!
I'm so glad I'm alive!
God! Buddha! I thank you so much!
Yeah, yeah, whatever. Just get on already!
Don't mind if I do, then!
You moron! I can't move like this!
Your expressions of love are dynamic!
I collapse and literally fall in love...
All right! Here we go!
Okay!
The One Fell Swoop Plan!
Jonathan's Surefire
Secret Tactic
Looks like we've been had...
I have to hand it to them...
I wanna catch a fish that big!
How can you be so carefree after
we nearly died trying to open it?!
Our commander said you would appear here,
since you had stolen the map.
Cunning man.
There is nowhere to run now!
Dammit! As strong as Luffy and Zoro are...
Do we wait for Sanji and the others
to break through from outside?!
No.
Our actions should already be known by now.
It's only a matter of time
until reinforcements arrive.
There's no use in staying here.
Yeah! If the gold's not here,
then let's just go look somewhere else!
Don't talk like it's so easy!
The only way out is to beat these guys
and bust down those sturdy doors!
So?
Exactly! We gotta do what we gotta do!
In the name of Navarone, we will defeat you!
Usopp's in trouble!
He's helpless to do anything!
End of the line, Straw Hats!
Huh?
Condoriano?
You came to the storage vault,
exactly as I expected!
Who the hell are you?!
Who gave you permission to open the doors?!
Quiet, you!
I am a special inspector from Navy HQ, Major Shepherd!
With the commander's permission,
I am leading a special mobile unit from headquarters.
You are not needed. Step back!
Huh? Haven't I seen you somewhere before?
Oh, yeah!
You were the guy in jail with Usopp and Zoro!
Who are you to talk all big?!
Hey! Condoriano! You managed to escape!
You seem well!
I owe a great deal to you all.
All the insults you've put me through...
It's payback time for that, with interest!
Major Shepherd!
What?! Things were just getting good!
Taking them down with that level
of military might is impossible.
You shouldn't underestimate them...
Shut up, shut up, shut up! Shut up!
Don't compare us HQ elites with you pathetic Navarone men!
We will eliminate the Straw Hats!
You just sit there and watch! Is that clear?!
Yes, sir!
Are you done?
Yes! I'm gonna crush you good,
so stay right there!
Bring it here!
Yes, sir!
What's that?
This is Navy HQ's very latest invention:
a portable bazooka!
The Sea Eagle Talon... the Eagle Launcher!
It packs as much punch as a warship's main cannon!
What?!
They've brought out another incredible thing!
You don't scare me! Bring it on!
I'll fulfill that request! Time to die!
Huh?
Way to go, Condoriano!
Major! You have it backwards!
O-Oh.
Hey, now!
Shut up! I'll get you this time!
No! No! Don't do that!
Way to go, Condoriano!
What the hell'd he come here to do?
That's pretty disappointing
for a "special mobile unit."
Well, then. Shall we go?
All right! Gold! Gold!
Wait! Wait, you guys! Hey!
D-Damn you, Straw Hats! I'll get you—
My bad, Condoriano!
Don't let them escape! After them!
So, where's the gold now?
Don't look at me!
Security's tighter than I thought...
All alone with Nami-san on a romantic night at sea...
Isn't it the damn greatest, Nami-san?!
Sanji-kun...
Damn bravo, Nami-san!
Sanji-kun!
You're damn fantastic, Nami-san!
It's bon voyage, Nami—
Sanji-kun! Could you be damn quiet?!
This means the Navy is certain
we're still inside the base.
But then why are they just sitting there?
I don't like this...
Let's rethink our plan somewhere safe.
Is there any safe place here on Navarone?!
Yeah! The kitchen me and Sanji were at!
That's where loads of marines gather to eat!
We can't go someplace that dangerous!
No, wait.
The enemy might think the same thing, too...
All right! It's decided!
Let's go get some food!
That's not what we're doing!
I'm a full-fledged pirate now!
I've grown a lot!
I'll protect it, no matter who comes!
I'm a reliable man!
Chopper!
Nami! Sanji!
You're all right!
I wasn't lonely at all, you dummies!
Are Luffy and the rest not back yet?!
Nope! I've been keeping watch all alone!
That's strange.
Something might've happened...
Eh? Then, the gold, too?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go look!
My date with Nami-san, Part 2!
All alone again?!
You stay here, too, Sanji-kun.
Eh?
I have a favor to ask you.
I'm pretty sure the vault was down here somewhere...
That's...
The Straw Hats fled into the mountains!
Comb the hills!
Hurry! No dawdling!
Are you all right, Major Shepherd?!
Damn it! I almost had them, too!
But finding an empty vault doesn't
mean they'll give up just yet.
We still have a chance!
Empty?!
Well, I figured this might happen,
so the next step is already set.
I always know what I'm doing!
The vault was a trap!
Then where is the gold?!
I think it was around here...
Hey, now. Come on already...
I guess it wasn't.
Weren't you just there?
The dining hall is at the far end.
This is the medical ward.
Sounds like there's someone here!
Dad! Please do as I ask!
I don't care if you are my daughter;
I refuse to drink that nasty stuff!
But it's medicine!
Those voices...
It's the doctor who acted as a hostage...
...and the old man!
The gold wasn't on your ship?!
Nor in the vault.
Still, I can't believe you're father and daughter!
Anyway, old man, are you sick or something?
Nah, just one swig of this
and I'll sleep it off like a baby!
This is a much better medicine for me!
No! There is no drinking or
smoking in the medical ward!
Just one drink!
No!
You're so stubborn...
Old man! You need to listen to
your daughter... no, your doctor!
What's this?
Are you trying to lecture me now?
I save your hides, and you
come waltzing right back...
Do you want your gold that badly, Long-nose?!
Of course we do, old repair guy!
We're pirates!
Yeah! These pirates worked
really hard to get their stuff!
You keep out of this, Kobato!
We're saving up money!
Saving?
We decided that after we
exchange the gold for money,
we're gonna do major repairs on Merry!
Like we can really believe a bunch of pirates!
I don't care if you don't believe me!
This was our decision!
It's got nothing to do with you!
What?!
I believe you!
After all... they said that ship was their home.
Home, indeed...
This is it! It's a bit of a long way around,
but this path is unguarded, and it'll
take you safely to the mountains.
This "path" is almost all cliff!
All right, then! Let's go gold-hunting!
Thanks, old guy!
Sure thing!
Get going.
Thanks for your help again, old man! See ya!
Wait!
What is it?
Our commander's hobby is fishing, you see...
So that explains why he showed
off that huge fish painting!
Your gold is probably the
perfect bait to reel you in with.
In which case, it should be
dangling somewhere you can see it.
Someplace we can see it? Bait?
Hurry up!
Yeah!
Now get going!
Right! See ya!
Hey! Wait for me!
If they do steal back the
gold and manage to escape,
all of Navarone will be in big trouble.
I must be crazy...
There was no time to think up
a plan after all, was there?
Dammit!
Are we left to look around aimlessly for it?!
What is it, Zoro?!
Thought I heard something...
A bug? Must be my imagination.
No, it isn't your imagination.
Something's coming!
A Waver?!
It's Nami!
I see. So you ran into Dr. Kobato...
We pretty much have no clues
about where the gold is!
I'm sleepy...
If we sit around and dawdle,
dawn's gonna come,
which'll make it even harder to move around.
Say, are there any other storage vaults?
If there are, they could be
traps to lure us in again...
Come to think of it, the old man
said something earlier about "bait"...
Eh? What do you mean by "something"?
I'm not really sure, but he said...
That's it! Usopp!
What's it?
Bait to reel us in...
In other words, the gold is somewhere in sight!
In sight?!
Could "sight" be referring to a
place we could imagine it being?
Oh, good thinking!
What do you mean?
In short, who's the one dangling the bait to catch us in the first place?
Navarone's commander?
Yes! Navarone's commander is the fisherman.
And if the bait is near the fisherman,
there's only one place it could be.
You don't mean...!
Yep, that's right!
What are you doing?!
You said you know where the
commander's room is, right?
Lead us there!
O-Okay...
Okay! Luffy and I will go!
Robin and the rest, get to the coast!
Chopper's group should come to get you!
Will you be all right?
The Waver can only hold two people.
Well, we're gonna get spotted anyway,
so it doesn't matter!
I'm gonna run it at full throttle!
You ready?!
Yeah! Anytime you are!
Here we go!
They've appeared!
Where is it?!
Let's see...
Hurry and find it, Luffy!
Up! Up!
Up where, exactly?!
Don't let them escape!
That's it!
Got it!
What a surprise this is!
What is that vehicle?
Is he the commander?!
Yeah, he's the old fortress guy!
I never imagined you would make an entrance through there!
Cool, huh?!
This is actually a vehicle from the sky!
Only Nami can ride it, though!
Quit getting excited!
Yes! I'm sorry!
I've not met this girl before. Welcome.
Were you not pirates, I'd greet you
warmly for your boisterous visit.
It's a real shame.
You're perceptive and bold.
But daring can also sometimes
be called recklessness.
There will be no soldiers coming
to eat this time, Straw Hat Luffy.
But first! If there's no bait,
we have nothing to bite onto!
Where's the gold?!
It's hidden in this room, isn't it?
Couldn't you at least show it to us?
Yes. It's right there.
Right in front of me?!
Oh, here it is! The gold!
Nami! We finally found it!
It's not fake bait, I hope?
It's indeed the genuine article.
Check for yourself.
Okay, then!
Luffy!
It's true!
This is our gold, no doubt about it!
All right! Let's go now!
Sorry for the intrusion, old fortress guy!
Whoops, I think not.
You can't just take the bait and run.
Try not to be too rough with the lady, now.
Thanks...
Straw Hat comes first.
I'll beat the whole lot of you up!
A-Another weird net... I'm out of strength...
Sea Prism Stone!
Straw Hat is captured!
Excellent work. Now, then...
Not good! What do I do?!
There's gotta be something!
Wait, if these guys have guns,
I do have a chance!
Rain Tempo: Sprinkler!
Cool Ball!
That's cold!
Heat Ball!
It's warm...
I did it!
W-What the...?!
A cloud?!
Today's forecast calls for clear skies and 0% chance of rain!
But cumulonimbus clouds may
suddenly develop in some places!
Please watch out for lightning!
What is this, Miss?
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Luffy!
Pull yourself together!
Thanks, Nami...
Hurry! Grab our gold!
I'm not one to let prey escape
after hooking it once before...
I'll catch all of you in one fell swoop.
Well, Luffy?! See the ship?!
It's too dark to see anything!
Look out, Nami! A Navy ship!
Say, it does look kind of like a warship...
There they are! Over here, Luffy!
Nami!
Nami-san! Are you all right?!
You just let Straw Hats who were in your own room get away.
They even stole the gold.
Even you must admit this is a grave failure.
They will not escape my clutches, Major Shepherd.
You still won't admit defeat,
after all that's happened?
No, I apologize. What do you say, Commander?
Why don't you sit there quietly
and observe my leadership skills?
I thought you had already had enough?
What happened earlier was
simply a minor complication!
I had already sent out my
special pirate subjugation squad,
separate from my main unit.
Oh. Then I think I will sit back
and watch you in action.
You're the captain of the Pinepeak?!
They will appear near the Sea Gate!
Just as planned, wait for them
to get drawn to it, then sink 'em!
Got that?!
Understood, sir!
Captain!
We're about to reach the ambush point!
All right!
Do not let the pirate ship slip by!
The minute it's spotted,
commence a full-scale attack!
That takes care of all the preparations.
Now to watch things from a high vantage point.
Place a pole in—
Could you please not touch that?!
May I ask you something?
I-If it's about how to catch pirates,
I can teach you anytime you want.
Wasn't this special squadron
of yours on the Pinepeak?
There seems to be one more ship...
Say what?! Th-That can't be!
That's no Navarone warship.
No, it doesn't even look like it is a warship.
W-What is that?!
Captain!
A warship... no, a warship-like ship...
is approaching from behind!
A Navarone ship?
And what do you mean, "like"?!
I-I'm not really sure how to answer...
It's going to smash into us!
Stop! Stop!
Full speed ahead, Merry!
W-What the...?!
Thanks for the piloting!
Couldn't have made it this far without you!
Thanks a bunch! We owe ya one!
Don't let them escape! After them!
This is no time for that!
What?!
I-Impossible!
To think they'd use the Pinepeak, of all things!
Damn you, you Straw Hats!
Don't be so aggravated.
They're as good as caught in a net now.
Net?
At 9:00 pm, the waters of
Navarone bare their fangs,
and the final... and inescapable... trap begins!
Okay! Now we can escape!
Plus we got the gold!
We did it! We did it!
Okay! Let's rush straight to the Sea Gate!
Yeah!
Mirai ni mukatte, saki o isoge! Ima sugu ni
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Yume to iu mono oikakete ikou
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
Afure dashi teru subete no kotae ga kokoni
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Hashire, hashire, hiraka reta michi wo
Rush forth, rush forth, on the road opened before us
Tomaru koto naku susumou, bokura wa dekiru
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
Makenai, makenai, ookina kabe demo
We won't give in, we won't give in, even if the obstacle is big
Kowagaru koto nante nai sa, norikoerareru
It's nothing to be scared of, we can overcome it
Attention, Straw Hat Luffy and his crew!
You've fought most valiantly against
the Navy's great G-8 Fortress!
You've done admirably, but this is the end!
Just give it up, Straw Hats!
We still have a chance!
Next time, on One Piece:
Farewell, Navy Fortress!
The Last Battle for Escape
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Farewell, Navy Fortress!
The Last Battle for Escape