Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy hurries for Navy HQ in order
to stop his brother, Ace, from being executed.
Meanwhile, the Whitebeard Pirates have stormed Marineford, starting an all-out war with the Navy.
Ace-kun...
Oars!
Climb Oars' body and advance!
What's that?
Heehaw!
The Straw Hat Team Arrives
Tensions Grow on the Battlefield
Vi feel a chill in my heart!
Hey, partner! Can't you do something?!
Do you really think that wax will help in any way?!
Why are Luffy and the others falling from the sky?
We have to go back a little bit in time to know what happened to them.
The ship that they were on
was hit by Whitebeard's seaquake.
It's speeding up!
H-Hey! Look at that!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
It's a tsunami!
It's really big!
We're gonna get caught!
The sea just suddenly drew back and now there's a big tsunami.
This must be...
Hey, Jinbe! We gotta do something or...
I don't want to be defeated by a tsunami here!
I... I gotta save Ace!
Take in the sails!
Luffy-kun, let's ride on the tsunami!
Shouldn't we get away?!
What are saying, you ass?!
Turn around already!
Hey, stop it!
We gotta hurry!
Jump into the sea!
Help! Help!
How long have you been a pirate?
Are you a bunch of amateurs?
If we turn around now, we'll take the
wave on the side of the ship and capsize.
We don't have any option.
That's right!
Hang tight so you don't
get washed off by the big wave!
Damn!
Hurry up!
Just hang onto something!
My face is too big.
What happened?
The wave stopped moving!
What happened?!
What the hell?!
The ship has iced in and we're completely trapped!
This must have been done by...
Look down. You can see what's going on.
Old man...
The war has begun already.
The old chap must have sent that tsunami
as a declaration of war.
And this ice is the work of Admiral Blue Pheasant.
Guys, listen!
I got an idea to get us through this!
We gotta hurry! There's less than
3 hours left before Ace's execution!
Uh-huh. And?
What?!
You want the ship to slide down this frozen wave?!
That's the only way! First, we gotta get this ship unstuck from the ice!
Are you nuts? It's a Navy ship! We can't lift it up!
He's right, you idiot!
We can do it if we work together!
Oh, that makes me think that I can.
Yeah! We have the next
Pirate King—Captain Buggy—on our side!
When Captain says that he can do it,
he will do it for sure!
Ring, ring, ring...
Attention, all ships and soldiers!
The target is TOTTZ.
Change the line and make the shift to operation 3.
It's a Navy operational message.
Advance the preparation!
TOT... what was it?
Dunno. Must be some kind of code.
When you are all set,
we move the schedule forward...
...and execute Ace immediately. That's all.
Luffy-kun...
Let's move!
This can't wait any longer. We don't have time to argue!
Everyone, let's get on
with Straw-boy's idea!
Let's go!
H-Hey!
No! That's not the side!
And that was how Luffy
and the others started falling!
What just happened?!
Did a Navy ship fall from the sky?!
It's water, thank god. We fell into water.
I thought I was gonna die by falling on the ice!
Why isn't it frozen around here?
Look! The ship landed in the area where Jozu had cleared the ice!
Is it a surprise attack from the Navy?
No, they don't look like the Navy.
Climb! Climb up!
It's nothing compared to
the water torture in hell.
It's inconvenient that
Devil Fruit users can't swim.
Where am I?
Oh yeah, I fell from there.
Ace!
Where are you? Where are you, Ace?!
Ace...
Get on the ship!
He's not on this side!
Where are you, Ace?!
Wait for me, Ace! I'll be there soon!
Don't get in my way!
Ace!
Ace...
Ace!!
Luffy!!
I can see you finally!
Luffy!
Ace! Hang on! I'll...
H-Hey, don't tell me that's...!
Crocodile!
That's not all! Who is in that lineup?!
All forces are here on both sides! There are a lot of big names!
The world's got to be ready for it!
Ace, we're coming to rescue you!
We're here for you!
Garp! It's your family again!
Luffy!
Look! It's not only Straw Hat!
Jinbe and Ivankov of the Revolutionary Army!
Behind them are many infamous pirates, too!
They must've escaped from Impel Down!
He always causes trouble... Straw Hat.
Straw Hat!
What brought him here?
And he's not with his crew.
Luffy! I'm glad that you're alive!
Look, Helmeppo-san!
What?! Nothing'll surprise me anymore...
Straw Hat!
I heard that he was captured at Impel Down! He's so tough!
He brought some big faces!
I didn't expect to see him again this soon.
He's the brother that Ace was talking about.
There's a former and an active Warlord together!
And that's the big troublemaker rookie—Straw Hat!
Smoker-san, look!
Die!
Straw Hat and Crocodile... Why are they together?
So it is him.
Grandson of the "Hero of the Marines"—Garp—
and son of the Revolutionary—Dragon.
I'll take care of him for good!
Of all things, you're working alongside Straw Hat Luffy...
So that's your response, Jinbe?!
Yes, it is! I resign from the Seven Warlords!
It's odd that those people are teaming up.
Prisoners, a commander
of the Revolutionary Army,
some bizarre-looking people and...
...Crocodile.
I don't think that they have a common goal.
At least, in this battle.
Where's Croco-boy?
Oh? I think he chickened out and...
There he is!
He went ahead of me!
Crocodile is aiming for Whitebeard!
Pops!
Long time no see, Whitebeard.
You never learn.
He knows too well how to fight against me.
You can't turn into sand once you touch water.
Now that we are here,
our agreement has been fulfilled.
Why do you want to protect Whitebeard?!
As I thought—this old man is Whitebeard.
Then leave him alone!
Ace likes this old man!
Ace's brother is quite a fighter.
Don't let him come close to Pops!
Everybody was surprised when a strong guy like you
came back after losing an arm in the East Blue.
Who is this enemy that you gave your left arm to?
I put it up for a new generation.
Hey, squirt, that
straw hat you have...
...it looks like the one
that Red-Haired was once wearing.
Old man, you know Shanks?
Shanks left it to me.
Look, Pops! This is my brother!
You came here to rescue your brother?
Yeah.
Do you know who you're messing with?!
A squirt like you will be dead meat!
Shut up! That's not up to you to decide!
I know what you're up to!
You wanna become the Pirate King, right?!
But I'm the one who'll become the King!
How saucy you are!
I won't forgive you
if you cause me trouble, spoiled brat!
I'm gonna do as I like!
I'm gonna rescue Ace!
H-He's competing...
...With Whitebeard!
It can't be!
We can punish all of them
by death, can't we, Sengoku-san?
Absolutely.
Luffy... Pops...
Hang on, Ace!
I'll get there...
I'll get there very soon!
At Navy HQ, Luffy leads the charge against the massive forces there.
As the men of the Navy attack Luffy in waves,
Ace shouts at him to stay away.
How will Luffy respond to his brother's wish?
Next time, on One Piece:
"Even If It Means Death
Luffy vs. the Navy; The Battle Starts"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Even If It Means Death
Luffy vs. the Navy; The Battle Starts