Until I can reach that great sky,
I believe, to that one tomorrow, hey
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one dream
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the good times
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Stumbling into the darkness, fumbling about to find the answer
Freezing up when there's no goal in sight
Umm you and me, yes, in this world where we share our feelings
I feel the beat guiding me, and begin to walk, oh yeah
Share the music, anytime
Share the one dream and believe in each other
Share the good times holding hands
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style
Beginning, expanding, this flavor is beyond imagining
I feel so good throughout my body, I know I can be free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far
Share the one dream, by telling each other
Share the good times and laugh
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall
I'll be there soon, I believe, to that one world, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
After Luffy and friends set out
in search of a coating craftsman,
Camie was kidnapped at Sabaody Park.
...Some guy brought in a Mermaid
just before the auctions started!
H-Hold on! Who was this guy?!
After learning that she had already been
taken to the auction house on Grove #1...
...Nami and company were the first to arrive.
And, while the auctioning continued,
Luffy and four others had yet
to reach the auction house!
We will save you! Hang on, Camie!
The Fist Explodes!
Destroy the Auction
Entry #15! The beautiful dancer, Pashia!
Incredibly, her starting
price of 800,000 berries
has rocketed to the sky-high
price of 7.2 million berries!
I'm finally here...
Okay! Now that things are
starting to getting fired up,
what do you say to this
next piece of merchandise?!
What a relief! It's still going on!
However, I heard him say
"Entry #15" just now,
so I believe it's almost over.
This thing really annoys me to no end!
Take this! And this!
Hey. Go sell this one too, while
we're here. I don't need it anymore.
I will make arrangements at once.
A Celestial Dragon...
Another World Noble is here...
Defy them and a Navy admiral
will come running, huh...
I want a Mermaid. I hope
they have one this time.
Merfolk are apparently a
rather hard species to catch,
so I'm unsure if one will be up
for auction this time or not...
Wh-What a pleasant surprise, Saint Charloss!
Take me to my seat already.
Yes, right away!
Please watch your step!
Brother Charloss is finally here.
Hey! Get walkin'!
Okay! It looks like we're ready to continue!
Entry #16 is none other than
the captain of a pirate ship!
A captain?
Feast your eyes on this man, with
a bounty of 17 million berries!
Goes by the name of Lacuba!
He's known as a tactful strategist,
but his well-trained body
is another great attribute!
You can use him as a horse, for heavy
physical labor, or as a punching bag!
He has many uses, indeed!
Now, then!
Bastard! Don't tell me you just--!
He collapsed!
What happened?!
I saw blood!
Hey! Shut the curtains!
What happened?!
What just happened?
He bit his tongue off.
He decided he'd rather die here
than live a wretched life as someone's pet.
In some cases, that could
be the smart choice.
Camie...
Where's the Mermaid already?!
Camie must be so scared...
Just hang on a little longer!
We will save her!
Good thing we have that
treasure from Thriller Bark!
Thank you so much, you guys...
No good.
Damn! I'm not gonna make any
money off of you now, you idiot!
Disco-san!
A doctor's on the way!
Geez! Do you know how much it's
gonna cost to treat you now?!
The Mermaid's next, right?!
Yes! Everything's all set!
It can go on at any time!
Good!
This super big-event item should blast
away the chilly mood in the air!
Bring her out now, men!
Right!
Hatchin... Everyone...
#13? Didn't I pass by #2 just now?
Must be my imagination.
That man had so much bloodlust...
Pirate Hunter Zoro... He ain't
worth 120 million for nothin'!
Get mixed up with him and you won't survive,
no matter how many lives you have!
I never wanna meet that guy
again, that's for sure...
Hey! Hold it!
Aren't you guys...
What brings you here again?
You guys gave me fake
directions, didn't you?!
Nothing of the sort! We gave you
genuine directions to Grove #1!
Then why'd you run away?!
B-Because you glared at us
with such a vicious look!
Huh?!
Zoro!
We gotta hurry to Grove #1! Just get on!
Hold on! Not this again...!
"Aaaaaaaah"
What are you doing?!
Oops...
Someday I'm gonna cut you in two...
Sorry, Zoro.
Let's hurry to Grove #1!
#16, pirate Lacuba, was extremely nervous
and collapsed after a nosebleed,
so his introduction will have
to wait for another day.
Nervous?
What crap...
But, ladies and gentlemen!
The next item I have for you is a
super-incredible piece of merchandise
sure to instantly blow all this trouble away!
A highly sought after item, to be sure!
Observe this silhouette!
Oh! Could it be?!
Yes! An incredible item!
I won't say much. Look upon
it with your own eyes!
Now for the moment you've been waiting for!
It's time for the unveiling!
Take a good look!
All the way from Fishman Island, the Mermaid Camie!
It's real! A young Mermaid!
Amazing!
What a find!
It's Hatchin and the others!
They came to rescue me!
Camie!
They're selling Camie now!
Alright! We're gonna get her
back! We have 200 million here!
Camie!
Hooray! A Mermaid! They're selling a Mermaid!
I see that there's immense interest
in this, our first Mermaid in a while!
Now, then! How much shall we start from?
Let's make the first move to
win! We will get her back!
All right, then! Let's begin!
Bidding will start at...
500 million!
I'll buy it for 500 million berries!
500 million...?
It's no good. We can't compete with him.
How could that happen so suddenly?!
We don't even have close to that much!
What another waste of money. You have
piranhas in your aquarium, you know.
I'm going to have them chase her for fun.
Merfolk are the fastest
swimmers in the world!
I can't hear what they're saying outside...
Help me get out of here, Hatchin!
Camie...
Is she gonna get sold to a Celestial
Dragon while we stand here, helpless?!
Camie...!
Everyone seems to be at a loss for
words, but I'll ask just the same.
Are there any bids higher than 500 million?
Can't we do something about this?!
Isn't there anything we can do?!
Isn't there, Sanji?!
Nami!
We can't let this happen!
We can't let our friend get
bought and taken away like this!
This is bad... I never even
imagined this happening.
We stepped back, thinking money
could solve this problem,
but things've just gotten worse!
If not, then that'll bring
bidding straight to a close!
I'll just have to help her
escape into the ocean by force!
Don't be stupid! What about that
collar?! It'll make Camie blow up!
Then... we'll have to get the
key to the collar somehow!
Time is up!
I did it!
It's almost like a miniature
version of the world.
What a pathetic farce. Let's go.
The bidding has ended!
Today's super showcase
item, the Mermaid Camie...
...goes to the World Noble,
Saint Charloss for his bid of...
...500 million...
What's that?
...berries!
What the...?!
How noisy.
Luffy!
What's your problem?! You
can land better than that!
I can't! It's a flying fish!
Besides, you said to run into it!
You told me to "just get on,"
but why're you guys in such a
hurry to get back to the Sunny?!
Where are we, anyway?!
Zoro, too?!
You guys...
That's Straw Hat Luffy...!
Camie!
Who are they?! Where'd they come from?!
Luffy-chin!
Camie! We've been looking
everywhere! What a relief!
Hold on, Straw Hat! What are you doing?!
What do you mean?! Camie's right there!
She is, but she's wearing an explosive
collar! We can't take her away!
Plus, there are Celestial
Dragons involved now...!
So what?!
Did he just call him "Straw Hat"?
He's a pirate!
Camie!
Please, stop!
His arms...! His arms...!
He's a Fishman!
Disgusting!
What's a Fishman doing here?!
It's an octopus monster!
I'm coming to save you, Camie!
Seize him!
You guys! Camie isn't for sale!
Keep him away from the stage!
What's a Fishman doing on land?!
Yuck, stay away! Your
very existence is scary!
Hey, staff! Apprehend him already!
Eww! Get away!
Go back to the sea, you freak!
Yeah!
Get off these islands!
Get out of here!
Hachi! Let's run for now!
You're the one in danger now!
Never mind me! It's Camie who's in trouble!
What the hell's going on here?!
It's exactly like Robin said...
Huh?
They discriminate against Fishmen
and Merfolk on these islands!
Discriminate..? Against Camie and Hachi?
H-Hachi...
I shot it! I took down a Fishman!
Hachi!
Thank heavens someone shot him.
It would've been terrible if it'd come
close enough to spread its diseases!
It was definitely plotting something.
But even if it can walk upright,
it still has a fish's brain!
Look, Father! I caught a Fishman!
I caught it myself, so
I can have it for free!
Free! Free! An octopus for free!
What a deal! What a deal! An
octopus slave for free! Free!
Free, free, free!
W-
Wait...
Straw Hat...!
Don't... Don't be mad...
I'm the one... who screwed up...
You promised not to defy
the Celestial Dragons,
even if you saw someone get shot...!
I was a pirate at one time...!
This is what I deserve... for
doing those horrible things...
I'm sorry... I didn't mean
for it to be like this...!
I just wanted to make amends with
Nami... even if it wasn't much...
So I wanted to be helpful to you guys...
But I guess I've always been a
screw-up... no matter what I do...!
I'm a real screw-up...!
Hachi...
All I ever do is cause trouble...
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry...!
You lousy fish, still blabbering
on even though I shot you!
You annoy me!
Straw!
What's with that look, you?!
Stop, Straw! You guys'll
get in huge trouble too!
Please, stop!
Do you not see this?!
What's he going to do?!
Straw Hatter...?
Is he serious?!
You annoy me, too!
I see it! The auction house!
What is that?!
The Marines have gathered around the auction house!
This could be trouble!
Wait a minute,
Luffy and the others must have started some trouble!
We have to hurry and save them, or they'll be ambushed.
I don't wanna!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Major Panic!
Desperate Struggle at the Auction House"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Major Panic!
Desperate Struggle at the Auction House