Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can become Pirate King!
Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
BON VOYAGE!  hito kakera no yuuki hirogete
BON VOYAGE!      Let that shred of courage grow
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
saisho wa minna BARABARA ni egaite ita chiheisen
The horizons everyone dreamed of were separate at first
ima nara hitotsu no bouenkyou de nozokeru
but now they can be seen through a single telescope
kimi no KOKORO madowasu unmei no shoppai KONPASU
A bitter compass of destiny is leading your heart astray
saka te ni kajitoru yo
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
BON VOYAGE!
SHIGARAMI mo kako mo sutete
Toss aside your bonds and your past
bokura nara sore demo waraeteru hazu
We can surely smile despite that
yume o kanaeru tame no namida naraba oshikuwanai
Tears shed trying to achieve your dreams aren't for naught
PRECIOUS IN MY LIFE
precious in my life
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
Where am I?
Oh, you shouldn't move yet.
Chief! The golden belfry...
We still have the duty to protect it to the end!
Don't rush, Wyper.
Vearth, at least, is not refusing anyone.
Right... Right now, at least,
no one wants to fight.
It's party time!!
The long battle of 400 years had ended,
and all the citizens of Skypiea continued their joyous party day after day.
I Made It Here!
The Yarn the Poneglyphs Spin
I... I... I can't drink any more...
There they are!
Hey!
What is it?
Nami, wake everyone up!
Why?
We're gonna steal the gold and run!
There's gold?!
Idiot! Not so loud!
What do you mean "idiot"?!
You're louder than I am!
Hey! I'm louder, you say?!
You're the louder one!
What?! You're calling me loud
when you're really super loud?!
Your voice is the one that's
really super-mega-ultra loud!!
There's no way that's true!!
I'm talking loud because you're loud!
Shut up! I can't sleep!!
You're the one who spoke loud first!
What?! You're the loud one!!
It wasn't me! It was you!
I'm a delicate woman!
I wouldn't yell with my mouth wide open, would I?!
What?!
There's no way I'd do something like that!
See? See?! Your mouth is wide open!
Geez, wake up, sleepyhead!
But you did hit me here!
Here! It's really true!!
Nami-san! Good morning!!
That's because you ticked me off!
Yeah, yeah... Go ahead and be feeble-minded like that.
Oh? It's not morning yet!
Like I said, you don't have to shout, you know!!
What do you mean, "feeble-minded"?!
Blue Sea people sure like to party, don't they?
This is the fourth day in a row.
Their vitality isn't normal.
So, that's the plan.
Okay, guys!
It's not often that we get to visit a sky island!
Make it so that you'll have no regrets!
He's so cool!
This is getting exciting!
Chief! We found the golden bell!!
What?!
Hey, are you serious?!
Yeah. It's stuck on the fallen Giant Jack.
We're pulling it out right now.
Those who can help, come to the western seashore!
Hurry! Hurry up!!
Okay, guys! Gather everyone!!
Hurry to the western seashore!
The belfry was found!
Where?!
At the western seashore.
Okay!
Are you sure?!
Yeah! Hurry!
They said they found the bell that fell in the sea!
Yeah. Those who can move,
gather at the western seashore!
The belfry was found!
It's at the western seashore!!
The belfry was?
One more time!!
One, two...!
Pull!!
Dammit! We still need more people.
It's the pride of our ancestors' city, Shandora.
We'll get it at any cost!
That's right!
Give it everything you got!!
One more time!! One, two...!
Pull harder!!
Rubber band?!
So you call this a rubber band?!
Yeah! My Usopp Rubber Band did 90% of the work of taking Giant Jack down!
Whoa!
Whoa! Incredible!
I'm the only one in the world that has them.
Whoa!
Whoa! Amazing!
But... put that aside for now.
I'd like to show you this iron sheet!
Now, ladies and gentlemen!
This is no ordinary iron sheet!
I tore it off from the Going Merry,
our ship that endured very hard travels
on the Grand Line, as well as Eneru's attacks!
It's the "King of Iron Sheets"!
How about it?! You guys want iron, right?
Would you trade me dials for this?
No! I want this rubber band!
I'll trade you for this rubber band!
I want one, too! Is that okay?!
Me, too!
Whoa... Are they serious?!
Give me one, too! Me, too!
Water, light, fire...
Things whose shape is transient...
Things with no form...
I cut them!!
Shells! I got shells! Oh, yeah!
Lucky, lucky! I got so lucky!
You're in a good mood, aren't you, Usopp?
Did the negotiation go well?
Hear that? I got lots of dials!
I press it and...
Just like that!
Good for you.
Good for me! With this many dials,
I can do many different things!
The Usopp factory'll be running full steam!
Hey, Zoro, if you make
your swords Flavor Swords
and store the smell of stuff like melons in them,
you can enjoy your everyday training!
No thanks.
Oh...
Oh, yeah!
I can make Nami's Clima Takt stronger!
My slingshot will be incredible, too!
So, where are Robin, Luffy and the others?
Luffy and the others are still inside.
Robin went somewhere.
In any case... this snake's really conked out.
He kept dancing day after day...
...though I don't know what
he was so happy about.
Anyhow, they'd better come out soon,
because if he wakes up,
he could give them a hard time again.
Huh? This good-tempered snake?
Idiot! You just don't know
how troublesome he can be!
This good-tempered snake?
Like I said, you can be so
optimistic because you didn't see
what a pain this snake can be.
This good-tempered snake?
Hey, now listen here, Usopp!
It was a Tone Dial!
Don't do stupid stuff like that!!
Yeah, it's stupid! It's really stupid!
What the heck?! What does this snake eat?
Are we there, yet, Luffy?
Look! There they are!!
Wow! Amazing!
This is the real thing!
It's pretty! It looks just like the ones that we saw at the monkeys' house!
See? See? See?! There's all this!
Isn't it awesome?!
So this is gold...
How beautiful...
Incredible...
How magnificent.
I didn't expect it to be this...
But one of the side columns has been broken.
Yeah, but there isn't much we can do.
Hey! Look at that.
So this is... the Poneglyph...
The stone that our ancestors
risked the city's life to protect...!
Just what is written on it, Chief?
Something we're better off not knowing...
We just...
"Hold our true motive in your hearts and speak not of it.
We are the ones who weave history...
...with the sounding of the grand belfry..."
How do you know those words?
They were carved on the Shandoran ruins.
So you were the keepers,
entrusted with this for generations.
Could it be...
You can read those characters?!
Poseidon, the "ancient weapon" named after a God...
Its whereabouts...
What?! What's that?!
She said "ancient"!
Ancient weapon?
Why is it talking about something like that?!
Yeah...
Another weapon...
...separate from Pluton that
I read about in Alabasta...
I hear that one shot from Pluton
will completely destroy an island.
To think that there are such dangerous
things in this world waiting to be found...!
Just as I thought, this was a disappointment.
This isn't what I want to know.
Hey! Aren't those the same kind of
characters on that engraving next to it?!
What?!
"Gol D. Roger"...!
I made it here.
I will guide this text to the ends of the earth.
Pirate Gol D. Roger.
The Pirate King...! Could this mean
that he came to this sky island, too?!
What on earth do these words mean?!
No, more importantly,
why can he use these characters?
So it says Roger?
You know him?!
He's a Blue Sea pirate who came to
this sky more than 20 years ago.
So his name is engraved there?
Yes. I don't know how he reached this bell,
but this sure is indelible proof that he did.
Come to think of it, there're
two kinds of Poneglyph stones.
Ones with information, and others that indicate their whereabouts.
And this stone is one of the ones with information.
"I made it here. I will guide this text to the ends of the earth."
Guide this text... Guide...
It couldn't be...!
Could the Rio Poneglyph be...?!
Chief...
This Poneglyph has already fulfilled its role!
It has?!
That's right. I bet those Poneglyphs with information scattered around the world
will, when put together, become one text
that will fill the "Void of History" for the first time.
In other words, the text
completed by connecting them...
That is the Rio Poneglyph,
which still does not exist.
Gol D. Roger, the Pirate King,
definitely delivered this text to its destination.
So it's no longer...
Then...
Hm?
...does that mean that our duty has been fulfilled as well?
We...
We... don't have to... fight any longer?
I see...
Our ancestors' wish has been fulfilled, then?
Chief!
Are you all right?!
Good... Good...
So our duty has been fulfilled!
Yes.
Which means I, too,
have to guide the text on those
Poneglyphs that I read in the past...
...to the end of the Grand Line... to Raftel...
Young lady, the feeling that straw hat
kid gives me is reminiscent of Roger.
Is it my imagination?
His name is Monkey D. Luffy.
My interest in him never fades.
D? I see.
He's got the same letter in his name.
Yes... and I'm sure it's a big issue that
has something to do with history.
By the way, young lady...
You guys wanted gold, right?
You said it's more valuable
than Vearth in the Blue Sea.
Yes.
How about taking the broken belfry column,
though we can't give you the bell...
That's a good idea!
Naturally, we have to show our
appreciation to you guys somehow.
That's right!
Don't hold back!
Are you sure?! They'll be happy to hear that!
Yeah!
Alright, then!
Let's bring this to the Blue Sea people!
Wrap it with cloths! It's hard to carry!
We'll give this to those who saved our land!
Man, this thing's huge...
What's Robin doing? She's late!
Darn! I'm hungry!
In any case, this place is so empty.
What's going on?
Where the heck did the guerrillas and angels go?
Well, it's better they aren't here.
If they find us, they'll chase us around!
Since we're trying to steal this much
gold and run, they won't just let us go!
Well, Nami and Conis are preparing to
set sail, but we still have to hurry.
Before that, Sanji, do you have something to eat?
Not until we get to the ship.
But you've gotta have
something to munch on, right?
Give me some!
What a pain!
We don't have to wait for that woman, do we?
I can't give you what I don't have! Just give up!
I'm gonna go on ahead and get on board.
Idiot! Don't!
Idiot!
Idiot Mosshead!
Mosshead Idiot!
If you go into the forest alone, you won't make it three steps without getting lost!
Hey, look! It's Robin!
Robin-chan!!
Yoo-hoo, Robin!! Hurry! Hurry up!
We've gotta run!! We stole some gold!
Idiot! Don't say that!
Take a good look behind her!!
They're all coming back here together!
There's tons of them!!
This is bad! This is bad! This is super bad!!
And what's that? A huge cannon?!
That's gotta be it!!
They all came back all at once!
Hurry to the ship!
We can no longer stay here!!
Check this out! We got a good catch!
The bag's stuffed! We're rich!
Hm? They all have bags on their back!
Don't tell me... Are they already leaving?!
Hey, stop, you guys!! Stop!!
See?! They found us out!
Hey! Stop! Stop, you guys!
Run!!
I'll strike a pose and say it!
You guys say, "Stop! Stop!" but...
Yeah! Tell them, Usopp!!
We risked our lives to come all
the way to this sky island!
That's right!
And we've found the legendary city of gold!
Robin-chan! Hurry up! We'll be caught!
How the heck can we, proud pirates,
just go back empty-handed?!
What?! Caught?! What's he talking about?
All we want to do is thank them!
Hey Miss, aren't you guys gonna take this gold?
Looks like they don't need it!
What?!
Oh, no!
Run!!
Hey! Wait!
They're all after us! It's scary!
How was that?! Wasn't I cool?!
Yeah! Well done!
Robin-chan! Hurry!!
Hey! Come back!!
Guys! Keep running all the
way to the end of the sky!!
Yeah!!
Samishii nara koe o kikasete
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
Samayoinagara sora o mitsumeteru
You gaze at the heavens as you wander about
Tsuki no you ni matataku koto mo wasure
Just like the moon, you keep your gaze constant
Shizuka ni kie fukaku utsurikomi kaketeku
And your deep reflection wanes as you slowly disappear
Kono mama kawarazu sono kotonoha ni nosete
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Yume o mite ikusen no yoru ni
Dream, you travelers
Tada nagareru tabibito-tachi yo
who spend countless nights drifting
Tatoe modorenakute...
Even if you may not be able to go back
sore demo mata ayumu deshou
you will surely start moving forward again
Listen, everyone! We'll split the treasure once we get back down, okay?!
I'll keep it safe, so don't worry.
Where?!
It's a secret.
There's no way I'll tell you where I hide my secret stash, right?!
Hey!
Just kidding!
That's a lie!
Her eyes say she's telling the truth!
Alright, guys!
We're going back to the Blue Sea!!
Yeah!!
Next time, on One Piece:
Off to the Blue Sea!!
Finale Woven by Feelings
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Off to the Blue Sea!!
Finale Woven by Feelings