Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
With the help of the queen
of New Kama Land Ivankov,
Luffy got to Level 6 where Ace was held!
We transfer custody of the criminal
- Portgas D. Ace to the Navy!
But it was too late! Ace was already on
a ship heading to Navy Headquarters!
I'm gonna go to Navy Headquarters!
After letting Jinbe and Luffy's former enemy
--- Crocodile out of their cells,
they are about to reach Level 4!
Even More Chaos!
Here Comes Blackbeard Teach
Level 2
Beast Hell
Hurry up!
What's going on out there?
--Camisole!
--Long johns!
Everyone, get down to Level 4!
I heard some kind of announcement too.
Maybe something has happened in the prison.
Hey, Buggy! Look!
All the jailers and Blugori are leaving!
Everyone, get down to Level 4 now!
Wow! All the beasts are going away!
--Go away, you fools!
--Don't ever come back!
Seems like they've got a problem
somewhere else, partner!
This is our big chance!
You're right!
When I look back, we've been chased
by the Army Wolves in Level 5...
That was pretty clever of them!
We've suffered the remnants of
Magellan's poison gas in Level 4...
This must be Magellan's poison!
Then we faced the Sphinx again in Level 3!
Gnocchi!
You're still here?!
Penne! Buckwheat noodle with an egg!
Camisole!
Long johns!
T-back!
--Pantyhose!
--Briefs!
And we pretended to be a part of the
floor to trick the beasts just now!
We were pretty much the comic relief
but now we've made it all the way here!
To Level 2!
Just a little more to go to get out of here!
Are you guys ready?!
Anytime!
These copies of keys that
Brother 3 made by wax,
they're fine pieces of work!
--Go to Level 4!
--What's wrong, A team?
--Get B team!
--We lost touch with C team!
--Hurry up! What're you doing?
--Answer me!
What?! Vice Warden, this is
the monitoring room!
What's wrong?!
It's weird...
What?!
No, no, this cool headdress is...
...something that I ordered secretly
to wear when I became the warden....
I'm not talking about that!
I see somebody sneaking around Level 2!
They look like prisoners!
What did you just say?!
Thanks!
You gotta thank Captain Buggy for this!
Send the remaining guards there to check!
Yes, sir!
Are there any jailers on Level 2?!
Answer me if you're still there!
--Yes?!
--What are you guys doing?!
We were gonna go down to Level 4 as ordered.
No, inspect that floor!
This floor?
This is our time, partner!
While they're having a riot here again,
we're gonna stow away on a Navy ship!
Yeah, then our prison break will be complete!
I think that Straw Hat and
Mr. 2 are already dead...
...or they will spend the
rest of their life in prison!
But my own life is the one I saved!
-- I feel very sorry for them!
That's Buggy the Clown!
Look! There's Mr. 3, too!
Look up!
Up?
All right, guys! This is our big chance!
If you wanna get back on the
street, go berserk for your life!
Now let's kick it off!
--He's our savior!
--Captain Buggy!
T-This is Level 2!
The prisoners are out of their
cells and rampaging again!
Send the Blugori back! It's out of control!
Snap!
This is Level 4!
--What now?!
--The Queen of Queers Ivankov and Inazuma...
...and Mr. 2 who tricked you earlier are...
Heehaw!
Gimme a break!
--They're here with a mob!
--A mob?!
Everyone, get down to Level 4
now! Everyone, get down to...
I can't believe this but the
people that they're with...
...are the prisoners who had disappeared
by "Demoning Away" over the years!
What?! What's really going on here?!
It's for sure!
Somebody tell me if I can
still become the warden!
Heehaw! Finally, I caught up with you!
Straw-chan!
Bon-chan! Looks like you
got your juice flowing now!
Yeah, I'm more than fine now!
No! Why are you here, Mr. 1?!
Who is it?
He's the guy who was defeated
by Sash-chan in Alabasta!
"One"
Oh, then I don't know him.
Vice Warden, we need backup on Level 4 now!
We need it on Level 2, too!
What should I do?
--Please hurry!
--Hannyabal-sama, give us an order!
--We need it on Level 4!
--No, on Level 2!
--Vice Warden, give us an order now!
Emporio...
...Face Growth Synthesis!
Heehaw!
So annoying!
Hell Wink!
We can't stop them!
They were all vicious
before they disappeared...
...but now they're very bizarre!
Fishman Karate!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Memoir of that Winter Sky!
For lots of reasons--we can't stop them!
Let's get to Navy Headquarters!
We've had word of an unprecedented
riot going on in Impel Down.
The ringleader is Monkey D. Luffy.
This is your last chance to see the sky.
Once you've been shackled on the
scaffold, you will never again...
...see the sky.
This is Onigumo.
Prepare to open the gates of Marineford!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
How did it go?
"Navy"
We still can't find him! Ace's
execution is in 5 hours...
...so time is of the essence because
Whitebeard could appear at anytime!
But we can't find the Warlord of the Sea,
\ Blackbeard, anywhere on this island!
And maybe this is unrelated but
a Navy ship without clearance...
...has just arrived at Impel Down!
What?!
I don't think that it's him but...
Why did he come here?!
Search the ship they arrived on!
Yes, sir!
Please wait! We didn't ask
for reinforcements and...
...there's a state of emergency here
so we can't assure your safety!
We're waiting to hear from
the Headquarters now so...
It doesn't matter! We're on the same side!
But even so, pirates are not
allowed to enter the prison...
There's no need to hesitate!
I'm...
...on the Government side!
What a gloomy place!
Sir! All crew members of the ship--
that Blackbeard was on are wiped out!
What?!
Hey!
Yes, sir!
Stop there!
Liberation!
We have an intruder! The Warlord
of the Sea - Marshall D. Teach!
Hey, you alright?!
They're the ones who vanished a while back!
Darkness...
Blackbeard and his clan are breaking
into the prison! This doesn't look good!
I was dragged into the darkness!
His motive is unknown!
Give us an order! H-Hurry!
It's over! My life is over now!
No, this is just a beginning!
A sad and long life in which I
will never become the warden...
...has just begun!
Vice Warden! Are you okay?!
Straw Hat on Level 4!
Buggy the Clown on Level 2!
Main Entrance
The Warlord of the Sea, Blackbeard,
at the main entrance!
I don't know...
...how to begin to deal with this mess!
"Impel Down's Exclusive, Premium
'Fried Rice Crackers'"
Anybody want snacks?
Are you nuts?! We gotta save Impel Down!
Ring, ring, ring...
That's easy for you to
say! You're not in charge!
--I see! You wanna become a vice warden!
--Hannyabal!
Can you hear me?!
W-Warden Magellan?! Where are you now?!
I'm on Level 2.
I've just taken care of the
fools running wild here.
Huh?!
Help me!
I blocked all the exits on this floor!
All of them will stop moving soon!
We're blocked up!
Captain Buggy! There is a
block of poison in our way!
Damn Magellan! How annoying!
We can't stay here!
I don't know why Blackbeard
is attacking us...
--...but I already did something about it.
--Nice!
It's not something that I wanted to do but
I have no option under the circumstances!
It's not something that you wanted to do?!
I decided to release Shiryu against my will!
You did?!
Anyway, we can't ask the Navy
Headquarters for reinforcements.
We have to handle this ourselves!
You focus on bringing the situation
on Level 4 under control!
I'm gonna head down to Level 4 soon!
Hold out until I'll get there!
Warden!
Hey, Warden! Hey, Warden! Hey, Warden!...
Can we go now?
Fever!
Heehaw!
Crab-chan! Where is the
staircase to Level 3?!
Go left! And across that bridge!
Got it!
Get out of my way!
"Prison"
Light.
Yes, sir!
Jail Manager of Impel Down
Shiryu of the Rain
Shiryu, how do you like it out of the cell?
Yeah, I really learned a lesson.
The eternal boredom makes you long for death.
But you're not gonna use me as a pawn
and then ask me to go back into
the cell, are you, Magellan?
You're a condemned prisoner! And
this is a deferred sentence!
This is your only chance!
Yeah, I bet.
I'll keep that in mind!
Here's your sword, Jail Manager Shiryu.
I'll leave Blackbeard to you!
Yes, sir!
Clank!
Oh my sword!
I haven't seen it for a while!
I have the right...
...to cut you down!
With the Blackbeard pirates having invaded,
Impel Down spirals further into chaos.
Blackbeard and the others manage
to evade the traps set out for them.
Meanwhile, the man freed
by Magellan stands in their way.
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Dangerous Encounter!
Blackbeard and Shiryu of the Rain"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Dangerous Encounter!
Blackbeard and Shiryu of the Rain