Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
But Ace has already been taken away to Navy Headquarters!
--I'm going!
--Huh?!
I'm gonna go to Navy Headquarters!
Now Luffy and others are trying to
break out and have gotten to Level 4...
but at the staircase to Level 3, they
face the furious Vice Warden Hannyabal!
This is the great fort of hell!
If we let prisoners out of here, the
world will be filled with terror!
So as I said, I won't let you take...
...even a single step!
The only thing I care about
is saving Ace! So just move!
Cut it out!
All this arguing about right and wrong!
Search the ends of the earth,
and you'd find no answer!
So, cut the crap!
Looks like you were in middle of something!
Teach! Why the hell are you here?!
Or should I call you Blackbeard now?
Blackbeard!
So you're... Blackbeard?!
Pay your respects at Ace's grave!
If it weren't for him,
you'd be the one who...
...would've been killed, Straw Hat!
Then why don't you try to kill me now?!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Pistol!
The Jet Pistol of Rage
Luffy vs. Blackbeard
Captain!
I won't let Ace die!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
Vortex!
Straw-chan!
Blood? I thought his body was rubber!
Blood?
Seems like you don't have
any idea of what happened!
You brother Ace looked like that!
I think that you got it when I grabbed you!
Another thing that my darkness drags in is...
...Devil Fruit powers!
That means as long as I touch them,
Devil Fruit users can't
use all of their powers!
And that's how I beat Ace! Don't you get it?
Devil Fruit powers are ineffective before me!
So what?!
Wait, Luffy-kun! Enough already!
Let me go!
Not now! Hold your anger!
No, Luffy-kun! What is your priority?!
Think about it! Luffy-kun!
Ever since he was on good old
Whitebeard's ship, he was so strange!
I don't know how he got it
but he has this power that enabled him
to defeat even the unbeatable Ace-san!
You can't waste your time and energy here!
Fighting with him out of anger now
doesn't help you to save Ace-san!
You're stronger than I thought!
You got more Haki than you did before!
Your name is Blackbeard?
I heard that a nameless pirate...
...who was on Whitebeard's ship
had taken my place as a Warlord.
But it's odd.
You should've been summoned
by Navy Headquarters already.
Why are you here?
You're risking your title of Warlord
that you really wanted by being here.
It's all part of my plan!
Do I have to tell you everything about it?
Mr. Crocodile!
No, you don't. Actually
I'm not interested at all.
Oh, how cold of you!
H-Hey! What's going on?!
Magellan's here!
It's not good.
Straw-boy, you better go now!
If you get poisoned by Magellan again,
there's no way for you to survive this time!
It's Warden Magellan!
Dammit! Everyone, run!
Warden Magellan...
Thank god! Warden's here!
Magellan... I get to meet him finally!
Climb up the stairs!
The bazooka troops are gone!
Nothing's in our way now!
Ivankov! Mmm... I won't let you go!
Let me hear the scream of a queer!
P-P-Princess! P-P-Please don't!
S-S-Striking me with your
whip? It's gonna hurt!
What happened to you?
But I like how you're freaking out!
Now stop fighting me!
I-I-I got it! I'm coming to you now!
Catch me if you can!
Mmm... My whip!
Give it back to me, Ivankov!
If you're so into screaming,
why don't you scream yourself?!
I'm the Queen of Queers--Ivankov!
Why don't you call me Mistress?!
Heehaw!
Ivankov!
Straw Hat! You better hurry and
climb up the stairs to Level 3!
It's fortunate for us that you broke
their defense on the staircase!
You helped us, too.
We took advantage of the
panic that you caused!
Yes! We can get to Level 3!
Let's go at once!
It's a Jailer Beast again!
This time, it's Minotaurus!
What?! Minotaurus?!
"Oh Come My Way" Kenpo:
Memoir of that Winter Sky!
Ready, Straw Hat?!
--Candle Lock!
--Alright!
Gum-Gum...
...Mallet Rifle!
I thought that we already
beat him on Level 3!
It's inevitable.
They're all awakened Zoan type Devil Fruit users!
That's why they're extremely
tough and resilient!
So you're saying that he
ate the Devil Fruit, too?!
If we don't hurry up, the
other three will recover soon.
But we shouldn't be afraid of them now.
Because the boss of hell
will be here any minute!
Warden Magellan!
I got a report that Blackbeard is already
on this floor at the staircase to Level 3!
I ordered Shiryu to handle
them! Was he defeated?!
--This is the monitoring room!
--What now?!
We've got a problem!
Somebody broke the Vision
Receiver Transponder Snail...
...and none of monitors are working now!
Plus, all communication channels to Navy HQ and government agencies are cut off!
So we can't contact...
W-What's going on here?
What's the matter?! What happened?!
--Who did all that?!
--Clank!
Don't blow my cover!
I don't want Magellan clued in!
The communication has been cut!
--Send someone to check!
--Yes, sir!
This is bad.
If Blackbeard got
to this floor, it means that...
...he has broken the block that I set
on Level 2 and made his way there!
Nothing is going as planned!
We allowed just this one rat to
sneak in and now look at this mess!
--Buggy!
--Mr. 3!
We are flashy lucky men!
Guys! We're finally here! It's Level 1!
Everyone! We're gonna go
out on the sunny street!
Our very lucky savior!
Captain Buggy!
I can't believe that the poison
block had gone on its own!
Yeah, me too!
We're so lucky!
I'm gonna save Ace at any cost!
Yeah, I'm not gonna say that it's a waste!
Anything is possible in this world!
I told you that the Sky Island exists!
She said "Sky Island"!
Give me a break!
Hey, you got me there.
You guys believe in such an ancient legend...
that there's an island in the sky?
Listen. The era where pirates
dream about things is over!
When I see idiots chasing after
dreams like that, I get disgusted!
Luffy!
The Sky Island exists.
You're that guy...
The new era they're talking about is crap!
The era where pirates have dreams
will be over, they say?! Huh?!
People's dreams... have no end!!
Isn't that right?!
And so does the One Piece!
It certainly exists!
You all should look forward to this!
In a few hours, we're going to...
...put on a show that's
gonna shake the whole world!
Don't stop, Luffy-kun!
Heehaw!
Keep going!
To Level 3!
There's no way that we can beat
him! We can't get through!
He's pushing us backward on
his way down the staircase!
Damn! We're helpless! What should we do?!
Hey, Straw Hat! Be careful!
--Straw-chan! Let me help...
--Wait!
Why?
We better not bother him now!
Hey! What do you mean
"bother?!" I just wanna...
Outta my way!
Straw-chan!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Pistol!
Ace!
A-Amazing!
He finished the Jailer Beast with a single blow!
He's quite a guy as I thought!
Straw-chan!
Okay, guys! The lid of the
pot of hell is off now!
Let's go!
Warden!
Can you just help me, Warden?!
Sadie-chan! What happened to you?!
Queer-kov... has beaten me!
It's humiliating! My life
is about dominating others!
Help her get down! I gotta run!
Oh, yes! Right away!
Are you Magellan?!
So you're Blackbeard?!
Yes, indeed!
Hydra!
I don't have time to ask
what brought you guys here!
Ouch! What is this?!
It should be poison! Dammit! That bastard!
Hannyabal!
I'm surprised that you held out this long!
Let me handle the rest!
Vice Warden!
You look horrible!
--Give him the treatment now!
--Yes, sir!
Vice Warden! Stay with me! Vice Warden!
You can't die! Because you're the only one...
...who can take my place!
Straw Hat! How did you survive
after I poisoned you?!
He's probably the one who
caused this situation!
I must take his life for sure this time!
Straw Hat!
Is that Magellan?!
That was from the bottom of the stairs!
Once he catches us, we're dead!
That poison bastard!
I will never let you get out of this prison!
Luffy and the others have finally reached Level 3.
In order to hold off Magellan,
who continues to gain on them,
Iva-san orders Inazuma to seal off
the stairway leading to Level 2
and remains behind on Level 3 alone
where he unleashes his secret technique,
New Kama Kenpo, on Magellan!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Stop Magellan!
Iva-san Unleashes His Secret Art"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Stop Magellan!
Iva-san Unleashes His Secret Art