Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
Fire!
What are you...?!
Luffy-san!
Straw Hat?!
That doesn't work!
I told you I was strong!
W-Who the hell are you?!
I'm Luffy!
The man who's gonna be the Pirate King!
Morgan vs. Luffy!
Who's the Mysterious Pretty Girl?
W-What?!
The Pirate King?!
Do you even know what that means?!
The Pirate King is the Pirate King!
Are there any other meanings?
I was shocked, too!
But Luffy-san is serious!
That's how he is!
He intends to become Pirate King
and obtain this world's ultimate treasure... the One Piece!
Here's your treasure!
Which is yours?
I couldn't tell, so I brought three of 'em.
All three are mine.
I use the Three-Sword Style.
You'll take 'em, right?
If we fight together now,
you'll be a Government-defying villain!
Would you prefer that,
or being killed by the Navy like this?
What are you, the devil's son?!
Well, whatever.
I'll be your pirate,
if I'm just gonna die here instead!
Hurray! So you'll join my crew?!
Alright! Woo-hoo!
This is great! Alright!
Okay!
Now untie these stupid ropes already!
What... is he?
He flung the bullets back!
He's no ordinary human, that Straw Hat...
Must've eaten one of those rumored Devil Fruits!
– A Devil Fruit?!
– The hidden treasures of the sea?!
The Devil Fruits...
Whoever eats one is said to
gain seemingly unworldly abilities.
The power to breathe fire...
The power to cause tsunamis...
There are all sorts of rumors,
but there are many types,
and almost nothing is known about them.
It's said the secrets to
them lie in the Grand Line...
...but there's no question
Straw Hat just displayed a devil power!
Hurry! Hurry!
Damn! These knots are tight!
Hey! Quit wastin' time!
No matter who they are,
everyone who opposes me gets executed!
If guns won't work,
then chop them to death!
Huh, that's weird! It got tighter instead!
Give me a damn sword!
Luffy-san!
Roronoa Zoro!
So cool!
Move and you're dead.
Too scary!
I'll be a pirate. I promise you that.
I'm officially a criminal,
now that I've fought the Navy.
But I'll tell you this right now.
I'm only going to fulfill my ambition!
Ambition?
To be the world's greatest swordsman!
If I wind up having to give that up,
you'd better accept responsibility and apologize to me!
The world's greatest swordsman?
That sounds great!
The Pirate King would need no less than that on his crew!
You sure talk big.
At this point, whether it's as
a criminal or whatever else,
I will spread my name throughout the world!
What're you standing around for?!
Slaughter them this instant!
Duck, Zoro!
Gum-Gum Whip!
Y-You did it! Incredible!
What the hell are you?
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Gum-Gum Fruit?
A rubber man!
So he does have Devil Fruit powers!
Captain!
We don't stand a chance against them!
These guys are crazy!
We can't even handle Zoro by himself!
This is a direct order!
Everyone who spouted weakness just now...
...must now shoot themselves in the head!
I have no need for weakling soldiers!
These troops are mental!
Luffy-san!
Crush this Navy!
Rankless, low-status bums have
no right whatsoever to defy me!
I am Navy Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan!
I'm Luffy!
Nice to meetcha!
Die!
Th-The captain!
R-Runt...
Die!
No thanks!
C-Captain Morgan is...
...being trounced completely...
And you call yourself a navy?!
You've destroyed Koby's dream!
Hold it, Straw Hat!
Check this out!
I said hold it!
Are you stupid?!
Pay attention!
I have a hostage here!
Helmeppo-sama!
Hey.
If you value this guy's life, don't move!
One move and I'll shoot!
Luffy-san!
I don't want to get in your way!
Even if it means dying!
Yeah, I know!
Give it up, stupid son!
Koby really is ready to die!
Don't move!
I told you not to move!
I-I'll shoot!
Behind you!
Gum-Gum...
I am Navy Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan!
– Dad! Kill him, quick!
– ...Pistol!
Nice!
Zoro.
My pleasure, Captain.
Captain Morgan's been beaten!
– Unbelievable!
– These guys are insane!
If anyone else still wants
to catch us, come forward!
– Hurray!
– We're free!
– Yahoo!
– Morgan's reign is over!
Hurray for the Navy!
Huh? Everyone's happy
their captain's been beaten...
Everyone was just afraid of Morgan!
What's wrong, Zoro-san?!
Are you hurt?!
I'm... hungry...
Sorry!
Just endure it for a while!
Doesn't seem to be in here, either...
Yes! A chart of the Grand Line!
I knew they had one!
"I'VE FLASHILY TAKEN THE MAP! BUGGY!"
Th-This isn't a chart!
What is this mark?!
Captain Buggy...
The man known as Buggy the Immortal...
I'm stuffed!
I was definitely at my rope's end,
having not eaten for three weeks!
Huh? You're finished already?
How the heck can you have
a bigger appetite than me?!
It tastes good! Right, Koby?
Thank you for treating me to food, too...
It's no problem!
The town has been saved, after all!
You really are amazing!
Yep, I am!
And I'm gonna be even more amazing!
'Cause I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
And I even have a crew!
So, how many others have
you gathered besides me?
You said you were in the
middle of gathering a crew.
To become Pirate King,
you must have a good number gathered.
Just you.
Huh?! Then...
Yep! Just us two!
We're gonna call just us two a pirate crew?!
What's wrong with that?
We are strong!
What about a ship?
Where's your pirate ship?
There.
That?
We'll have a ship this big before long!
And how's that?!
And I'd like a pirate flag, too!
Yeah! Yeah, yeah! So cool!
I think Luffy-san was born
without any sense of planning.
Did I really make this guy my captain?!
Well, we'll get more
crew members before long!
Hey, hey!
Where are you guys gonna go to now?
Isn't it obvious?! The Grand Line!
You still only have two members!
There's no way you can go there!
No way! No way! No way!
Is the Grand Line that terrible of a place?
Naturally!
You know this world has two oceans, right?
And the giant continent that cuts
them right in two is the Red Line.
Supposedly, there's a town right
in the middle of the Red Line,
and the Grand Line goes
through it at a right angle...
...and stretches around the world.
It was said that Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
once obtained everything
this world has to offer,
and before he died, he said he left
the great One Piece treasure there,
so pirates everywhere have
since set sail for the Grand Line!
It's now an intense battlefield,
and even called a pirate graveyard!
I've heard from patrons before...
...that whoever enters the
Grand Line never comes out alive...
But the One Piece is somewhere there,
so we're going there!
Guess it can't be helped!
Not you too, Zoro-san?!
What's it matter?
You're not going, are you?
N-No, but I'm worried about you!
Is that so wrong?!
Luffy-san and I haven't
known each other long,
but we are friends!
Right?
Yeah! We're gonna part ways,
but we'll always be friends!
Since I was a little kid,
I've never had friends...
Much less anyone who
would fight for my sake...
But more than anything,
I never tried to fight for anything...
But you two taught me
how to live for my beliefs!
I've decided to make
my childhood dream come true!
I want to join the Navy!
Shouldn't you be more
worried about yourself, then?
Even if you were just a chore boy,
you did spend two years
on Alvida's pirate ship.
Don't underestimate the
Navy's info-gathering skills.
If they find out about that,
you'll never get to join.
N-Now that you mention it...
Pardon me!
Is it true that you are pirates?!
Yeah. We gained a member
and became a pirate group just now!
We appreciate that you saved our
base and this town from that tyrant!
However, now that we know you are pirates,
in the name of the Navy,
we cannot stand by quietly!
You will leave this town at once!
Out of obligation, we will refrain
from contacting headquarters.
Hey, Navy guy!
How can you talk like that?!
Even you guys were subdued and terrified of Morgan!
We owe these people our lives!
Yeah! Yeah!
Well, guess we should go!
Thanks for the food, lady!
You guys are leaving already?
Yeah.
Aren't you part of their crew?
Eh? I...
I'm...
Hold it!
Well? Is he?!
I know what he's done until now.
Luffy-san! You wouldn't!
There was this really fat pirate lady,
I think her name was Ahiruda.
Luffy-san!
If they find out I was on a pirate ship,
I'll never get to join the Navy!
And she had this iron club.
Man, she was an ugly hag!
And for two whole years, this guy was her-
Please don't!
Please don't, Luffy-san!
Now you've done it, you bastard!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
Stop that!
We won't allow you to cause
any more trouble in this town!
Hey! You've gone too far.
That's enough.
It's very clear that you
guys aren't crewmates!
Now leave this town at once!
On purpose...
He did that on purpose...
For me...
He purposely got me riled up to make me hit him...
Even in the very end,
I wound up relying on him!
Nothing's changed at all!
Am I an idiot?!
Please!
Please... let me join the Navy!
I'll gladly do chores or anything else!
If it means I can be a marine!
Lieutenant Colonel! I'm against the idea!
I still don't fully trust this kid!
There have been cases of
marines being pirate spies!
We'll first need to conduct a background check...
I'm a man who will become a Navy officer!
Countless comrades of ours
have been killed by pirates.
Don't take the Navy lightly.
Then...
Permission to join granted!
Yes, sir!
"I'VE FLASHILY TAKEN THE MAP! BUGGY!"
That was a pretty lame act.
Wouldn't be shocked if they saw through it.
Koby'll handle the rest on his own now.
I just know it.
It's a nice way to leave, though.
Being unable to turn back
'cause everyone hates you-
it's pirate-like!
That's true!
Luffy-san!
Thank you!
I'll never forget all you've done for me!
I've never heard of a pirate
being thanked by a marine...
Let's meet again sometime, Koby!
– Luffy-san...
– Bye!
All hands, salute!
See ya!
That's a great friend you have there.
Yes, sir!
Our salute just now is in violation of naval law!
Therefore, we will all go without
food for three days! Understood?!
Yes, sir!
I'm sure...
I'm sure we'll meet again
sometime, somewhere, Luffy-san!
Even if we're divided as pirates and marines...
...let's meet again someday!
Alright!
Our pirate crew finally sets sail!
Looks like some pretty good
adventures'll be waiting for us.
I will be the Pirate King!
You really seem obsessed
about this Pirate King thing.
Is there some sorta reason for it?
No reason. It's just...
It's just?
I swore to a certain man that...
...someday I would gather a great crew,
find the world's greatest treasure,
and become the Pirate King!
This straw hat knows!
I see...
Alright! Let's go!
Set sail for the Grand Line!
Geez, you don't even know how to navigate right?!
– Do you know how?
– No!
Ahh! Hey, stop rocking the boat!
My hat'll fall off!
Is your straw hat that important?
Yeah! It's my treasure!
I have to return it to him
once I'm the Pirate King!
Who's "him"?
Next time, on One Piece:
Luffy's Past!
Enter Red-Haired Shanks
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Luffy's Past!
Enter Red-Haired Shanks