How many times do I have to tell you?!
I said "I just wanna eat meat"!
I'm sorry!
Boy! If you don't have any meat,
bring me more candies and stuff!
It's still gonna take a while
before we reach Mary Geoise!
We don't know when we'll be attacked!
--Everybody, keep up your guard!
--Yes, sir!
I managed to get out of that crappy place
but I got caught by these crappy people...
Crap!
I've been looking for a
chance to escape but...
...no luck.
I can hear you.
Where did you hide the Pure Gold?
Humph! I wouldn't tell you even if I knew!
Is the World Government looking for the
treasure that's worth enough
to buy the whole world?
How greedy is that? But...
...it's all mine.
Because I'm greedier than you!
What?!
What?! What's going on?!
Get back!
Okay...
This is my chance to escape.
We can hear you!
Take evasive action!
We can't see where they're
attacking from at all!
How can you not see your
enemy ship on the water?!
Where is it?
Where are they attacking from?!
Hey!
Don't you see anything up there?!
I don't! I don't see a thing!
Who are you?!
I was born in the North Blue
I ate the Color-Color Fruit
and became a camouflage man
Psycho P!
Are you surprised?
My cool graffiti!
I hope you know.
Tesoro-sama is very interested
in the Pure Gold.
So be sure...
...not to kill the girl.
Shut up.
You're sobering me up.
I won't do something like sink a treasure.
Four warships aren't enough to stop me.
Mad Anchor!
Camoufla-paint!
Hey! Where are you?!
Your never-give-up attitude isn't half bad!
Naomi...
Psycho P...
Hey, my boss...
It's a treasure hunt!
That hurts! I said "That hurts"!
We can't let you have it.
The Pure Gold belongs
to the World Government!
No! The Pure Gold is all...
...mine!
I found you, Myskina Olga...
You're the key to the Pure Gold!
You're quite strong.
Are you one of those Devil Fruit users?
You want the Pure Gold too, don't you?
I can show you the way if you want.
You're unexpectedly obedient, young lady.
But only if you can get me out of here.
Stop! Don't speak so freely.
How did you know about the girl?!
I have a patron who gives me
information about the Government.
Who is it?!
I'm not obliged to answer that!
I can't believe they sent
out Cipher Pol "Aigis" Zero.
I guess the Celestial Dragons are desperate
to have the Pure Gold, aren't they?!
I don't need to answer that!
They're fighting really hard.
This is my chance to run.
We can hear you!
Chain Hammer!
There's nowhere to run now, Little Betty
What the...?!
He has some strange ability.
You'd better give up now.
All right, take us to the
legendary island, Alchemi!
I don't like classless guys like you!
Elizabeth!
Idiot! There is a place to run!
Idiot! Idiot!
She's got an associate.
Don't kill her.
This is interesting.
Let's let her go for now.
Will it be okay?
You sure?
Tell Tesoro...
...that I'll get the Pure Gold at any price!
All right, then I'm gonna
go back to Grantesoro.
This will tell you where it's anchored.
There is a Vivre Card of Tesoro-sama inside.
He said he'll pay whatever
you want as a reward.
I don't care about money.
I have no interest
in the treasures that I've gotten already.
They're already dead to me.
They don't excite me at all.
I'm a treasure hunter.
I just wanna be drunk on the
excitement of the moment
when I find a treasure!
I'm sorry.
We were attacked by Mad Treasure.
And we let Myskina Olga escape.
Find her no matter what.
If you let anybody else have the Pure Gold,
you know what'll happen to you.
Yes, sir.
A gentle smile and a dignified smile
Your adorable smile
Silver hearts and gold hearts
I'll give them all to you
Alchemi, Alchema
Hold the gold star
Go into a dream
Now I managed to escape but
I'll die of hunger like this.
I gotta do something.
What's that straw hat symbol?
Are they pirates?
That pirate looks like an idiot.
He looks weak.
Chopper-san, are you alright?!
Yeah!
I'm gonna fish more!
Alright, I'm gonna fish more too!
Look! A lizard is running on the water!
How can you do that?
You put your left leg forward
before your right leg sinks.
I can do that.
A girl is on its back!
Seems like she's unconscious!
We gotta save her!
Leave it to me!
--Now's your chance!
--Yeah!
Yes!
What?!
What is it this time?!
Oh?
What are a lizard and a kid doing here?
You're causing us more trouble.
How did they get here?
I caught them.
It's strange...
What? Is something wrong with her?
It's odd!
I don't see any wound and her pulse is stable
so I don't think she's in a
life-threatening condition...
Is she just sleeping, then?
You don't wanna sleep here.
You're gonna catch cold.
Okay, let's just wake her up!
You're up!
Thank you for saving me...
Don't move!
Oh, she's good.
Elizabeth! Come here!
All right, don't try to come closer!
He's a hostage!
If you wanna save your friend's life,
give me some water and food!
I'm hungry and it's driving me mad!
Move quickly or...
...I'll just park my blade right here!
There's no point in taking Luffy hostage...
Why are you guys ignoring me?!
I said water and food!
If you're hungry, do you wanna eat this?
I'm not gonna eat such a salty thing!
You guys are just a goofy,
weak group of pirates!
Elizabeth and I can easily destroy you!
She says "No sweat" as well.
What?
Do you understand what Elizabeth is saying?
Yeah.
Oh, wow! I mean you're...
...so fluffy and cute!
Your compliment doesn't make
me happy at all, you fool!
You're so cute!
She's wide open.
Luffy-san has been freed as well.
You're so horrible. You almost got me.
You were trying to lower my guard
with your cuteness, weren't you?
That was close.
What?!
That brat... How has she
survived being that stupid?
Give me water and food... now!
Are you okay?!
Eat it.
You put poison or something in there,
didn't you?!
I'm a cook.
I wouldn't do anything to waste food.
Now, you can't eat holding that, can you?
Don't rush. I'll make
you as much as you want.
She says "Thank you for feeding Olga."
Olga, after you eat,
you need to tell us why you did this.
Oh... That pattern...
Is that the script of Alchemi?
Alchemi?
Damn! I can't believe someone noticed.
What's that?
Alchemi is a legendary island
that suddenly disappeared 200 years ago.
Did you have enough?
I've never had anything
this delicious before!
Hey! Tell us about Alchemi.
In Alchemi, there was a person
named Myskina Acier...
...who was doing research
on how to refine metal, I heard.
He created a metal called Pure Gold.
Pure Gold?
It's a legendary metal.
They say it even shines in darkness
and it's worth a fortune,
enough to even buy the whole world.
People have been looking for the Pure Gold
since the earliest times.
However, those who obtain it ruin themselves.
This Pure Gold thing is unbelievable.
A legendary metal, huh?!
"It's worth a fortune,
enough to even buy the whole world"?!
I want it!
Do you have anything to do with Alchemi?
Do you know where the treasure is?
Tell us!
I won't tell you!
You're a horrible liar.
Saying "I won't tell you" is almost like
admitting that you know where it is.
Where is Alchemi?!
Even if I tell you,
it's impossible for you weak pirates to get it.
You're not gonna believe where it's located.
It sounds interesting!
We'll take you to Alchemi.
Dangerous people are everywhere
in the New World.
We can protect you if we're with you.
I don't need any help from others!
I've been living by myself for so long!
I only interact with other people
to take advantage of them.
You're just a kid
but you've been through a lot!
Your pity won't make my stomach full.
What the... When did you change?
Oh, this?!
We need to be prepared if we're
gonna hunt for the treasure!
All right! Let's go treasure hunting!
What? I haven't said I'm coming with you yet.
The Straw Hat Treasure Gang!
Go!
Listen to me!
You can't stop them
once they get into that zone.
Olga.
We need to talk.
About what?
We have nine people on our side
but we can do with 6:4 for
the ratio of the share.
Of course, you take "6"!
Weak pirates like you guys can't get
to the Pure Gold anyway.
We guarantee you we will. Look!
We have this many champs
worth over 100 million.
We'll also offer you the
service of taking you
to any island you like after
exchanging the treasure for money.
I give you such a special offer
because of our friendship.
Isn't it a good deal?
Humph! Honestly!
Okay, so these people are strong.
That means I can use these Straw Hat idiots
as much as I like...
...to get the Pure Gold and
betray them at the end.
I can have it all to myself that way!
I heard everything you said.
So that's how it is and...
...Olga has agreed to guide us to Alchemi!
But she's gonna betray us
at the end so be careful!
And how are you gonna guide us?
Do you have an Eternal Pose or something?
I have this.
This will lead us to Alchemi.
The thing is there is a piece
of Pure Gold inside this ring.
What?! Pure Gold?!
Let me see!
No! If I let it shine in a place like this,
it's gonna be a problem!
Hey, you damn Mosshead!
I know. You don't have to call
me every time, Dirty Cook!
What's this?
I feel something is here!
What?! What's going on?!
There must be enemies.
Tsk! I don't like stubborn guys.
It's...
...Mad Treasure!
Do you know him?
He's a treasure hunter who'd
do anything to get treasure.
He's the worst.
I can't believe you detected the camouflage.
Seems like even Psycho P's
ability isn't good enough
for Observation Haki!
The ability of camouflage?!
What's wrong? Are you okay?
It's nothing, Robin-chan.
Hey, you Dirty Water Imp!
Do you know that guy too?
No... I wish I had known...
Are you guys going for the Pure Gold too?
Yeah! We're gonna go on
a treasure hunt with her!
I let her go so that she
could guide us to Alchemi.
I'm not happy with some pirates
stealing the lead to the Pure Gold!
Crap! It's started!
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
Oh, now that I get a good look at them
and it's clear that they're the Straw Hats
who are drawing so much
attention in the New World.
This is gonna be fun.
Exploding Star!
Dos Fleurs:
Clutch!
You guys really are strong!
I'll protect you even if it kills me!
Oh, I'm already dead!
Luffy is the guy who took down
the ill-famed Doflamingo!
What? What's a Doflamingo?
Olga, you really don't know anything...
Well, just watch.
You'll see that it's a pretty safe
bet to go on an adventure with us.
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
This is great.
The stronger the enemy
who you fight over treasure,
the more exciting treasure hunting gets!
Young lady.
Cheating is bad.
I'll go along with your
treasure hunt to the end!
No, I don't want you!
I don't like classless guys like you!
Olga has already become our ally!
I'm the one who decides that!
Straw Hat!
I'll take the lead for the Pure Gold!
That's not up to you to decide!
You bastard!
No, fools!
She'll die if you keep pulling!
Something's gonna come out of me!
I knew she had it!
Is that...
...the Pure Gold?!
The treasure that can even
buy the whole world, is...
The treasure sank into the sea!
So why don't you guys go away already?!
Olga, are you okay?
I almost threw up.
Oh no!
Bonbori-sama's gonna come!
Bonbori-sama...?
What's that?
--Isn't that too big?!
--Yes!
That's a giant footballfish.
Bonbori-sama.
H-Hey! This is bad news, isn't it?!
My boss, let's pull out!
Franky, make an emergency escape
with Coup de Burst!
Okay!
Guys! Hang onto something!
The Emergency Escape System!
Coup de...!
Wait!
You shouldn't run!
What are you talking about?!
Do you really wanna look for the Pure Gold?
Yeah because it sounds interesting.
Then, let me tell you something.
The phantom island, Alchemi, is...
...located inside Bonbori-sama's stomach!
I thought the Pure Gold sank
into the sea earlier...
That was just a tiny piece of it!
A really jumbo piece of
Pure Gold is in there!
A really jumbo piece of Pure Gold?!
Franky! Bring us about 180 degrees!
Okay!
Wait a sec!
If you want a really jumbo piece of Pure Gold,
head into the mouth!
--Okay!
--No, you idiot!
Don't do it!
We're gonna die if we get chewed up!
My boss!
We're gonna sail in there too!
It looks interesting!
Well, we have no choice but to go.
This is an adventure!
Oh no!
The Pure Gold!
We've been completely devoured!
If nothing is done, we'll be digested
and be nothing but bones.
Oh! I'm already nothing but bones!
They followed us!
They came into the mouth?!
They must be out of their minds!
So are you all!
Here they come!
Avoid the uvula!
Uvula?
That's big.
He wants to make us crash into the uvula!
I know! But...!
The uvula is huge!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Nice, Luffy!
Luffy-san, grab my hand!
Yeah!
--Luffy!
--Luffy-san!
Those who get in our way
are destined for hell!
Oh no! Luffy's gonna die!
What? Why?
Devil Fruit users can't swim
because the sea hates them.
They can't even use their abilities
so they'll just drown.
In that case, it's not a bad idea
to have them owe me a favor or two.
Elizabeth!
I'll save Luffy!
Whoa-whoa, will she be okay?
Tsk! What a pain!
--Sanji-kun!
--Yes, Nami-san!
Leave Luffy with Olga and you stay here!
Luffy's in trouble but...
...seems like we're also in trouble.
We passed through the uvula
but now, are we gonna
fall through the throat,
straight down to the stomach?!
And we'll be broken down to pulp
by gastric juices.
Quit the scary thoughts!
Guys! Don't get thrown off!
Now...
How is it gonna be?
It's one of the most exciting
treasure hunts ever!
I'm losing strength...
Luffy! I'm coming to save you!
Where am I?
Anyway, I gotta find everyone else.
Ouch!
Be careful.
If you soak in Bonbori-sama's
gastric juice, you'll be dissolved.
Oh, you're alive!
Cut the crap!
If I didn't save you,
you would've been in trouble!
Drowned! Sunk! Dissolved!
And you would've been dead by now.
You should be thanking me,
and have a sense of obligation!
Alright. Thanks!
Thank you too, Elizabeth!
If you thank me without protesting like that,
it makes me feel like I'm an evil-minded jerk
who expects something in return.
Olga!
--Are we in the stomach?
--That's right.
There's even an island! It's so vast!
It must be one of the islands
Bonbori-sama swallowed.
Bonbori-sama has three
giant stomachs like this.
We're in the first stomach now.
If you go through the second stomach
and get to the third stomach,
you'll find the island of Alchemi
where the Pure Gold is.
We're in the stomach
but it's nice and bright here.
Yeah, thanks to Bonbori-sama's lamp.
Since its light is so strong,
it goes through its body
and even reaches inside the stomach.
So it's bright in here all the time.
You know quite a lot about it.
Oh no. If nothing is done, we'll be eaten.
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Well done, Straw Hat!
Finally, I get to... I get to...
Do you have something against them?
Finally, I get to... eat it!
Oh, I'm full!
My dream of 200 years finally came true.
200 years?!
For 200 years, I've only
been living on fish that
washed ashore and fruits on the island.
So it's been my dream
to eat as much meat as I want.
"For 200 years" means
you're like a very old grandma!
That's so rude!
If I'm a grandma, you're a grandpa!
You look a lot older than me.
I've only been alive for 19 years.
You're so much younger than me.
You've been living for 200
years but you don't look old.
That's amazing! Are you sure?
I am.
I was swallowed
by Bonbori-sama 200 years ago.
200 years ago,
I was living on the island of steel, Alchemi,
with my parents.
But since my crappy old man
who was a crappy scientist
created the Pure Gold,
everything went wrong.
Pirates who heard about the Pure Gold came
and killed my mother.
It's your fault, Dad!
If you didn't create the Pure Gold,
this never would have happened!
I'm gonna throw out this piece of junk!
And I was swallowed
along with the island, Alchemi.
What happened to your dad?
I guess he died when we were swallowed.
That served him right.
I'm the only survivor...
And for 200 years thereafter,
I've been living in this stomach all by myself.
I see.
You've been through a lot.
It wasn't so bad!
It's actually quite nice to live here.
But I managed to get out of
here by accident a while ago.
And when I was playing around outside,
I got caught by a group of freaks.
Then do you know how to get out of here?
I do.
If you wanna get out of here with
your friends and the Pure Gold,
you have to listen to me!
Okay!
I'm counting on you!
Well, leave it to me.
Olga, I was worried that you might've died!
Now, I want you to guide us to the Pure Gold!
It's been decided
that she'll go on an adventure with me.
I'm sorry but why don't you ask someone else?
All right but...
...the best part of treasure hunting is
robbing someone of theirs!
Gatling!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
That's what I expected of a man
with a bounty of 500 million.
You're a wonderful opponent
who makes my treasure hunt
so much more exciting.
But...
...you can't go any farther!
I'm sorry, Luffy!
We were captured when we fell
into water and became helpless.
Luffy...
Don't move!
Stop!
If they're so important to you,
don't move an inch!
Chain Lock!
--Luffy!
--Luffy-san!
You're not playing fair!
Don't get me wrong!
I'm not here for a head-on confrontation!
I'm here for treasure hunting!
I'll do whatever it takes
to get the treasure!
Now, Olga! Straw Hat drops out here!
Show me the way to the Pure Gold!
Otherwise, I'm gonna kill
everybody including you!
On one condition.
I want you to share
the Pure Gold half-and-half with me!
Half-and-half?! You're quite greedy!
I know how to get out of Bonbori-sama.
So even if we get the Pure Gold,
we still have to follow
your lead until we get out of here.
All right! I promise!
Olga! He'll kill you after you get out!
Just leave us and run!
It's your fault because
you can't go on an adventure
to the Pure Gold with me!
I hope your ship won't be dissolved
in the sea of gastric juice!
The Shark Emeralda is hardened
by steel and jewels.
So it's extremely sturdy!
And I have a favor to ask.
I don't want you to kill Straw Hat here.
You got along quite well with him.
It's nothing like that.
I'm just a kid so...
...I won't be able to sleep at night
out of fear if I see a dead body.
Olga...
That's really cute!
Even if it's a lie, I'll go along with it!
I have to make sure to keep you happy
until we get the Pure Gold!
The tide of gastric juice will
begin to come in to this beach soon.
So suffer and die a slow death.
Straw Hat!
You'll be dissolved here!
--Luffy!
--Damn!
Luffy!
Damn!
What?!
It's late!
I can't believe
it's running this late for feeding time!
I'm gonna be too hungry!
Hey! Let me out! You jerk!
Alright! Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
I was almost fed to them.
Oh, they look delicious.
I can't catch them like this.
I didn't expect to meet a human
in Bonbori-sama's stomach!
You!
Ouch!
What are you...?! Some kind of monster?!
How rude!
If you look carefully,
you can tell I'm a human right away!
I don't have to look
carefully to tell you're...
...a human, aren't you?
You don't look like a human, either.
This chain goes on top like this and...
It's quite complicated.
Okay, you're free!
Oh, thank you, old man!
No, I thank you.
It's really been a while since
I talked with another human.
You were swallowed
by Bonbori-sama too, weren't you?!
Yeah, it was 200 years ago.
I got swallowed along with
the island I was living on.
I somehow survived without being
dissolved by the gastric juice but...
...there are so many dinosaurs here
for some reason.
I couldn't escape, either.
So I survived pretending
that I'm one of them.
It was like - meat, meat, meat
and I couldn't have enough vegetables.
How picky can you get?!
What's wrong with meat?!
There was somebody here who's been eating
only vegetables and fruits for 200 years!
Is there somebody else in here
other than me and you?!
Yeah, there's a funny girl named Olga!
Olga?!
Olga is my daughter.
I can't believe she's alive.
I couldn't be happier.
Oh yeah!
Where is she now?!
She's been captured
by a guy named Mad Treasure.
I'm gonna go save Olga and my friends!
Goodbye, old man!
Thank you for unchaining me!
Take me with you!
I have to save my daughter!
All right.
Let's go together!
I'm Luffy!
We gotta build a ship!
A ship that won't be dissolved
in the sea of gastric juice!
Could you wait here for a while?
I'll go look for materials.
Shouldn't we just ride on this?
Well, Water Lizards sure have an
ability to go across the
sea of gastric juice but...
Please! Let us ride on you!
Alright, let me ask him.
I see.
If you can make him laugh
in a staring contest,
he'll become friends with you, he said.
That's amazing!
Do you understand what he says?
Yeah, I've been pretending to
be a dinosaur for two centuries.
Okay, got it!
Gum-Gum...
Damn! He's strong!
Luffy-kun, trying to make
your opponent laugh by force
is what second-raters do.
The important thing in comedy is... contrast!
Like the gap between my beautiful smug face
and over-the-top funny face!
This equation for comedy is
perfect and excellent!
First, my beautiful face...
Smug face!
You're funny!
What's wrong?
Nothing. It worked out so that's all right.
I'm counting on you, Chavez!
This is too much for my bones...
I wonder if Luffy's okay.
Yeah, I'm worried
about Zoro, Sanji, and Franky too.
You two are lucky.
All you gotta do is beat the drum.
Won't the Sunny be dissolved
by Bonbori-sama's
gastric water and disappear?
--Don't say such an ominous thing.
--Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't worry. Whatever happens,
they're not gonna die.
It's gonna be alright!
You're right.
You slaves!
Stop talking and keep rowing.
Mad Treasure.
Oh, you're...
...the Cat Burglar from back then.
Do you want me to torment you again?
I have friends this time!
I'm not gonna be defeated by a guy like you!
You have friends?
It doesn't matter.
You shouldn't trust your friends anyway.
Nami, did you have something to do with him?
Yes, a little bit, a long time ago.
I once stole his treasure.
When I got to his safe,
somebody else was already there, stealing.
She was one of my chief competitors.
We slipped up
and both of us got caught by Mad Treasure.
Then...
...she just used me as a decoy
and never came back.
Because of her, I was almost killed.
So I was right. I shouldn't trust others.
I should just take advantage of them.
That's not true.
Friends aren't the people you betray.
They're the people you trust.
I'm sure Luffy and the
others will come save us.
It's the second stomach from here.
The color of the water looks dangerous!
What's wrong, Chavez?
Oh no! His legs are starting to be dissolved!
Let's let him rest on an island!
The Sunny!
Sunny! I'm glad to see you!
Is that your ship?
Yes, it's the Thousand Sunny!
Who are you boys?
Oh! Zoro! Sanji! Franky!
Aren't they your friends?!
I kill you.
I'll dish you up!
I'll take your life!
There must be something wrong with you guys.
Chest!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
What happened to you guys?!
Why are there so many of you?!
Luffy-kun, don't you think they're fake?
Are they?!
My throw ups
You noticed they were fake!
I pay you a lot of respect!
But I need you to finish
yourselves off right here!
Copy Paint!
Wow! There are a bunch of Zoros!
But their bodies haven't changed...
I'm not scared of the funny Zoros!
Next is this!
Which one is the real old man?!
Damn! It's annoying
so I'll just beat the crap out of you all!
Don't! If you hit me,
I'm pretty sure that I'm gonna die!
--He's right! He's right!
--This is really annoying!
Oh yeah! Old man,
make the face you made earlier.
You mean the smug face?
All right...
Look!
This will prove that I'm the real one!
Smug face!
You really are funny!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
He's extremely strong.
Old man, that face is really hilarious!
I'm kind of hurt but it worked
out so that's all right.
Camoufla-paint!
Paying respect to your strong power
I spare your life for now
and I'm fading out...
What's with that guy?
Old man, we gotta go too!
Finally, it's the third stomach!
That's the island where I was born
and where the Pure Gold is hidden, Alchemi!
The Pure Gold is in a laboratory
deep in this abandoned mine.
There's some writing.
Nico Robin, you're an
archaeologist, aren't you?
Read it for us!
All right.
"Those who invade this land
seeking glimmering gold..."
"...must pay the price with death."
Death... With death?!
"My name is Myskina Acier."
Acier?!
Do you know who that is?
Yes, I know him too well.
He's my crappy old man
who created the Pure Gold!
What the...?!
B-Boss...
We're all dead.
He's dead!
Those who went first must've
been caught in a trap.
I'm starting to smell the
sweet scent of danger!
I-I'm already dead.
So if it's just some simple traps,
I-I'm not gonna die because I'm dead.
Looks like there's a trap in this room.
Peacock Organ...
"Only those who can play the right notes"
"and those who have a pure mind
can approach the bright gold."
What does that mean?
I think...
...if you can play the organ exactly
as it's written in the
score there, you survive.
But if you fail,
a rain of arrows comes down.
Really?!
You can count on me for
playing an instrument.
I'm a musician.
That's perfect!
But don't even make a single mistake!
It'll mean death...
...for you and...
...your friends!
I'm aware of that, of course!
I'll even risk my life for my friends!
Although I already don't have life!
We're counting on you, Brook!
This is a beautiful lullaby.
This song is....
A gentle smile and a dignified smile
Your adorable smile
Silver hearts and gold hearts
I'll give them all to you
--What's the matter?!
--He stopped playing!
I may not look it but I'm a musician!
Even if the score isn't perfect,
I'll try to see what the writer wanted,
and play it right!
This is how the next part should be!
What is it?
Cien Fleurs!
Robin-san!
Continue playing, okay?
Yes! This time...
All right!
Play the right notes this time!
We'll take care of the arrows!
Okay! I'll leave them in your hands!
Mil Fleurs:
Gigantesco Mano!
Chopper and Robin's Vortex!
I can't believe it! He's...
He's trusting his friends and
not running from such a terrible situation!
I can't figure out the next part!
I'm still pretty unskilled.
I'm not really getting what the writer
wanted to express with this song!
If it keeps on like this,
Robin-san and Chopper-san would get hurt!
I want... I want some kind of a clue!
Follow my singing!
Olga! It's dangerous there! Come back!
A gentle smile and a dignified smile
Your adorable smile
Silver hearts and gold hearts
I'll give them all to you
Alchemi, Alchema
Hold the gold star
Go into a dream
How's that?
Seems like you played it right.
The door to the next room has opened.
Don't drop dead just yet.
I'd be in trouble
if my handy "tools" get broken.
Olga-san, thanks to you,
I felt what the writer was feeling
and it touched me to the bones!
The song is filled with a parent's love
for his or her child.
How could you sing it?
That's because my mom used to
sing it for me when I was little.
You were loved so much!
That's not true!
But that crappy old man...
why did he bother using my favorite song?
My boss! We have a problem!
What's wrong?
You killed all of Straw
Hat's friends, didn't you?
Straw Hat Luffy is alive!
He's so tenacious!
You guys, stand guard at the entrance.
Don't let anybody in!
--Luffy's okay as we thought!
--Yeah!
It's gonna be okay
if we can hold up until he comes!
Old man, how much longer will it take?
Okay, it's done.
According to my calculation,
Chavez's legs will be
okay like this till we get to Alchemi.
Hey, do you need help?
Cut the crap!
You actually can't carry
it any longer, can you?
Who do you think you're talking to,
you spiral-eyebrowed Dirty Water Imp?!
Oh? Aren't they your friends?
Maybe they're fake again!
I gotta hit them to see if they're real!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
--Gum-Gum?
--Is that Luffy?
You posers!
Hey, Luffy! It's me! Me!
Are you the real one?!
No, you could be just a strong poser!
No-Sword Style: Dragon Twister!
Here's the proof that I'm the real one!
They're the real Zoro and Sanji!
--We are!
--Don't give us trouble!
Old man, they're my friends!
So they're as strong as Luffy-kun.
I feel like I'm in good hands.
Right?
Yo, Luffy! You're okay as I thought!
Franky!
Where are the others?
Are they having lunch or something somewhere?
Nami and the others are...
They're all being held by the chain guy
and were taken somewhere!
--What?!
--Seriously?!
I grasp the situation!
I'll alter the Sunny to be
able to cross the sea of acid!
But it'll take a while to beef
up the Sunny to prevent it
from being dissolved.
So give me some time.
No, I can't wait!
When I think of the things that
they could be doing to
Nami-san and Robin-chan at this moment,
I feel like I'm going insane with rage!
Does he fly?!
Sky Walk!
Nami-san, Robin-chan! I'm on my way!
We're gonna go now too!
I'll catch up with you later
after I beef up the Sunny!
--I'll leave it to you!
--So, where is the chain guy now?
He's probably at Alchemi
where the Pure Gold is!
Okay, let's go!
Old man, guide us!
"The Eagle Bridge."
"Those worthy of the bright gold..."
"...must have both excellent power
of concentration and bold courage."
"Hit the saintly eagle and build the bridge."
Will the bridge come down
if we hit the target?
The road cuts off here
so we have no choice, I guess.
It's your turn.
Arm Point!
Hoofprint Roseo!
Usopp!
Hey, I'm gonna shoot at
the target so unchain me!
If you get scared and come back,
I'll kill the hostage.
It'll be a pain if he brings
that dinosaur with him.
I know!
Usopp! Now's your chance!
It's not too far.
And there's no wind in the stomach.
I'll hit right in the middle!
Green Star: Explosive Skull Grass!
What's the matter?!
There's a rapidly rising current
from the gastric juice below!
It gusts up randomly with varying strength.
I can't measure the trajectory like this!
What's that?!
Usopp! Watch out! It's coming at you!
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
No, no...
Hoofprint Roseo!
I'll stall this one so hurry
up and hit the target!
That's easy for him to say.
There's a random updraft
blowing up from the gastric juice!
How can I predict it?!
Oh yeah! If I can generate a current
that counters the updraft...
I can measure the trajectory!
Green star: Explosive Skull Grass!
Now!
He did it!
Good job!
You guys are very useful "tools"!
Are you okay?
Whoa-whoa, it's too early to be broken down.
I need you to work for me a little bit more.
So this is Alchemi.
Being dissolved by the gastric
juice, it changed a lot
but I'm sure the mineshaft hasn't changed.
The Pure Gold is in there...
So are the kidnapped
Nami-san and the others...
Let's go!
This is where you guys are gonna die!
The end!
It's an ambush!
Shoot!
Luffy, go ahead! We'll keep them busy!
Okay!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Old man, lead the way!
What's that?
"The Final Gate."
"Those worthy of the bright gold are
trusted by others."
"Unlock the key along with
your courageous friends."
"The treasure lies ahead."
This is the last one.
What should we do?
Seems like we need to unlock
the door deep in the
alligator's mouth with that key.
But there must be some kind of trap.
Guys, it's your last job. I need you to go.
I knew this'd happen!
Me too!
Nami, hurry up and unlock it!
Okay!
I don't have time to think this over.
What's the matter?!
If it's incorrect, the trap will get you!
Feels like it got heavier!
Hurry up, Nami!
Nami-san!
There are 17 keyholes left.
If I don't pick the right one...
Every time we miss, it gets heavier...
I'm gonna break!
This is exciting!
That's a cool trap!
1 out of 15!
1 out of 10!
1 out of 5!
Leave it to me!
There are two holes that
we haven't tried yet.
This is our last chance!
Left?!
Right?!
No, I'll take the one on the left!
We can't hold out any longer!
Are you okay, guys?!
Luffy!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
Boy! After all our pains and troubles...
He's done a reckless thing as usual!
You jerk!
What did you do to my friends?!
I just used them as tools.
Olga!
Are you...
...my old man?
Olga, you need to get away
from here with Luffy-kun and the others.
What's this place?
Where does it lead to?
I don't think we can climb back up
so we should just go forward.
This is...!
The Pure Gold!
So this is the treasure!
I can buy the whole world with this!
Why is such a valuable thing here?
What is this place?
It's my crappy old man's lab.
But I can't believe he's alive...
He said he was having a hard time
after being caught by a dinosaur.
Does that mean he was
in Bonbori-sama's stomach?
Yeah. He cried when I
told him you were alive.
What?
This is...
What is it?
It's Acier-san's research journal.
"I decided to make the forbidden Pure Gold."
"I know that it's wrong as a scientist."
"But in order to save my daughter
from a fatal disease,"
"I'd even sell my soul to the devil."
A fatal disease?
"I found out the light of the
Pure Gold has the effect of..."
"...suppressing the growth of living things
to an extreme extent."
"I should be able to stop the
progression of my daughter's disease
by letting her absorb the light."
Don't ever take this ring off, okay?
So he put the piece of the
Pure Gold in that ring
to stop the progression of your disease.
No...
That's why you haven't changed for 200 years.
What?! Are you 200 years old?!
A grandma?
When my mother died,
my crappy old man was suffering too, I guess.
Despite that, I...
Even though he made the Pure Gold
to save me...
I'm a big fool!
For 200 years, I've been holding a grudge
against my father who saved my life!
You're Myskina Acier, aren't you?
How dare you do that!
I couldn't help my daughter
in any way for two centuries.
I finally got my chance to protect her.
Even if I'm a worthless man,
I'm glad that I'm alive.
I thought something like this
might happen so I set explosives
to protect my research!
Olga.
I love you.
Everybody, run!
My crappy old man must've pushed
the self-destruct button!
I'll protect Olga!
You bastard!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Ow, ow, ow...
The Pure Gold?!
There it is!
Is this the treasure you tried to protect
at the cost of your own life?!
Old man!
The Pure Gold can extend a human life!
It's the treasure that the damn
Celestial Dragons drool over!
Now I, Mad Treasure, got it!
I'm sorry, Luffy-kun.
By my calculation, I was gonna be
buried under the rocks along with him!
You can't just die by your own choosing!
I've been holding a grudge
against you for 200 years!
So I'll be in trouble if you don't make it
until I get my revenge on you!
You created the Pure Gold
in order to extend my life, didn't you?
I didn't know that
because you didn't make it clear to me!
Crappy old man...
Dad!
Olga.
I'm sorry.
What's so funny?
What did you say?
There's no point in getting a treasure...
...if you cast off your friends!
Why are you getting mad, Straw Hat?
You can get as many friends
as you want with money and
power, don't you think?
You can just dominate your friends
by taking advantage of their greed and fear.
Your friends are very handy.
After I kill you,
I'm gonna reuse them!
This is...
--What the...
--What's going on?!
Bonbori-sama is reacting
to the light of the Pure Gold!
I'll use the power of the Pure Gold
and hunt treasures forever!
How boring!
Your treasure hunting is...
...so boring!
Luffy!
You can't have my friends!
Quit it with that dull crap!
Three-Sword Style:
Dragon Twister!
Hey, what's up?!
Mad Chain!
Gear 2!
Hey! Is he gonna be okay?!
Luffy's not gonna be dissolved, is he?!
We're in danger too!
The gastric juice keeps swelling!
If nothing is done,
we'll be dissolved along with the island!
He's here!
Iron Pirate...
...General Franky!
It's a robot!
I'm here to save you!
I parked the beefed-up Sunny nearby!
Now,
come on board!
How can you attack me when I'm camouflaged?!
I've been strategizing about the
power of invisibility for a long time
so I totally know how those abilities work.
Eye, ear, nose, tongue, body.
Mind.
Those six sense organs have senses of...
...good, bad, and neutral!
Then, each of those 18
senses are classified into
the purified and defiled states!
One life, 36 desires!
That's enough playing,
drunken lady!
One-Sword Style:
36-Pound Phoenix!
Sober-up Stimulus Strike!
No!
How could you be that surprised?
Flying slash attacks aren't so rare nowadays.
I'm thankful to you.
Thankful?
I couldn't eat the Clear-Clear Fruit
which allows its user to become invisible
so I buried one of my dreams.
But your ability to camouflage...
...opens up new possibilities for me!
What are you talking about?
A man can't help peeking in women's baths...
I mean,
we can't help having dreams!
Have you ever had a dream?!
I...
I don't dream!
Don't lie!
If there is any possibility,
people can't help trying it!
Blaze up! A boyhood dream!
Remember-My-Dream!
Women's baths...
I mean,
don't give up your dream!
Luffy!
It's no fun!
It's no fun to get a treasure
when you sacrifice your friends!
It's meaningless to go on an adventure
without your friends!
Friends are perfect...
...when you can use and then discard them.
I don't care if it's fun or not!
This is the way I live!
Mad Chain!
Gigantea!
Straw Hat!
I thought you went out to sea
because you wanted to get the One Piece!
It doesn't matter
if you sacrifice your friends.
The one who gets a treasure
any way he can is the winner!
I'm not like you.
I'll never cast off my friends.
I'll cherish both my dream and my friends!
What?!
Isn't that too greedy?!
Gear 3:
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
It surprisingly took a lot of trouble
to bring them down.
Alright, let's get out.
Okay!
My boss!
Your life is more important
than the treasure!
All treasures in the world are mine!
Here we go!
The gastric juice is backing up!
Isn't it a little too fast?!
I think Bonbori-sama's having dry heaves
from the impact that Luffy-kun caused!
So the way to get out that you
were talking about was to make it puke.
Yes, that's how I got out.
But you caused too much impact!
Oh, the uvula! I missed it so much!
There's the exit!
Make it out in one burst
so that we won't be caught up in the puke!
You can count on me!
Coup de Burst!
We got out successfully!
Yes! We did!
We're back alive!
I've always been dead though!
You should be happy
that your bones weren't dissolved!
Don't tell me that light is...
Yes, that's a giant Pure Gold.
What?!
Bonbori-sama really likes to eat Pure Gold.
And all the Pure Gold that has been digested
in its stomach build up in the lamp.
"Those who get the Pure Gold will
meet with disaster."
The "disaster" actually is
Bonbori-sama's appetite.
Bonbori-sama is swimming away.
It'll never appear in front
of us without the Pure Gold.
And I'll never create Pure Gold again.
We'll never see Alchemi again.
Luffy-kun, everybody.
Thank you very much for everything!
Thank you.
When we were swallowed by Bonbori-sama,
she lost her Pure Gold ring.
Will she be okay with the disease?
That's okay! It'd be so much better...
...to stay out here and die
than to go back in there!
Olga.
What's the name of the disease do you have?
The South Blue Emperor Fever.
It's incurable.
What?!
That disease has a specific cure already!
What?
It's not incurable now!
Are you sure?!
It was worth living for
200 years, wasn't it?!
If you get this shot, you'll be okay!
I...
I don't like those!
Hey! No! Stop running!
Hey! You're gonna die without it, you know?!
Hey, wait!
That's great.
Both creating the Pure Gold
and the last two centuries were...
...worthwhile, I guess.
Give me your arm!
I really don't like to get shots!
They're gone now.
I actually feel better without those fools!
Now, what are we gonna do?
We can do whatever we want.
I've done everything by myself
for two centuries.
It's gonna be okay.
I can do anything too
as long as I'm with my beloved daughter.
I may be your daughter
but I'm a 206-year-old woman!
In the end, we couldn't get anything.
No, we got something!
I found something good!
What's that?
It's an invitation to Grantesoro!
A Vivre Card is attached!
What's Grantesoro?!
It's the world's largest entertainment city!
There are casinos and luxurious hotels.
It's a dream city where celebrities
from all over the world gather!
Gambling, huh?
I bet they have good restaurants.
And high-end hotels.
I wonder if they have rock shows
or something like that.
Maybe, they have an amusement park!
We gotta go there, Luffy!
Sounds like fun!
Let's go, then!
Destination: Grantesoro!
"Legendary Alchemi Research Lab"
Yes, I'll never forget at any time
If I get to see you again
I'll never lose my way and
do as my heart tells me
I said it to myself over and over again
"Legendary Alchemi Weight-Loss Method"
Even if we're far apart
Even if we're pushed back by headwinds
You just keep looking ahead without turning back
Those eyes that never lose their color are
miracle diamonds that started sparkling in your heart
My excitement is going out of control and getting entwined
I'll never shed tears even when I grow up
The future you're imagining is just around the corner
Don't look back if that's our destiny
Mad Treasure couldn't get the Pure Gold.
The Pure Gold vanished into the sea.
Should we search for it?
No, leave it as it is...
...to maintain the balance of the world.
Yes, sir.
Anyway, was it that man who was manipulating
Mad Treasure behind the scenes?
Yes, I think it was...
...Tesoro.
Guild Tesoro.
What an annoying guy.
Mad Treasure has been taken down by someone
and he couldn't get the Pure Gold, I heard.
I see.
I can't believe that formidable Mad Treasure
has been brought down.
I'm really surprised.
Now that's entertainment!
Who did it?
Oh, I'm afraid I don't know.
Well, forget it.
We can just hire somebody else.
We have so many ways to enjoy ourselves
with the excess amount of gold I have!