It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement—there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail—let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag—together, we're one
One Piece
Long Ring Long Land's
Great Adventure!
How's our bearing look, Nami-san?
Perfect!
That's our Nami-san for ya!
The holes are just about patched up.
Boy, am I glad I had the foresight
to take a bunch of scrap
lumber back at that dock!
You're great, Usopp!
We should be okay for a little while now.
It went out!
Out of fuel?
Hey, Usopp! We're about
to make a splashdown!
Hurry, Chopper! Bring all those boards up!
R-Right!
You can do it, octopus balloon!
You idiot! Just hit the deck!
Hurry! Hurry!
J-Just in the nick of time!
There, you should be all better now.
That's twice you've helped us out now!
Thanks!
Take care!
I hope you make some
good friends in the Blue Sea!
Go give all those Grand Line
octopuses a throttling!
So long, seafood ingredient!
Thanks for everything!
Be careful on your way!
Okay, then...!
Set the sails, men! Let's go to the next island!
Whoa, hold on, Luffy!
--Let us rest a little!
--Don't forget where we are!
Anyone could sail these seas
if it was okay to be so carefree!
What are you getting at?
The waves have been looking a little strange.
Hop to it, everyone! Turn to port!
Right, Nami-san!
Oh, here it comes!
Full speed ahead!
--This isn't good!
--There's stuff in the wave, too!
Huh? Those are Sea Monkeys!
What's all the ruckus here?!
Run!
Quit pushing! W-We gotta stay away from 'em!
They're having a falling out?!
--Bellamy!
--Sarquiss!
Please! Make him stop!
Please! Stop! Why are you doing this...?!
--What's happening?!
--Sarquiss is in pain!
Why? Why, you ask?
Sarquiss... Bellamy...
It's because you've tarnished
this symbol of mine, of course.
"Does the sky island exist or not?"
"Is the city of gold real or not?"
I don't give a care about any of that.
You're to twist people around by
taking advantage of differing opinions.
That's what I told you...
...wasn't it, Bellamy?
That's... Donquixote Doflamingo!
He's one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
He used to have a bounty over 300 million!
What's a guy like him doing here?!
I don't need useless punks
like you serving under me...
Crap! My body's moving on its own!
Stop! Please, don't...!
No!
Bellamy!
G-Give me...
Give me one more chance...!
I-- we-- will follow you loyally!
--Bellamy!
--No more, Bellamy!
Yes, I lost, but I never went
against your principles!
I swear on your symbol!
This is just my way of doing things!
We couldn't just run 'im off;
he would've reached you someday!
How very touching,
obedient subordinate of mine.
That's what I like about you, Bellamy.
A "New Era" is just around
the corner. Do as you wish.
But... I don't need you anymore.
Doflamingo!
He took out the notorious Bellamy--
a rookie worth 55 million--
like he was a baby!
It's finally beginning!
You'd better get ready!
A world where only true pirates
can survive is drawing near!
Those of you who are powerless--
run for your lives!
Soon, the tide of the times will wash over all
and a new era of champions will be upon us!
Things've sure calmed down...
Can't lower our guard yet, though.
Emergency report! Emergency report!
Ship spotted at 12 o'clock!
--Huh? Are they bad guys?!
--This is the worst possible time!
Actually, there's no flag or sails!
I don't know what kind of ship it is!
Seriously, nothing at all?!
What are they on the sea for, then?!
Heck if I know!
The crew seems unusually small, too...
Plus...!
They're looking really timid!
Almost like they're lifeless!
Sea Monkeys! Run!
--Again?!
--They followed us?!
--Crap! There's no wind!
--Hurry! Furl the sails!
Row! Row!
What the...?! Is that ship gonna be all right?!
The wave's gonna swallow 'em!
Hey! You guys!
A giant wave and monkeys are coming! Turn!
--Oh!
--Whoa! A ship!
A pirate ship!
Men! Get up! An enemy ship!
Let's swipe their treasure!
Wait! A giant wave's coming!
We gotta escape first!
--We can't let that ship get away!
--Ready the cannons!
Who made you boss?! You do it!
Turn! Someone turn!
What an unorganized ship...
Forget 'em. They're not on our side.
They wanna steal our treasure.
--Which way do we turn?!
--How should I know?!
--Someone, give orders! Navigator!
--Don't got one!
--Captain!
Who just fired that?!
Grrr!
--It's no use! It's gonna swallow us!
--Damn! You're all incompetent!
--You're one to talk!
--We can't handle a single wave?!
Man, it's one thing after another...!
It's finally calmed down.
Those waves were actually
the Sea Monkeys' doing.
The humidity and temperature
are pretty stable now,
so we must already be in
the next island's climate zone!
Hey, Robin. See anything?
An island's been visible for a while.
Why couldn't you say so sooner?!
You're such a wet blanket!
Listen! Whenever you see an island, say this!
Go ahead!
Men! I see an island! Yahoo!
Now you say it!
--The fog is rather thick.
--You're ignoring me again?!
Fog? We gotta be careful.
--Chopper! Keep forward watch!
--Right!
Hey! Do you know how much we've
been waiting to see an island?!
I'm sorry. I'll be more mindful.
Really? In that case, okay.
Hey, is anyone else curious
about that ship from earlier?
They said they had no captain or navigator,
and they didn't even have flags,
sails, motivation, or organization...
What kind of pirates
would go around like that?!
Probably got into a battle and lost.
And their captain died
and they got plundered...
No, that can't be it!
I got a good look at their ship!
There weren't any signs of a battle at all!
Yet the ship was completely bare of
all the essentials that pirates need!
So they weren't pirates, then.
Don't worry about it.
But they sure seemed like pirates to me...
I somehow get a bad feeling about this...
You always do.
Okay! I wonder if there's a town!
I hope they have a shipyard!
Luffy! Don't go jumping off right away!
I hope we'll get a good shipwright to join us!
We're near the shore! Get the anchor ready!
C'mon, guys... Listen to me...
Chopper! Usopp's got the
"Can't Go On the Island" disease!
There's no cure for that.
All right! All right!
What the...?
There's nothing at all!
What is this place?! So cool!
It's all grass as far as I can see!
Man, what a dull place.
Do you suppose anyone lives here?
--Yahoo!
--Hey!
Me too!
Sheesh. They barge right into
uncharted territory like it's nothing...
With a view like this,
it's clear there's no danger.
What is it, Chopper--?
A human?
No human's this fluffy and shaggy!
It's a bear!
Whoa! So long! A long bear!
So high up!
Hey! This is an apple! It's so long!
--Don't eat it!
--Yum!
All the other trees are crazy tall too!
Hey, look! Is that a house?!
Yeah, it looks like it.
Let's check it out!
It's your relative!
That's a deer! I'm a reindeer!
Shake!
--Watch this, Chopper!
--Oh!
Wow! You're awesome, Usopp!
Sit!
Beg!
So long!
I-I can't even see its head!
Where'd they run off to?
They were rolling around just a minute ago...
We should disembark too.
There could be food here.
Hey! Robin-chan! We're getting off the ship!
Right!
Man, talk about long...
Why is everything here so loong?
I feel like just looking at them's
gonna make me looong too...
Just what kind of island is this?
Hi! We're coming in!
Just like that?!
H-Hold on, Luffy! I bet this is
where the boss of the island lives!
He's gonna be some horrifyingly long
snake-man monster! I just know it!
No one's here.
Hey! Luffy! Usopp! I found a giraffe!
What?!
That ain't a giraffe...
It's got a long neck,
but it's a horse. A long-horse...
You're a horse?
What a pretty horse!
She's a girl! She says her name is Shelly!
This saddle must mean
someone's here after all...
What's up, Luffy?
Usopp.
--See those two bamboo trees?
--Yeah.
Whoa! I can't see their tops! Talk about long!
Take a closer look...
Okay...
They're running away!
Wha...?! This must be another long animal!
The bamboo tree's attacking Luffy!
H-Hey! You all right?!
I can't let you beat me, bamboo!
Careful, Luffy!
Gum-Gum Whip!
All right! You beat it!
Yeah! I cut it!
Where's your owner?
You don't know? That sounds lonely...
It could be bad guys! Stay there and hide!
What's going on?!
Actually...
...I cut a bamboo tree and a spirit appeared!
Our ship's... been blocked from leaving?
What are they planning?!
That's the ship I saw earlier...
Who are you guys?!
If it's a fight you want, get down here!
We are the Foxy Pirates!
Don't be hasty! All we want... is a showdown!
A spirit?
Yeah. He appeared after I cut the bamboo tree.
Hey. Say something, you.
Of course I remember you.
It's been a long time. How are you guys?
One of you knows him?
--Nope.
--Me neither...
Ah, no wonder I didn't recognize you.
Whoa, what a flake! Who are you, old guy?!
My name is Tonjit. You have my thanks.
I assume you're the ones
who knocked me off my stilts?
Stilts?
Oh! They are!
But they were so long,
we couldn't see the top at all!
Indeed. I was at the very top!
Oh, so you're not a spirit that came
out because I cut a bamboo tree,
you're an old guy who fell
'cause his stilts broke?
Why were you on such long stilts anyway?
I've always been fond of stilts,
so I tried to make the world's longest
stilts using this island's bamboo!
I managed to get on them, but then
I was too scared to come back down!
You're crazy, old guy!
I was up there... for ten years!
You're really crazy!
You were on stilts for ten whole years?!
That's right. The bamboo continued
to grow the entire time, too,
making it even harder
for me to come back down...
So scary...
That's your only comment after ten years?!
There are many trees on this island
just as tall as the stilts, though.
I was able to survive on fruit I could find.
He talks about it so casually.
Especially being up there for so long...
Speaking of long...
Why is everything on this
island so long, old guy?
It might seem that way to an outsider,
but there is a reason.
As you can see, a giant,
grassy plain covers this island.
In short, everything here is long
due to a longing for excitement.
Whoa. He went and said it.
Over there, for example...
--...is a plaaatypus.
--You just said it longer!
That's a Daaachshund.
Oh? Are you that same dog?
You're still passing by?!
Be careful-- there are ferocious animals too.
See? That's a snow leooopard.
Don't let it bite you!
Leopard?!
Why is it only long sideways?!
There he is...
That's the captain.
We're setting off toward the distant orange horizon
Today's winds are blowing
across the morning sea
I can't sleep
The kind of passion I saw this very morning
cannot be stifled by anyone
Hope, frustration
and much more might come our way
but for now
we can just start from scratch
Some time ago, we had a dream
in which we followed our aspirations
so we'll raise our hands high
and embrace the shining sun in our hearts
We're going to make it to that place
My name is Foxy! I take whatever I want!
Not another weirdo!
I challenge you, Straw Hat!
--Stop talking crazy, Split-Head!
--"Split-Head"?!
Bring it on! I'll fight you all you want!
No, Luffy! Don't agree to his game!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Davy Back with the Foxy Pirates!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Davy Back
with the Foxy Pirates!