A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
What?! A cannonball will be shot
into the Square in ten minutes?!
That's right. The attack is scheduled at four thirty
Four thirty?!
We found you, Princess Vivi!
I wonder how far I'll be promoted if I kill you...
I'll go on ahead!
On ahead!
Ten more minutes...!
This is really the last chance!
The next ten minutes...
will decide... this country's fate...!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
We don't have the slightest
intention of giving way to you!
Don't get in my way! Treinta Fleurs:
Strangle!
Sergeant Major! This woman... is Nico Robin!
She's got a bounty and was talked
about worldwide 20 years ago!
My right hand dries out everything...
Ground Death!
That Looks Gator-ish!
Luffy, Run to the Royal Tomb!
That was close!
His right hand is a problem...
The lawn has turned into desert!
Where'd he go?
You made me waste my energy...
You missed...
Cro...co...
You...
...lose again...
Straw Hat Luffy... This is a good way to die...
Within six minutes or so, this yard will
be blown up along with the Square.
Sorry, but I'm in a hurry...
You just relax here and celebrate the
birth of a new king of the sand country.
Well...
I should get going, too...
He said it's in the mortuary
temple to the west of here...
Ahh! That was close! I thought I was a goner!
That bastard... He's gone now...
I saw him flying that way!
I won't let him get away! That gator!
West of the palace — The mortuary temple
(royal tomb)
So this is the royal tomb... where the
bodies of generations of kings sleep...
Where's the Poneglyph?
Hidden stairs!
The Poneglyph is deep underground.
Normally, people aren't even
aware of Poneglyphs' existence...
What's happening behind the scenes is deep.
Even if countries belong
to the World Government,
it doesn't mean their kings know everything.
You aren't to be blamed...
...since you probably didn't know
there was someone in this world
who can decipher them.
You can read Poneglyphs?
Yes... That's why Crocodile and I teamed up.
Because of that, he can't kill me.
It's likely that the Poneglyph in
this country tells where Pluton is.
Isn't that right?
I don't know...
Alabasta's royal family has been
obligated for generations to protect it.
That's all it is to us.
Protect?! Don't make me laugh!
What an impressive-looking place...
It's behind the doors in the back.
Indeed...
I won't... let you go...
How many times do you have to
come at me before you're satisfied?
Nico Robin...
I'll... capture you...
Croco...dile...
Looks like you were taken
down by that woman...
I never thought that you'd
follow me to this town... Navy...
Where's your boss?
Did that smoke bastard run away?
Losers can't speak about justice.
We're in that kind of sea.
Go back to your base and just devote
your time to talking about justice.
Crocodile!
You small fry...!
What the heck are you doing?!
What am I doing?!
I'm trying to put myself in Crocodile's shoes!
Like, if I were him, where would I shoot a cannon from...?
Forget it! Just look for the cannoneer!
We've got less than five minutes!
Five more minutes!
A million lives will be blown up in five minutes!
We gotta hurry...!
We gotta hurry up and find the cannoneer!
Chopper!
Can't you find the guy by using your nose?
I can't.
The smell of gunpowder is all over the town!
Then... listen.
Find the smell of "a cannoneer who may
be aiming at the center of the Square."
What kind of smell is that?
How should I know?! Try your best!
What?!
A cannonball that can blow up a 5 km diameter...
Wait. Then it must be big...
If it is to be shot from a cannon,
it won't travel very far...
Then it should be closer to the Square after all?!
Ahh! I don't have time to go around!
I'll take a shortcut!
How is it from the sky, Pell?!
I searched every corner of the rooftops
of the buildings near the Square,
but I saw no preparations for the cannon anywhere.
Then... it might be from
somewhere inside a building...
I'll search all of them!
Okay!
Straw Hat!
Where did... the gator go?
We've been warned that at 4:30 p.m.,
an explosion will happen
in the Palace Square where the
rebellion is going on right now!
Please stop it somehow!
A million lives are at stake!
Losers can't speak about justice.
We're in that kind of sea.
Go back to your base and just devote
your time to talking about justice.
Tell me! Where's the gator?!
He went in the direction of the mortuary temple.
That way?! Thanks!
What justice...
The hell with Navy Headquarters...
Oh? I can't move well...
This is strange... when I ate meat...
What's wrong...?
These are such small wounds...
I wonder if I'm a little tired...
Did it tell you what you wanted to know?
Hm...? Oh, I see... Hidden stairs...
Four... four more minutes...!
Aren't there any others?!
Is this all this country is hiding?
You're not satisfied? I kept my promise.
Yes...
Just as you'd expect from a national secret...
No matter how desperately you search,
it can't be found unless you know where it is.
So this is the Poneglyph, huh, Nico Robin?
That didn't take long...
It's strange, or how should I put it...
Were you able to decipher it?
Yes.
Good.
Now, read... the so-called Poneglyph...
Kahira conquered Alabasta...
in Sky Ephemeris Year 239.
In 260, Taymer ruled the Bitain Dynasty.
In 306, the Taff Cathedral was completed in Erumalu.
In 325, the hero Mamdin of Oltia...
Hey, hey... Wait! Wait!
Is that what we wanna know?!
Who cares about the history of this country?
Just tell me the location of the world's
most disastrous "military power"
that is sleeping in this country!
Where is the Pluton?!
It's not written here.
What?!
History is the only thing written here.
Is that true?!
Pluton... I didn't see that
word mentioned even once.
Well... I see... That's unfortunate...
You've been an excellent partner to me, but...
...I think I'll kill you here.
Wha...?!
The agreement that we made four
years ago has been achieved here.
This is what you said then.
If I take you to where the Poneglyph is,
you'd turn over the information
on the weapon to me...
Your work in Baroque Works
these past four years was excellent
both in terms of brainpower
and command ability.
That's enough for me... to say
that you were a useful woman.
But... you broke your word at the end!
The Poneglyph in this country doesn't
even show a clue on the Pluton.
Or... is it that you weren't
planning to tell me from the start,
even if you found out?
However...
I don't feel any anger against you...
You know why, Nico Robin?
How silly... We were a team for four years.
I knew you'd pull something like this.
Water?!
If you get wet, a knife can stick in you, right?!
He dodged it! Where'd he...
I'll forgive you for everything, Nico Robin...
...because I've never... trusted anyone...
from the beginning.
I now know from Cobra's reaction
that Pluton really exists.
I don't have to depend on the Poneglyph.
I'll find it on my own.
Once this country becomes mine,
it's just a matter of time.
Hm?! What's going on?!
It's still too early for the attack on the Square!
It must be you. What'd you do?!
Well... nothing major...
This underground sacred temple is built
so that pulling just one small column
out will cause the entire balance
to be disrupted and destroy the temple.
You two... will die here with me.
As the 12th king of the Nefertari Family,
I can't give this sand kingdom
to someone like you.
Where is it? Three minutes left...
A cannon big enough to
blow up a 5 km diameter...
There can't be many places
where such a thing would fit...
Why can't we find it when
we search this much...?
An open space where a big cannon can fit...
A stray bullet!
An open space...
Hey, no fair, Koza!
You were hiding in a place like this?!
Leader! No fair!
That's right... That place can...
That's dangerous, you bastard! Smoke Star!
It doesn't attract people's
attention and it's a big space.
Idiot! Ahh! I'm not from the Rebel Army!
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp's Rubberband of Doom!
Did that teach you, you bastard!
Geez... who do they think I am?
Don't be surprised when I tell you this.
No, be surprised!
I am that famous Captain... U...
What? O-Oh, it's you, Vivi.
Did you find the cannoneer?!
I figured it out! It's gotta be there!
What?! Really?! Okay, then! I'll signal them!
In any case, I'll call everyone!
You're sure about it, right?
Yes!
Special Attack... Red Serpent Star!
Ahh?!
Oh?!
Boy, I slept well.
Huh...? Oh, that's right.
My body suddenly became incapable of moving...
...so I decided to risk it and take
a nap since it couldn't be helped.
And now I feel fine, so...
Oh, yeah!
Gator! I'll beat him up!
That hole...
It looks gator-ish...
Whoa... You're a model king...
Are you trying to be buried alive,
taking me with you...
...for the country...?!
But... you can't kill me...
Hm?
I can change all the bedrocks
into sand and escape from here.
You'll die in vain, Cobra.
It's now less than three minutes.
With the collapse of this sacred temple
and the big explosion of the Square,
everyone in my way will be blown up in an instant!
In that moment, this land...
will become my country.
Crocodile!! Where are you?!
Doko ni mukatte hashireba
Which direction should I run towards
Motto suteki na ashita ni aeru?
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
Kaji o totte mune ni shimatta
I took the helm and opened the
Kiseki no chizu o hirogeta
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
Sora o mezashite yume o sagashite
I aimed for the sky and sought out my dreams,
Michi ni mayotta toki mo aru
though at times I got lost
Yume ja nakute kimi to deatte
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
Suteki na jibun o mitsuketa
I discovered the wonderful person in me
Chiisana yuuki kara
With just a bit of courage,
ookina mono te ni shita
I gained something grand
"Negai" o ima koso "chikai" ni kaete
Now's the time for my "wish" to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Mirai no monogatari o egakou
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
Atarashii kaze ni subete no omoi nosete ima...
I'll put all my feelings in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
Doko made mo oikakete Shining ray
I'll chase after you wherever you go, Shining ray
I've cornered you, gator!
Straw Hat... Why are you alive?
Just how many times do you want to be killed?
What? Is the cannoneer really in such a place?!
Yes! There's nowhere else I can think of!
Okay then! Everyone's headed here.
So we'll leave a message!
I'm gonna go on ahead!
What?! Hey, Vivi! Wait! Wait for me!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Nightmare Draws Near!
This is the Sand Sand Clan's Secret Base
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Nightmare Draws Near!
This is the Sand Sand
Clan's Secret Base