Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After forming an alliance-- with Trafalgar Law,
Luffy finally encountered Caesar Clown
aka the Master who rules the island. However...
You shouldn't underestimate me.
You're a Warlord-sama now, aren't you?
You've done so well.
When did you come here?
Vergo!
It's inevitable. This is Joker's important territory.
I can't just let those who learn about his identity walk away.
Hey, Tra-guy, who's Joker?
He is a member of the Seven Warlords authorized by the World Government.
He is Donquixote Doflamingo.
Protect the Children!
Master's Demonic Hand Approaches
Doflamingo...
Who is that?
Didn't you see him at the Navy Headquarters?
At the Navy Headquarters?
Oh yeah!
Hey, you, gator guy!
You turned me down and now, you wanna team up with Whitebeard?
It makes me jealous.
That bird guy!
You better not take him lightly.
He's right.
And they say that Doflamingo
attacked Moria after the Paramount War!
He attacked Moria?
Team Nami/Usopp
Ruins of the First and Second Research Institutes
Master!
So...
...you're the one who kidnapped these children?!
Why is he here?
Luffy and the others couldn't meet him?
How could you do such a horrible thing?
Horrible?
Why did you take them away? The children are suffering!
What?!
Hey, no! Don't, Nami!
You're making them suffer!
Whoa-whoa,
Law said he's a Logia-type Devil Fruit user with a 300-million-berry bounty!
What did you give to such small children?!
They said they want to go home!
I'm sure their parents are looking for them!
We will get them out of here at any cost!
Where are the children who wanna go home?
Master!
Hey!
--Master! --Hey, wait!
Don't go! Do you wanna go back to the institute?!
Get out of my way!
Usopp!
Candy...
What?
Master, give me the candy!
That's it. Come back to me, children.
Wait, you all!
You shouldn't go back to him!
Don't you wanna go home?!
Don't touch me!
Cockroach!
Go away, cockroach!
Nami!
--You alright?! --Y-Yeah.
You brat, don't push your luck!
No, Usopp!
Let go of me!
We have no choice but to stop them by force!
He must be hallucinating! He called you a "cockroach"!
But...
They're victims!
It's not their fault!
Unchain me!
It's painful!
But we have to do something before they beat us!
Focus that anger at...
...that jerk!
Take these off!
Unchain me!
--No way! --They broke the chains?!
Amazing!
You became so powerful!
That bastard!
Candy...
Master...
--Master... --Give me...
That gas bastard! I'll show him!
This should work against gas!
Special Attack!
Fire Bird Star!
Kids, move aside!
What?!
Did you think I would catch fire and explode?
You knew my powers are gas-based, didn't you?
But it's too bad. I put the fire out before it even touched me.
Poison gas is not the only kind of gas, you see.
The air all around us is gas, too!
Which means I can manipulate the air within a certain area.
--He can manipulate... --...The air?
If I remove the oxygen, fire can't burn.
And you people can't even breathe!
Master?
Like this!
Usopp!
Black Ball!
Storm Cloud...
Master...
C-Candy...
Candy...
Hurry...
Were you wondering if Straw Hat didn't meet me?
Well, he did.
Straw Hat and two others.
I made them suffocate!
Hey!
Candy!
--Master! Candy! --Candy... Candy... Candy...
--Candy! Candy! --Hurry!
--Master! --Candy!
Give me it! Give me it!
Children.
I'm only giving it to the good children who go back to the institute!
Good children only?
That's right!
Yes, yes! I'll be good!
Then just wait a little bit longer, can you?
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
Let's go back! Master!
Okay, okay! Well, before we do...
Kill these devils who took you away
and tried to worsen your pain!
Kill them...
Crush their skulls with that giant pipe!
Uh-huh...
Don't...
I can't think clearly...
Caesar!
--Browncolor?! --No, Brownbeard!
Straw Hats!
I came to my senses!
I don't remember this one.
Oh yes! You're my dutiful lackey - Brownbeard!
You bastard! Did you even forget who I was?!
Of course not!
What happened to you?
Your whole body is charred and you look terrible.
That's because you ordered them to kill me!
I remember now!
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
Your name is also on our kill list.
He was easy to manipulate because he was so dumb but he's a pain now.
I don't need him.--
Kill him.
The Cool Brothers, huh?
That's how you got charred.
I trusted you.
Don't be so angry.
You're still alive after getting attacked by the Cool Brothers.
You're very lucky!
Shut up!
Caesar!
Hey, children, it's dangerous here!
Get on board the Flying Gas Balloon outside.
Let's get away from here!
Wait, everybody! Don't go!
Caesar!
I don't care that you fooled me.
I don't care about myself anymore.
But I want my crew back!
I'm not gonna let them go through hell like I did!
Idiot! You don't have a crew anymore!
You and all of your crew became my subordinates!
Stop acting like a captain!
You're just a shitty pirate who got beaten in the New World!
Hey, Nami! Let's go after the kids!
Okay!
They will keep following me thinking I'm their savior!
They're too dumb to notice.
They don't know that I kept them alive because they're my guinea pigs!
You bastard!
Gastanet!
--Brownbeard! --What happened?!
Punk Hazard, Center Lake
They're so persistent!
How far is the institute?
The one that was on the other side made it completely to this side now!
Which means this one is the last piece of him, doesn't it?
It merged with a smaller one?
It's getting bigger and bigger!
Just keep running to the institute!
Wait for me!
Momonosuke!
--Open it! --Give us back Captain-chan!
Give us back Smo-yan!
Caesar Clown's Research Institute, Out-Front
It's starting to move!
They're all heading in the same direction.
Where are they going?
Caesar's Laboratory
I found out the formula of the drug and I found sedatives.
Now I have to find a way to rescue-- Luffy and the others.
Easy...--
Wh-Who was that?
Can I have the candy?
Where did the Master go?
Master...
Hey, Master!
Where are you?
This is Caesar. Are you there, Monet?
Yes.
I retrieved the children safely.
Is Smiley's food ready?
Everything you ordered me to do is prepared, Master.
The Navy soldiers are in front of the closed shutters.
And we can transfer the Straw Hats anytime.
The Video Transponder Snails are on standby outside.
So, when Smiley gets there,
we can start broadcasting the fun experiment?
Yes.
Great. Connect me to all the receivers.
Okay.
To all unlawful "brokers" wherever you are.
I'm sorry to contact you on such short notice
but you all are very lucky to see this!
What you're about to witness is the deployment of a poison gas weapon.
I added a new feature to the one from four years ago.
It's something those scum from the Government-- can only dream of creating.
Today, we have uninvited guests here on our island.
That's why I decided to perform the experiment.
Invasion, war, domination.--
It has various uses.
If it appeals to you,
let's talk business.
Give us back Captain-chan!
Are you interested in a weapon of mass destruction?
No.
But...
...I'd lose nothing by learning about it, right?
An agreement has been made between Law and Caesar.
As that secret comes to light...
...Zoro and gang, fleeing from Smiley, come upon a large object.
It is nothing less than an indication of the beginning of Caesar's fearsome plan!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Shock to the New World
Caesar's Horrendous Experiment"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Shock to the New World
Caesar's Horrendous Experiment