Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
When the Thousand Sunny
drifted into unknown waters,
the crew landed on Hungry-la Island,
an island brimming with strange foods,
to restock their exhausted food supplies.
There they met the Gourmet Hunter
Toriko and the chef Komatsu,
and they teamed up to capture
the legendary Hungry-la Bird.
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Fork!
Knife!
Thank you for this excellent meal.
And so, the time passed
on their lively feast...
Now this goes in...
Hey, could I get some more soup?
Just a moment, please.
Here we go...
What's that?
They're spice seeds.
When I put these in, the spices take
effect and change the soup's flavor.
The Strongest Tag-Team!
Luffy and Toriko's Hard Struggle!
Whew, I'm stuffed!
That Hungry-la Bird was delicious!
You're really not going to include this
Hungry-la Bird in your Full Course Meal?
Yeah, that's the thing...
What's wrong?
He says Komatsu and Nami are gone!
What left these tracks?
Something smells good.
It's the aroma of fine cocoa.
These tracks were definitely
left by Cocoalas.
Cocoalas?
I've never seen one myself,
but they're Capture Level 3.
Their meat doesn't taste good enough to eat,
but sweet cocoa beans of the highest
quality grow on their backs.
Something that fancy took
Nami-san and the chef?
No, they probably carried
them back to their nest.
Cocoalas are omnivorous.
They'll take anything and store it as food.
And they make their nests
in Multi-fruit Trees.
Multi-fruit?
A fruit that combines the
sweet and savory flavors
of wintermelons, watermelons,
apples, mangos, and other fruits.
It's also known as the
Fruit Parlor of the Earth!
I'd love to eat one!
You're more worried about
food than about your friend?!
So where can we find these things?
In order to grow the sweetest fruit,
Multi-fruit Trees are said to grow
where the sunlight is most abundant.
Found it!
So that's it?
There's no doubt. That's Multi-fruit!
Nami-san! I'm coming!
Just you wait, Multi-fruit!
I feel so sorry for Komatsu right now...
Luffy... What happened to our food?
Luffy...
Usopp...
You've aged a lot.
At this rate, you're gonna
end up all bones, like Brook.
Nice skull joke...
Still...
What's this vapor?
A geyser?
Yow!
Look out!
You don't know where they'll burst up from!
That's really hot!
But it's sweet! It's chocolate!
What?! Really?!
Quit making your eyes sparkle and just run!
While we're doing this, Nami-san is...
What's that?
A big one's coming!
Hot!
Crap! A river!
What's wrong?
People with Devil Fruit powers can't swim!
What?!
Huh? This isn't water.
Cream?
It's a river of whipped cream!
Tasty!
All right, not much longer now!
Once we're through this forest,
we'll be at the Multi-Fruit Tree.
What was that?!
I knew it. A Caste Leo.
Caste Leo?
Caste Leo (Mammal Beast) Capture Level 4
Capture Level 4.
Their manes are exquisite,
fluffy castella cake!
Growling in that super deep voice...
Is this supposed to be a joke?
We're going to where Nami and Komatsu are!
I won't let anyone get in our
way, no matter who it is!
Luffy!
What is that?
Sound shock waves!
His castella sponge cake emits sound.
It's like a giant speaker.
Isn't there any way to beat it?
Well, can you draw his
attacks straight ahead?
Right!
Okay, now!
Toriko!
His sound attack only works
directly in front of him!
We can get him from the sides!
Threefold
Nail Punch!
Amazing!
What was that?!
I drive multiple punches into one
spot, like hammering in nails.
It's my Nail Punch.
There were this many of them?
And they're huge.
These guys roam in prides.
Five Caste Leos and one small Caste Leo...
Looks like we're surrounded.
What?!
Spatula!
Such a beautiful way to make an entrance.
Sunny!
Poison Rifle!
Endorphin Smoke!
What now?!
It suddenly got quiet.
Hey, Toriko.
Coco! Rin!
Toriko! I'm so glad you're safe!
An angel has come down!
Wow! They're your friends, Toriko?
Well, yeah...
But what are you doing here?
We heard that you had set out
to capture a Hungry-la Bird,
so we came to tell you the
secret of Hungry-la Island...
Anyway! I can't believe you left
me behind! You're awful, Toriko!
It was so hard to find this island!
I'm so mad!
By the way...
Where's Komatsu-kun?
Actually, he was taken by Cocoalas.
What?!
Yeah! Our friend is with him, too!
That creature is unreal! It talked!
They've recovered, huh?
We don't have time to deal with these guys!
Quick! We've gotta go save Nami!
These guys are gonna be a pain, though.
Beautiful...
A heart that cares for its friends...
That is more beautiful than anything.
Toriko, leave this to us,
and go save Komatsu.
We'll be fine on our own!
You guys...
All of you, hurry!
Thanks!
I'm counting on you!
I'll get that Multi-fruit, no matter what!
Multi-fruit?
What about Komatsu-kun?
Does it seem like Toriko's goal
is different from everyone else's?
Well, in any case...
We will take you on!
What is it, Toriko?
Oh, I was just wondering why the Caste
Leos didn't attack the Cocoalas,
since their Capture Level is lower.
Huh?
To get to the top of the mountain,
the Cocoalas must have passed
through the Caste Leos' area.
Carrying Komatsu and your friend
would've slowed the Cocoalas down.
They should've been prime
prey for the Caste Leos.
And they were obviously hungry.
There must be some reason why
they didn't eat the Cocoalas.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Put me down, you monster koalas!
This is...
Multi-fruit!
It's my first time seeing them! I'm so moved!
Huh?!
I wonder what they taste like...
I wonder how they should be cooked
to bring out their flavors...
Forget about that!
Think about what's happening
to you right now!
That's Nami-san's voice!
Sanji!
Nami-san!
Koalas... Huh?
Luffy! Sanji-kun!
Toriko-san!
Nami!
That's...
A Knock-out Koala!
So he's their boss?
Knock-out Koala (Marsupial Beast) Capture Level 5
They say that when Cocoalas reach
adulthood, they become Knock-out Koalas,
but I've never heard of one getting that big.
Now I know why the Caste Leos
didn't attack the Cocoalas.
They were afraid of the Cocoalas'
boss, the Knock-out Koala!
So now he's shown his true colors.
Oh, boy... So if we don't beat these
guys, we can't save Nami-san anyway?
How are they so fast?!
So the Capture Level of Cocoalas
in battle mode exceeds 3, eh?
Hey, Toriko!
Luffy! Toriko!
Hey!
You guys can handle things here!
What?!
Got it!
Luffy, Toriko! Take care of Nami-san!
Right!
We'll save Nami!
What?!
Um, what about me?!
I won't let you get in
Luffy and Toriko's way!
Something's making a lot of noise.
There's no helping it.
Nothing's gonna happen if
we just wait around here.
Let's take the ship around to
the other side of the island.
I'm too hungry to move...
So this is what they call
"bones broken for nothing"...
And I'm nothing but bones...
Quit your whining! Unfurl the sails!
Luffy!
Toriko-san!
Luffy! You okay?
Yeah!
Damn that thing... It can't
really only be Level 5!
Not bad!
Hey, you! Give back Nami!
Yeah! Give me the Multi-fruit!
What?! You didn't come to save me?!
Luffy!
Toriko!
It's incredibly strong!
Okay, now it's my turn!
Gum-Gum—
Knife!
Using Nami and Komatsu to shield
yourself is playing dirty!
Toriko!
Nami! Komatsu!
That's a Multi-fruit Tree for you.
Huh?
It can support that Knock-out Koala's
intense movements without even budging.
What's more, the recoil gives
its attack power a huge boost!
Sounds like a pain.
But...
Those huge stems must be sending
tons of nutrients to the fruit.
Multi-fruit...
I swear I will eat you!
He's still talking about that?!
Yeah!
Luffy! You, too?!
What are you thinking?!
I give thanks...
...for all this world's bounty.
Now let's eat!
H-Hey!
Gum-Gum...
...Nail Punch!
Thank you for this excellent meal.
Now, I'll just help myself
to that Multi-fruit...
Huh?
What's going on? It's waving around.
Wh-What's happening?
You guys...
Hey, this is unreal!
Huh?
Everyone get down the mountain!
What?!
The island is about to show its true form.
Its true form?
I told you that we came to tell you
the secret of Hungry-la Island, right?
Yeah.
You okay?
It's sweet.
Yum! This is caramel!
What?
It's true!
What's going on?
The legend of Hungry-la
Island has been recorded
in many texts since ancient times.
Our predecessors have transcribed
those texts and handed
them down throughout history to the present.
That's why we relied on the legends
in those texts to find this island
and capture the phantom
ingredient, the Hungry-la Bird.
But it turns out the phantom ingredient
is not the Hungry-la Bird.
Huh?
You know, the characters for
"bird" and "island" look similar.
Hungry-la Bird
Hungry-la Island
Apparently, whoever transcribed
it read the name wrong.
Then, the phantom ingredient is...
Not the Hungry-la Bird,
but Hungry-la Island?!
No wonder the Hungry-la Bird
was such an easy opponent!
This island itself is the
legendary ingredient...
A natural pudding à la mode!
Amazing!
What the heck is this?!
I wonder if Luffy and the others are okay...
Delicious!
This luxurious sweetness achieved
by condensing a multitude of fruits!
So this is the Multi-fruit!
It is indeed the Fruit Parlor of the Earth!
Hey, Toriko, you think this whole
mountain is made of pudding?!
You're right! It's delicious!
Hey! I was gonna eat that part!
What's the problem?! There's plenty!
Oh, and apparently the next
mountain is all ice cream!
What?! You should've said so sooner!
Wow! This castella is tasty, too!
Isn't that the mane of
one of those Caste Leos?
What?!
So after you ate all that, you're not
using any of it in your Full Course Meal?
Well, it's a big world.
I'm sure there's still lots
more delicious food out there.
You really are a big eater!
We're stocked up on food now.
We can set sail anytime.
Okay!
Well, we're gonna get going.
Right. Let's meet again somewhere.
Next time, I'll treat you to
my life's Full Course Meal.
Sure! I look forward to it, Toriko!
See ya, Luffy!
Bye!
So long!
A cheerful goodbye is a nice thing, but...
Who the heck are they?
Okay, now that we've got food supplies,
we're leaving these waters!
That's all pudding!
No, no! Pudding is a very
variable good that tastes like
sea urchin if you put soy sauce on it...
If you want sea urchin, get it from the sea!
Well, Komatsu, ready to get going, too?
On our journey to find new ingredients!
Yes, Toriko-san!
His heart deeply wounded after losing Ace,
Luffy remembers his life ten years ago.
Ace, who wouldn't accept anyone,
and Luffy, who followed him everywhere.
The story of the strange bond
that led them to become brothers begins...
Next time, on One Piece:
"Luffy and Ace!
The Story of How the Brothers Met!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Luffy and Ace
The Story of How the Brothers Met!
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...