Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Straw Hat!
You wanna stop the Noah, don't you? Then you have to beat me.
Otherwise, you can't save Fishman Island!
Hody, what's with you?!
You even abandoned the ones you grew up with in the Fishman District!
Don't you realize what you are doing?!
Or is your hatred for humans so deep that makes you lose your mind?
What happened to you?
Did humans beat you?!
Did humans kill your loved ones or someone dear to you?!
What did you go through in the past?!
Answer me, Hody!
What did humans do to you?!
This is the Air Tank. We met you a while ago.
Oh, it's you guys.
We've been listening to what's been going on out there.
And we see the Noah falling towards the island.
We're getting ready as planned.
Enough with the difficult stuff and just do it!
Luffy-san, please save the island!
Hey, Straw Hat. Can you hear me?
Listen carefully.
About Hody Jones...
I found out who he really is!
That bastard!
"A Shocking Fact! The True Identity of Hody!"
Before the Noah started to fall...
Ouch!
Damn you!
Now I'm mad!
Just you wait and see!
Intimidation Mega Monk!
He was very big already!
Is that necessary?
How is this? Are you surprised?
I'm a tiger blowfish Fishman. Scared?
Not at all. Anyway, why are you talking so fast?
Because I'm gonna deflate if I don't.
The Kraken is bigger than you.
What?!
Then, how's this?!
Blowfish!
--So annoying! --I don't wanna get crushed!
--Help me! --Hey, Wadatsumi-san, no!
You're squashing the people on your side!
Still smaller than the Kraken.
What?! Then, how's this?!
That's enough!
Your Majesty!
Are you all right?!
I'm sorry that we couldn't protect you!
We are such useless vassals!
That is okay. More importantly, did you see the Noah?
Yes.
I can't believe it's moving.
Damn Decken! If the Noah had crashed into the Princess and the island,
everything would have been destroyed-jamon!
We didn't know what was going on. We tried to order an evacuation to all citizens
but I guess all the communications centers were seized by the New Fishman Pirates!
We have been trying to reach the border guards out at sea but...
Ring, ring, ring...
--Get ready to shoot the bubble now! --Hurry up!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Why aren't they picking up?
In any case, take the King somewhere safe!
No.
I'm going to wait for the Princes.
What the...
Tell me what is going on, guys!
Why are there so many pirates?!
Well...
The Straw Hats!
Jinbe!
Princess-sama?!
Hody! Decken!
So that is what happened...
All right! I understand everything now!
All soldiers! Go to the plaza!
Follow Jinbe and the Straw Hats!
If they can handle the strong ones for us, the rest are just average fighters.
The pirates who we mistrusted and falsely charged are fighting for our country.
We should be ashamed of ourselves.
The least we can do is offer them our support!
Yes, sir!
It's Neptune's army!
--We can handle them! --Kill them all!
It's time to show our strength!
He's a human!
Go slaves!
Fight for us if you don't wanna die!
Advance, "Slave Tank"!
Go that way!
Oops!
You are good for nothing! Just drag him!
How weak!
Somebody, take his place!
How terrible.
That is like...
Nico Robin.
Do you think you can free those human slaves?
Are you sure it's wise?
I'm sure they're holding a grudge against Fishman Island.
If those human pirates come against me, I will just beat them up.
But they can hardly be called "humans" now anyway.
I can't stand watching Hody and the others copying the Celestial Dragons.
All right! I'll do it!
Thanks.
Hey! You guys are too slow!
Dammit! Son of a bitch!
The cuffs came off!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Who uncuffed the slaves?!
You're a member of the Straw Hats, aren't you?
Hey, turn around already!
What's wrong, you slaves!
The cuffs...
--Did you do it? --Why did you save us?
I can't turn down a request from a handsome man.
You can thank Boss Jinbe for that.
Jinbe asked you to?
You can't just do that!
Trawl Net!
I got you!
Cuerpo Fleurs:
How did you get behind me?!
Wh-What the...
It won't take long. Relax.
Let go of me! Who are you?!
You! How are there two of you?!
Double Clutch!
--Hammond-san! --That bitch!
--Thank you, Sis! --You bastards really treated us like shit!
You guys can't beat us on earth!
The human slaves are...
...rising in revolt!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank!
This is one of the border guards. Is this the Minister of the Left?
Yes, I is. I have been trying to reach you - why didn't you pick up?
Forgive me! But I have no time to go into detail now!
Please warn the whole kingdom!
The giant ship, Noah, has just lost its power
and is starting to fall towards the island again!
What?!
The Noah is falling again?
Where are you now?
At the Air Tank control tower.
That's good. Then, you need to warn everybody about the crisis.
None of the communication centers on the island are working.
I know you can reach the state-operated Transponder Snails
all over the country from there!
Hurry up!
Yes, sir!
To all citizens of the kingdom-- from the Air Tank above the island.
An emergency evacuation order has been issued!
The giant ship - Noah is falling onto the island again!
Please leave the island immediately!
What?!
CORAL HILL
Look!
It's the shadow of the Noah!
WATERWHEEL TOWN
Decken did it?
That's what I heard.
That damn stalker! I can't believe he threw it!
The bubble's gonna break!
FISHVERLY HILLS
The island will be destroyed!
Hurry up! Forget about your suitcase!
B-But...
Get out to the sea!
Everybody, escape from the island!
CORAL APARTMENT
I heard Princess Shirahoshi was drawing the ship away from the island.
Yeah, we can't just run and leave her alone like that!
But the Noah is falling onto the island!
Well...
You wanna just stay here and have Princess-sama's effort wasted?!
--We've got to leave the island! --To the sea!
Hurry up, everyone!
No! That thing is gonna come back?!
Are we gonna be alright, Luffy?!
What happened to Princess Shirahoshi?
Decken, again?! That crazy pirate!
We have to run, too! It's too dangerous!
Leave Hody and the others up to us.
All you spectators leave here and get off of the island!
What are you doing? Hurry up!
No!
Wh-What?
Especially women and children. Go now!
No!
The Straw Hats are human pirates but they're fighting for the island!
We can't just run out on them!
He's right! We were the ones who asked them for help!
I can't do anything but I want to share their fate!
--Me too! --Me too, Minister of the Right!
Be quiet!
Listen, here is your duty!
You have to make sure to tell all the other spectators what I said!
Understood?
I'm sure everyone has their own reasoning and ideas.
If you want to stay here, suit yourself!
Bring it on, outlaws!
Straw Hat Luffy-san.
This is the Air Tank. We met you a while ago.
Straw Hat? What are they broadcasting?
We've been listening to what's been going on out there.
And we see the Noah falling towards the island.
Luffy-sama! What should I do about the Noah?
What are they doing?!
They are broadcasting their conversation across the country by mistake!
Hey, hello? How can we get air from you?
If we make a bubble and shoot all the air from the Air Tank,
maybe we can surround the Noah.
Shirahoshi! Straw Hat!
I'm afraid you'll have to take it from there!
Enough with the difficult stuff and just do it!
It's Luffy! I'm glad to hear him!
He sounds all right!
Well, I wasn't worrying much since it's Luffy!
What are they talking about? I heard Princess-sama's voice too!
--Straw Hat is the serial kidnapper, isn't he? --He's a human.
Luffy-san, please save the island!
Why is the border guard counting on the human pirate?
--Is the human trying... --...To handle the Noah?
Hey, Straw Hat.
Can you hear me?
Prince Fukaboshi!
About Hody Jones...
I found out who he really is!
Brother-hoshi, so who is Hody?!
Hody is...
...a monster who was brought to life by our environment!
Our environment?
What does he mean?
The New Fishman Pirates are a group of
monsters created from an ancient grudge!
The grudge was born from their ancestors
in the shadow of Fishman Island.
And they fear that the grudge will be forgotten
and their anger against the humans will be dispelled.
That's why they are so impatient.
And they want humans to be evil
so they can justify themselves for their crusade!
They just want to see bloodshed
and they don't even want peace for the Fishmen!
What did you go through in the past?!
Answer me, Hody!
What did humans do to you?!
Nothing.
Did you just say "Nothing"?!
We were chosen by heaven to punish humans...
...and granted powers!
I see!
Now I see everything!
Their hatred is...
...not rooted in their experience or true beliefs.
They have no substance!
They are completely "empty"!
Hody has become consumed by his deep hatred of humans.
His dangerous emotions...
...are directly fueling his assault on Luffy.
The only thing that can help Luffy in his desperate struggle on the airless Noah...
...is air from the Air Tank.
All hope is placed...
...in a single last-ditch shot!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Back to Zero! Earnest Wishes for Luffy!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!