All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
They learned about the ruler of the island and the puppeteer
of Land of the Dead - Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate ally - the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are caught in a climactic battle.
And they finally defeated Caesar.
Smoker! The least I can do is...
...take you along to hell with me!
Monet. I can't believe you're alive.
Vergo's been beaten.
It's all because of my misjudgment.
I feel bad for you all.
But I want to make sure to wipe out all those squirts now.
At the Third Laboratory, there is another weapon that was
responsible for destroying the First and Second Laboratory
and the rest of the island four years ago.
With just the push of a button,
there will be only one survivor on the whole island.
No one else can take that highly toxic gas.
And that's Caesar!
The button is at...
You don't have to say it, Joker.
I was gonna do that, anyway.
Thank you.
I need you to perish along with everything else.
Understood.
"A Critical Situation! Punk Hazard Explodes!"
It's fast!
Hey, get off of him!
I won't!
Hey, you're heavy! Get off!
Why is there a dragon here?!
Oh, I met him at a garbage dump.
You brought him with you?
It's no mistake!
Father!
What's wrong with him?
The eel is gonna attack me!
Hey, Momo!
Who is this dragon? He said "Father."
Find out later.
I don't see any light. The exit must be farther away.
How far did Caesar fly?!
This is it for you!
Smoker!
The Straw Hats.
Trafalgar Law.
G-5.
Poor children.
You all...
...have to...
...die with me.
Goodbye, Young Master.
I know you will become...
...the Pirate King.
Why is the Transponder Snail still receiving the signal?
Are you okay?
Uh-huh!
Seems like there was an explosion!
I think it was in D Building.
The SAD Manufacturing Room where I was before.
Monet.
Goodbye, Smoker!
What happened, Monet?
Young Master...
Hey, Law.
If we can get out of here, we'll go separate ways.
But there is something I want to ask you.
What?
This is yours.
I thought Caesar had my heart.
How did it end up in your hands?
He just got the wrong idea.
Let me keep your heart!
And that's a deal!
To earn the trust of Caesar,
I let him keep my heart
and took his secretary Monet's heart in return.
Now it's a deal!
And then I cut your heart out when you got to the lab.
So I had two hearts in my possession.
The Navy G-5 Vice Admiral Smoker's heart!
What a nice gift, Law.
I gave his secretary Monet's heart back to him out of kindness.
Respond.
Monet.
As they say, if you are kind to people,
good things will happen to you.
How did you like it? This Missile Girl's...
...flame of love?
Hey, Baby 5!
Do you need this weapon? Even though you're a weapon woman yourself.
Thank you for picking it up, Buffalo!
That's my good luck charm!
An owner of this weapon is destined to become happy
and if you buy this, you'd make me happy, too!
What?! He...
...needs me!
I'm absolutely sure that he fooled you!
Behind you-dasuyan!
I don't know who you are but...
I'm an invincible Iron Pirate!
I don't fight for the peace of the sea!
--Iron Pirate! --How persistent!
Weapon-morphosis!
Revolver Girl!
Oh! It doesn't work!
It just made me itchy!
This guy's pretty tough!
Baby 5!
Catch it!
Thanks, Buffalo!
It's not over yet!
This is no good! It's collapsing faster!
Look out!
The passage is gonna collapse!
We're in a tunnel through a mountain. If it collapses, we'll be buried alive.
Don't say it in a relaxed matter!
Oh no! The wreckage blocked our way!
Where are the brakes?!
Keep going.
What?!
Cool!
Can't believe it! He saved us!
I don't want him to be my enemy! Although he already is!
Don't get too comfortable yet.
The deadly gas!
You've got to be kidding!
It's that thing again.
Is it flowing in through cracks of walls?
It's gonna be more than just being buried alive.
Stop saying such horrible things in a cool manner!
There is going to be gas around the exit.
Can anybody here generate wind?
What?
It's not so easy to find a person with such a special skill!
I can do that.
How easy?!
I see the exit!
Alright, we're almost there!
Go faster!
Young Master!
Young Master?
I can't find him.
Young Master!
The Young Master is nowhere to be found.
He must be in the room on the fourth floor.
Uh-uh! He wasn't there.
The window was open.
Oh, okay.
Then I don't know where he is.
He went out by himself again.
It's me. Tell me what's going on over there.
W-We've actually been blocked by some kind of iron guard!
Is it still safe there?
Yes, it is!
Which means the island and those squirts haven't been wiped out.
You two.
Take care of that guard.
I'm on my way!