Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
I've been looking all over for you, Sanji!
Hm?
For ten years!
Her name is Carmen.
She's the No. 1 cook in the East Blue.
I'm a woman of passion!
People call me Fiery Carmen.
Ole!
And, I'm Carmen-sama's first apprentice, Leo!
I'm her second apprentice, Jose!
Fiery Cooking Battle?
Sanji vs. the Beautiful Chef
Wow! How beautiful you are!
Say what?!
To think that you've looked all over for me...!
What a lucky man I am!
I'm honored to meet you, Carmen-san!
Don't you dare...!!
What a passionate woman you are...
B... But, Carmen-san, have we met befo...?
Jose!! Leo!!
Explain it to him.
Yes, Ma'am.
Please have a look at this.
Hm? What're these?
They're all cooks...
Yes!!
They're all famous, skilled cooks in the East Blue.
Every single one of them competed
against Carmen-sama and lost.
That's right!
I'm the No. 1 cook in the East Blue.
Those cooks who challenge me
are all disappointing cowards.
I thought that I no longer had
any rivals in the East Blue.
However...!
I came across a feature on
the Sea Restaurant Baratie
from when you still worked there.
That cook said that the Sous Chef
there is the No. 1 cook in the East Blue.
He said that you were an excellent cook
and that we were no match for you!
Since then, I've kept looking all over for you...
searching every nook and cranny
of the East Blue... for ten long years...!
It's actually been ten days, though...
Carmen-sama likes to exaggerate.
Keep your big mouths shut!!
I challenge you, Sanji!
Come to the Cooking Championship
at the market at one this afternoon!
I'll defeat you for sure at that championship!
Got that?!
Well, then! We'll see you later!
Ah, Carmen-san...
What a passionate woman she is!
Young man, are you going to
participate in the competition?
Huh? No, I'm not interested
in things like that, so...
Damn...!
That damn detestable Straw Hat!
To think that we can't find him despite
looking all over for him like this...
But Captain, why in the heck do
we have to wear cloaks like this?
Don't you know anything about being a pirate?!
There's an annoying Navy captain
named Smoker in this town.
If he finds us, my plan to get revenge
on that Straw Hat will be ruined!
Anyhow!
Hurry up and find that Straw Hat!
Got that?!
Man, I'm stuffed!
We have to eat good before we leave Loguetown.
I was starving.
To be honest, so was I.
I was hungry, but I didn't have money.
I'm glad that I ran into you.
Hm?
If you mean money, I don't have any.
What?!
You don't have money?
Of course I don't!
That's true.
But, really... that Straw Hat is an annoying bastard!
Next time I see him, I'll crush him!
Then how're we going to pay for this?
I can't let him off the hook!
I wonder if they'd let us off the hook...
There's no way I can!!
Oh, lucky!
Hey, you're going to treat us? Thanks!
Ahhh...
Thanks again!
Thanks for treating us.
You're... welcome...
Thanks for coming!
Thanks!
That voice...?!
Oh, yeah! It was that Straw Hat guy.
Uhh... Anyone home...?
You flashy idiot!!
Go after him already!!
Yes, sir!
Wh-Which way did he go?
A market, huh?
Whoa!
Just as you'd expect from Loguetown!
They have far better quality and more
kinds of seafood than other places!
Hm?
This is premium!
You have a good eye, young man!
Those're coastal fish caught just this morning.
Coastal fish?
It's true that they're firm and fresh,
but I've never seen fish like this before.
Were they really caught in the East Blue?
Hmm... You're really knowledgeable.
As you noticed, these're fish that
you can catch only in the West Blue.
It's just expected that East Blue
people don't know this fish.
West Blue?
Why do you call them costal fish then?
Young man, I bet you've never been here before.
Huh? Yeah...
It may be because Loguetown is
the closest town to the Grand Line,
but we can sometimes catch fish from the
other seas, in addition to the East Blue.
From the other seas...?
That's right. They probably get
mixed in crossing ocean currents.
That's something that often happens here.
Hm?
Oh... sounds like they caught something.
Wanna go see it?
What's going on?!
Wha...?! This is...!
Amazing!
That's an elephant bluefin tuna!
That's right! It probably got
mixed in from the southern ocean.
I caught it with a pole and line!
A pole and line?!
Elephant bluefin tuna...
Ah!
Look at this!
It's a weird looking fish!
What're you doing with the illustrated
food reference book? Studying?
That's the elephant bluefin tuna.
What? You know this fish?
Of course!
That's a miracle food called a gem of the ocean.
I've never seen it though.
Of course not, since it's a fish from the South Blue.
You never see it in the East Blue,
but it's a different story if there's the All Blue.
Now that's impossible.
Yeah, I know.
What's the All Blue?
It's a legendary sea. I hear that fish
from all over the world swim there.
Stop it. He's a kid.
He'll take it seriously.
Where is it?
See? He doesn't get jokes.
That was a joke, Sanji.
There's no way such a thing exists.
Don't worry about it.
Just keep studying.
All Blue...
Okay, then, haul it away.
Okay!
H-Hold on a second!
Hm?
How much is it?! Sell it to me!
What?!
I've got money! Let me buy it! Please!
No, you can't! This isn't for sale!
It's been decided just now that
this is going to be a prize. Sorry.
A prize...?
That's right.
The annual Cooking Championship
will be starting a little later today.
Cooks from all over the East Blue
gather for this competition.
This'll be given to the winner.
After all, this is an elephant bluefin tuna.
It's exactly what a champion deserves.
So we decided to give it as a prize.
If you really want it, you should participate.
You're a cook, aren't you?
Y-Yeah...
The registration is over there.
If you're interested, go register.
Hurry up or it'll close soon, young man.
See ya!
A cooking competition, huh?
All right, then!
Huh...? Wait a second...
I challenge you, Sanji!
Oh, well...
Now, the annual Cooking Championship
festivities are about to start!
We have famous cooks from
around the East Blue gathered here!
What a crowd!
I wonder what's going on...
This year's prize is an elephant bluefin tuna!
It's a treasure of the ocean and miracle food!
Who will earn the "East Blue's No. 1"
title and win the elephant bluefin tuna?!
That will be me!
I'm glad you came instead of running away, Sanji!
But the East Blue's No. 1 title will be mine!
This time I'll finally prove my real abilities!
Oh, Carmen-san!
I'm excited to see you again!
Here's a kiss for our reunion!
Don't you dare!!
You haven't changed...
How passionate...
Hey! Hold on a sec!
Look! Look at that!
That's Sanji!
Yeah!
Hey! Hey!
– Sanji-kun!
– Sanji!
Nami-san!
You came to give me your support?!
Not really. I was just passing by.
But why in the heck are you
participating in a competition like this?
Oh, Usopp.
I didn't realize you were here.
I was the one who called out to you first!
Now it's time to start the championship!
These're the judges!
Also, to be fair, we asked Sam-san,
a member of the general audience
on his way home from a wedding party,
– to join the judges!
– Where am I?
Are you ready, Sam-san?!
Sam-san?!
Let's go!!
The rules are simple.
First, each cook will compete against another.
Whoever receives a higher
total score from the judges wins.
And whoever remains undefeated through all the matches
will be the East Blue's glorious No. 1 cook!
Well then, we'll now start the first round!
The first match is Shoo the Lizard
from the easternmost extremity versus
Eoccoli, representing Loguetown!
Now, ready... Start!
What, Sanji? You're interested in becoming the East Blue's No. 1?
Don't be stupid. It's nothing like that.
I just want to cook that fish.
Fish?
Oh yeah, that fish does look different from others.
Though that fish's secrets
can't be obtained so easily...
Huh?
And at last, the final match!
Hey, people're really excited.
Yeah.
With his remarkable cooking sense and skills,
Sanji won through to the final!
With her gorgeous dance and cooking skills,
Carmen has kept crushing others!
– Which one will win the
glorious elephant bluefin tuna?!
– Hi!!
Hmph!
The anticipated final match starts now!
Rinsing!
There she goes!
Carmen's cooking looks showy at first glance,
but what she's actually doing is quite simple.
Also her opponents get confused by
those two in front and lose their pace,
but how is Sanji doing?!
He's not affected!
Far from that, he's exhibiting amazing knife skills!
Contender Sanji is silently proceeding
with the preparation at his own pace!
It definitely exists!
You're still saying things like that? How silly!
That's why we say you're a child!
I'm not a child, you damn bastard!
That's enough, Sanji!
We don't have time for your stupid stories!
Forget it and go collect plates!!
I know... Theoretically it's impossible.
I know that much...
The North Blue, South Blue,
East Blue and West Blue...
They're separate seas that you can't cross
due to the Red Line Continent
that runs from north to south
and the ocean current in the Grand Line
which extends from east to west.
A sea where you can find all
the fish from those four seas...
...should be impossible...
But it definitely exists!
That's right. Otherwise how do
you explain those West Blue fish
and the elephant bluefin tuna?
The possibility that the damn geezer
was talking about may refer to this.
If that's the case, I have no choice but
to look for it in the Grand Line after all!
It doesn't matter how long it takes.
I'll find it for sure!
The legendary sea...
All Blue!
Now it looks like Sanji is starting to finish up!
Carmen is also close to the end!
Looks like all she has to do now is dish it out!
The championship is reaching a climax.
Who will win the elephant bluefin tuna?!
The decision... will be made soon!
He did it!
Contender Sanji completed it!
And here is Contender Carmen!
Looks like she's completed it, too!
The dishes are all completed now!
Who will win the crown?!
Well then, here goes.
The winner of this year's Cooking Championship is...
San...
Wait!!
I can't forgive...
Hm?
I can't forgive myself!
What?!
I always wanted to compete against
you some day. So I've trained like crazy!
I wanted to be on a level with you...
But ten years later...
...your dream hasn't changed!
I can't forgive myself for being stupid
enough to think that I could defeat you.
You win... Your dishes are delicious.
You're the No. 1 cook in the East Blue, Sanji.
Oh... To think that Carmen-san
is giving me such a compliment...
– I'm so happy!
– Don't you dare!!
What'd you do that for?!
I'll withdraw for now, but be
prepared when we meet next time!
I definitely won't lose.
Yeah, if it's a challenge from you,
I'll happily accept it any time.
The winner is... contender Sanji!
Ah! That was fun!
– I don't know why but today
was a day of face-offs.
– Hey, why am I carrying the heavier part?!
Well... an elephant bluefin tuna, huh?
I wonder what it tastes like...
Looks like I can use the fins for making stock.
What can I use the ear areas for?
Ahhh! I can't wait to cook it!
Hm?
What's the matter, Nami?
The air has changed...
Air?
It'll rain.
Huh? When the weather is nice like this?
There's no doubt about it. Let's hurry.
Huh? Hey...!
Ah! My hat!
Wait!
Wait, hat!
Luffy?
Phew! Good! My hat!
Hm?
Ahh... I'm here!
Lucky!
Found him! This way!
What?! Really?!
He showed up?!
Yes!
We were watching the square like you told us,
and the man on the wanted
poster appeared just now...
Okay.
Let's go flashily.
So he just walked right up...
Just wait, you brat.
Wow! So this is the scenery
that the Pirate King saw...
And he died here...
hamidashita kimochi tsunagara nakute
my overflowing feelings don't connect
kimi no te o gyutto ni girikaesu yo
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
hitori demo boku wa arukidasu kara
I'll set off by myself,
tooku made zutto mitsumeteite ne
so keep watching me intently as I go into the distance
kesa kara chotto kangaeteita
I was thinking about it a bit since this morning
doushite konna ni atsui no
why is it so hot?
itsu kara ka sonna koto bakari ga
starting from some point,
hanarenai yo
I haven't been able to get away from that
kakedashita kimochi tsukamaetakute
I want to catch those feelings that rushed off,
jibun sae mou oikoshite yuku yo
and I'm already about to overtake myself, even
tobidashita yume o dakishimetetai
I want to embrace my dreams that have jumped out
issho nara boku wa hashitte yukeru
with you, I can run there
What?! Luffy's gonna be executed?!
No way!
By Buggy?! What a shame!
So all we have to do is beat them?
Yep! Help me!
Okay, then!
We'll bring down the execution platform!
I know.
Zoro, Sanji, Usopp, Nami!
Sorry! I'm dead.
Next time, on One Piece:
Buggy's Revenge!
The Man Who Smiles on the Execution Platform!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Buggy's Revenge!
The Man Who Smiles on
the Execution Platform!