Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World, the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After landing on Punk Hazard; an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen,
they learned about the hideous experiments performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
and headed off to investigate but as things got going,
they came to form an alliance with the Heart Pirates led by Trafalgar Law.
And Luffy finally encountered Caesar!
You shouldn't underestimate me.
Who is there?!
Why are you...
...here?!
It's been years.
You've grown up.
Law.
The Samurai Who Cuts Through Fire!
Foxfire Kin'emon
Do you really think that he had no idea?
We don't trust Caesar, either.
That's why he was being careful and sent an undercover agent.
Monet is that agent.
You're a Warlord-sama now, aren't you?
You've done so well.
When did you come here?
Vergo!
Just arrived. Luckily, I was at Dress Rosa.
I got a ride in an SAD tanker that was about to leave.
It was the right move.
The right move?!
Did I cause any harm to you guys?!
No but if you did, you'd be dead by now.
You can't fool grown-ups, Law.
In that case, I should just finish you!
Oh, I forgot to mention.
You've got to say it properly.
It's Vergo-san to you.
IN FRONT OF THE LABORATORY TEAM LUFFY
What just happened?
I have no idea.
What should we do?
Tashigi-chan!
It's Vice Admiral Smoker!
I can't believe I saw him get taken down twice a day.
Three of the Straw Hats got beaten, too!
Was it Conqueror's Haki?!
No way! There can't be that much difference in their strength!
Then what was it?! He beat all of them without even touching them!
That serves you right, Navy!
That was what our savior - Master is capable of!
Master! Master! Master! Master!
Master! Master! Master!
My strong soldiers!
Tie these five up!
Use Sea Prism Stone chains for the Devil Fruit users!
Leave the Navy soldiers here and get inside the laboratory.
It's dangerous out here.
Something strange is raining down but don't worry.
I'll protect this place where you belong!
Yes, Master!
Looks like the Cool Brothers blew it.
But it can't be helped.
Fighting against Straw Hat and Law must've been too much for them.
CENTER LAKE - TEAM ZORO
Gross!
Alright, Brook. Convince them.
That's impossible!
What kind of negotiation skill is going to work for these monsters?!
They're merging into one another!
Boy, they're merging into one another and getting bigger.
I-I-It got bigger!
Do I have a choice? It's my personal mission!
I'm Sanji, I'm a man! I've got to do it!
Sanji-san!
Do something about the Slimes behind you.
Please be careful!
What a pain in the ass! That worthless chef!
Oh, it's coming!
Don't... Don't... Don't attack me!
It's big, it's big!
Oh no, you better not do that!
Whoa, don't! Help me!
You did it!
I knew you could do it, Zoro-san!
It's gas! Run!
I've had enough!
I-I-It's poison gas!
My eyes, my eyes!
Oh, I don't have eyes.
Hey, what's your problem?!
You jelly-ish body entity!
Poison gas, again!
What should we do, Zoro-san?! It's poison gas!
I did the same thing before!
Learn from observation, skeleton!
I thought you were just unlucky.
We're surrounded.
This is not good.
It's cold!
Where is the samurai's torso?
Alright. Let's use it!
Observation Haki!
We have nowhere to go now!
Oh yeah, they're jellies!
Why don't you eat and digest them?
No way!
Could you stop talking to me like a bully?!
I'm like 70 years older than you!
I'm sorry, grandpa!
Who did you call "grandpa"?!
I'm still a lively skeleton...
What's the matter?!
Samurai-san?! T-T-Take it easy!
So cold!
Sorry, Nami-san.
Could this be the Slime's toxin?!
Whoa-whoa, I hope his torso is not engulfed by it!
I've been using Observation Haki for quite a while
but maybe the torso's getting weaker.
I can't distinguish its life force from that of the fish!
A shark?
No way!
A-Are you alright?
Hey, what's the matter?! What's going on?!
Wait, you shithead! Don't mess with me!
Stop chewing on it, shark!
I-I-It doesn't hurt at all! It itches!
What's wrong with him?!
Is he bluffing?
That hurts... Not really!
Maybe something happened to Sanji-san?!
You fool, let it go!
Now!
Joue Shoot!
Alright, I got the last piece safely!
The samurai puzzle will be complete!
I gotta go back now!
It's gonna close up!
Dammit!
The poison got this far!
Shit! It's all around me now!
Can I do it with Nami-san's strength?
It's gonna put a strain on her body again...
This is not good!
The whole lake is turning to the color of the poison!
Sanji-san, hurry up!
Blue Walk!
Don't close up! Don't close up! Don't close up!
Don't close up!
Sanji-san!
Oh, he got it!
He really did it!
What can I say?!
I have never felt so happy to just have my own body!
THE SAMURAI FROM THE WANO KINGDOM FOXFIRE KIN'EMON
Oh, I didn't know you were so tall!
You're as tall as I am.
Oh yes! Excuse me for not introducing myself sooner!
My name is Kin'emon!
I was born in Kuri, Wano Kingdom!
Just do it already! I'm gonna freeze to death!
Yes! I'm sorry!
Poof!
It's still cold.
The coat will disappear once he takes it off, right?
Funny-eyebrow man, what is your honorable name, sir?
I'm Sanji!
Cut the "sir" crap!
Now you have your whole body back so you've changed your attitude!
But you were insulting me so much earlier
hiding behind the fact you were disabled!
I hope you're not forgetting what you said!
You people are pirates?!
No wonder you people are barbaric!
I don't like pirates! You make me sick!
Don't irritate me!
Why don't you just ask me to find your body?!
I don't wanna owe anything to pirates!
I wouldn't ask you even if it kills me!
Now, I'm not even capable of fighting back if someone hits me
so you can carry me if you want to.
I will never forget!
Ever!
I will never forget your kindness for the rest of my life!
I appreciate everything!
And please forgive me for having doubts about you all...
...until I got my torso back!
I'm begging you! I'm begging you!
I'm begging you!
I'm begging you...
Stop it, fool! Lift your head up!
Men shouldn't kneel on the ground that easily!
But if you, sir, weren't there, I probably...
Um, I'm sorry to interrupt you but, Sanji-san...
Looks like we're in big trouble.
Look. You see?
THE THIRD LABORATORY
The drug...
If only I could find out how he made the drug...
Is that...
Great! It's a book about drugs!
Now I gotta look for sedatives.
Master, the airship is ready.
Okay.
Then let's go pick them up.
It's about time for them to have these.
Put Straw Hat and the others in a cage and carry it to my chambers.
Yes, Master!
We have nowhere to run now!
Hey, guys! Didn't I tell you to do something about them?!
It can't be helped because we couldn't do anything.
That's right.
Don't be such children, you idiots!
I can't cause any damage to Nami-san's body!
This body...
Th-This body, I have to...
You're not gonna return it, are you?
Of course not!
Why don't we burn them down?
What?
People call me Foxfire Kin'emon.
I can burn and slice an enemy with my sword.
Let me burn them down and clear the way to escape!
You can burn and slice an enemy?
It sounds like magic!
He cut the fire!
Now I cleared the way.
I'm coming for you, Momonosuke!
Huh?! I'm still alive!
I thought we were engulfed by the fire from the explosion!
K-K-Kin'emon-san? What just happened?
I just cut the explosion.
The explosion?!
My Foxfire Style
allows me to cut something with fire and then cut flames.
There is no flame that I can't cut!
Now I'm going to go to the laboratory to save Momonosuke!
If you'll excuse me!
Wait!
I'm intrigued by a samurai's fight.
I'll go with you to rescue your son!
A mysterious individual appears and manages
to injure Law with overwhelming strength.
While the horrifying truth of this individual
leaves the Straw Hats shocked,
it's nothing compared to
when they discover the true identity
of the mastermind behind Caesar and the enigmatic man!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Shocking!
The Mystery Man's True Identity—Vergo!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Shocking!
The Mystery Man's True Identity—Vergo!