Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
2 years have passed since the Paramount War.
Luffy and his crew returned to Sabaody Archipelago
and on their way to the New World, they reached Fishman Island
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
Luffy and the others find themselves caught up in the turmoil.
Zoro and the others facing Hody and the New Fishman Pirates...
...tried to escape after the tides turned against them
but were caught by Hody whose strength was multiplied tremendously
by taking the Energy Steroid.
Meanwhile, Luffy and the others finally got to the Sea Forest...
The person who is responsible for setting Arlong loose into the East Blue was...
...me!
Haunting Ties!
Nami and the Fishman Pirates!
I'm sure there is a key to the void in history somewhere here.
The missing piece must have been
lying here secretly at this serene place for several centuries.
If I keep going, there'll be...
Here it is!
King Neptune...
Don't look back! Think about what the King did for us!
I see the exit!
Yeah!
We made it outside!
Use the Bubbly Coral!
What a disaster!
So few soldiers made it out even after we left the King there!
We failed!
Stop moaning! It was the King's order!
Men, this is not a retreat!
We will exterminate the pirates in the palace and rescue the King at any cost!
First, we need to communicate with Prince Fukaboshi and the others!
Get in touch with the Princes A.S.A.P. and reorganize the forces...
...and let's go back to the palace!
Yes, sir!
The nearest town from here is...
Fishverly Hills, sir!
Look out!
Fishverly Hills
Meanwhile, at the high-class district - Fishverly Hills...
Run!
--All of you, get in line! --Hurry up if you don't wanna die!
Th-This is... What do you want from us?!
--Step on it! --What?
--It's a test! --No way!
Much...
Shut up! Captain Hody's gonna rule this country-ch!
New Fishman Pirates, Officer Ikaros Much
Now, step on the image!
No, I can't...
Step on it now!
Candy Factory Town
At Candy Factory Town in the northeast...
Hey, just do it already!
I can't!
Huh?!
Please forgive me! I can't tread on the image of her face!
Shut up!
Those who can't do it are human sympathizers.
New Fishman Pirates, Officer Daruma
Which means they're our enemies!
In Front of the Fish Cultural Center
In front of the Fish Cultural Center in the southeast...
Whoa, whoa! It's easy!
New Fishman Pirates, Officer Hyouzou
It's either step on this image or flee from this island.
Screw you!
Damn! I can't take it anymore!
Just do it! If somebody refused to do either...
...I've been told to slice 'em up!
Marine Shopping Mall
At the Marine Shopping Mall in the east...
"Leave the country"? Don't be ridiculous!
This is the only place on the seafloor that has light.
And we can't live in the humans' world!
See?
You can see how heartlessly the humans discriminate against others.
What is it?! What are you doing?!
What's going on?
There is no way that humans and Fishmen can get along.
You must submit to King Hody!
We will reign over humans and change history!
New Fishman Pirates, Officer Zeo
Waterwheel Town
At Waterwheel Town in the north...
Dosun!
--Now, you're next. --It's gonna be easy.
I can't!
New Fishman Pirates, Officer Dosun
I'm gonna pummel those who won't step on it-dosun!
Take this!
You're... Fukaboshi! Don't get in my way!
What do you think you are doing?!
How dare you make people of this country tread on the image of my late mother!
Coral Hill
At Coral Hill, after Luffy and the others left...
--What should we do?! --We let Vander Decken get away...
...and we couldn't stop the Straw Hats from taking Princess Shirahoshi away!
But the Princess said that she'd be back by dinner.
You fool! They made her say it!
A group from the Fishman District is rampaging all over the island!
--What?! --What's going on on the island?!
Mermaid girls are going missing all around the island!
If they sell the Princess to the Celestial Dragons...
Hey, it seems like another Mermaid girl went missing!
I'm scared!
Oh no!
I took her!
That aside, I just saw something great!
A big size Mermaid-san!
A human-sized Mermaid is worth 70 million
so if I can catch a Mermaid who is 7 or 8 times bigger
and sell her...
I'll make a bundle!
Y-You are...
Hello.
Good afternoon!
Sea Forest
Father-sama!
Princess Shirahoshi, don't worry.
Maybe they got the King but they can't really take his life!
What? Are you sure?
Yes. And I will save the King at any cost!
Okay. I will be counting on you, Boss-sama!
Now let me talk to Luffy-kun and the others for a while.
Ladies!
Have some tea!
Thanks. Leave it there, Sanji-kun.
And we're having a serious conversation so stop acting like that!
I love you, Nami-san, even when you're so severe!
Sanji-chin hasn't changed a bit.
Good!
It's not for you!
Now, Jinbe-san.
What do you mean?
You set Arlong loose into the East Blue?
Jinbe-san!
I know.
That's what I heard.
What?
When Luffy and I first heard the name Jinbe of the Seven Warlords,
that's what Yosaku told us.
In exchange for joining the Warlords,
Jinbe set loose a terrible man into the East Blue.
--Was that what he said? --I bet you don't remember it.
I wonder how Yosaku is doing.
When I read that you were with Jinbe 2 years ago in the newspaper,
it raised so many questions in my mind.
Because I thought Jinbe was the key figure who was pulling Arlong's strings.
Hey, Jinbe.
If you wanna make excuses, I'll listen. But you better watch what you say.
As a matter of fact, this beautiful navigator - Nami-san here had her home island...
...taken over by Arlong!
And she's been through hell because of it!
Depending on what you have to say, I might not forgive you!
--Jinbe-san! --Hatchin!
Your wounds are gonna open up again! Don't get up!
He's right! We gave her so much pain...
...that we can't heal no matter how much we apologize.
I’m gonna use my navigation skills to travel to all the world’s oceans!
And then I’m gonna make a world map of everything I see!
So your map of this island is your first step toward your dream, then?
Yeah!
I'm a fill-in mother for you two, Nami and Nojiko.
You two are my dear family!
Pirates, everyone!
Pirates are coming!
You seem to be in excellent spirits, pathetic humans!
As of this moment,
this village - no, this island - is now under my control!
100,000 berries per adult. 50,000 berries per kid.
Those who can’t pay... die!
I just can’t say I don’t have a family...
Even... if it costs me my life...
Yeah, maybe we’re not related by blood...
...but we’re a family.
I want to be their parent, even if it’s only in name.
They’re... my kids.
Die with your pathetic love.
Nojiko! Nami!
I love you!
What's this?
--A sea chart? --No!
I drew that! It's important to me! Give it back!
You drew it?
--Give it back! --Nami! No!
Oh? This is quite impressive.
She’s an invaluable asset! Bring her with us!
--Right! --No!
Let go! Let go! No!
We have no food for humans! Shut up and keep drawing maps!
Gather up 100 million berries and bring it here.
Do so and I’ll let the village go and give you freedom.
Thief! She stole our treasure!
--She's a kid! --Who cares! Shoot her!
Shit! Go after her!
70 million more... 70 million more to free the village!
Oh, you're back!
Humph! It seems like you have nowhere else to go.
Welcome home, my dear navigator!
Sounds like you had a terrible experience.
You bastard! Don't distance yourself!
Yes.
It would never make me change the way I feel about Arlong,
but until I went to Sabaody Archipelago 2 years ago,
I never knew that such tough Fishmen were persecuted by humans.
When Camie was kidnapped and I was going after her,
I couldn't believe what I saw!
Sabaody Park in front of me looked exactly like Arlong Park that Arlong built!
We were yearning for it.
I'm not just saying this to make you forgive me.
Nami! Arlong-san really didn't like humans!
He hated them.
We went too far.
But ever since we were kids,
we yearned for the world that humans live in.
Me, Arlong-san...
Everybody...
But we hurt so many humans!
Hachi, don't push yourself! I'm gonna prepare some medicine so lie down.
I heard that Fishmen and Merfolk were considered mere fish a long time ago.
But 200 years ago, the Ryugu Kingdom became a member country of the World Government.
They established friendly relations with humans
and the king was allowed to participate in the World Summit.
Despite that, humans kept disliking Fishmen.
The worst time that I experienced was the beginning of the Great Pirate Era.
I vividly remember the fear of seeing human pirates running wild on the island.
I can't get it off of my mind!
Fishman Island was taken over by humans.
And then, the late, good-old Whitebeard saved us.
He claimed Fishman Island as his own
and peace returned to the island.
However, it didn't stop humans from disliking Fishmen.
I know that you people saw it at Sabaody Archipelago.
The reality.
The funny thing is those who seize power tend to be more afraid of change.
Even though the Government bridged the gap between Fishmen and humans
those who held the real power ended up being much more bigoted than all the others!
The relationship between Fishmen and humans remained the same.
Then, two people rose up on Fishman Island, to change our hopeless history.
One was Queen Otohime.
She kept trying to tell the islanders to live in harmony with humans.
She was Princess Shirahoshi's mother.
And the other is the hero who freed the slaves - Fisher Tiger.
Something Tiger... I heard that name before.
Calling for parting ways with humans, he broke an unspoken rule
and invaded the Holy Land of Mary Geoise by himself and freed the slaves.
Later, he formed the Sun Pirates with the Fishmen who were slaves.
The Sun...?
Yes! Me, Arlong, and Hachi joined the...
...crew of the Sun Pirates, naturally.
However, having the "Fishman Pirates" who went against the Government...
...made it harder for Queen Otohime to establish good relations with humans.
Queen Otohime was trying to weather great hardships and change the future.
Fisher Tiger threw his future away
to save the slaves of his race who were suffering at the time.
No one can say which one was right or wrong.
Let's talk.
They fought for the future of Fishmen and humans.
They were two monumental figures!
But what was their hidden angst?!
Queen Otohime tried to guide the Ryugu Kingdom
toward a future where humans and Fishmen could live together.
There was also Fisher Tiger, a hero who rescued Fishmen
from enslavement by humans.
Their fates intertwined as they imagined a new future for Fishman Island,
and an incident that shaped history occurred!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Hero Who Freed the Slaves
Tiger the Adventurer"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Hero Who Freed the Slaves
Tiger the Adventurer