Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
With his special body,
he is a General Zombie.
This man hails from the Land of Wano in the New World!
Wh-What gives? I thought
he was going to attack us.
I-It doesn't matter!
C'mon, let's make a break for it!
The door is wide open!
--You're right!
--Y-Yeah!
Three-Verse Humming... Nock Slash!
That hurt, you bastard! Lemme out, dammit!
--What was that?
--Bastard, lemme out! I mean it!
I'll let you have it if ya don't let me out!
--A casket?!
--Open the lid!
That voice...!
What's he doing?! Sheesh!
Did that idiot get caught?
Straw Hat!
Now then, we'll hold the
wedding ceremony right away.
I've already dealt with the preparations.
Put me down! It was you, wasn't it?
You're the invisible man
who was in the bathroom!
My name is Absalom.
It is the name of your future husband.
You'd best remember it!
I haven't been babying my skin
every day for a perverted beast!
We're getting out of this forest.
I won't let you escape!
Monkey, monkey!
Immortal zombies are blocking the
paths in front of you and behind you.
Now say your prayers!
Hey, wait! What're you doing?!
Coup de...
...Vent!
You've demolished the breezeway!
Cien Fleurs:
Wing!
All of them fell into the courtyard.
I doubt that finished them off...
What is that?
This bag of bones goes...
Ka-bone!
"Appearing from the Sky!
That Man Is the Humming Swordsman!"
Whoa, stop! You can't do this!
Don't kill her! She's my friend!
Darn boar! Stupid sow! Stop!
Hightail it, Nami!
Wait, you vile Cat Burglar!
No!
--I'm going to take Absalom to be my husband!
--Stop, dammit!
--Get off of me!
--No!
Now say your prayers!
H-
Hold your horses!
I...
I...!
I'm actually a man!
Whoa, there.
I-Is that true?
S-Sure is! I just cross-dress for fun!
Gimme a break!
Besides... I think you and Beast Man
would make an awesome couple!
I was totally shipping you!
--Really?
--Really! Gimme a break!
No one has ever encouraged me to
pursue my feelings for him before...
You're the first person to offer
such kind words of support.
I... I...!
Raise your head, my friend.
This is what you call "friendship."
I am Namizo. Please call me "Nami."
Friendship...? Nami!
You tamed her!
You know, like, I'm always trying
to catch him when his guard is down
so I can get a fingerprint
on the marriage certificate.
But his guard is never down!
He even manages to avoid touching the paper
when I play dirty and hold him in an armlock!
Really, Lola! You're
going about it all wrong.
You're leaving too much room to chance.
Eh?! Eh?! What do you mean?
The thing is, he's resisting
because he's conscious.
You should wait until he's sound asleep.
Attack him in his sleep?!
Is that okay?! Won't it make me a bad person?
Lola, aren't you a zombie?
I forgot about that! What
a rotten blind spot!
If he isn't asleep, you can knock
him out and that'll work just as well!
Hey, Namizo!
Weren't you gonna escape?
By the way, Lola, I forgot
something in the treasure room...
I'd like to go back and get it,
but I can't recall how to get there.
Could you tell me?
You're such a klutz! Sure, I'll tell you.
The closest way there is
through Perona-sama's room.
Look, see that? Notice the
room with the tiny veranda?
She seriously turns her
misfortune into fortune.
If you keep going straight this way,
you'll hit a staircase.
Nami's a guy?
That will take you to Perona-sama's room.
No wonder I thought
she seemed so masculine.
From there, you'll head inside...
Hey, Nami! He's closing in on us!
Really? Lola, this is your chance to attack!
I'll never see him again,
so don't worry about me!
Good luck! You two make the best couple!
I'll do my best!
Thank you, Nami!
I'm bursting with courage!
Absalom!
Lola!
Guys, now's our chance!
In the end, the boar didn't hurt us any.
Nami, you're amazing!
Couldn't you tell how nice and honest
she was after we sat down and talked?
There is something very wrong with your eyes!
Master!
We did it, Master!
Cut the crap, you freaks!
And who's this "Master"?!
Lemme outta here right now!
Lemme out, dammit!
Who are you?!
H-Hey, let go! Knock that off!
H-Hey!
Jerks, you'd better be ready for a fight!
'Cause I'm gonna let you have it!
Sheesh! Who the heck are these guys?!
Doesn't this ship have a
single treasure chest?!
There are boxes, but they are all empty...
There is also a tiny bit of money...
Unbelievable! We're hardly getting
anything out of the two ships.
Does this ship really belong to
the man who defeated Crocodile?
Oh, well. Go ahead and pilfer their
ridiculously large supply of food.
--Yes, ma'am!
--Perona-sama!
Hildon...
Moria-sama is summoning the Three Phantoms.
The master beckons? Whatever for?
I've heard that Straw Hat Luffy
has been captured!
He wants to make a show
out of reanimating No. 900!
No. 900?! Is he serious?!
Who're you? You're stinking huge!
Hey, punk! Careful how
you speak to the master!
So you are Straw Hat Luffy?
I'm glad to see that you're doing well.
Is it you?
Are you that moron, Moria?
What a thing to say!
You have quite a bit of spunk
in you. Quite a bit, indeed.
I should have expected as much from
someone with a 300-million-berry bounty.
I imagine you will make an excellent
subordinate in just a moment.
A subordinate?! Screw that!
Who do you think you are?!
Who...? "Who do you think you are," eh?
I am the future Pirate King!
Ab-sama! Absalom, you jerk!
Come out and marry me!
You vanished and fled again, didn't you?!
"Evil Be Gone"
--Did we lose him?
--Probably.
I'm sure Lola...
He's coming!
He's headed straight this way!
Over here!
Hurry! Get in here.
What is this?
Beats me, but we've gotta
focus on hiding for now!
What was that...?
That's strange... This is the
only way they could have gone.
Hey, Kumacy!
Erosalom--er, Absalom-sama,
there is trouble afoot!
Stop, that can wait. My business comes first.
Did three pirates come this way?
Actually, about that--
Absalom!
What are you doing here? This is my room.
Perona...
Welcome back, Perona-sama.
Zip it, Kumacy! How many times
must I tell you not to talk?!
I know, but I have something important--
Shut up! I don't wanna hear your voice!
I see you're as harsh on Kumacy as ever.
You're beary harsh.
Butt out of it. He's my subordinate.
More importantly, have you heard?
The master is summoning us.
Has there been some sort of incident?
Well, I suppose you could say that.
He's going to reanimate No. 900.
No. 900?!
Does that mean the
300-million-berry bounty has been caught?
They still haven't found us,
if you can believe that.
It's a miracle!
Why did we hide here in the first place?
We didn't have much choice!
Who knew Beast Man was
gonna catch up so soon?
And I didn't realize this was a zombie!
Let's look for a chance to make
a break for it. Sound good?
Absalom-sama!
So this is where you went!
I have something I'd like to tell you.
What is it?
It looks like we have one more
intruder on top of the pirates.
An intruder?
It's the Humming Swordsman!
What?!
Someone... just fell from the sky.
Hey, what just came hurtling down?!
It couldn't be...
Well, actually, I have a
pretty good idea who it is...
Where the heck did that doof fall from?
Tch! This bites! Guess
we'd better go save him.
Hey, hey!
Despite that bizarre interruption,
you can't escape from me!
I can always make more footing if I have to!
Monkey, monkey!
We'll have to deal with
this headache first, huh?
Buy me a bit of time.
What are you going to do?
Ooh! Those pillars are just what I needed.
I'm gonna whip up a weapon right quick.
How dare you act like I'm no big deal?!
Don't treat me like a small fry!
Spider's...
...Sticky Net!
He has spinnerets on his hands!
Seis Fleurs:
Slap!
Something touched my eye!
Oh, shoot! I got sticky net in my eyes.
Thanks, Nico Robin! I'm
ready and raring to go!
Get back!
What is that?
Nothing much! I just thrust the steel
nunchakus I had on hand into some pillars.
Ya need a big weapon when
dealin' with a monster like this!
Heavy Nunchaku!
Why is he so powerful?
Isn't he supposed to be human?
Stop--
Tararan is in trouble!
Who are those guys?
At any rate, we need to hurry up there!
S-Stop!
Give it a rest, jerk!
Spider's Sticky Net!
You're lost without your trusty weapon!
You were asking for that!
Weapons Left!
Hey, hey!
Nico Robin!
What are those things?
Mouse, mouse! Mouse, mouse!
I'm sorry. I let my guard down.
I didn't realize there were more spiders.
C-Crap!
Moron! Monkey, monkey!
It's impossible for you to notice those guys.
They're my subordinates, the Spider Mice.
There are a whopping five
hundred of them in Thriller Bark!
They've never failed to catch
our prey, not even once!
They strike from the darkness
or from their enemy's blind spot
to catch him unawares!
Hogback-sama has modified our silk
so that no human could ever break it!
We hung out quietly in the ceiling
and snatched your friends up.
It doesn't matter how strong the person is--
we don't give him a chance to resist!
By the time he realizes what
has happened, it's already too late!
Now we'll take you to the same
place we took your friends!
Brace yourselves!
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho...
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho!
Yo ho ho ho...
Yo ho ho ho!
Huh? What's that?
Time to ship out Binks' Brew!
The sea breeze blows us to who-knows-where,
let the waves be our guide!
O'er across the ocean tide,
the sunset stirs, going wild!
Look to the skies! Watch the circling birds
as they sing and pass us by!
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho...
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho!
Who is it?! Who's singing that song?!
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho...
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho!
Goodness, I see everyone really
did disembark onto this island.
How did you get up here?
I jumped.
I'm light!
Seeing as you're here, I suppose
you've left me with no other choice.
I shall tell you everything
about this island.
Hey! Who the hell are you?!
You aren't a zombie, are you?
I bet you're with these pirates!
Hey, Skeleton!
Yes, yes. Not to worry.
The fight is already over.
Huh?
Three-Verse Humming...
...Nock Slash!
Knock it off, you oversized shallot!
I'll get you for this, jerks!
Put some light on him!
Let go of me, dammit!
What's happening? My shadow is...? Stop it!
I've gained a 300-million-berry bounty's
worth of power to add to my forces!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Luffy's Emergency Situation!
The Ultimate Shadow's Destination!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!