Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy and his friends
chased after a big beetle
which appeared suddenly during their journey,
in order to recruit him, and in doing
so they reached an unknown island.
Alright, you giant beetle! Join my...
My boss...
...will never become...
...a pirate!
With this beetle as their guardian angel,
Yoko, a girl who hates pirates and...
...the people from the same ocean
live on this island called...
This is Kansorn Island where people
from the East Blue live together!
It also known as Little East Blue!
Meanwhile, the Amigo Pirates, working on
orders from the legendary pirate Shiki...
...are heading to Kansorn Island as well!
Movie Tie-in Special
Little East Blue in Danger
Reefs surround the island. It's
too dangerous to speed up.
Ready?
Nami-sama!
Over here! It's this way!
What the... hell...
L-Look at her! Nami-sama in
person is there in front of us!
She's mega cute, way more
than the wanted poster!
I can't help crying! I'm
so happy to be alive!
Yeah, yeah!
W-Who are you people?
Thank you for asking!
We're members of the unofficial
Nami-sama fan club...
Known as Orenami Group!
Orenami?
Yes! L...!
O...!
V...!
E...!
We love you! Nami-sama!
Stop it! That's so irritating!
Take me to see Luffy, already!
Yes, it's our pleasure, Nami-sama!
For God's sake...
Can you stop calling me Nami-sama?
Yes, Nami-sama!
Ah! Feels great!
This is awesome!
Do you like it?
You're from Windmill Village so
they must be familiar to you.
Yeah, but none of ours were this big!
That windmill is like a
symbol for Little East Blue.
See? This is the training hall!
Hmmm...
I'm here to challenge you!
Against me?
Sure.
My 2001st win.
Man... Bad memories.
Lunch break is over! Let's
start afternoon lessons!
Okay!
Ouch! Please!
H-H-H-He wants to challenge us!
Hey! He's not a challenger!
Take a good look! He's
"Pirate Hunter" Zoro-san!
Wow! Really? Amazing!
Can I have your autograph?!
How pathetic!
This looks just like Kaya's mansion!
This brings back memories!
She'd always poke her head
out of the window upstairs...
--Usopp-san!
--Hey, Kaya!
Did I keep you waiting?
So what adventure are you
going to tell me today?
Hmm, let's see...
The story of when I fought the
giant goldfish at the South Pole
when I was five!
Goldfish?
Yeah! What first shocked me was
the immense size of its poop!
It was so big that I landed on
it, thinking it was solid ground!
I wonder how she's doing...
Wow, it's so thin!
W-What's wrong here?!
I heard that Luigia who lives here
built this in the style of the
mansion that she used to live in.
N-N-No way! It wasn't like this!
But maybe...
if she used to live in the mansion
that means she's a relative of Kaya?
D-Don't tell me that you're K-Kaya?
Who is she?! Who is she! Who is...
You're a member of the Straw Hats, right?
Yeah, I cook for them.
Where did you learn to cook?
At an on-the-sea restaurant in
the East Blue for several years.
The Baratie?!
Are you really from the Baratie?!
K-Kind of...
That's great! I'm thrilled!
I fell in love with dishes that Zeff cooks
and tried to steal some idea
s by going there often around
the time when it started.
Oh, really...
The building is similar, right?
I don't have Zeff's courage so I
couldn't imagine making it on the sea
but I still wanted as style similar to his.
Go ahead and try it.
I'm sorry but I don't have any money...
No problem! Come on!
Oh yeah?
Alright.
This must be...
Ouch!
Yes! I figured out how the
damn geezer cooks the dish!
How is it? Does it taste like Zeff's?
Yeah. In fact, you're better
than that old geezer!
Are you sure? I can't tell
you how happy that makes me!
Gee... even the cook seems happy!
So tiny...
Shut up!
So you're from Syrup Village?
Huh? Yeah.
You must be Yasopp's son.
You know him?!
Sort of. We had a lot of
troubles with his lying.
Dad? Oh, by the way,
did you really live in the mansion there?
You must know if you're from there!
That mansion is not only
the symbol of the village
but it's everybody's dream house!
Y-Yeah!
I always wanted to live in a mansion
like that since I was a kid.
I finally made my dream come after
I ended up being on this island.
So that means you're not
related to Kaya at all.
I'm known as a cranky princess here so don't
tell anybody if you don't wanna die!
Yes, Ma'am!
Damn, even the granny is bonding with them?!
Oh, please watch your step there!
It's a strange place to walk through.
This is a maze made by nature!
Hmm.
It connected to different
parts of the island!
That's nice but, are we there yet?
Ah, we're almost there!
W-W-What the hell is this?!
It's the symbol of Orenami!
It was hard because we only
had the poster to draw from!
W-Well... I mean... Why is it naked?!
That was decided by consensus!
Don't worry! We made sure
to get the front, too!
That's enough!
Sorry...
Boss...
They're all stupid!
They let pirates on to the
island which you and my father
have always been protected!
I hate them! I hate them!
That tickles! Boss!
Stop it! Hey!
Alright, guys! Let's take this
thing to the legendary pirate Shiki
and become his brothers!
Remember, we're after the big beetle
that took off from Shiki's hide-out!
Do you understand?! Failure is not an option!
Be ready for anything!
Yeah!
Uh, sorry, Big Bro,
but you're the captain so you
better say something about...
Oh no, he's in the middle of a siesta now!
Uh-oh! He's not gonna wake up for a while!
--You bastard!
--Don't do it, Colt-san!
You know what's gonna happen if you
wake him when he's having a siesta!
He's right! We don't wanna die yet!
How the hell could he take a nap at this
crucial moment for us Amigo Pirates!
We gotta do it without him
then! Are you ready, guys?!
Órale!
Okay, it's done! We have a
steel cage for the beetle!
Amazing! It only took you a minute!
Huh! It's a piece of cake for me!
You're good!
We're ready for the beetle at any minute now!
Yeah! They might be back
with it at any minute!
Awesome!
It's a welcome party for you.
Mitsuboshi really wanted this to happen.
Everybody, dig in!
Cheers!
So good!
Having a party for pirates?
What're they thinking?!
--We're here!
--The town square is right there!
You kept saying we were "almost"
there but you made me walk for hours!
We wanted you to enjoy our
island to the full extent!
You're a pirate, too, right?
Even women are into pirates?
These are crazy times!
Humph! Everybody's into pirates!
Yoko! You can't talk to
Nami-sama like that...
Augh! Ouch! Stop it!
Oh, hey!
I'm sorry, Nami-sama! Her father
was killed by pirates...
Oh...
What happened?!
Hey, everybody, I need your
attention! Yes, look at me!
We're Amigo Pirates! This
island is under siege!
If you don't wanna get killed,
let us have the beetle!
The beetle?! Why does he know about Boss?!
Couldn't you hear what I said?
How about these?
W-What's this?! What's going on here?!
I don't know!
No! Don't go to them!
W-What's going on?!
I heard that the big beetle
is protecting this island!
But if he has nobody to protect, there'll
be no reason for him to stay here!
Don't you think so?
They want Boss!
No, Boss! Stay there! Don't show yourself!
My restaurant...
They destroyed it!
Old man!
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
I represent this island's inhabitants.
Is that so? Then where's the beetle?
I'm sorry but you can't have him!
Instead, you can have all
our money and food and
everything on this island!
Just take it all and go away!
Oh, believe me, we intend to do
so! We intend to take everything!
Money, food, and the beetle as well!
Whew! Couldn't eat another bite!
W-Who the heck are you? What're you doing?!
Hey, you, Fancy Hat! Go home!
W-What?!
The giant beetle doesn't
want to join a pirate crew!
Just give up on him!
What?! Join the crew?!
You got me wrong, stupid!
I'm here to catch him!
Oh no!
That's not gonna work on me.
I'm a rubber man!
A Devil Fruit user?!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Zoro! Sanji!
--Alright!
--We got it!
They're coming!
Do you wanna fight more, Fancy Hat?!
That beetle's gonna fight me again tomorrow!
I'm not gonna let you ruin that!
Mucho Needle Net!
Ow, ow, ow... Ouch!
Luffy!
Amore! My beloved brother Colt!
What a shame!
Even if you are a rubber man,
I will not let you get away with it, senor!
Yeah! That's my Big Bro!
Boo-hoo-hoo, so melancholy!
What's this?!
Luffy is captured by Largo.
Zoro and Sanji also struggle against
the powers of the Net-Net Fruit.
And when the beetle learns that
it is the pirates' target,
it makes a grave decision in
order to protect the island.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Movie Tie-in Special
Fierce Onslaught of the Amigo Pirates"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Movie Tie-in Special
Fierce Onslaught of the Amigo Pirates