Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece...
head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
returned to Sabaody Archipelago.
And on their way
to the next stage—the New World—
they reached Fishman Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level, but then...
they were suddenly attacked
by the New Fishman Pirates—separating them.
Luffy and the others were rescued by Mermaids
and were brought to Camie's house.
Sanji-chan!
We don't have time! Anyone?!
Somebody please! I beg you!
Give blood to Sanji!
Fishman Island Will Be Annihilated!?
Sharley's Prophecy
Please! Spare him some blood! My friend is dying!
Someone with blood type S RH negative?!
We don't have time!
Donate your blood!
We beg you!
I'm sorry, Sanji-chin.
It's very hard for humans
to get a blood transfusion on this island.
But Luffy-chin and the others will...
Damn! I've been looking so hard
but I can't find anybody who'll give blood!
I'm not gonna give up!
There must be somebody!
Sanji...
A human!
Luffy! I found a human here!
That barrel drifted here
along with Camie's friends. What's in it?
Liquor? Treasure?
I don't know.
It's very tightly-sealed.
What do you think?
Should we open it secretly?
Is it okay to do that?
I think so.
Oh? You're well-prepared, Ishilly!
Sanji! Are you awake?
Sanji-chin!
Where am I?
What a relief!
We're in a town at the harbor.
Sanji-chin, you lost almost all
the blood from your body.
I'm so glad that we found a blood donor!
Oh, blood...
What's wrong with me?
Don't get up so fast!
You need to rest more.
But why won't the Fishmen donate blood?
We looked everywhere in town but we couldn't find a human.
I almost gave up!
Guys, thank you for doing that.
But I don't remember anything.
Where was I and what was I doing?
I can barely remember...
No, don't think back!
We don't want you to have a nosebleed again!
Oh yeah, Sanji!
Let me introduce you to the blood donor
that we finally found at a bar!
You have to say "thank you"!
Huh? Don't tell me that I got blood
from such a delicate lady!
It's okay!
We're both humans.
We have to help each other when we're in trouble.
It's okay, silly!
If you want...
We can give you more, silly!
I'm glad that he's back to his old self!
Hey, say "thank you" to them!
Luffy, let me see your right arm.
Positive reaction for poison!
That's a poisonous wound as I thought!
Come to think of it,
when I fought against the Fishmen...
I felt something sting me.
But you're okay?
Uh-huh.
Okay, let me see it.
This must be deadly poison.
Are you really okay?
Uh-huh.
I can't believe it!
An antibody must've developed in your body
to counter this kind of poison.
Have you ever been poisoned before?
Poison, huh?
I almost died from poisoning in the Impel Down.
Almost died?
It's not funny!
I think it was that guy!
The swordsman with octopus tentacles.
He blocked my punch!
I bet he's very strong!
That's coming from the cove.
Those Mermaids are really noisy.
Now what should I do?
These guys are all messed-up.
And I accidentally poisoned Straw Hat.
I'll be in trouble if he dies.
Ishilly and the others were screaming!
Ishilly!
I heard them around here!
Where did they go?
I heard them talking about opening a barrel.
Everyone, come here.
There's somebody I'd like you to meet.
The owner of the Mermaid Cafe who let Sanji stay...
What is this?
Madame Sharley.
Oh yeah? Thanks!
Is the blond boy okay now?
Owner of the Mermaid Cafe
Madame Sharley
Uh-huh. But since you're such a beautiful lady,
it's best you stay away from the room.
And let's not tell Sanji-chin
that this place is in the back of the Mermaid Cafe.
Why's that?
His doctor, Chopper-chin said that
if he finds out, there'll be trouble again.
What a strange prognosis.
Hey, Big Mermaid!
It's Madame Sharley, Luffy-chin!
What's this?
It's beautiful!
Don't touch it, Straw Hat boys.
That's a crystal ball.
It's used for fortune telling.
Madame's precognition is famous in Coral Hill.
I'm not practicing anymore.
It's better not knowing the future.
Well, how about this?
Do you Mermaids poop?
What does that have to do with telling fortunes?
Don't you have any class?
A-Apologize to her, Luffy-chin!
Sorry.
Camie, you can take a day off today.
Show them around the island.
Huh? Really?
You always work hard.
And...
these days we don't have human pirates as guests,
so my business is drying up.
The girls from the cove will be coming soon,
so we have enough
star waitresses to handle customers.
Enough star... fish...
Oh no! I should have delivered those clams to Pappagu by now!
That was so out-of-context!
He must be hungry...
What? Monsieur Pappagu is having fun
at the cafe with his old friend.
At the cafe?
Old friend?
I couldn't mention this in front of her,
but when Madame was a little child,
she predicted that many pirates would come to the island.
That was a year before the Great Pirate Era began.
What?!
Among a host of other things,
she recently predicted the war at Marineford
and Whitebeard's death.
What?!
She can't stand knowing what bad things will happen.
Must be scary!
Where's Chopper?
Oh, he's taking care of Sanji.
Luffy-chin! Usopp-chin!
Yeah!
This is the main street of Coral Hill.
Look! That's the entrance of the Mermaid Cafe.
Oh, I'm getting hungry!
It's a cafe!
We have food too!
Cakes and sea fruit.
What about meat?
We Merfolk don't eat meat and fish
so what we have is:
Wakame Brûlée, Mozuku Tart, Kelp Soufflé...
Are they edible?
Oh, we have meat too!
What?
Shellfish meat! Scallop Sandwich, Freshwater Clam Pizza...
That's not meat!
Don't ruin meat's reputation!
Whoa... Anyway, let's get going!
To the Mermaid Cafe!
Yeah, Pappagu will be there.
Hey, don't ruin meat's reputation!
Thank you very much!
Resting my bones! Resting my bones!
I'm happy for you, Bones!
Brook!
Brook-chin!
Oh, Luffy-san and Usopp-san! And it's been a while, Camie-san!
Could I look at your panti—
She's a Mermaid!
Straw! Nose!
I missed you guys!
I didn't know that you were here!
Long time no see!
So you were with Pappagu!
Yes, I didn't expect to be rescued by Pappagu-san!
I was so lucky!
Yeah, that was just as surprising to me!
While I was polishing off
an idea for a new design at the cove,
I saw some bones drifting towards me in the river.
Those are bones!
Soul King, come to see us again!
I had a wonderful time!
I'll be back, beautiful Mermaids!
What?!
I'm going boneless!
Oh, I can't exist without bones!
Oh, I don't care if I die now!
Oh no, I'm already dead!
How cool!
He got so hyper in the cafe...
Yeah, I wonder what's going on inside.
Wait, wait, wait!
You aren't leaving today, are you?
I know you are interested in the cafe
but you can come back with everybody later.
I was gonna take Bones to my house now.
Come with me!
Do you like sea monster meat?
Do you have meat?!
I'm wild, I don't wanna eat seaweed or shellfish!
What I mainly eat is violent sea monsters!
Oh, Pappagu, I almost forgot! Here are your clams for today.
Yeah! Camie's best clams!
So you eat shellfish!
Damn!
Lovely Mermaid...
Yes?
Fantastic Mermaid...
Are you alright?
Beautiful! Elegant! Wonderful! Sniff, sniff!
I wonder how they're doing...
Unlike Merfolk, Fishmen eat meat and fish.
It's not like we don't have them here.
Oh, glad to hear that!
Oh, just what I was looking for! Hey, taxi!
Here I go!
What?!
Vander Decken!
He's a ghost—why are they looking for him?!
Oh, this guy was on the ghost ship we saw?
What?! Did you guys see him?
Yes.
The whole nation
has been looking for him for years!
He's a pirate—an undersea bandit!
I'll tell you about it later.
Get on first!
Vander Decken was sending love letters...
to the Mermaid Princess
of the Ryugu Kingdom at least once a week.
Before long, the letters became packages,
then threats to marry him...
Oh, it's fluffy! Feels good!
Yeah, it's like heaven!
Listen to a starfish!
Okay!
Oh, sorry.
His eccentric behavior
made the Mermaid Princess afraid
and it became a national concern...
Yeah, the Mermaid Princess' father,
King Neptune, got mad
and those three princes that we just met
have been looking for him with the army
but they can't find him.
Camie, Camie... I was just telling them about it...
King Neptune, the God of the Sea,
who runs this country...
has four children including the Mermaid Princess.
The Mermaid Princess is the youngest and the three princes are older than her.
Hey, Camie...
But what I can't understand is
Vander Deck must be a ghostly pirate
from hundreds of years ago...
Well, those legends are often exaggerated.
He truly existed and in fact,
I heard the legendary captain—Vander Decken...
reached Fishman Island and died here.
The ship that you saw
was the Flying Dutchman, wasn't it?
It's his descendant who is on the ship!
Vander Decken IX!
What?! His descendant?!
Oh, is that so?
That means he's not a ghost.
I thought that it was a real ghost
and felt more dead than alive since I'm a skeleton.
That's good. That's just good.
Camie... Camie... Camie...
When I look closer,
Merfolk and Fishmen are all different.
There are old Mermaids!
Like Grandma Kokoro!
Look, there's a baby!
The father is a Fishman
and the children are Merfolk and Fishmen.
When a Mermaid and a Fishman get married,
their kids would be
either Merfolk or Fishman, either boy or girl.
So there are four possibilities.
Hmmm, that's why they're all different.
Interesting!
Alright, let's get on the highway!
It's fast!
What's that?
That's a candy factory.
No, why is there a pirate flag?!
That? You can see the same flag
at the entrance of the island and at the harbor.
That flag is protecting Fishman Island.
The mark belongs to a pirate
called Charlotte Linlin of the New World.
Also known as Big Mom, one of the Four Emperors!
Th-The Four Emperors?
Before the war,
Whitebeard was protecting the island from pirates
but now it's Big Mom.
Hmmm.
But she demands a lot of sweet candies
every month in exchange.
That's what the factory is for.
Candies?
This country can't exist
without the protection of those powerful people.
That's how dangerous this place is, where pirates come and go frequently.
But she's protecting the country after old man Whitebeard.
Isn't Big Mom a good person?
It's hard to say.
Whitebeard never demanded anything.
So Big Mom views it as business, maybe.
Big Mom...
One of the Four Emperors like Shanks.
Wonder if I'll meet her someday.
Look forward!
We're in Fishverly Hills,
the town of celebs!
That tall building right in front of us
is Pappagu's house.
That?! That's too much for a starfish!
We have to do something!
She's the Madame from the Mermaid Cafe.
What's the matter, Madame Sharley?
Why are you so upset?
We have to do something before it's too late!
Hey, Madame!
What's wrong?
Look for him!
The pirate boy with a straw hat!
And throw him out of this country!
Is it a precognition again?
I wasn't planning on using it.
But I felt something about him
so I couldn't help looking into the future!
What's wrong?!
What did you see?!
Madame!
Sharley! Say it!
I hope it won't happen!
I hope it'll be proven wrong!
A human with a straw hat on...
At Straw Hat Luffy's hands... at his hands...
Fishman Island will be...
destroyed!!
Fishman Island shines with beauty.
But history has created a darkness.
Hating humans, they desire retribution.
Their plans are mobilizing beneath the surface.
Meanwhile, Luffy and his crew run amok at Pappagu's shop,
and the king of Fishman Island,
Neptune himself descends from his palace.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The King of Fishman Island
Neptune, the God of the Sea!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The King of Fishman Island
Neptune, the God of the Sea!