Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World, Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island,
where the New Fishman Pirates
who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil.
Friends or foes? That's something...
...you'll have to decide on your own!
"A Big Clash! The Straw Hats vs. A Hundred Thousand Enemies!"
S-So he's the Straw Hat Luffy who invaded Navy HQ twice, 2 years ago!
A pirate ship is here, too!
So are all the Straw Hats!
Silly Straw Hat! I can't believe he was hiding in the shark's mouth!
I thought that skeleton and the others were captive in the Ryugu Palace.
--We've been waiting for you, Straw Hat! --H-He really came!
Madame Sharley! The pirate with a hat just showed up!
He saved the King and the Princes!
Straw Hat boy...
Did I do okay, Jinbe?
It wasn't so disastrous, considering it was Luffy.
Mm-hm. Although it did not go exactly as we had planned...
A FEW HOURS AGO--SEA FOREST
Outta my way!
No, I won't let you go!
Luffy-chin... Boss Jinbe...
Hey, that's enough already!
E-Excuse me, but they are going to kill Father-sama!
I said "Outta my way"! I'm gonna go kick those guys' asses!
How many times do I have to tell you? I said "Wait"! Let me finish!
How would you describe our relationship?
We're friends!
That's right.
It's such a simple relationship but the Fishmen and humans couldn't establish it
and have been struggling to do so for years.
When I left you the message "Don't fight against Hody,"
I meant "Don't fight him recklessly."
Don't rush!
If you just go and beat Hody up,
people on the island will think that you are just another violent human bully.
Instead,
I want you to become the hero who will save Fishman Island!
Hero?
No!
What?!
We're pirates!
I love heroes but I don't wanna be one!
Do you know what heroes are?
Say there is a chunk of meat.
Pirates will have a banquet and eat it
but heroes will share it with other people.
I want all the meat!
Is that how he defines a hero?
So it all comes back to meat again.
I will let you have your meat just as long as you do as I tell you!
Okay.
What?! That easy?!
In the simplest terms, I will call for your help so I want you to respond.
Help you?
Yes, first, Megalo and I will get caught voluntarily and enter the plaza.
While they are paying attention to us,
one of you sneak out of Megalo's stomach and...
Out of his stomach?
They will have the letter from the Celestial Dragons.
What letter?
Oh yeah.
Luffy was sleeping so he missed most of Jinbe's story.
It is...
...something Queen Otohime acquired 10 years ago, at the risk of her life
and it will define the future of this island!
And they will also have the key to free the King.
We need to get our hands on those 2 things.
Who is up to it?
I'm good at stealing! I can do it with Robin.
Yeah.
All right. Once you free the King, I will call for Luffy-kun's help.
And once Luffy-kun emerges gallantly, out of Megalo's body,
people will notice that Luffy-kun and I are working together.
Princess-sama, you wait somewhere completely safe outside of the plaza.
And after we pass you the letter, flee with the freed King and the Princes.
Meanwhile, the rest of you, get to the Ryugu Place now and save your friends.
And then, hurry to the plaza with them.
Now--about how to rescue your friends in the Ryugu Palace...
Figure it out yourself!
You don't care about us, do you?!
Okay! Super count on it!
We have the Sunny!
We'll figure it out!
Mm-hm.
Once this is all set into motion, how do you think the citizens will respond?
Both the citizens of Fishman Island
and the outlaws of the Fishman District respect Jinbe-san.
Uh-huh. So if they find out that Boss trusts Luffy-chin with his life, to save the King,
they'll root for you, Luffy-chin!
Straw Hat.
Luffy-sama.
I am only doing this because you asked me to, Jinbe!
It's uncomfortable having everybody cheer me on.
Yeah, we're not used to that treatment.
I'd fight the king of demons himself if the Mermaids-chan cheered for me!
Thank you!
That settles it.
Okay, let's do it!
Is there something else?
Should we pick a codename for this operation?
Who cares!
Alright, let's hurry up!
So you saved your friends at the Ryugu Palace successfully.
Straw!
Pappagu! I'm happy to see you again!
But, but, I've had quite a few brushes with death because of them!
Straw Hat Luffy is a human and a pirate
THE OUTSKIRTS OF CONCHCORDE PLAZA
but he's on our side, right?
Princess Shirahoshi called for his help!
It looks like he came to save this country with Boss Jinbe!
Straw Hat!
They love you so much.
But you only saved the King temporarily so don't push your luck!
You're just a human pirate!
Mermaid Princess-san, you're so beautiful!
Excuse me, could I look at your panties?
Don't ask the Princess that!
Then, show me yours.
Why should I?!
We're all together again finally!
They're ignoring you!
Well, that's because I said it in a small voice!
Nami-san! I rescued those idiots!
--Do you love me now? --Yeah, yeah.
You fool! We got to the exit on our own.
Uh-huh.
And you couldn't have done it without my help!
Pappagu helped them?!
No, before that, Brook became a ghost and...
Ghost?
That's right.
My newfound ability helped us!
I don't have much time! I need the key... I mean, the sword!
I don't have time...
Stay away, Ghost!
Pappagu-san!
Huh?
How did the ghost know my name?
It's me!
I don't have any ghost friends!
You're the Bone, aren't you?
The water is here finally!
What are you doing, Brook?! It's too late!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, welcome back.
Here, your sword!
Good job, Zoro-san!
Alright, Zoro, let's get out of here!
--Three-Sword Style! --What?!
You cut too much!
Oh yeah?
I can't swim anymore!
I-I need to breathe!
Damn!
I-I'm gonna die!
Zoro! Usopp! Brook!
Super we're here to pick you up!
We made it.
That's how it went.
Brook's new ability sounds awesome! Anyway...
Those guys got their captain beaten by Luffy.
How come they don't seem worried?
You're right. That's odd.
Here you go.
It's the letter from the Celestial Dragons.
Thank you all!
This is the hope of Fishman Island, that Mother-sama left behind.
But I think it's not safe for Wimpyhoshi.
Mm-hm, her capture was not a part of our plan.
Neither was asking her to escape on her own.
Luffy-sama, what did you just call me?
You were calling me "Wimpy" before.
Yeah, it's not like I know everything but you're not as timid as I thought you were.
So I'll call you Wimpyhoshi from now on!
It's understandable why someone would hate those who they think wronged them.
That man who insulted you...
That's exactly what he's doing.
But a coward couldn't have been so strong
and borne such hardship on her own for this long.
She is right.
Princess Shirahoshi, it must have been hard for you through the years.
I'm sorry.
I caused you trouble because I kept it secret.
It's okay. I like you just the way you are now.
No passing on hatred to the next generation.
That's what those brave heroes were trying to teach us.
Don't tell the people on the island anything!
Don't let resentment or hatred get the better of you for my sake.
There is a small "sprout" that bloomed in your heart.
If all people on the island share it and think the same way as you do one day,
there will be no more fighting and the conflict
between Fishmen and humans will be over.
I don't think the years you suffered through were meaningless.
You must have been trying so hard to protect...
...that small "sprout" single-handedly, day after day.
But let us protect it for you this time.
Y-Yes!
Thank you very much!
She may not be a coward but she sure is a crybaby!
Straw Hat! Kick the crap out of them!
Vander Decken was so useless!
I needed him to get rid of Shirahoshi.
Captain Hody!
The Energy Steroid is still working as I thought.
No wonder. He took a lot of them.
Captain's back!
She's the legendary Mermaid Princess with that troublesome power.
So I needed to take out Shirahoshi as soon as possible, but...
...you people duped me completely.
Jinbe.
I should have noticed when you gave in without resistance.
You're quite taken with these humans, aren't you?!
I despise your kind the most!
Fisher Tiger who you grew up together with in the Fishman District
and Arlong who was like a brother to you, were both beaten or killed by humans!
But instead of seeking revenge for them, you joined hands with humans!
You are as gutless as Neptune!
When I become king of the island, I'll change everything!
This year's World Summit is a perfect opportunity!
I'm gonna kill the human kings from all over the world at Mary Geoise
and the legend of a terrifying underwater kingdom will begin!
We'll drag all humans in the world into the water and enslave them!
Eventually, no one will be able to stand against Fishmen.
Even in the world of pirates!
All pirates will fall down on their knees before us--the New Fishman Pirates!
Look at these human pirates with confidence in their ability to fight!
You will all be like them, Straw Hat!
I'll be the one who becomes Pirate King!
The Pirate King?
You're just a band of 10 half-assed pirates. You can't do anything!
We have 100,000 on our side!
Th-There are so many of them.
Straw Hat and Boss Jinbe have only 10 people. Are they gonna be okay?
If they lose, Hody will take over Fishman Island!
And we will be kicked out of our home!
Beat them up! Straw Hat! Boss Jinbe!
Straw Hat!
Kill them all, New Fishman Pirates!
Here come 100,000 enemies! How can we fight them?!
It's impossible!
This is why I don't wanna get involved with you guys!
Before we fight, we could get squashed.
Squash?! No!
100,000 enemies?! I'm so stunned - my eyes will pop out!
But I don't have eyes to pop out!
100,000 is nothing! Let's do this!
Don't hide behind us while you say that!
Here I go! My time has come!
Super Armored Me!
All right! Bring it on!
There are 10 of us.
So we each have to beat 10,000 of them.
They outnumber us but it doesn't mean they're stronger.
It's not like they're elite Navy soldiers. So don't shit yourself.
What did you say, you stupid Mosshead?!
Bring it on, you Bloody-nosed, Two-bit Chef!
Hey, Luffy!
L-Luffy-kun!
Luffy-sama?
That 400 million berry prize is mine!
No, mine!
No way!
Kill him!
What's going on here?!
He didn't do anything but so many of us got knocked out!
Hey, stand up, guys!
Damn! He beat half of us in a single moment!
That means 50,000 people in an instant? What did he do?!
What's going on?
Wh-What? What just happened?
He's so strong. That Straw Hat boy...
The Straw Hat pirate did it?!
Cool, Straw Hat!
That was Haki!
He's gotten much stronger in just 2 years.
That was Conqueror's Haki? So he was capable of that, as I thought.
That's what I needed from my captain. Otherwise, he needs to step down.
That was amazing! Luffy-sama!
You're Hody, right? I guess I have to kick your ass.
You can become king of whatever you want in any country.
But there can only be one Pirate King!
The Straw Hats have begun their all-out battle against the New Fishman Pirates.
Surrounded by Hody's superior numbers,
they must protect Shirahoshi from the relentless assault.
And the new attacks developed over two years
by Zoro and Sanji will erupt!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Deadly Attacks One After Another! Zoro and Sanji Join the Battle!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!