Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After landing on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen,
the Straw Hats learned about the hideous experiments
performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
and headed off to investigate.
What?
An alliance?
I have a plan...
...to bring down one of the Four Emperors!
It's Formed!
Luffy and Law's Pirate Alliance!
An alliance?
Are you saying that if we work together, we can take down an Emperor?
How absurd!
I don't know what he wants but don't listen to this jerk's fast-talk, Luffy!
I'm not saying we can beat the Emperor straight away.
All I'm saying is we'd get a chance if we advance the plan step by step.
What do you say, Straw Hatter?
Which of the Four Emperors are you talking about?
Hey Luffy, why are you interested?!
We can't trust this guy!
The Emperor's name is...
I see.
Okay, let's do it!
What?!
What?!!
THE STRAW HATS' ENCAMPMENT
What?!
We're gonna form an alliance with the Heart Pirates?!
You just went out to reclaim Nami!
So how did you come back with such an eccentric idea?!
Listen...
If we ally ourselves with this creep who gives me the chills,
I won't be able to sleep in peace at night!
See, Luffy? Everybody's against it.
Let's not do it. It's too risky.
We wanna travel at our own pace.
She's right, Luffy!
Besides, it's too early to even think about the Four Emperors!
We can't fight them yet!
Hey, treat this raccoon dog.
Forget about some raccoon dog now!
Huh?
What?!
It's me!
Z-Zuber...
What happened?! My body!
Luffy.
I'm gonna go along with your decision
but alliances between pirates are often marked by betrayal.
Maybe it's dangerous for you since you are so trusting.
Huh? Are you gonna betray me?
No.
Hey, have at least a little doubt!
Anyhow, a pirate alliance sounds like fun, doesn't it?
I think Tra-guy is a good man but...
...even if he isn't, don't worry!
Because I have you guys who spent the last two years training!
What?!
Luffy, you're...
D-Don't mention it! Luffy, you're making me blush!
Yeah, I know we're zuper dependable but...
We just do what we got to do!
You're not flattering me, you fool!
A-Alright, Luffy! You can count on us!
If Zoro and the others wimp out, I'll convince them!
I'm counting on you guys!
Room.
Shambles.
I got it back! My great body!
I knew I liked myself the best when I'm me!
Super!
I'm happy for you, Franky!
Don't ever take Chopper's body again. Ever.
I'm...
...back to myself, too, but...
Why are there cuts and bruises all over my body?!
What did you guys do to it?!
--I'm sorry. It's his fault. --I'm sorry. It's his fault.
Why?! You went out of control in Chopper's body
so I had no choice but to stop you!
But you didn't have to use the same technique you used
to beat the Kraken!
I blame both of you!
--I'm sorry! --I'm sorry!
You should be happy just being back to yourself, Chopper.
Why do I have to be in someone else's body again?
First, it was Franky and now, Sanji-kun!
Nami became Sanji!
You're looking good!
It wouldn't be funny if it happened to you!
It can't be helped.
Chopper and Franky could
go back to themselves because their bodies were here
but since Sanji went out looking for the samurai in Nami's body,
you have no choice but take Sanji's body.
Can't you do something about it?!
I can't do anything without your body here.
These are the children?
Yeah, I wanna help them.
I'm giving them this drug candy everyday.
They're such a pain - just forget about them.
I heard they're drugged.
We know! Because I tested them!
I just wanna take them home
but it'll take a while for them to recover
and most importantly, they are so big.
Boy, I can't believe somebody's doing such a horrendous experiment.
Turning people into giants is a project that has been underway for
hundreds of years by the World Government.
The Government? For what purpose?
Military might, probably.
If they can produce an infinite amount of giant soldiers,
they'll become invincible.
Caesar wants to achieve the goal first
and outsmart the Government and Vegapunk
but I don't think it's that easy.
Do you really wanna help them?
You don't even know who they are.
Yes, I do. Although I don't know them well,
they asked me to help with tears in their eyes.
It seems like the Master tricked them and brought them here
but they already know there is something wrong with this place.
Until I know that they are safe, I won't leave this island!
Are you willing to stay here alone?
I'm not gonna leave my friend behind.
If that's what Nami and Chopper want, I want it, too.
And Sanji wants to stick the samurai's body together.
You got to help us if you wanna team up with us!
I thought so. You have no idea.
You think an alliance is...
...a cooperative relationship just for some common goal, don't you?
Of course, I do.
Listen. Luffy's idea of an alliance is a little different from yours.
It's like being friends, isn't it?
If you're thinking of taking control, it won't be that easy, either.
That's what they say.
Once he feels sure about something, he won't back down.
It's a pain in the ass!
His selfishness is as formidable as the Four Emperors.
That must be hard.
But what your friends want has nothing to do with us at all...
Hey! Don't throw your booger at me, fool!
Oh, sorry!
I can't move right now!
Sorry, sorry!
Okay, I understand. There is not much time.
You guys have to take care of the samurai.
I'll look into the drug that the kids were taking.
Who is your ship's doctor?
He's got to come with me and help me research it behind Caesar's back.
Okay, this is good.
I'm sorry but I can't walk right now so, thanks!
D-Don't drop him, Tra-guy!
Sorry! I shouldn't laugh! But...
Super cute!
Good luck, Chopper.
Count on me!
THE BURNING LANDS
1, 2, 3!
Alright, it's unlocked!
What do they keep in this warehouse?
What's that?
I can't see. It's too dark.
What happened?
Are you mad?
As you can tell from the assassins earlier,
Caesarer wants to get rid of you guys and Asher's G-5
and take back those children.
Until he gets what he wants, he won't stop attacking.
He is a former Government scientist,
who became a criminal four years ago.
If the fact somebody is here on this restricted island leaks out,
he will lose this perfect hiding place.
That's why he'll try to kill you all at any cost.
A 300-million-berry bounty.
A Logia-type Gas-Gas Fruit eater who owns
weapons of mass destruction.
That's who Caesar Clown is.
300 million?
Those of you who can't use Haki, stay away from him.
He's not just a scientist.
Those who can use Haki among us are me and Zoro and Sanji.
And you.
I think that's enough.
I'm gonna go back to the lab now.
So what we're gonna do is kidnap the Master, right?
Yes, that's it.
But why should we kidnap him?
Money? I thought the Master guy is their boss.
Who else can pay us a ransom?
We're not gonna do it for money. Just to raise havoc.
--Havoc? --What do you mean?
There's no point to tell you
what lies ahead before we even kidnap him successfully.
Focus on capturing Caesar Clown for now.
It's not gonna be easy.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
I'll tell you all the details of my plan after that. However,
when we kidnap Caesar successfully,
things will start moving whether you like it or not.
There will be no turning back.
This is the last chance for you to reconsider.
That's okay. We're with you.
Then, I will go along with what you guys want to do.
You need to convince the rest of your crew.
Yeah, I got it!
CAESAR CLOWN'S LABORATORY - THE FRONT
You bastard! Damn you creature!
"Rebar" Smoothie!
Fen Bock of the Gourd!
"Rope-Tugging" Chappe!
Smoker-san! They are former prisoners as we thought!
Just looking a little different.
What's going on here?
Then why did they say none of the prisoners survived four years ago?!
Smo-san, what are those people?!
How should I know?!
In any case, just hold them back!
We have to put the ship to sea...
...to make a report!
Shoot! Shoot!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Master, the Transponder Snail is ringing.
You don't have to take it.
They probably want to report they opened the door.
"And something came out."
"It attacked our comrades. Help us."
They'll just go on like that. Quite annoying.
We don't often have this many visitors here.
You can stop gathering test subjects now.
What?
Hello?! Master?! Hello?!
Please come in!
We're in the Burning Lands! We opened the door as you said!
No good! The Master is not picking up!
It's coming! What is that?!
It came out of the building!
It killed all of our comrades! Just run!
--Wh-Which way?! --Th-This way!
What is that thing?! It's bigger than a mountain!
It's coming! Help me!
Master!
Let me tell you about my pet.
It's a very rare slime-type creature.
Master...
No one...
...can leave this island!
How does it feel to be loose after so long,
Smiley?!
The ultimate weapon that Caesar created...
While its identity is slowly coming to light,
the Straw Hats make their move to capture Caesar.
However, Luffy's actions cause the situation to go in an unexpected direction.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Capture Master
The Pirate Alliance's Plan Commences!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Capture Master
The Pirate Alliance's Plan Commences!