Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Yuba
Erumalu
Nanohana
Katorea
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a mighty swell.
Erumalu
Yuba
Nanohana
After parting with Ace, Luffy and company continue to trek
Katorea
through the vast desert as they hurry to Yuba.
As for whether they can stop
the beleaguered rebel army...
...the setting sun watches over them silently.
Ruins and Lost Ways!
Vivi, Her Friends,
and the Country's Form
Looks like he's back with us.
Huh?
Are you finally sane again?
You're such a nuisance.
Huh? Wha? Huh?
Where are the others?
Dunno.
Huh? You don't know?
I'm not sure, to be more precise.
Don't be funny.
This is no time to be laughing!
Yeah.
So we're lost again?
Whose fault do you think that is?!
Wha? M-My fault?
– Get back here, Crocodile!
– Huh?
– What's he freaking out about?
– I'm gonna kick your butt!
– Plus he's flying...
– Did he eat another weird cactus?
Ugh! Can't he ever not cause trouble?!
Chopper!
I don't think he can help.
Oh, geez. Alright, Zoro. It's up to you.
Why me?!
Want me to talk more about your debt?
If you don't end up in hell,
I'm gonna kick you down there myself!
I look forward to it!
Okay! Let's get going!
Eh? Shouldn't we wait for them?
They can just follow our footprints.
With their strength, they'll catch up in no time.
We can wait somewhere relaxing.
Agreed...
Will they really be all right?
You idiot! Wake up!
Urgh!
Stick him with a needle or something, quick!
O...kay...
Come on, now...
Can't count on anyone!
Crocodile!
I found you!
What're you talking about?!
I'm gonna...
– You dumbass! Don't make me...
– ...kick your butt!
Gum-Gum...
...wake you up!
...Submarine!
Even though this happens every single time...
...stopping him when he's gone crazy is a pain!
Urgh!
How did I wind up following a captain like this?
Oww! Hot!
What am I...?!
What are you doing?!
What's going on?!
What in the world happened?!
Hey! Zoro! Hey!
Get up!
A restorative!
Thanks...
What were you doing?!
Stuff...
He's still buried.
Leave him be for now.
Where are the others?
They were gone when I came to...
Those coldhearted bastards!
But that's alright.
We can just follow their footprints.
Umm, footprints?
Say what?!
You're actually Crocodile?!
Don't be stupid!
Huh? We got separated?
You moron!
Why didn't we go after them sooner?!
That would be because of you!
Chopper! You smell things good!
I'm already trying.
But I don't smell anything at all.
Then we have no clues at all?
Which way is the wind blowing from?
I don't know the direction,
but it's coming from our left.
Left, huh?
That at least means they didn't go that way.
You're just makin' that up.
Shut up! Stay here if that's what you want!
Let's go, Chopper!
Yeah...
C'mon, wait for me!
Don't leave me behind!
So hot...
Will be he all right?
He's not the kind to kick the bucket so easily.
Say.
Yeah?
Is pirate life always like this?
Like what?
Always climbing snowy mountains, crossing deserts...
Ain't that the truth?
But we're just a little out of the ordinary.
Plus there's our captain.
I think I might've gotten on
board a not-so-good ship...
What a coincidence.
I was just thinking the same thing myself.
Say.
Huh?
You're the most veteran
crew member here, right?
I guess, but there's not that much of a difference between us.
Why did you join?
Why do you ask?
To me, since I just joined,
it seems like everyone's a maverick.
Especially you.
That's true. In my case, things pretty much just turned out this way.
The others are the same.
Our real goals are different from his.
We're trying to do what we want to do.
It's crazy.
It's just like someone said before.
On the outside, we have no teamwork at all.
Especially given our captain.
He's a real handful.
I think so, too.
But, really, what is teamwork?
Is helping each other and
protecting each other enough?
Some people say so,
but, sorry, that only sounds
like they're fooling themselves.
I think teamwork only begins
when everyone risks their lives
to do what they can and then says,
"I did it! You're up next!
If you can't do it, I'll kill you!"
When you think about it that way,
what's wrong with having
mavericks as companions?
That's my opinion, anyway.
So that's what Usopp meant by,
"Just do what you can!"
It sounds like BS when he says it, though.
As for why I still stay with him...
...being by his side all this time's
given me another goal to strive for.
Another goal?
Sorry. I dunno how to answer about it.
I found shade!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Whoo!
It's nice and cool!
I oughta chop you apart!
Oh! My bad! My bad!
Huh? Where's Chopper?
Oh! There he is!
What's he doing out there?
Is he trying to act funny?
Yes. It was my fault. I'm sorry.
Geez!
What was the point of that conversation—
Hey.
I didn't know you were a comedian.
I'm not!
Oh! You're okay?
Dammit! That hurts!
What is this place?
What's this?
What is this?
What's something like this...
...doing underground?
Why are you down here?!
I used my arms.
I'm asking why!
Just 'cause.
You idiot!
With you down here too,
we might get separated from Chopper!
Without him, we'll never meet
up with Vivi and the others!
Oh! That's okay!
Why is that?!
Because Chopper was falling down here too!
See?
Oww...
What is this place?
Heya. You seem to be alright.
Zoro! Luffy! Where is this place?
No idea.
But whatever it is, it's definitely underground.
Underground?
I'm exhausted!
Let's take a short break!
Yes, Nami-san!
C'mon! You're pathetic!
Easy for you to say! You rode Lashes!
We gotta walk the whole way!
Thanks, Lashes!
Vivi?
Will Luffy-san and the others know where to find us?
I think they'll be fine.
We're on top of a hill.
It stood out clearly, even from far away.
I hope so...
Say. How much further to Yuba?
Seeing as we made it to these ruins,
we should be there by night
if we continue walking.
Close, at last...
Oh? So these are ruins?
Yes.
I believe they're from quite an old era.
Civilizations first began here thousands of years ago.
Many kingdoms have risen and fallen.
Resettlement in search of water,
the occasional war...
Ruins of such things remain
all throughout this land.
Many are full of mystery.
And time flowed on, leading to
the Alabasta dynasty of today?
That's an epic story.
A prosperous kingdom, destined to disappear...
It's almost romantic.
Sanji-kun!
Sorry, Vivi-chan!
I didn't mean it like that!
It was just, you know, a figure of speech...
It's all right.
I've often felt the same way as of late.
Just what is a country?
Even if the ruler of a land changes,
its people will keep on living.
Culture, lifestyle...
If those stay the same even
when a country changes,
I wonder if it's really necessary
to struggle to protect the country.
Certainly, there are other
things that need protecting.
Ever since the sand pirates and the
town with the fake rebel soldiers,
I've been thinking that way a lot.
I'm sorry! That's just me being strange!
I haven't found the answers either!
But I do know what we must do now!
Baroque Works' scheming is about
to cause a meaningless war!
We must stop it, at all costs!
What they're trying to do is throw this land into ruin!
I don't care if it leaves a
dark splotch in our history!
I absolutely refuse to let Crocodile have his way!
Well, we should get going!
Usopp-san! Are you all right?!
Are you kidding?
I can't control the strength welling up in me!
Liar.
Oh, shut up!
They'll stop in a second!
I'll show you how gutsy Manly Usopp is!
I'll never fall to my knees easily!
What's the big idea?!
– You fell easily.
– Well, we should get going, Vivi.
Eh? But what about Luffy-san?
You're such a worrywart.
He says he's going to kick Crocodile's butt.
Once he has a clear goal,
you can let him do his own thing.
You know that!
Yes!
My eyes've adjusted.
On closer look, we're inside a giant dome.
Built by people, no less.
Huh?
These are probably ancient ruins or something.
How can you tell?
Look at this.
See all the picture-like writing on this wall?
I saw it in a book or something before.
These are ancient letters.
Who cares about that stuff?
It's so nice and cool in here!
If you're right, then what is
this place doing underground?
I don't really know...
Was it built underground, or did
it get buried after it was built?
Either way, I get the feeling they
were trying to hide this building...
Dunno who did it, but they sure worked hard.
In any case, it's none of my business,
and it doesn't interest me.
What we gotta do now is get the
hell outta here. Right, Captain?
Really? But it's cool in here.
Just get up!
No! No! Let's stay here a little longer!
It's hot outside!
Okay! Time to get outta here!
We gotta meet up with the others!
So that's Zoro's comedy hole?
Shut up!
Alright! Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
What are you doing?
Darn it!
I missed 'cause the target's so small!
Alright! Got it!
Again, what are you trying to do?!
Just grab onto the boulder above the hole!
This is getting annoying!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Alright! All better!
Are you crazy?!
What are you gonna grab on to
now that you broke that boulder?!
It's okay! I got an idea!
Huh?!
Chopper. You should probably turn little.
Huh?
Gum-Gum...
Oh, now I see...
Grab on!
Just give it up. This is the only way!
Okay.
Here goes!
...Spring!
Yahoo!
How are we going to land?!
Heck if I know!
You don't mean...?!
I told you to just give it up!
Nobody mentioned this!
Successful escape!
Where'd they go?
Oh, there they are!
I think I did choose the wrong ship to ride on...
We're on the same wavelength today...
I was just thinking the same thing...
Usopp. You're falling behind.
What happened to showing how gutsy you are?
I-I only said that out of spirit...
Hang in there! Just a little further!
Still worried?
Oh, no...
It's written all over your face.
I'm sorry. I do have faith in them, but...
I'm guessing you'll never get over being a worrier.
But that has its good points, too.
You people are amazing.
Eh?
I've felt that way ever since Little Garden.
How can you have so much faith in your friends?
How?
It's not something I'm conscious of.
I've never even thought about it.
That's what's amazing.
Having unconditional faith in someone.
That's not very easy to have.
Hmm.
I'm not really sure, but maybe it's because
we all do what we can as best as we can?
A while back, he said something on the island I lived on.
I don't know how to use swords, you bastard!
I don't know how to sail the oceans!
I can't cook!
I can't lie, either!
Hey, now!
I'm confident that I can't live without help!
I remember those words very well...
I thought,
"Oh, this is how these pirates are..."
Alone, there's a limit to your strength.
Sometimes, things you really want
to do are too much for one person.
You need friends.
But it amounts to nothing if those
friends don't do what they can.
Whoops! Sorry that wasn't an answer!
Thank you!
I can't keep my thoughts straight in this heat!
That answered plenty.
Yes...
That may be one of this country's forms.
Hey! Hurry up!
Of course he gets energetic
when it starts to cool off...
What is it?
The wind has changed direction.
I smell something!
What?!
No doubt about it! It's Nami's perfume!
It's this way!
Way to go! Luffy!
We found Nami and the others!
In the sunset direction!
For reals?!
Hey! Guys!
Don't rush off on your own!
We'll get separated again, you moron!
When I'm with them,
I start to see many things...
These people may have the answer!
Kodomo no koro yume mita boukenka mitai de
Like the adventurers I dreamed of when I was a child
Omoi no hate ni tsurenatte yuku yo
I continue on to the ends of emotion
Sukuiageta tenohira kara
I scoop up my hands,
koboreochiru suna to jikan
and the sand and time that spills from them
Kono tame ni umarete kita to oshiete kureru
show me that this is what I was born to do
Korogeochisou na supido de
Let's continue swimming
Bokura oyogitsuzukeyou
at a near-tumbling speed
Soshite dare mo
Until we wash up someday
shiranai shirahama he itsuka
on a white sandy beach
Uchiagerareru made
no one knows about
Did we make it to Yuba?!
I can't tell with all this sand!
The city doesn't look right!
This is horrible!
Wasn't this an oasis?!
The sand has raised the ground!
The oasis has been swallowed up!
And there doesn't seem to be any water...
The rebel army doesn't seem to be here!
I will stop the revolt!
Next time, on One Piece:
Spiders Café at 8 O'Clock!
The Enemy Leaders Gather
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Spiders Café at 8 O'Clock!
The Enemy Leaders Gather