Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
rashinban nante jyuutai no moto
compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
delirious with fever, i take the helm
hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
if the dusty treasure map has been verified,
tashikameta no nara densetsu janai
it's not a legend!
kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
when it comes to personal storms,
biorizumu nokkatte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
omoi sugoseba ii
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
poketto no koin
a coin in my pocket,
soreto You Wanna Be My Friend
and do you wanna be my friend?
We Are
we are!
The look in Arlong's eyes changed!
You inferior human!
What did you do to me, a Fishman?!
A Shark Saw!
That room is...
You can no longer escape.
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
What's this room?
Full of papers...
These're not just ordinary papers.
This room is where I make that
woman draw sea charts. It's...
...the survey room!
Nami's room...
These're all sea charts that Nami drew.
She's good.
She draws quite accurate sea charts.
In the past, as well as in the future,
her talent should be used for us Fishmen!
Nami is our friend.
Friend?
So don't interfere anymore...
...you damn rubber man!
What's that look in your eyes?!
She is...
Nami is...
...our navigator!
End of the Fishman Empire!
Nami's My Friend!
You plan to make her the
navigator of some shabby boat?
You'd only end up wasting her talent.
Just look! How many people in this
world can draw such accurate charts?
The girl has a gift.
There's nothing as unfortunate and foolish
as letting a natural-born talent go to waste.
Staying here and drawing sea charts
is the greatest happiness for her!
This pen is stained with blood...
Nami's charts are absolutely vital
if I'm to attain world supremacy!
She's going to continue drawing sea charts!
For my ambition!
And once her charts give me full
knowledge of all the world's seas...
we Fishmen will be invincible,
and the world will become our empire!
Our first stepping stone is this island... and the East Blue!
Could you use the girl as efficiently as that?!
Huh?!
The Shark Saw won't move one bit!
What?!
"Use"?!
What's goin' on inside?!
Dammit...
What happened, Big Bro Luffy?!
I can't tell what's going on up there at all...
Luffy...
What do you take her for?!
An inferior creature, but a smart girl.
If all other humans are sewer rats,
I'd say she's a cheeky-as-hell cat.
After all, she is adorable.
And I'm going to keep on feeding
her and buying clothes she likes.
She'll have everything she needs to live.
All she needs to do is
keep drawing charts for me.
She will forever be my tool...
...no, my friend.
What's that?!
A desk...
It's a desk!
W-Whew, just a desk.
Man, that scared me.
I thought it was Big Bro Luffy for sure...
Hold on, partner!
Are you sayin' you don't have
faith in Big Bro Luffy's strength?!
Huh?! You were scared too, Johnny!
D-Don't be stupid!
I was, uhh, you know...
O-Of course I thought it was that damn Arlong!
Huh?!
That sounds kinda fake if you ask me!
Say what, you jerk?!
Of course there's no way Big Bro Luffy'd lose!
Luffy?
What do you think you're doing?!
What in the...?!
There's an awful lot of stuff flying!
Alright! As of today, this is your room!
Your desk, your pens...
Everything you'll need is here!
Stop that!
The charts!
M-My charts!
You damn brat!
Don't think you can trick me,
drawin' fake charts like that!
Do you have the time to be
drawing crap like this in secret?
Try to fool me again and I'll drag
people from the village one by one
and make you watch as I crush them!
Just like I did with her!
Damn you!
I spent eight years making her draw those!
I invested eight years in those charts!
In my ambition!
Bellemere-san...
Nojiko...
This... is a pretty intense fight!
Yeah! Looks like a fight to the death!
Definitely!
Thank you...
You've gone too far, you damn rubber man!
"Fishmen are great" and "sea charts" this,
"circumstances" that...
I don't know much about any of that stuff...
But I finally figured out how to save her!
She can't go because this room is here!
If she doesn't want to be here,
then I'll just destroy it all!
Gum-Gum...
Don't get cocky!
Arlong Park can't ever be brought
down by you inferior beings!
Shark Tooth Drill!
...Battle-Axe!
L-Look!
That shock's caused Arlong Park to...!
Impossible! It's gonna collapse!
This is dangerous! Everyone, get away!
Big Sis Nami! Hurry!
But Luffy's still inside!
Big Sis!
Luffy! Luffy's still...!
Luffy!
I finally figured out how to save her!
She can't go because this room is here!
If she doesn't want to be here...
...then I'll just destroy it all!
Luffy!
Luffy...
Oww!
What's all this damn noise?
Luffy...
Arlong Park... has collapsed!
Big Bro...
What on earth happened inside?
Which one won?!
Given all this debris...
Don't tell me it was...!
Luffy...
Luffy!
Big Bro!
Is he okay?!
Nami!
You're my friend!
Yeah!
H-He won?!
He won...
He won!
He won!!
Arlong Park has fallen!
We did it, older sister!
Gen-san!
This... This isn't a dream, is it?
I never thought this day would come...
Way to go, Luffy!
You get my praise, too!
Though I'd be praising you even more
if you would've been the
star performer instead of me!
Man, talk about being on pins and needles...
Take care of things quicker
from now on, you damn jerk!
This is awesome!
Hold it right there, you!
He's...!
What a lucky day today is!
Well done. I watched the entire fight.
Fluke as it was, I never once
imagined the Fishmen would lose
to a bunch of nameless pirates like you.
However, thanks to you,
all the money I was to give Arlong
and all the money and valuables
stored in Arlong Park are now mine!
Everyone drop your weapons!
I, Colonel Nezumi of Navy Branch #16,
hereby take credit for what you've done here!
Zoro!
Don't ruin people's fun when they're finally happy!
J-Just you try laying a finger on me!
You'll be sorry!
He's still sayin' it?
This is for shooting Nojiko
and tearing up Bellemere-san's tangerine orchard.
Huh?
Colonel!
Thanks, Nami! That felt good!
Give 'im 1,000 more of those!
You guys are gonna clean up after those Fishmen now!
And you're gonna help rebuild the town of Gosa!
And you're not gonna touch any
money or valuables in Arlong Park!
That's the island's money! Got it?!
Oww! Oww! I-I'll do what you say!
And one other thing!
Give me my money back!
I'll give it back! I'll give it back!
I don't care anymore...
I'll get you, you rotten pirates!
Straw hat man!
Your name's Luffy, right?!
You're the captain, right?!
Don't forget this!
Some major stuff's gonna happen to you now!
You've made me mad!
It's too late to regret what you've done!
I'm gonna get revenge on you!
Just you wait and see!
Says some major stuff's gonna happen now.
How does he know I'm gonna be the Pirate King?
That's not what he means!
Man, you're stupid!
H-Hey, what do we do?!
What if we really do wind up in big trouble?!
Hey! Hey! Hey, I said!
Alright, everyone! This is no time
for us to be the only ecstatic ones!
We need to tell everyone on the
island about this big incident!
Arlong Park...
Arlong Park has fallen!
Good for you, Nami!
To think we'd end up being saved by pirates...
You never know what's gonna happen next.
You seem to be in excellent spirits,
pathetic humans!
As of this moment,
this village- no, this island-
is now under my control!
Gen-san! Help!
Keep your hands off the children!
T-That's an Arlong tattoo!
You...!
You can stop now...
You fought very well, carrying our
lives on your back all this time...
Gen-san...
And then it went boom!
We didn't know each other long!
Now, Bellemere's spirit can finally go to heaven...
Hello?! Hello?!
Yes. This is Navy Headquarters.
Headquarters?! Navy Headquarters?!
Hello!
This is Colonel Nezumi of Navy Branch #16!
Marine Code 00733!
I have a request for HQ!
You don't need to shout.
I can hear you.
Listen! There's a pirate named Luffy,
who wears a straw hat!
I deem him and his four crew members
as enemies of the government!
"Luffy"...
They managed to take down Arlong,
the Fishman of Arlong Park who
was purported to be invincible!
Based on their threat and dangerousness,
a large bounty has been placed
on their captain, Straw Hat Luffy!
Now sending a photograph!
Roger that.
Huh?!
Couldn't you have taken a better one than that?!
No, that's all I could get...
After a quick verification,
I will submit it for approval.
Don't forget, now!
He's a vile pirate! "Dead or Alive"!
Put him on wanted posters throughout the world!
hamidashita kimochi tsunagara nakute
my overflowing feelings don't connect
kimi no te o gyutto ni girikaesu yo
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
hitori demo boku wa arukidasu kara
I'll set off by myself,
tooku made zutto mitsumeteite ne
so keep watching me intently as I go into the distance
kesa kara chotto kangaeteita
I was thinking about it a bit since this morning
doushite konna ni atsui no
why is it so hot?
itsu kara ka sonna koto bakari ga
starting from some point,
hanarenai yo
I haven't been able to get away from that
kakedashita kimochi tsukamaetakute
I want to catch those feelings that rushed off,
jibun sae mou oikoshite yuku yo
and I'm already about to overtake myself, even
tobidashita yume o dakishimetetai
I want to embrace my dreams that have jumped out
issho nara boku wa hashitte yukeru
with you, I can run there
It's finally goodbye to Cocoyashi Village!
Nami! Bet you're happy to be onboard
with Great Captain Usopp again!
You idiot!
Nami-san is joining me on a journey of love!
No! Raw ham melon!
Bellemere-san.
It took eight years, but we're finally free!
Next time, on One Piece:
Setting Out with a Smile!
Farewell, Hometown Cocoyashi Village
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Setting Out with a Smile!
Farewell, Hometown
Cocoyashi Village