All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
They learned about the ruler of the island and the puppeteer
of Land of the Dead - Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate ally - the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
were drawn into a climactic battle
which ended with Caesar's defeat.
Finally, they beat Doflamingo's subordinates
Baby 5 and Buffalo.
"A Touching Reunion! Momonosuke and Kin'emon!"
Listen, you damn pirates!
The tanker is yours!
And this is the line between good and evil!
So don't think of crossing it! Got that, Straw Hats?!
Who told you to do such a childish thing?
What I said was "Don't make friends with the pirates."
Then it's better to just shut them out, Vice Admiral Smo!
But it doesn't apply to the medics!
I got a connection to the G-5 base.
We're gonna wait to be picked up here.
Yes, sir!
What?!
Brownbeard, you're turning yourself in?!
We became friends after all.
Seems like he has performed poisonous drug
experiment on us, too, a little bit.
And they said they're gonna treat me if I allow myself to be arrested.
I see.
Hey hey, Straw Hat!
I just told you not to come across the line!
You're not listening!
I don't care! You guys just made it up!
Well,
it's better to go to prison than let
Caesar do whatever he wants to us.
And my people are all gone so...
It felt so good when I saw you knock Caesar out!
Thank you!
Here.
By the way, what are we making?
A stove.
It's so big.
We have so many people here.
I have to use a big pot so I need a big stove.
I see.
Oh, Kin'emon-san! It's so painful to see you like that!
I can't turn my eyes towards him! Even though I don't have eyes!
1, 2, 3!
Okay, pull!
1, 2! 1, 2!
Honestly! If we were gonna use this tanker,
you should've told me!
If I knew that I'd have to fix it,
I wouldn't have fought them here!
What?
Hand the children over to the Navy?
Yes!
They ended up
like that because the Navy was in charge!
Am I wrong?!
Because you people were irresponsible,
the children had to go through such a terrible time.
It must've been very painful for them.
I promised them!
Let's help these children!
You can't turn your back on a child crying for help!
I will save them!
So...
All I can do is apologize.
But I'll take full responsibility.
As for their treatment, I'll ask Vegapunk for assistance
and look after them until they're fully recovered.
And I'll take them to their parents safely at any cost!
So...
Please!
Leave the children up to me!
Law said "Whatever you do, don't look inside"
but I wonder if they are really okay?
What is he gonna do to them?
What's wrong?!
What?!
Why is he screaming? What's going on?
Luffy!
Y-You have to stop him!
What?
He's a murderer!
What?! A murderer?!
I am a murderer, too!
Who is a murderer?
It's Law!
Tra-guy?
What's going on there?
I-I murdered somebody, too!
I mean, Kin'emon-san was already dead but...
I broke his body!
He's dead and now broken?!
Dead and broken?!
Wh-Wh-What should I do?!
What can you do?!
He's broken - you can't do anything!
What if we stick them back together?!
Idiot! It's not gonna help!
Momonosuke!
Why are you alive?!
What are you doing, Sanji-san?!
I don't know!
You said he was dead but he was alive!
But you didn't have to kick him!
I did it on the spur of the moment. What's wrong with that?
It's all wrong.
Hey, look at him!
The guy who they thought was killed by the gas was alive!
I'm glad, Kin'emon-san!
I thought you were...
Father!
Mo...
Momonosuke!
Father!
I can't believe you're okay!
What? Momonosuke?
Oh yeah, he said he used to be a human.
So he was the Momonosuke-san
who Kin'emon-san had been looking for!
Uh-huh!
You are naked!
What?!
Poof!
A CHILD FROM WANO KINGDOM (KIN'EMON'S SON) - MOMONOSUKE
That's how a kid from Wano Kingdom looks!
You look good in a kimono!
But, Father,
how did you know that I was... here...
Momonosuke! Are you alright?!
I'm...
not hungry...
Momonosuke?!
Law! Show yourself, Law!
What did you do to the children?!
If you hurt them in any way, I...
That's why I told you not to look inside.
Those kids...
...I sliced them up.
It's a drug.
They still have to go through a long, painful treatment.
Oh, Raccoon Dog-chan!
Raccoon Dog-kun!
Is everybody okay?!
The young man with a fur hat just...
...Cut out the bad parts from our bodies!
What?
I was scared but I feel good now!
Our bodies' got all chopped up and it was fun!
I'm hungry!
I see.
Mocha hasn't woken up yet.
She fought for us, didn't she?
I had no idea that the Master was such a bad person.
I remember vaguely that
Mocha spewed up blood and passed out!
Hey, Raccoon Dog-kun.
I'm a reindeer.
Is she gonna be okay?
She can go home with us, right, Raccoon Dog-kun?!
Of course!
Let's get out of this nightmare and go home!
Where is the young woman with orange hair?
She said she's gonna take us home.
We want to say "Thank you" to her!
Hi!
We Navy are going to take care of you all from here!
What?! No!
--What about the robot?! --The bouncy guy?!
The spiral-eyebrowed guy?!
Smells good! I wonder what Sanji is making.
Can't wait!
Okay! Now it's standing straight!
Let's do a super quick fix!
Nami?
Have you come to terms with the Navy?
Uh-huh.
I'll leave them up to the Navy.
Even if I commit myself to saving them,
we're pirates. It could cause them trouble.
The most we can do
is get wrongly accused for kidnapping as always.
They're in better hands!
You're right. And...
...I have this thing for the eyes of female Navy soldiers.
Female soldiers?
Uh-huh.
They make me feel at ease.
Oh yeah!
Your mother was a Navy soldier, wasn't she?
It's always better to get help
from a strong, warm-hearted female soldier!
That's true!
You have no right to say it!
No, you said it!
New Kama Kenpo Secret Art:
99 Vital Recipes!
It'll boost up your cold, weary body!
Hormone soup with sea pork!
Since you guys haven't eaten for days,
start with the soup and eat it slowly.
Yum-yum!
You're starving, aren't you, Momo?
Sanji is the best cook!
I-I don't want it! I'm not hungry at all!
Hey, wait, you!
What're you gonna do with the bowl?!
Even if you're a kid, I can't stand anyone who wastes food!
I said I don't want it!
See? Your stomach is growling!
No, it's not! I'm not hungry and...
...I'm not gonna eat this!
Don't!
I'm going to eat!
What?
H-Hey!
Delicious!
What is this?! I feel like my energy's back!
Let me try this!
And this!
I can't believe how good this is!
Father...
Let's accept their kindness!
In fact, they saved my life!
You can trust them!
I can... trust them?
You haven't eaten anything until today, have you?
That's my son!
But it must've been hard!
You don't have to worry about anything anymore!
Let's hope that everybody else is okay, too!
Now,
let's keep living, Momonosuke!
Uh-huh.
Oh, is it so delicious that you can't help crying?!
Idiot!
They must've gone through something serious.
What happened to them?
Oh?
You jerks!
What happened to the line between good and evil?!
We call for a ceasefire, brother!
Then why don't you guys go
get some sake from the tanker?
Gotcha!
Juice, too!
Hey, Straw Hatter.
We have to leave in hurry.
We don't have much time to eat here
somebody's coming after us.
Really?
Tell your crew.
All right.
Guys!
Somebody's coming after us.
So...
...you gotta hurry!
It's a banquet!
Cheers!
No!
Stop!
Momonosuke, what are you doing?
Father.
Warriors shouldn't cry in front of people!
Momo!
What do you want, Luffy?
Hey, it's a banquet! Why are you crying?!
Laugh! Laugh!
Cheers, brother!
Yeah!
Look closely!
1, 2, 3!
Here.
Thank you!
It's good!
Get in the line if you wanna eat!
You can have more - there is a lot!
--It warms you up, doesn't it? --Uh-huh!
I see!
Then I won't let anybody eat the candy!
I wanna go home with everybody!
Mocha!
Law.
I'm sorry that I suspected you earlier.
He told me.
I got better because you treated me.
Thank you!
Vice Admiral Smo-yan!
We're heading back to the island!
What happened?
We made Caesar tell us about the weakness of the deadly gas!
Our colleagues are still alive! We can save them!
Why is Smoker still alive?
Let's go, guys!
Yeah!
Law.
I know you don't really think that I'll keep
my promise with a pirate like you.
But if you really wanted to silence me,
there were several occasions that you could've killed me.
What are you up to, taking advantage of Straw Hat?
I'm taking advantage of him?
Maybe he's taking advantage of me.
Which of the Four Emperors are you talking about?
The Emperor's name is...
...Kaido the "Beast King"!
What?!
As long as Shanks is not the first one to fight, I have no problem.
Because...
...I plan to beat all of the Four Emperors!