Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy hurries for Navy HQ in order
to stop his brother, Ace, from being executed.
Meanwhile, at Navy HQ on Marineford,
the world's greatest pirate, Whitebeard, has finally shown himself.
He cracked the air?
A seaquake! He's distorting the sea!
I won't...
Still some fight left in you?
You are too valuable to let die now, boy.
If you still wanna run wild,
run as wild as you want on the sea under my name.
Become my son!
Screw you!
Why...
...do you people call him Pops?
Because he calls us "sons."
We are all hated by the world.
So it makes us happy.
I know it's just a word.
But it still makes us happy.
The Power of the Tremor-Tremor Fruit
The Force That Could Destroy the World!
That's a lie! Cut it out!
You told me not to go but I...
I'm the one who told you to go.
I'm the one who told him to go.
Isn't that right, Marco?
Yes, that's what I heard.
I'm sorry that we put you through so much, Ace.
Everybody in this world knows.
What will happen to someone who messes with...
...our crewmate!
We won't let anybody
who hurts you get away with it, Ace!
Count on us! We will save you!
Prepare yourselves, Navy HQ!
We brought this upon ourselves.
It's too late to say such a thing.
That's so hideous.
On this side, we, the Warlords,
the Navy's greatest powers—3 admirals
and a hundred thousand elite soldiers!
On that side, there are the Whitebeard Pirates
and more than 40 allied ships!
Now, how do you wanna do it, Whitebeard?!
It's so exciting!
Do you wanna be on the sideline as always?
I know that you just came to kill some time.
So be it.
There are rowdy men everywhere and I can't stand it.
He is also a man but he is an exception.
I'm praying for you, Luffy!
H-Hey!
What's wrong?
The water is receding!
What does it mean?
What's going on?!
The ship is flying backwards!
Is this for real?!
It was really smooth just two minutes ago!
Why all of the sudden...
Oh no! My waterworks!
We've gotta keep moving!
What's going on here?
This must be...
F-Finally it stopped!
What was that all about?
We went back a good distance.
I wonder when we can get to Marineford like this.
Ow, ow, ow...
Wh-What was it?
Hey, Jinbe!
Can you hurry up? Please!
I gotta get there before Ace's execution!
Don't worry, Luffy-kun. We'll make it!
Okay.
Hey, hey!
How can you be so sure?
Roll-y roll-y.
You think your Fishman Karate can help?
Or are you gonna call out whale sharks to help again?!
My power is not enough.
Then, who are you depending on?
He said we'll make it! So we'll make it!
"He said we'll make it! So we'll make it!"
Fine! Whatever!
That's nonsense.
I'm gonna take a nap.
We can't stick around here any longer!
What happened to your dream
to become the King, Captain Buggy?
Well...
If the time is right,
I'm sure that there'll be a miracle.
But if it's too early,
then I'll just wait for the right timing.
Y-You're gonna just give up?
I'm disappointed in you!
Can't you see it?!
I mean, can't you see his magnificent confidence?!
No... It doesn't look like that to me.
This is what they call "perfect composure!"
He's got the regal presence to become the King!
Now that you mention it, I see it!
How great!
I can't see it at all...
I know that miracles don't happen that often.
But there is nothing I can do but wait.
Dammit!
The tide has changed!
We're going forward!
Did you do something?
I was just steering.
It's speeding up!
C-Could this be...?!
Ouch! What? What happened?!
Captain Buggy!
The miracle that you were talking about is about to happen!
I don't think so.
I don't know what's happening but this is it! Go!
Do you see it, guys?!
The time is calling me now!
Saying "come and become the King!"
You're so great! Like no other!
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
Great! It seems like we can make it!
H-Hey! Look at that!
Wh-What a hell is that?!
They've quieted down all of the sudden.
Are they waiting for Whitebeard's command?
I can hardly breathe!
The water level is rising again!
Wh-What's that?!
I can hear the ground rumbling!
Now it's coming!
The seaquake that he set up before!
Coming in the form of a tsunami!
The Tremor-Tremor Fruit made him a quake man!
Edward Newgate a.k.a. Whitebeard!
Look! What is that?!
It's a giant tsunami!
Don't think that our superior forces
will guarantee us victory.
We could well fail.
Because that man has...
...the power to destroy the world!
It's beginning! The war!
Let's go!
The invaders: a fleet of 47 ships
from the New World led by Whitebeard.
The defenders: the 2 greatest forces
of the Government—
Navy HQ and the Seven Warlords.
No matter who wins and who loses,
the times will change!
It's a tsunami!
What power!
He certainly is the legendary monster!
Ice Age!
Blue Pheasant!
You young squirt!
I-It's frozen!
Th-That was close!
Admiral Kuzan did it!
Partisan!
Uh-oh.
The whole bay is frozen!
The ships can't move now!
W-We have the greatest force
of Navy HQ—the admirals—on our side!
Th-That's right!
There's no reason to be afraid of the Whitebeards!
Fire! Destroy the Moby Dick!
Let's go!
We've got a good foothold now!
Show them what we're capable of!
The commanders came out, too!
Don't stop firing!
Mount a counter-offensive!
Yes!
He must be the 5th division commander—
Flower Sword Vista!
Stay alert, Tashigi!
They're all mighty soldiers—
not just the commanders! Don't forget it!
I-I got it, Smoker-san!
It's nice to have ice in the water!
Because my blood is burning!
Let's shoot them up and invade the island!
It's not that easy, huh?
Here come the vice admirals of Navy HQ!
It's so rare to see all of them together at the same place!
It's like when they have the Buster Call. But...
...when it comes to Pops
and us, it won't work that way!
Tsuru-san, why don't you stand back?
Leave it up to us
and have some tea or something from a comfortable distance.
Don't talk smart to me, fledglings!
There is no safe place
even if I back up to the end of the sea!
Bring the ship to the ice gorge!
Trounce them all and get to the land!
Go!
We'd be happy to give our lives for Pops!
We're not scared of Navy HQ!
Let's go, Squard Pirates!
It finally started!
Dracule Mihawk!
Is the Warlord on the move?!
That's very unusual!
The capricious Hawk-Eye seems like he's willing to fight.
What? Do you wanna fight?
I just want to figure out the true distance...
...between us and that man
who seems like right in front of us.
They say even the most skilled fighters
are struck by fear, left unable to move,
just by looking into his eyes.
"Hawk-Eye" truly suits him well.
I've always wanted to see him.
It's every swordsman's dream to cross swords with him.
Because he is assumed to be the strongest in the world.
That's the instinct of swordsmen!
So that's the Black Blade
that everybody's talking about.
To be precise...
...it's the Black Blade "Night!"
It's one of the only
Twelve Supreme Grade Swords in the world.
And its dark blade edge has an irregular temper line and a double clove pattern.
It's a noted sword suitable for the greatest swordsman.
Hawk-Eye!
Mihawk and Yellow Monkey launch their attacks on Whitebeard.
In response, the Whitebeard commanders
fight back using their own powers.
As the unpredictable battle rages,
Admiral Red Hound finally unleashes his incredible power!
Next time, on One Piece:
"An All-Consuming Inferno!! Admiral Red Hound's Power!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Admiral Red Hound's Power!
An All-Consuming Inferno!!