Luffy reunited with Toriko and his friends when he popped out of a Spring Shark.
The group headed to Chinese Tower Island,
an island full of healthy foods and natural cures,
in search of Seafood Fruit to cure Chopper's illness, Deep Sea Fever.
They worked together to defeat the fierce beasts on the island
and found the Seafood Fruit, which they fed to Chopper.
However...
Chopper's illness
was not cured.
Chopper!
"A Team is Formed! Save Chopper"
Isn't there anything we can do?
Well, since we don't know what caused it...
Why...
Why is the Sunny here?!
We flew here with the Coup de Burst.
These guys said there was a sea in the middle of the island.
Coco! Sunny!
Rin!
And even Kiss?!
Toriko! I was so worried!
Why are you guys here?
My fortune told me that danger was coming your way.
I thought it must be about you or Komatsu-kun, but...
It looks like I was wrong.
The Sunny!
Yay! It's magnificent!
And it flies! Beautiful!
The name "The Sunny" is truly fantastic!
We didn't talk much last time, so I didn't notice,
but you're one weird-looking guy.
I don't want to hear that from a guy with swirly eyebrows!
What'd you say?!
This is... Deep Sea Fever?
You know it?
Yes. I heard about it in Life, the nation of healing.
First, you turn cold and blue, like the deep sea.
In the terminal stage, you turn red hot, like the burning sun.
It peaks at sunrise...
And as the sun comes up,
death comes with it.
We only have a few hours until sunrise!
This is terrible!
Well, there is a way to save him.
You need the legendary Seafood Fruit to—
We tried that!
Just eating the fruit isn't enough.
Spring, summer, autumn, winter.
He must eat the legendary ingredient of each of the four seasons together.
Legendary ingredient of each season?
Yes. The one said to be hardest to obtain
is the Mango Karin that blooms in spring.
Mango Karin?!
A sweet flower that tastes like mango pudding,
also called the "spring pudding" that heralds the coming of spring.
I hear its sweet flavor works as a revitalizing tonic that cures exhaustion!
I wanna eat one!
Toriko-san, you're drooling! You're drooling!
It blooms in spring? Wait a minute!
You mean we have to go to Spring Island and Winter Island now?
We can't do that in just a few hours!
It's all right.
This is Chinese Tower Island, home of healthy foods and natural cures.
Let us go verify the legend handed down on this island!
Seal
Are these four ingredients really in a place like this?
Terry, you sense it, too?
I thought so. I can sense powerful electromagnetic waves here.
Toriko! This is definitely the place!
Okay! We just have to get it out from under the earth, right?
Nail Punch!
This is...
Wow!
It's a huge mushroom tower!
I see.
This is "Mush Room."
Mushroom?
Mush Room is a tower divided into four rooms,
Winter Autumn Summer Spring
with a different season on each floor.
So we just have to get the seasonal ingredients from each floor, right?
What's something like this doing underground?
This island's name
Chinese Tower Island
means "an island of Chinese with a tower."
This tower is the core, the center,
of the island.
But you people certainly are knowledgeable about foodstuffs.
How very heartening!
Toriko-san, Coco-san, and Sunny-san
are among the Four Heavenly Kings of Gourmet.
They're the cream of the Gourmet Hunter crop!
Four Heavenly Kings? Then is there not one more?
Zebra is...
...is prison right now.
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Nami! Take care of Chopper!
Right! These two are here, too, so we'll be fine!
Leave it to us!
Okay! Ready to go?
Yeah!
It's hot...
This is like the tropics!
So this is the summer floor, huh?
But why is it so bright when there are no windows?
Oh, that's because of the Light Mushrooms growing on the walls and ceiling.
Komatsu, you okay?
This heat is nothing compared to Chopper-san's fever!
Banjyan Tiger (Mammal Beast) Capture Level 29
S-S-Something jumped out!
Oh, a Banjyan Tiger, huh?
It's said that you can harvest rich, ripened chili paste from them.
The Banjyan Tiger is the first ingredient.
Oh?
Poison Rifle!
We don't have much time.
Perhaps we should split up and visit each floor in groups?
I agree!
Then I'll head upstairs!
What? You, too?!
You two are so compatible!
We are not!
Luffy-san! Everyone! Leave this floor to us!
Why is it chasing me?!
And up...
Is this the autumn floor?
Toriko! Leave this one to me!
I'll stay here, too!
You guys really are compatible!
I told you, we are not!
Don't copy me! I'm staying on this floor with Rin-chan!
No, no! I decided at the start that I would stay on this floor!
I have a personal interest in the ingredient here!
What ingredient is that? It sounds interesting.
Okay, we'll leave it to you!
Toriko! It seems the ingredient you can get on the next floor is sake!
Got it, Rin! Take care of this floor!
Toriko asked me to take care of it!
Well? What are we gonna see here?
Huh?
Have you heard of unicorns?
Unicorn? You mean the horse with the single horn on the forehead?
Yes. It is beautiful!
The unicorn is a mythical horse of many legends.
The creature we'll see here is not a unicorn,
but an eight-horned beast: an Octohorn!
I can't wait!
You mean that thing?
Octohorn (Eight-Horned Boar) (Mammal Beast) Capture Level 29
It has an eight-horned herb on its head.
Wh-What?!
What is this?!
I-It's not what I imagined at all!
Nah, you just made up that image yourself.
It's c-c-cold!
This cold really has a kick!
It does...
But how is there a blizzard indoors?
There's probably warm air coming from somewhere, causing convection.
Is that the cause?
Huh?!
Something's there!
An orangutan wearing clothes!
Has it adapted human customs?!
Wait, it looks like it's drunk!
This smell is...
Raochu!
That's the Raochu Spring, erupting with raochu!
So that's the third ingredient?
Excuse me, could you share that sake with us?
Toriko-san!
You okay?
I see... That's...
It's my first time seeing one.
An orangutan whose favorite treat is raochu!
Raochutan (Mammal Beast) Capture Level 32
A Raochutan!
Its favorite treat is sake?
Then it probably won't be easy to get it to share.
Be careful.
With all that wobbling, we can't predict its attacks.
It's like drunken boxing!
Hang in there, Chopper.
I'm sure the others will bring back the ingredients.
There's no more time.
It's almost dawn...
You guys!
Don't just watch! Hurry up and catch this thing!
Just capturing it isn't enough.
If you don't make the Banjyan Tiger run fast,
you can't collect the chili paste.
Looks like it's figured out by instinct that you're the easiest prey.
Better run hard.
Hey! It turned into chili paste!
So all that running around melted it.
We did it!
All right. We've got the first ingredient.
Well, this is just what I can do!
Franky Rocket Launcher!
So it's got speed, too?
Not bad.
I was so excited to see what beautiful creature would appear...
and yet...
Rin-chan! Are you okay?!
I'll protect Rin-chan!
How dare you betray my hopes so deeply?!
It stopped moving!
My brother stopped it with his Hair Lock!
What the heck? Looks like that ended easily.
The eight horns are a little cute, but I don't care about the rest.
Sorry my brother made trouble with you with his made-up expectations.
Now, I'll just... take these!
Let's get moving!
You two really are compatible.
We're not compatible at all!
Toriko-san! Luffy-san!
That little...
It's so cold, I can't move the way I want to...
The more it drinks, the stronger it gets!
The sake isn't the only thing making it stronger.
There's also that leaf it's drinking out of!
That's a Mango Karin leaf!
If the leaves are here...
Does that mean the Mango Karin is nearby?
Komatsu!
Oh, no!
Don't get cocky, now!
What was that?! It was incredible!
It's Zebra! That was Zebra's Sound Bullet!
He shot a Sound Bullet from inside the prison!
Let me enjoy this a little longer, Toriko.
You figure out how to deal with the rest.
This is the power of Zebra-san of the Four Heavenly Kings...
It's warmer now that the outside air is coming in!
I can move really well now!
It grew gigantic!
Could that be...
A Mango Karin flower?!
Yeah. There's no doubt.
All right! I'll be taking that!
Just wait, Chopper!
Gear 3,
Armament: Hardening!
Fifteen-fold...
Gum-Gum...
Elephant Gun!
Nail Punch!
All right!
Amazing! They beat the Raochutan!
This is the Mango Karin?
The flower isn't blooming!
Looks like it's too cold for it to open completely.
What?! So what do we do?!
If it gets some warm light, like the spring sunlight...
You mean light from the sun?
But once the sun comes up, Chopper will be done for!
What the heck can we do?!
That's...
What? Is it dawn?
No, it's...
A school of Spring Sharks!
Spring Sharks? Like the one that swallowed me?
Yeah. They're a highly valuable shark, but they're called Spring Sharks
because, during the spawning season, they glow!
And that glow is said to be as warm and bright as the spring sunlight!
The glow of a whole school rivals the warm glow of the sun!
That's...
The Mango Karin!
So... So beautiful!
Luffy, it looks like you have great Food Luck for finding ingredients.
You had already met the last ingredient you needed to heal Chopper,
the Spring Shark, once before!
Seafood Fruit, chili paste from the Banjyan Tiger,
the eight-horned herb from the Octohorn,
raochu from the Raochu Spring, and the Mango Karin flower.
It's finished!
Seafood Fruit with a sauce made from the four seasonal ingredients!
Here, Chopper-san, eat this.
Yum!
You're doing that again?
We did it!
He's cured!
Thank you all so much!
I'll never forget this!
Toriko! See you again!
Yeah! Let's eat our fill of tasty food again!
The food you eat with your friends is the best!
What's with him?
I guess, in spite of everything, he's sad to say goodbye.
Goodbye!
Take care!
Let's meet again,
The Sunny!
That's what you meant?!
After a long voyage, Tiger finally returns Koala to her home.
Watching Koala and her mother in a tearful embrace,
Tiger sees hope for a new future for Fishmen and humans.
But his hopes are cruelly trampled upon by humans.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Death of the Hero! A Shocking Truth of Tiger!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!