Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
A long time ago, I made the decision
that I'd never again build a ship.
But I wanted to catch up to the
person who was my goal after all.
The next thing I knew, I was
drawing blueprints for a ship.
My dream is... to use that jewel tree...
...to build one last ship...
A dream ship that crosses any sea!
I've already obtained this jewel tree.
I've already got blueprints, too.
I'm going to build this ship now.
So... when it's completed...
...will you set sail on the ship I've built?!
What?
What?!
Dammit!
Wake up!
Luffy!
O-Ouch! That hurt!
That hurt?! What're you saying?!
That was a punch! There's no
way that'd work on rubber!
There's no means to ward off a fist of love!
Looks like you've gone on
quite the rampage, huh, Luffy?
Ack! G-G-G...
Grandpa!
What?
What?!
A-A Navy vice admiral is...
The Strongest Family?
Luffy's Father Revealed!
Luffy!
Isn't there something you
"Monkey D. Garp
'Garp the Fist'
Vice Admiral, Navy Headquarters"
need to apologize to me for?!
Vice Admiral Garp's got a grandson?!
This is the first I've heard of it!
Garp?!
"Garp" is the name of a Navy hero!
What?!
Luffy! Is he really your grandpa?!
That's right! Don't you dare mess with him!
When I was small, he almost
killed me a bunch of times!
Now, don't go around giving me a bad name.
I shoved you into a bottomless pit...
I threw you into a jungle at night...
I attached you to balloons and let them fly...
I did all those things in order
to make you a strong man!
I think I've just discovered where
Luffy's endless vitality comes from...
I eventually entrusted you with my
friend and had you train with Ace...
...but I take my eyes off you,
and look what happens...
I trained you to become a strong marine!
I told you over and over that
I wanted to become a pirate!
You got corrupted by "Red-Haired"! How foolish!
Sh-Shanks saved my life! Don't badmouth him!
How dare you talk like that to your grandpa?!
Ahhh! I'm sorry!
This is terrible! Luffy got captured by the Navy!
Luffy!
Let go of me! Ow, ow, ow...
Oh, no! Luffy's combative spirit against
that old man has already been broken!
What?! They fell asleep?!
W-Well, what the heck should we do?
I've never been in this kind of situation!
Oh, no. I fell asleep.
Hm?!
Wake up, Luffy!
Is that how you behave
when you're being scolded?!
And that's not how you should speak
to your grandpa in the first place!
I don't care anymore. Do as you please.
Ribbit?
Seriously?!
So Luffy's grandpa is a marine
at Navy Headquarters?
This is getting crazy...
Ribbit...
Th-Th-That hurt!
Do you even know what kind of pirate
"Red-Haired" is to start with?!
Shanks?! Are they... Are Shanks
and the others doing okay?!
Where are they?!
Doing okay?!
Well, there are countless pirates
nowadays, but out of all of them,
he's ranked in the top four pirates,
in the same league as Whitebeard.
These four reign over the second half
of the Grand Line like emperors.
So people call them the Four Emperors.
Navy Headquarters and the Seven Warlords of the Sea
have joined together to
fight against these four!
If the balance among these
three great powers is lost,
it is said that world peace will fall apart.
That's how large their power is.
Huh? Err...
I didn't really get all that,
but it's good to hear he's doing okay.
It really brings back memories.
I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Take good care of it!
Come bring it back to me someday!
Once you've become a great pirate!
That's our promise, Luffy!
Luffy and "Red-Haired" know each other?
Luffy told me that this guy
entrusted the straw hat with him.
But I didn't realize this guy
was such a famous person.
Th-This way, Zoro-san!
Dammit! The Navy is already here!
Please go on ahead!
Well, really...
We're sorry that we tried to extort you!
Well, don't worry about it!
Thanks for showing me the way! Later!
Hm? What's going on?!
That's Pirate Hunter Zoro,
a criminal with a bounty on his head.
Oh...? That's Luffy's friend.
He's quite energetic, huh?
Well, you guys, try stopping him.
Yes, sir!
Kukris, huh? It's not often that you see those.
Hiya!
Hiya! Hiya!
Hey, Zoro, wait! You don't have to fight!
What the...? You bastard!
Shave!
This technique...
--Sergeant Major!
--Sergeant!
You guys are no match for them at all!
You really are strong.
I'd expect no less from you!
I concede!
Luffy-san! Zoro-san!
It's been a while. Do you recognize me?
Who are you?
It's me! Koby!
Don't you remember me?
Koby?
Do you think... even I could join the Navy?
--Navy?
--Yes! Catching bad guys is my dream!
It's been my dream ever since I was little!
Do you think I can do it?!
Luffy-san and I haven't known
each other long, but we are friends!
Right?
Yeah! We're gonna part ways,
but we'll always be friends!
Thank you! I'll never forget
all you've done for me!
Let's meet again sometime, Koby!
--Luffy-san...
--Bye!
All hands, salute!
See ya!
Koby?!
I do have a friend Koby...
but the Koby I know was short.
That's me! The Koby who
was a hopeless crybaby!
What?! Is that true?!
That Koby?
Why are you in the Grand Line?
I've still got a ways to go
to become a Navy Officer,
but when I heard that you were nearby,
I just wanted to see you guys so badly.
What?!
We owe you two for helping us
"Koby
Sergeant Major, Navy Headquarters"
become who we are now!
"Helmeppo
Sergeant, Navy Headquarters"
Well, I wouldn't go that far, but...
For various reasons, Vice Admiral Garp
is currently training us at Headquarters.
Oh, yeah?
At any rate, usually people can
only grow so much, you know!
I'm so surprised!
Your body was flabby!
Sorry for visiting now, when you're
tired after all you went through.
Don't worry about it. It's been
a while. Let's have a party!
Hold on a sec, you guys!
You haven't noticed me, have you?!
Who are you?
It's me! It's me!
I don't know you. Who are you?
The answer is...
...Helmeppo. The son of Captain Morgan...
Helmeppo!
I'm the man who crucified you and
nearly executed you, Roronoa Zoro!
Huh?!
Now you remember me, right?
Huh?
Hey, hey, that's enough.
It's not nice to be a bully!
You seem surprisingly well, Roronoa Zoro...
--Take this! And this!
--Stop! Stop!
That specially treated stupid son!
Oh...
It's you...
Hey!
Oh, yeah... There was a
guy like that. So it's you!
I still can't stand these guys, Koby!
It can't be helped, Helmeppo-san.
You should accept the past.
Oh, that?
Yeah, that.
Luffy-san, you and I are now enemies, but...
Hm?
...are we still... um...
Yeah. We're friends.
Well then, you guys...!
Yes, sir!
Repair this wall.
What?!
That's so selfish!
If you were going to have it fixed,
why did you break it in the first place?!
It's cooler to go in that way, isn't it?!
Don't break things for reasons like that!
Well then, we'll repair it,
so please help us, okay?!
What?!
Okay.
I thought your grandpa was a big shot.
Well... I don't know much about his job.
Come to think of it, Luffy...
I heard that you saw your old man.
What?! My dad?
What do you mean by my dad? I have a dad?
Oh... Then he didn't tell you who he was?
I heard that he saw you off at Loguetown.
Loguetown...
Err...
Huh?
So that's the island where Loguetown is!
That island is where Gold Roger
was born and then executed, right?
Wow, you actually remember!
The town where the Pirate King died...
Also known as the city
of the beginning and end...
Wh-What's going on?
To my several hundred billion
servants around the world! Look!
We'll now super flashily
start the open execution!
Monkey D. Luffy! You can
no longer move even an inch.
You feel honored, Straw Hat?!
You can die in the same place
the Pirate King died.
Since you have a big audience, do you
wanna say something before you die?
Well, that's okay.
Whether you wanna say something or not
doesn't matter, since you're gonna die.
I'm the man who'll become Pirate King!!
Out of our way!
Not even Zoro can stop me now!
This is the end of your captain!!
Damn bastard!
If I cut down the execution platform...
Zoro! Sanji!
--Hurry up!
--Usopp!
--This is heavy!
--Nami!
Sorry.
I'm... dead.
I'm still alive after all.
I got lucky.
The Straw Hat gang is running away!
Capture them!
Go after them!
Luffy's old man was in that town?!
Wh-What's my dad like?
I'm curious... about Luffy's father!
Your father's name is...
...Monkey D. Dragon. He's a revolutionary!
You're running out of your devil's luck.
Don't be so sure.
You're...
Dragon?
What?!
Whaaat?!
Th-Th-The "Revolutionary" Dragon has a son?!
Luffy-san is the son of that Dragon?!
Then... Dragon is Vice Admiral Garp's son?!
What the hell is with his family?!
I've never heard Dragon's full name before!
Hey, guys... What are you so surprised about?
Idiot! You don't know the name "Dragon"?!
Your father is a dangerous man!
Huh?
Ribbit...
Hey, Robin...
How can I explain it...?
Pirates wouldn't start a fight
with the Government or Navy,
but there's a power trying to bring down
the World Government directly now.
That's the Revolutionary Army.
And Dragon is the man who leads it.
Their ideology has now spread in
many countries around the world,
which caused rebellions and
led several kingdoms to fall.
The Government naturally became angry
and has been searching everywhere for
their mastermind, Dragon, all this time
as the world's most heinous criminal...
...but he's been considered a mysterious man
whose background was completely unknown.
And yet...
And yet?
Ah! I guess...
...I shouldn't have said anything about it, huh?
What?!
Well, then...
...forget what I just said!
Whaaat?!
Are you really going back already?
Why don't you have dinner with us? Dinner!
We're enemies. We can't become close, so...
I'm so glad that I was able
to see you two again today!
Let's meet again for sure in the New World!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Its Name Is the New World!
The Fate of the Grand Line"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Its Name Is the New World!
The Fate of the Grand Line