All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
They learned about the ruler of the island and the
puppet master of Land of the Dead - Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate ally - the Warlord - Law,
were drawn into a climactic battle
which ended with Caesar's defeat and capture.
Pirate brothers and sisters!
Thank you for helping us!
When we grow up, we will become...
...Pirates!
Don't!
Let's sail out!
Let's negotiate.
Your most important business partner is one of the Four Emperors.
The big-time pirate - Kaido the Beast King.
What would happen if he finds out you can't produce SMILE anymore?
He'll destroy you.
What do you want in exchange for Caesar?
Name your price.
Resign from the Seven Warlords.
Damn squirt!
"The G-5 Wiped Out! Doflamingo's Sudden Attack!"
How were you doing, Sunny?
I can't see the island anymore.
The fire, the ice, and the deadly gas.
The centaurs, the G-5, and the Warlord.
It was like hell.
Well, we're in the New World.
I'm sure it's not gonna get any easier.
Ow, ow, ow... Easy!
Be quiet!
To be honest, I wanna kick your ass!
Ouch!
But I'm a doctor.
So I won't!
Please don't hurt me!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
No, Brook! It's not a "little lamb"!
It's the Mini-Merry!
MINI-MERRY
I see.
You're the eighth person to ask me that.
Like I told the rest,
after I broke out the cage parting ways with Luffy and the others...
There you are, Sunny!
So they hid you here, huh?
Let's go, Sunny!
I got out to the sea through a channel in the lab
and retrieved the Mini-Merry...
...which had been docked at the entrance to the island.
And then, in order to join you guys,
I used the General Franky which is impervious to toxic gas
and went back to the lab.
Super!
I see, I see.
So that little lamb was okay. That's good!
Can we have a cup of tea?
Sure.
Here you go.
It was very delicious!
I'm glad that you liked it.
By the way, why are you two on this ship?
Oh yeah, I haven't thought about that
but the kids had gone with the Navy.
We're in the midst of our important trip.
So we didn't want to get
involved with the Navy and waste our time.
You can drop us off on some island with a harbor.
Until then, please let us stay on board.
Please!
Okay, no problem!
Yeah!
You can pay us later.
Are you gonna charge us?!
Nami, where are we going next?
Hold on.
The next destination is already set.
It's Dressrosa.
The gas didn't work at all?!
This protective suit is made by Vegapunk and in fact...
...it's way beyond Caesar's ability.
Caesar knew that, so that's why he said
that to my colleagues who were his test subjects.
You all, just run!
The protective suit won't help!
Take it off and run to the lab now!
What? O-Okay!
Master!
And that's how they all got petrified.
--Let's get going! --Yeah!
Those who got petrified are still alive!
If Caesar is telling the truth,
they're just in a state of apparent death paralyzed in the shell.
Yeah, but the poison will damage
their body and kill them in twelve hours!
We have to find them and break the shell before that!
Let's save them all at any cost!
Yeah!
Thank you...
...for allowing us to enter the island.
I'll never forget your name.
I can save my people's lives!
I promise I'll come back to turn myself in!
This is the only exit anyway.
Just go!
Okay!
What should we do with these?
Are they pirates?
I don't know. It's just creepy.
Something's flying toward us.
What?!
Isn't that somebody's head?!
Huh? Don't be ridiculous!
Y-You were right!
Heads are...
...Flying toward us!
What?!
That guy is...
N-No way!
Y-You're...
D-Doflamingo!
The Warlord?!
W-Why is he here?!
Conqueror's Haki!
Why did you do that?!
They're not here.
The ship is gone.
You're a Warlord! Why are you attacking the Navy?!
I know some pirates were here a little while ago.
Where did they go?
How dare you do that to our colleagues!
Don't do it!
I can't move my fingers.
What happened?!
Wh-What are you doing?!
W-What about you?!
No, I can't... control my body!
Law is different
but Straw Hat is just an ordinary pirate.
Don't!
Where did they go, you bastards?!
Wh-What are you gonna do to me?!
Answer my question.
Ouch!
Which direction did those shitheads go?!
I don't know what you're talking about!
Then go to hell.
Stop messing with my soldiers!
S-Smo-yan...
Smoker.
Tell me where those shitheads went.
I'm thinking about going to Green Bit.
Well, I don't know,
"Joker."
We could've caught them but we let them get away.
I don't know what to say to our base commander - Vergo.
He died, didn't he?!
I think you know too much.
Smoker!
Take this!
It's no use!
It's no good!
He keeps suffering that guy's strange attacks!
He has to defend himself!
Why doesn't he use his jitte with the Sea Prism Stone tip?!
It'll cancel out Devil Fruit powers!
Demon Bamboo!
You're no match for me.
Stop resisting and just accept your death.
--Smo-yan! --We'll fight, too!
Do you guys wanna die first?
Stay away!
Smo-yan!
Vice Admiral Smo!!
Dressrosa?!
Yes, there is something we have to do there.
D-Dressrosa?!
What? Do you know the place?
Th-That's exactly where we... I mean, I want to go!
You need to go there, too?!
Uh-huh, I think so!
You have no idea what's going on, do you?
Nope!
The current is shifting?!
What's going on here?!
A slope?!
Yee-ha!
It's fast! The ship's going fast!
Look out for rock reefs!
What's going on around here?!
It's a sea slope. It's not uncommon.
It is uncommon!
We don't have to go against the current.
The needle in the middle
on your Log Pose must be pointing toward Dressrosa.
But don't try to go straight. Take a detour.
Why?
Because it'll work out better for us.
He's being such a know-it-all smart-ass.
Come to think of it,
you were talking on the Transponder Snail earlier.
Who were you talking to?
That was Doflamingo.
Doflamingo?! The Warlord?!
I've heard he's the most evil one!
The plan is already in action.
What plan?
Yeah, tell us about the plan! Get together, everybody!
We formed an alliance to kill one of the Four Emperors?!
The Four Emperors, huh? It's great!
No, it's not!
That's a super big deal!
Wait, wait! Let's calm down, everybody!
Luffy, tell them about the alliance.
Okay! We and Tra-guy's pirate crew formed an alliance!
Let's be nice to each other!
Does anybody wanna oppose this?!
--I do! --I do!
I do!
Does it make any difference?
Luffy's mind is already set, isn't it?
Thank you.
But I have to warn you.
There may be a slight difference between
how you define "alliance" and how Luffy defines it.
Be careful.
That's why Luffy kept saying "kidnap"
which was so out of character for him.
If he had just come to me with that strange sheep
and ask me to cook it, I wouldn't know what to do.
You bastards. You're not gonna get away with this.
Extraordinarily big names will hunt you down!
Idiots!
Realize how stupid you are! Go to hell!
Hey, Sanji! I was in the middle of his treatment!
Wait until I finish it.
Really?!
I asked you guys to kidnap Caesar at Punk Hazard.
Meanwhile, I destroyed the machine which was
manufacturing a substance called SAD.
The great pirates in the New World often have their own territory.
They lead countless numbers of people and reign like a syndicate.
It's nothing like what you've seen before.
One pirate crew is never strong enough even to see their captain's face.
But since it's an underground community,
they have to do their businesses secretly to avoid the Navy.
And Doflamingo is the most trusted and powerful man among them.
His underground alias is Joker.
And Joker's most important business partner now is...
...one of the Four Emperor - Kaido the Beast King.
Our target.
--Stop! --Smo-yan's gonna die!
If you kill him,
who would lead misfits like us!?
Don't worry.
There is no way to find out who knows what.
That's why, Law, Straw Hat, and you soldiers,
I'm gonna kill you all!
No!
Whoa-whoa.
Excuse me, young man.
Could you step aside?
What?!
He is my...
...friend.