Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World, the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After landing on Punk Hazard; an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen,
they learned about the hideous experiments performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
and headed off to investigate but as things got going,
they came to form an alliance with the Heart Pirates led by Trafalgar Law.
Do as we discussed.
Yeah. While you're taking Caesar and that woman somewhere else,
I'm gonna find out about the drug.
And Luffy is now headed to see the Master Caesar Clown.
You will all experience it!
The chemical weapon explosion that happened four years ago on Punk Hazard!
A world of death in which no one can survive!
And you will learn!
Just how powerful my weapon is, that it can destroy an island!
And the greatness of the world's best scientist who created the weapon!
It's me--Master Caesar Clown!
I got you!
A Ferocious Battle
Caesar Reveals His True Strength!
Team Zoro
Punk Hazard, Center Lake
Is that a Slime?
A Slime?
Yes. I was once reading a book that had a monster...
...that looks exactly like this one called a "Slime."
I couldn't stop reading it.
The Slime liked to attack women
and its body fluids would only melt what the women were wearing!
"Slimy, Slimy"
It was such a dirty monster!
NO!!
What?! That's too convenient!
C-Can I borrow that book sometime?!
Me, too!
Fools! Look carefully.
Pinky promise! Huh?
I don't know if it melts your clothes but you might not wanna touch it.
The fish are dying from the fluid that it dropped into the lake.
It's like it's made of toxins.
If nothing is done, the poison will spread all over the lake.
Poison?
Then, samurai-san's torso will...
D-Don't tell me you're going in, Sanji-san?!
Do I have a choice? It's my personal mission!
I'm Sanji, I'm a man! I've got to do it!
Sanji-san!
Do something about the Slimes behind you.
What? Behind me?
Copies of the Slime?! When did they get here?!
Sorry, Nami-san.
I'm better at swimming than anyone else.
I'll try to get out of the water before it causes damage to your beautiful body!
Please be careful!
He's risking his life for me
and going into the poisonous lake!
Th-The water is ice-cold!
Where is his torso?
The Slimes are coming toward us!
What should we do about them?
Yeah, what should we do?
Just Monet in the room.
This is the chance.
The Master is not here.
Yeah? Where did he go?
I don't know.
Being such a hideous person, he's probably watching the fight outside.
I've seen pretty much everything what I wanted to see on the island.
I'm thinking about leaving here soon.
Oh, we'll miss you.
There is something I could use your help with though.
Could you come with me?
Are you asking me out? How sweet!
You're such an unfriendly person. What is it?
You'll see.
Alright. I was bored anyway.
Is that the bird woman that Usopp was talking about?
What?!
Team Luffy
Caesar's Research Institute, Main Entrance
S-Straw Hat caught Master!
Way to go, Luffy!
Dammit! That bastard!
Straw Hat!
Let go of me, you fool!
No!
That's what Haki can do? I can't believe Luffy can do that.
He's grabbing a Logia eater!
Straw Hat! Stay away from the Master!
Let's save the Master!
I won't let you guys do that!
Clutch!
Outta my way!
Since Luffy became so strong, I bet he can easily beat that guy!
We don't know that yet.
What?
With Armament Haki,
it's possible to strike Logia eaters who you can't even touch normally.
However, unlike the sea or Sea Prism Stone,
it doesn't drain their powers.
We don't really know the extent of the Gas-Gas Fruit's power.
Don't get carried away!
Armament; Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
...Bell!
Gas Robe!
The smoke!
Damn! Gas Robe!
What is this?
I can't shake it off!
Luffy, hold your breath! The guy who got it is...
Shit! It's poison gas!
Fool! It's no use doing that!
Once you get wrapped up in the Gas Robe,
you can't get away from it no matter what you do!
How much longer can you hold your breath?!
Just breathe deeply
and drop dead!
--Luffy! --Dammit!
After countless experiments,
I finally discovered the deadliest gas!
Now, suffer and die!
I have front row seats!
Is he going crazy?!
He's sucking the Master's poison gas up voluntarily!
--He inhaled it all! --He'll be dead soon!
I've never seen an idiot like that!
Go to hell!
What?!
Poisons don't work so well against me now, I guess.
Thanks to Magellan.
Magellan?! The venomous fool from Impel Down?!
I'm not like that pathetic Paramecia eater!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Mace!
Master!
Yeah!
How could he do that to our Master?!
I'll kill him!
Attack Straw Hat!
Yeah!
Stay out of it, weaklings!
W-Weaklings?
Did he call us "weaklings"?
Or did we hear him wrong?
That fool!
I'll show him my Gas-Gas Fruit power!
Armament; Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
Come on!
...Gatling!
Gastanet!
What?
Luffy!
That's our Master!
Now, I'm gonna finish you off!
Smilies, wake up!
Smilies?
What?! All of a sudden, they're moving...
Smilies, cling onto Straw Hat!
Jump!
Why are they listening to the Master?!
Luffy, watch out! They'll explode!
Luffy!
Go away!
Gastanet!
Luffy!
Straw Hat's gone!
That was a huge explosion! I don't think there is even a hair left!
He wasn't strong enough to fight against our Master, the savior, in the first place!
No... Luffy!
You've got to be kidding!
I'm the greatest scientist in the world, eater of the Gas-Gas Fruit!
You shouldn't have made me mad!
Master! Master!
Master! Master! Master...
You didn't know who you were messing with!
Oh, that was close!
What?!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
M-Master!
That was a big explosion.
That fool! Did he avoid the explosion? How fast can he move?!
What a relief.
--S-Straw Hat?! --Is he invincible?
All right!
How dare you do that to our Master?!
Move out of my way!
Okay, I really got you this time!
Master!
Robin! Franky! Is there anything that I can put him in?
He's a Logia eater so tying him up won't do it.
Isn't there a barrel or something?
Whoa-whoa, hold on, Straw Hat!
We, the Navy G-5, are taking him into custody and putting you guys under arrest!
Fools, be ready for it!
Smoker-san, Straw Hat and his crew caught Caesar!
Dammit, those fools!
Smoker-san!
Let's go, guys!
Follow Smo-yan and Captain-chan!
Yeah!
You can't escape, Straw Hat!
Straw Hat?
Luffy?
You shouldn't underestimate me.
Luffy!
Oh no!
Robin! I'll draw their attention to me!
You go and save Luffy!
Be careful! That guy's really tough!
What did you do to Luffy?!
Get out of my way!
Strong...
Right!
You're next!
Franky Radical...
...Beam!
Wing!
Luffy!
Robin!
She passed out all of a sudden!
What happened to her?!
Everyone, get out of here now!
Tashigi!
Captain-chan!
Robin, are you alright?!
Robin, stay with me!
Luffy!
You bastard!
Strong...
Ri...
Damn! What's going on here?!
I have them all now!
Caesar's Research Institute, Team Law
Law?
Who is it?
What's wrong?
Oh no. You look like you're in pain.
Who is there?!
It's me.
Why are you...
...here?!
It's been years.
You've grown up.
Law.
Sanji manages to make it out of the poisonous lake safely,
but there's little time to rejoice.
They end up surrounded by Smileys
and are unable to escape from this crisis.
It's in this hopeless situation,
where the samurai reveals his true power.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Samurai Who Cuts Through Fire!
Foxfire Kin'emon"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Samurai Who Cuts Through Fire!
Foxfire Kin'emon