Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates
who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken,
who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil and...
The Noah is already...
...stopped!
Sea Kings? Why?
Luffy-sama! The wound is opening up again!
You are bleeding a lot!
Well... Well... That's good...
...as long as the ship is stopped.
I'm glad...
everybody's...
safe.
"To the Future! The Path to the Sun!"
Princess Shirahoshi.
We have been waiting for you to be born for a long time.
For me?
This ship is designed to be pulled by us.
Since very early times, the duty has been passed on.
Is that why the Noah is so big?
Yes.
Once in many centuries,
our queen comes into the world in the form of Mermaid.
I wonder why.
I wonder why as well.
Ever since you were born,
you have been our queen.
Brother!
Yeah, I think Shirahoshi is...
She is talking with the Sea Kings.
I can't believe it!
What is going on, guards? How did the Noah stop?
Well, actually a group of Sea Kings showed up here
around the island, out of the blue.
It seemed like they came to protect the Noah...
...from getting destroyed by Luffy-san.
I wonder if the Noah is something very important to them.
Neptune-sama?!
Sea Kings...
It awakes finally-jamon.
The power that could destroy the world!
Look,
the bubble is getting absorbed by the island.
The human can't survive in the deep sea.
You better go and save him.
Luffy-sama! Oh no!
We should go capture Hody and the others.
Yeah.
We have to hurry!
Noah... I wonder what secrets that ship holds.
Am I imagining things?
What?
That human with the hat noticed our voice.
I doubt it.
Something like this happened not so long ago.
Yes, I remember.
Rayleigh, did you just hear that voice?
What are you talking about?
It's really quiet down here.
Who are you, talking in such deep sea?
Hey, show yourself!
--I wonder why. --I wonder why as well.
I wonder if Straw Hat and the others are okay.
They're strong, aren't they? Then they're fine.
Uh-huh, we have to trust them, Hatchin.
You're right.
S-Sea Kings?!
They're pulling the Noah!
They're gonna eat us!
The ship is falling apart.
Can it be fixed?
Does it still work?
I don't know.
In order to fix it, we need help from "them" but...
...times are changing.
Can it be fixed?
I hope it can be fixed...
...by the appointed time.
This is the Ryugu Palace!
Minister of the Left, you might want to hear this!
What is it?
We found the Mermaids who had been kidnapped...
...inside the palace!
What?!
Are they all right?
Yes, they are. They say they still feel groggy
but they remember the kidnapper's face clearly!
Also, the treasure chamber's been emptied.
There isn't even a single piece of treasure left.
Not to mention the national treasure--the Tamate Box!
King-sama! S-Somebody robbed the palace while we were gone!
Forget about the treasure thief.
We almost lost the whole country just now-jamon.
Instead, let the whole nation know that those Mermaids were okay.
I know it's too late
but we need to clear Straw Hat and the others' name-jamon.
We did them wrong.
We shouldn't be here!
Hurry up!
They'll catch and kill us!
Let's go! We humans have nothing to do with this battle!
Where are you going?
Let us go!
Let's fly over him with bubbles.
Water Shot!
I will shoot you down if you try to fly over me with those!
Dammit!
I beg you, Boss! Let us go!
We were just afraid of Hody and the others!
We have nothing to do with this civil war because we're humans!
I thought this island was a tourist spot
largely depending on us human pirates for money!
Let us get out through the exit!
No one says that you all are going to get your heads cut off.
Wait for Neptune royal family's decision.
There is something that we would like all islanders to know.
The Straw Hats were not involved in the kidnap of the Mermaids at all.
We admit that we made a mistake in our fact-checking process
and we take full responsibility - we want to apologize.
I didn't think the Straw Hats did it.
I knew it wasn't them the whole time.
Don't lie!
We all thought that they were the kidnappers!
--N-No, we trusted them, didn't we? --Y-Yeah.
--Liars! --Hey!
That's not fair!
He's right!
Admit it.
We didn't trust them.
We didn't trust them because they're humans.
That's how we've always treated humans...
Super...
...Afro!
--Franky-san, that's so cool! --Isn't it super?
Hey Chopper, are you alright?
Yeah... I'm fine...
Whoa!
--Thanks. --Oh boy...
When I use the Monster Point,
I can't even walk for a couple hours from fatigue.
But I can still treat you.
Is anyone hurt?
Look who's talking!
Everybody looks okay.
Robin-chan! I used a daring technique and I'm exhausted too!
Let me put my head in your lap, too! Please!
--Put your stupid head somewhere else! --You do it!
Luffy...
There they are! Hey!
Prince!
Everybody!
It's the Princes!
I'm glad that they're okay!
--Hody! --Vander Decken!
Father! We are sorry to make you worry!
I am glad that you are all okay-jamon.
Well done!
Thank you!
Everybody! No worries!
We won't allow them to make trouble again!
We can live without fear now!
I can't believe there was such an awful guy so nearby in the Fishman District.
--C-Captain Hody! --He looks like a monster!
This is great!
Hey, that's...
They are back!
Luffy-san!
Hey, Luffy!
It's Straw Hat Luffy and Princess Shirahoshi!
Please help me!
I cannot stop Luffy-sama's bleeding!
Hey Luffy, stay with us!
Luffy!
Luffy-sama pushed himself so far in order to save us!
Straw Hat!
This is bad!
There are hemostatics in my backpack!
--Get it for me, Robin. --Okay.
This makes me worried about how you'll fight from now on, Doc!
Okay, go ahead!
-I'll help you move. --We have an odd doctor here!
A little bit to the left.
Will Luffy-sama be all right?!
I can stop the bleeding but he already lost a lot of blood!
He's lacking blood!
Luffy is the only one with blood type F among us.
Oh no!
There must be somebody in the plaza!
Somebody!
Hey!
Is there someone with blood type F here?!
He needs blood!
Can somebody donate blood?!
Really? Nobody?
My blood type is F.
Mine is F but...
Dad, your blood type is F, isn't it?
Well, I mean...
Oh yeah! Donating blood to humans is prohibited in this country!
What?!
What kind of law is that?! That's horrible!
I beg you! Luffy is dying!
M-My blood type is not F but mine's red too!
It's no good?!
Yes but thank you for offering!
Princess Shirahoshi...
Oh yeah! There are human pirates!
Hey please! If nothing is done, Luffy is gonna...
Luffy is gonna die!
Take my blood.
It's F.
You can have as much as you need.
Jinbe!
Jinbe-chan!
But it's against the law...
I am a pirate!
Boss! I'm so glad!
Jinbe-san!
Thank you!
Jinbe, you...
It is okay-jamon.
K-King-sama!
What is so wrong with it?
That old law is also...
...a curse-jamon.
Okay, let me prepare for the procedure.
I'm fine now. I can move for a while.
Let me help with something.
OK, thanks.
Jinbe, it may hurt a little bit.
I don't mind.
If you hurt somebody...
...or if somebody hurts you,
the same red blood will be shed.
It hardly seems like a path...
...because it's a very thin and narrow tube - but it makes its way through...
...the prejudice that makes people fear each other...
...and blood feuds...
...so very easily.
This is a path towards a very real sun,
not some empty wish.
Jinbe...
Luffy-sama, you came to life again!
Luffy!
--Luffy! --Luffy-san!
What is it?
I didn't know that you were awake.
Straw Hat!
Luffy!
We are back to zero now!
Mother!
Hey, Jinbe.
Join...
...my crew!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Secret Revealed! The Truth about the Ancient Weapon!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!