Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can become Pirate King!
Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
BON VOYAGE!  hito kakera no yuuki hirogete
BON VOYAGE!      Let that shred of courage grow
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
saisho wa minna BARABARA ni egaite ita chiheisen
The horizons everyone dreamed of were separate at first
ima nara hitotsu no bouenkyou de nozokeru
but now they can be seen through a single telescope
kimi no KOKORO madowasu unmei no shoppai KONPASU
A bitter compass of destiny is leading your heart astray
saka te ni kajitoru yo
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
BON VOYAGE!
SHIGARAMI mo kako mo sutete
Toss aside your bonds and your past
bokura nara sore demo waraeteru hazu
We can surely smile despite that
yume o kanaeru tame no namida naraba oshikuwanai
Tears shed trying to achieve your dreams aren't for naught
PRECIOUS IN MY LIFE
precious in my life
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
Upper Yard
Angel Island
I should never have come!
Get down from there!
Impudent Blue Sea woman! I'll chop you up!
Seis Fleurs:
Twist!
Just awful.
Have you ever seen a flying slash?
Single-Sword Style: 36-Pound Phoenix!
The Roaring Burn Bazooka!!
Luffy vs. War Demon Wyper
Damn him! He... He... killed Sanji...!
It's no use! His heart isn't beating at all!
Hey! Sanji!
Sanji! Sanji!
Dammit! If only Chopper were here...!
Wait, Usopp!
That's his right side!
The heart's on the left!
Right
S
i
d
e
Right
S
i
d
e
Right
S
i
d
e
Right
S
i
d
e
Yikes! It's beating!
Thank goodness! He came back to life!
But he's seriously injured! He could die!
What?! Oh crap! This is bad!
Eneru...
There's no need to be indignant.
It's been so long since we last met.
Why don't you cheer up a bit, Gan Fall?
H-Hey! What the hell did you do to Sanji?!
J-Just try something else!
My 8,000 subordinates won't sit by quietly!
H-Here. If you run away now, I'll forgive you.
What do you say?
He... ran...?
Damn you!
Remain silent... and I will do nothing...
Got that?
Good.
Who is this guy?! What did he just do?!
Just what are you thinking?!
Your men that I captured when we
invaded this island six years ago
are working very hard for me.
My Divine Squad...
They're also very strong.
Truly great talent, they are.
But it appears that their six years
of hard labor is nearing its end.
And as I'll no longer have any need
for this island once they're done,
I thought I would come to bid you farewell.
That is all.
However, the denizens of
Skypiea are all ignorant fools.
They only view this island
as a clump of Vearth, you see.
What do you mean?!
The reason we forcefully took this island away,
the reason the Blue Sea flies
stepped foot onto this island,
and the reason the Shandians are
intent on returning to their home
are not at all different.
In other words... there is but one
thing everyone seeks on this island!
It was because everyone desires
the great relics of Shandora,
the legendary city of gold that
prospered in the Blue Sea long ago!
Gold? What is that?
That's what I mean by ignorant!
No one living here knows of gold, or its value!
Funnily enough, this game is the final battle.
The winner of this survival game
will make the bountiful gold his own.
Can you hear it?
The sounds of the lively festival...
As a matter of fact, I'm a participant myself, so I must be off.
Wait, Eneru! The Divine Squad...
Are you going to free them?!
God only knows.
Wait, Eneru!
He disappeared...
Usopp!
Thank goodness!
His heart is still beating somehow...!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Try all you want, it's no use!
Not even cannons or guns work on me!
Apparently not.
So I'll change the style!
Peeyew!
What's this smell?!
Gas is stored inside the
Breath Dial of this weapon,
which is called a Burn Bazooka.
The bluish flames that ride on the
expelled gas burn prey to a crisp!
What the...?!
It went right through that giant tree!
Huh?! He disappeared!
Bastard! Where is he?!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Gum-Gum Stamp!
That was close!
Gum-Gum...
...Spear!
If it's a bazooka you want, you can't beat mine!
Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
Burn...
– ...Bazooka!
Straw Hat!
That bastard!
What's wrong, Straw Hat?!
I know you haven't kicked the bucket yet!
Yeah! Of course I haven't!
What the...?! What the...?!
What happened?!
Where did he go?
No matter.
This is no time to be wasting energy on him.
I need to save some strength...
...and make it to Eneru!
One more Reject, and my body
probably will be blown to bits.
I'm coming for you, Eneru!
How do ya like that?!
Damn it!
We absolutely won't let you go any further!
Shut up! I'm after Eneru's head!
Out of the way!
Not another one!
I have no business with Divine Soldier small fries!
That's some rare ammunition you have there.
Heavy matter that doesn't
normally exist in the sky...
The Vearth mineral, iron?
It seems you've taken down
many of my men, Shandian.
You're Genbou, one of the main forces, yes?
Divine Commander Yama!
Get out of my way!
Damn you...
I-I refuse...
...to die in a place like this!
Oh! You're still alive. You're tough, indeed.
Very well. As a symbol of respect
for your determined spirit...
...I will finish you off with my secret technique.
10-Axe Combo!
Damn you, Yama!
Axe Mountain!
So close. You did well to make it this far.
What?! Who are you?!
Don't give us, "What?!"
We're the Deputy Divine Commanders!
How dare you kill our brother Satori?!
How dare you?!
What?! I don't know any brother of yours!
Don't play dumb! My name is Hotori!
My name is Kotori!
You guys killed our brother!
I told you, I don't know
what you're talking about!
Satori was one of Eneru's four priests.
He guarded Illusion Forest.
Then, the priest Luffy and the others beat was...
Yes! Their elder brother!
See! You do know!
You must pay!
Pierre!
I must take care of them and hurry after Eneru.
There is no telling what he
might do to my subordinates!
Stand back, girl!
Even with my injuries, I will not lose to them!
No! Sometimes, even I...
...have to protect these guys!
Very well!
First, ascertain their dials!
Right!
We're going to avenge our brother!
It finally stopped...
Where am I?
Hey! Guys! Is anyone here? It's me!
If you're here, say something!
I guess no one's here...
Where?
Where did it go?!
G-Gedatsu-sama.
Y-Your eyes are rolled inside your head.
Y-You cannot see ahead of you like that.
How careless of me!
Have a look at this photograph.
Here it is. That puny creature.
He's with the Blue Sea people!
What? It isn't a raccoon dog?
Raccoon dog? No, it is not a wild animal.
It is unquestionably a
creature from the Blue Sea!
Luffy! Where are you?!
Zoro! Are you asleep again?!
Robin! Hurry over here!
Where is everyone?!
I'm feeling insecure!
Hey! Guys! It's me!
Where?!
Where did you go?!
Yikes! W-What is this?!
Itsumo no you ni zenryoku shissou
Racing full speed ahead as always
A to Z hashirinuketeku
A to Z, we run through it
Nayandari suru sa shichiten battou
We all have worries and fall many times
Itsuka joushou sureba ii zetchou
But we just need to rise to the top someday
Asahi noboru ano umi no
What could be beyond the sea
mukou-gawa ni nani ga arun darou
in which the morning sun rises?
Koukou to hikaru taiyou no aru houkou sukoshi zutsu ikou
Let's go little by little toward the brilliantly shining sun
I never treat you "bad"
Nankai koronda?
How many times did we fall?
Daijoubu bokutachi wa tashika ni ima ashita ni sa yubisashiten da
It's all right, we're definitely pointing at tomorrow now
Smile! Come back to you, friends
Come back to you, friends
Are you a priest?!
This area is already my territory!
All around us are Swamp Clouds!
There is no escape!
Yeah! Everyone protects me
because I always run away!
That's why they don't rely on me!
I'm going to raise a pirate flag right here!
I'm gonna beat him!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Ordeal of the Swamp!
Chopper vs. Sky Punk Gedatsu!!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Ordeal of the Swamp!
Chopper vs. Sky Punk Gedatsu!!