You shouldn't swim.
But it's a nice feeling for my bones.
Hey! Ugly, perv-skeleton! Would you tell me what the hell...
you think you're looking at, you bastard!?
It's a joy for the eyes!
Even though you don't have eyes! I've got you!
What a beautiful day!
Something appeared!
Oh my, how cute!
Is it a horse?
A horse...?
Where did it come from?
Hold on, Nami-san! I'll drown if you continue! I'm scared! No, I'm happy!
Quick, do something! Think of something!
Don't you think it's similar to a cow?
Luffy, don't let it escape! I'll make horse soup for dinner!
Soup? Sounds tasty...
I knew the New World was going to be completely different!
There're full of unique ingredients here.
Let me take care of it!
Rubber... Jet Bazooka!!
You had enough?
You moron!
Oh right! The meat!
Now the booze will have to wait.
We must find it!
So scary!
Brook, stay with us!
Anyway, why did his body inflate so much?
He's really unique.
There it is!
What a relief! Horse soup tonight!
I can't wait to try it!
Don't forget about the booze. A good one.
You can't think about anything but booze.
The New World is filled with different routes,
we don't know if there's going to be a town on the next island, you have to stay sharp!
I can take care of myself! You're the one who's risking your life!
We can't risk the annihilation of the whole crew because you're completely drunk!
Why don't you think about getting that meat from the seahorse instead?
Without booze I can't concentrate!
Now, now, calm down Zorosuke.
Zorosuke?
To me you seem like a pure-hearted guy!
What the hell are you prattling about?!
We have enough meat, don't we? Even without booze, we can still party!
Even without flowers, petals might rain down!
A rain of petals?
Wouldn't you like to eat horse meat under a rain of cherry petals?
May I ask you something, Nami?
Hm? Something wrong, Chopper?
I'm a little busy at the moment... what's up?
Actually I'm following a milk diet lately... what's your opinion on it?
It won't open, give me a hand!
What are you up to?
The poolside has to be sheltered.
This feels good.
It's super good! I'm so happy!
Do you want some?
I'd prefer an orange juice instead!
As you wish!
I'll make gallons of orange juice for my Nami-san!
Yes! With great pleasure!
What are you talking about, Sanji?
Idiot! Didn't you hear what Nami-san just said?
But right now Nami is very far from here... I didn't hear anything!
My ears heard her perfectly fine!
I can hear Nami-san and Robin-chan from miles away!
Huh? What are you doing?
There's an awful stink!
On the garden above parasites have appeared...
I'm preparing a pesticide!
Then do it outside! This is a kitchen!
Robin-chan! Want to drink something?
No, I'm fine. Thanks!
Usopp... do you know where the sprinkler is?
It's in Usopp's Factory! I've just modified it a little.
It's very beautiful, Usopp!
What's so great about it... Robin-chan?
It's a zombie sprinkler!
It was very fun making it!
Really? I can't wait to use it then!
A big buffet?
That's right!
Even if we don't have a thing, we can still party!
What idiocy...
Listen Zorosuke...
Still with the "suke"?!
Try imagining...
that here we have tasty fries, a gigantic hamburger... and cola as well!
Ah, everything was great!
Incredible!
It seemed like you were really enjoying it!
Of course!
Whoever has a pure heart, has a fervid imagination as well!
Alright! Then I imagine I'm having the biggest dinosaur leg in the world!
No... wait!
Here are islands made of meat!
How's this?!
Yummy! This island is really good!
A waterfall of booze... creating a river.
Fantastic! Cool!
There's lot of stuff!
Good! They're almost here...
a hamburger bigger than the previous... delicious fries and lots of great cola!
Clouds of cotton candy and cow milk!
I did it!
Wooo!
This is a dreamlike place!
If... if this is a place where everything comes true...
then I... I... I...
Would you care to show me your panties?
Come back to reality!
This calls for a toast!
Yes!
I feel like I'm flying!
Guys, pay attention! Real horse meat is coming!
The real one!? I knew the real ones are always the best!
Take, drink.
Booze?
One of the best!
While eating and drinking, for you everything is the same! Don't harm a cook's pride! Idiot!
I'm not complaining.
Right! Prepare those cherry trees...
and let's party eating horse meat under a rain of cherry petals!
Let's do it!!
Usopp! Quick! I'll teach you how to imagine stuff!
This petals' shower is really beautiful, and look at this booze! Brook, bring the mugs!
A rain of petals? With pleasure!
Huh?! How did he make it?!
From where do all this cherry petals come out?!
How did those cherry trees end up on the Sunny?!
When did it happen?
Nami-san, sorry if I made you wait.
Good, let's go!
Amazing!
Cherry trees. Booze. Cherry trees and booze. Booze! Booze! Booze! Let's drink some booze!