Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
rashinban nante jyuutai no moto
compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
delirious with fever, i take the helm
hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
if the dusty treasure map has been verified,
tashikameta no nara densetsu janai
it's not a legend!
kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
when it comes to personal storms,
biorizumu nokkatte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
omoi sugoseba ii
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
poketto no koin
a coin in my pocket,
soreto You Wanna Be My Friend
and do you wanna be my friend?
We Are
we are!
Witch of Cocoyashi Village!
Arlong's Female Leader
What's this guy saying?
Let go.
I told you, that's mine!
Say what?! Who decided that?!
I took it myself and put it on my
own plate, so of course it's mine!
Oh. Really? Then you should've said so!
And I was saving that for last, too!
Okay, I'm sorry! You can have this!
You know I can't eat that!
I'm not a dog, you know!
Quiet!
Something's down there...
It's big...
What's that?
A sea monster!
It's a cow! It's huge!
A cow? They don't swim. It's a hippo.
What's something like this
doing in the East Blue?!
This is a Grand Line creature!
Huh? What's this guy doing?
He's after the food!
What?!
Hurry and give it to him!
He'll flip the boat over!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Stay away from my food!
You did it!
You're incredible, Big Bro Luffy!
Looks like you made it mad!
Another one, huh?!
You dumbass!
Don't beat up someone
who's hungry for no reason!
He's probably hurt or something
and can't catch his own food.
Right?
What love...
Here, eat up.
No need to hold back.
Die, you damn thing!
What're you doing?!
What happened to that love?!
The bastard just tried to eat me, too.
Here he comes!
He's gonna sink the boat!
That jerk!
Get back. I'll do it.
Collier Shoot!
Damn hippo...
Alright! Back to food!
That was good exercise.
These guys are crazy...
W-Where am I?
My house.
You awake?
W-Who are you?!
I'm Nojiko. I grow tangerines here.
That's right! You thwacked me!
Just when I was trying to save you, too!
I'm the one who saved you.
Had you done anything to that Fishman,
there's no question you would've been killed.
This is why I hate outsiders!
But you're a kid from Gosa, right?
Surely you know all too well
from firsthand experience
that you'll be killed if you mess with the Fishmen.
I know!
I know, but... they killed my daddy!
They stole everything, destroyed our town,
and killed tons of people!
They have to pay!
No matter what, they have to pay!
So I went to Arlong Park!
But a girl on his side got in the way!
She... was like a witch!
I hate this! I don't care if I die;
I'm going to avenge my daddy!
Then die.
If you're prepared to die,
then go get your revenge!
But know this much.
Now that me and that witch
at Arlong Park have stopped you,
you've escaped death twice now!
Leave when you're done with your tea.
Hey!
Isn't that being a little harsh on the kid?!
Kid or not, if someone wants to die, then just let 'em die!
He doesn't have the guts to live
through hard times anyway!
Say what?!
I know a kid who's staring
fixedly at the distant future
while she endures a life
more painful than death.
That's why I hate people like him
who consider death right off the bat!
What... should I do?
I hate this! I'll endure it!
What should I do?!
What about your mom?
She's alive...
She's worried about you. Go back to her.
Okay...
You're actually a nice person!
Even though you have tattoos...
Prejudice!
I don't know anything about you, you know...
Oh, right!
My name is Captain Usopp!
I'm looking for a girl named Nami...
Nami?!
You know her?
What?!
Nami's a leader of the Arlong Pirates?!
Yep. She's infamous in this area.
Even that little boy said she seemed like a witch.
Even more surprising, that witch grew up in this very house!
Me and Nami are adopted sisters.
So this is...
...Nami's house?!
Me and Nami are both orphans.
We were brought up in this house.
Our foster parent is dead, too,
but the three of us used to live
happily here in Cocoyashi Village.
Then... Nami betrayed her own
parent and fellow villagers
and joined Arlong's group?!
Yeah, pretty much. A real witch, huh?
Damn it! So that's the deal?!
So she had us fooled the entire time!
She was after treasure from the very start!
Even after she helped fight to protect my village
and smiled so happily aboard our ship!
Oh? Happily?
Her?
We came here to bring her back with us,
but I guess there's no need for-
That reminds me, a friend
of ours was unlucky enough
to be caught by the Fishmen...
This is bad...
I wonder how the guy's holding up...
Well? Now do you see?
I was only using you guys from the very start.
You had some decent skill, and you
were good suckers worth using.
So you had them completely fooled!
This girl's like a cold-blooded witch-
she'll even forget about her
own parent's death for money!
Just chalk it up to bad luck
that you crossed her and give up.
I see.
Though it's not like I ever
trusted her to begin with.
Even if she were a homicidal maniac,
I wouldn't be too surprised.
In that case, could you
get the hell out of here?!
You're an eyesore!
What happened?!
Why'd he suddenly jump into the water?!
Is someone pulling some kinda lame joke?
No, it's not like he slipped or anything...
Then he ran away!
No, his arms and legs're tied!
He can't swim like that!
It's a suicide!
Leave him be.
Can't believe he'd kill himself...
He was terrifyingly good at giving up!
It's like, damn, value your life more!
T-That idiot!
He's back up!
Hey! What's going on, Nami?!
What do you think you're doing?!
No, what do you think you're doing?!
You're just a small fry who
can't even watch one guy die...
Quit tryin' to act cool!
Save me sooner next time, you idiot!
I thought I was gonna die!
Screw you!
Mess with me any more and you will die!
I wonder.
That's a lot of bandages you have.
Didn't have a change of clothes,
so I used these instead.
Hey, Nami.
What should we do with him?
Lock him up! I'll deal with him myself!
Arlong-san! Arlong-san!
What is it, brother?
I'm sorry!
That guy had a long-nosed friend with him,
but he got away!
What the hell, Usopp?!
You wound up getting spotted anyway?!
I think he might've escaped
into Cocoyashi Village...
Cocoyashi Village, huh?
Perfect.
I have other business there, too.
Guess I'll head out for a bit.
Hey! Arlong's coming!
What?! What for?!
We just paid our tribute money to him!
It's probably about the weapons of mine they found...
Return to your houses, everyone.
Gen-san...
They're here!
So you're the bastard who
was in possession of weapons...
Yes. That's right...
Because I've always enjoyed looking at weapons.
Are collections not allowed
under your rule, either?
No, I can't have that.
Weapons breed nothing but evil thoughts and violence.
They're the chief things that undermine peace.
He's huge! That's Arlong?!
H-He's not human!
Nope. Because he's a Fishman.
Yeah...
I control 20 towns and villages.
As their manager, I can't afford to have rebellions.
I destroyed the great port
town of Gosa as an example
to the other communities!
The blunder of being unable to pay tribute money
is an act of rebellion against us!
Hey! Tribute money?
Exactly as it sounds.
It's money that we offer to them.
We buy our lives every month with money.
Adults and kids...
If anyone in a village can't
pay the tribute money...
If there's even just one person...
...the village gets wiped out just like Gosa.
Then that huge town was destroyed
just because of one person?!
That's how Arlong governs.
They're species-obsessed and don't
give a damn about killing people.
Listen.
You lowly humans simply need to
keep paying up without thinking!
I need enormous funds!
Your tribute money will eventually become the cornerstone
of the Arlong Empire,
which will rule the East Blue!
A-Arlong Empire?!
They're planning to turn the entire
East Blue into a Fishman empire?!
Hurry and escape.
Before Arlong comes back.
Gen-san!
The possession of weapons
is a clear sign of rebellion!
To keep any more rebels
like you from showing up,
I'm going to kill you right now,
as an example to the other humans!
No way!
He'll kill someone just for having a weapon?!
He has no right...
H-H-Hey, you!
You have no right to do this, Arlong!
For these past eight years straight,
we've paid you your tribute money!
Why would we want to
rebel now, of all times?!
Take your hands off Gen-san!
Yeah!
It's not like he used any weapons!
Stop this!
Let Gen-san go!
I'm saying that the possession of
weapons indicates the will to rebel.
Or what?
Shall the entire village be destroyed?
If just one of you lays a hand on us,
your village will meet its demise.
Either way is fine with me!
Get inside, everyone!
If we cause trouble now, the last
eight years will be for nothing!
If you're going to fight to
the death to defy his rule,
then you should've done
so eight years ago instead!
But we all swore to fight the patient fight!
To live!
Gen-san!
But...
What a valuable opinion!
You're a great speaker!
Yes! Being alive is enjoyable!
Even for puny insects like you!
Gen-san!
Not all living things are born equal!
– Damn you!
– Stop!
Don't do anything!
B-But, Gen-san!
If you die, it's all over!
Don't stop fighting the patient fight!
Even if I die!
That's nice resolve!
Pay close attention, humans!
This is what happens to those who
have even a sliver of evil thoughts!
Exploding Star!
W-What was that?!
Look! Up there!
There's someone on the roof!
Who the hell are you?!
My name is Captain Usopp,
Brave Warrior of the Sea!
Him!
T-The world fears me and
calls me Demon King Usopp,
the man from the netherworld!
If you run away now, I'll forgive you!
I have 8,000...
Arlong-san! That's him!
The guy who got away earlier!
Eep.
Bring all the tens of thousands of men you want.
I'll tear apart every last one!
He's not scared, and the
Exploding Star had no effect!
What has a human...
...a mere, lowly human... done to me?!
Arlong-san! Wait!
We'll lose another source
of tribute money, after Gosa!
Human settlements are easy to destroy,
but our goal is to rule them!
If we lose some, we can just get some more!
We are the supreme species!
Now he's destroying the village!
Is he-
Whoa! I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
H-He's still alive! After 'im!
Crap!
Catch him and kill him!
Hey! Let's get back to Arlong Park!
He's seriously about to destroy the village!
Yeah!
Do not let him get away!
Who does he take us for?!
We'll be back another day.
Looks like you're spared for now!
I'm sorry... I caused you all trouble...
What are you talking about?
You're not at fault here!
Yeah!
But who was that youngster earlier?
Everyone! It's good to see you again!
Nami!
– It's Nacchan!
– It's her!
What's going on?
You never walk right through the village...
I heard a loud sound...
Arlong, huh?
Just seven million berries left to go...
You have as horrible a reputation as ever.
That's fine. I am a pirate!
But Arlong's a reasonable guy.
Money will fix all this,
so it's just a little more until our agreement.
No matter what, I'm going
to earn 100 million berries
and buy this village!
She tells me to run, but I got
nowhere else to go but here...
Plus I promised Luffy I'd bring her back.
What's he up to now?
Things're starting to get messy.
Yahoo! So fast! So fast!
Big Bro Luffy! I see it! Arlong Park!
Go! To Arlong Park!
hamidashita kimochi tsunagara nakute
my overflowing feelings don't connect
kimi no te o gyutto ni girikaesu yo
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
hitori demo boku wa arukidasu kara
I'll set off by myself,
tooku made zutto mitsumeteite ne
so keep watching me intently as I go into the distance
kesa kara chotto kangaeteita
I was thinking about it a bit since this morning
doushite konna ni atsui no
why is it so hot?
itsu kara ka sonna koto bakari ga
starting from some point,
hanarenai yo
I haven't been able to get away from that
kakedashita kimochi tsukamaetakute
I want to catch those feelings that rushed off,
jibun sae mou oikoshite yuku yo
and I'm already about to overtake myself, even
tobidashita yume o dakishimetetai
I want to embrace my dreams that have jumped out
issho nara boku wa hashitte yukeru
with you, I can run there
Hey! Luffy!
Why're you flying here in a boat?!
'Cause I was in a hurry!
That's not what I meant!
What the hell are you doing?!
I'm here to get Nami back!
Have you still not found her?
About that... it's a long story.
That reminds me, where's Long-nose?
Crap! He's been caught by Arlong!
Next time, on One Piece:
Usopp Dead?!
When is Luffy Going to Make Landfall?
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Usopp Dead?!
When is Luffy Going
to Make Landfall?