Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Now with Jinbe and Crocodile,
they're battling on Level 4!
This is the great fort
of hell! No one may pass!
No Price Too High!
Serious Hannyabal
Who is that?! Why did he
open the door so wide?!
He is Hannyabal - the vice
warden of this prison!
Shoot!
Look!
We have a thousand Cage Shot bazooka
troops on the stairway to Level 3!
There's no way out for you guys!
--Vice Warden got all fired up!
--Maybe somebody's posing as him again!
This is for the bright future
of all innocent people!
You, the worst pirate in
the history, Straw Hat!
I impose the death penalty on
you on the Warden's behalf!
He's really out of character!
Outta my way!
No way!
I can't believe it!
Hey! Look at that halberd!
That's the Bloodsucker!
You bastard!
Don't underestimate me!
--Looks like he's serious!
--Then we can depend on him because he's strong!
Hannya! Hannya! Hannya! Hannya!
W-What's going on here?
As you may know, it's the Hannya Hustle Dance: Inferno Hell Wheel!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
If you don't move, I'll move
you myself! I gotta save Ace!
That's hilarious!
If I moved away that easily,
I wouldn't be the vice warden!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Gatling!
We've been waiting for you!
Warden Magellan, please hurry!
Where are the ringleaders?!
In front of the staircase to Level 3!
That's the opposite side of
this floor! We have to hurry!
Vice Warden Hannyabal and the others are
managing to keep them there for now!
Vice Warden!
That was too easy! I'm not
a very good vice warden!
If he were here...
"Warden's Office"
Twenty years ago
T-This is my first day as a jailer!
My name is Hannyabal!
You look like a viper as they say.
What?! No! That hurts!
You're the only person who can
look out for him as I thought.
Magellan!
I got it, sir!
Damn Magellan!
Why should I be assigned to Level 1?
On top of that,
I'm only in charge of
the security check for new prisoners!
--The next one has come!
--Oh, okay!
She has a 50-million-berry
bounty. A pirate--Ms. Olive!
She's a vicious criminal!
Take extra care with her!
She's so my type! Oops, I
shouldn't have said that!
He was so easy! Like all other men!
I gotta strip all my clothes off, right?
It's embarrassing,
so can you turn away?
S-Sure!
Are you ready yet?
Not yet!
How foolish is he?
Quite.
L-Let me go!
Don't let your guard down!
Ouch!
It doesn't matter if it's Level 1 or
6! All duties are equally important!
You gotta keep in mind what's going
to happen if any one person fails!
Let me go!
It's not over yet!
You can't go through here!
Follow the Vice Warden! Don't hold back!
Bring it on!
Outta my way!
I'm gonna save Ace!
So what?! It's not over yet!
Outta my way!
You...
You can't go through here!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
Stop!
Quit bothering me!
Dammit! I have to hurry to make it on time!
You can't go through here!
You're the King of Diarrhea!
Why don't you wear a toilet
seat instead of your hat?!
He's been cussing for more than 30 minutes!
That's our Captain Buggy!
Your mom's got an outie belly button!
I don't have anything more to say!
I can't ad-lib anything else!
A-Are you alright?
Magellan's kind of tough, huh?
Let me just go to the bathroom!
D-Don't tell us...
...that you got diarrhea, Captain Buggy?!
No, I just wanna pee! Ha!
Then, we'll go with you!
What should I do?!
If nothing happens,
we can't break out and
my reputation will be ruined!
I gotta come up with something!
What shitty fortifications!
That didn't help them avoid their destiny!
Liberation!
That's a long leak!
You gotta hear this, Captain Buggy!
What's wrong?
The wall...
...is gone!
What did you just say?!
W-What happened?!
The block of poison's really gone!
My attack finally worked!
What a pain in the butt!
So you were really fighting the
venom with your venomous tongue!
Was the peeing part of it?!
Cool! I knew that you were in another league!
Oh no. This doesn't make sense at all.
Alright! The block is gone now!
Come and follow my lead, you guys!
Stop bothering me!
Get out of my way!
No, I won't!
--I said "Outta my way!"
--I won't let you go a single step!
There's no time!
I said "Outta my way!"
I... I gotta save Ace!
"Wanna save my brother?"
You're the dreg of society
so just cut the crap!
You guys are all pirates and
rebels who earn only infamy!
--Vice Warden Hannyabal!
--Don't stand up! You're gonna die!
With you on the seas,
people can't even sleep at night from
fear of losing their loved ones!
That's why we lock up all the vicious
criminals to make them feel safe!
This is the great fort of hell!
If we let prisoners out of here, the
world will be filled with terror!
So as I said, I won't let you take...
...even a single step!
Vice Warden!
The only thing I care about
is saving Ace! So just move!
You're too stupid to understand...
V-Vice Warden, help me!
Hey, what's the matter, you guys?!
Cut it out!
All this arguing about right and wrong!
Search the ends of the earth,
and you'd find no answer!
So, cut the crap!
I met him at Jaya!
Wow! Wow!
How interesting to see
all these faces at once!
Looks like you were in middle of something!
Teach! Why the hell are you here?!
Or should I call you Blackbeard now?
Jinbe!
Hey, that's not nice! Why
don't you loosen your fist?!
Oh yeah! You're close to Ace, aren't you?
But you're barking up the wrong tree!
Blackbeard!
I'm chasing a certain man.
His name is Blackbeard.
People's dreams...
...have no end!
I heard a pirate called Blackbeard...
...became a Warlord by
defeating Fire Fist Ace.
Blackbeard...
So you're...
You're...
...Blackbeard?!
Huh? Oh yeah, I never gave you my name.
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
I was surprised, too, when I heard
you were my commander's brother!
Are you sure you want to be
here? You're gonna miss it!
Your brother's public execution!
I found out later that the
former Warlord right there...
...Crocodile was defeated
by you, Straw Hat Luffy!
At that time, I was trying to
take his place as a Warlord so...
...killing you was the most effective way
to show my ability to the Government!
Teach, let's cut the idle talk!
You should know the rules, having
lived through twice as much as others.
Whitebeard's reign is over! I'll
become the next Pirate King!
For starters, I'm gonna kill Straw Hat
Luffy who is in the Water Seven...
...as a gift to the Government!
Luffy? What did you just say?
Oh! You know him?!
Another reason I can't let you go free!
He's my brother!
But fate has saved you instead!
Ace who has been chasing after me for
the crime on Whitebeard's ship...
...happens to be your brother!
When he faced us - we, who were
going to kill his brother -
he had his retreat cut off!
If I yield to power, there's
no point in being born a man.
I'll never leave anything to
be regretted later in my life!
Do you understand, stupid?
The sun or the darkness -
there'll be only one winner!
I'm gonna make Whitebeard the king!
Do you get it?
If he let us get away, not only
would it disgrace Whitebeard's name
but he'd allow his brother's death!
There's no coincidence in fate! That means...
Yeah! You're so lucky! Burp...
Our captain became the
Warlord and made his name
so you're useless to us now!
Your brother fought bravely!
Pay your respects at his grave!
If it weren't for him,
you'd be the one who...
...would've been killed, Straw Hat!
Then why don't you...
...try to kill me now?!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Pistol!
While attempting to escape during the choas,
Luffy is confronted by Blackbeard.
Blackbeard tells of his involvement
in arranging Ace's execution.
Having heard that,
Luffy ends up fighting him, enraged.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Jet Pistol of Rage
Luffy vs. Blackbeard"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Jet Pistol of Rage
Luffy vs. Blackbeard