Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil.
Super it's getting pretty exciting, isn't it?!
There are 50,000 enemies. This is the perfect opportunity to unveil them!
Them?!
What are they, Franky?!
There are 2 new weapons on the Sunny!
Who wants to ride along?
What?! New weapons?!
Three-Sword Style...
Kalasutra: Grand Dragon Twister!
--It won't stop! --It's like a cyclone of blades!
--Run! Or you're gonna get cut! --Don't come after us!
It'll chase you to hell's end!
Huh? Where did he go?
Sky...
...Walk!
Cool! Sanji is in the air!
Diable Jambe,
Poele a Frire:
...Spectre!
Doesn't matter if there are 100,000 or 1,000,000!
We'll just beat them all!
"Unveiled! The Secret Weapons of the Sunny!"
How annoying...
It's not over yet, Mosshead!
You can't top me, Nosebleed!
Why are they competing against each other?
Ignore them. They're always like that.
Honestly, that side of them hasn't changed a bit!
Everybody's getting pretty warmed up, aren't they?
Maybe it's time for them!
--By them, you mean... --Finally, the new weapons?!
That's right! Follow me!
We've been waiting for this!
Oh, hey, wait!
G-Guys! Don't leave me alone!
You're bugging me! Go somewhere else!
You go!
Don't push your luck, you bastards!
--Shut up! --Shut up!
They're too strong...
What did you just say?
Nothing!
The humans are "too strong"?
How dare you call yourself a Fishman?
C-Captain!
I-I'm sorry!
Don't disappoint me.
I don't need a soldier who is afraid of...
...stupid humans!
Why don't you kill Shirahoshi already?
It's awesome down here!
Did you change something?
There wasn't a "5" or a "6" before!
You're right! And "0" is gone!
It's been renovated!!
I remodeled "0" to create "5" and "6."
The new weapons are in "4" which was empty before
and in the newly made "5."
Okay, hurry up! I wanna see the new weapons already!
Alright, alright!
Take a look and be surprised!
Here they are!
Cool!
Let's finish this up already-dosun!
Artillery Unit!
Kill Shirahoshi!
I do not like it!
You want to hurt the world's favorite Mermaid Princess?!
Party music!
What's going on? It got dark all of a sudden.
It's nice to have you along on this festival night!
What the...
Is this...
...An amusement park?
Hey, let's dance!
Huh? Were we just dreaming?
Now, set off the fireworks!
This is fun!
It's beautiful!
Hey! I said "Kill the Princess"-bokan!
But...
Dosun-san, we're enjoying today's joyous festival...
Okay, I cut you already.
What?
Quinto Tierce Fantasia!
Huh?
Ganging up on a weak woman? You people are a bunch of brutes.
Mil Fleurs...
...Gigantesco Mano...
Legs?!
...Stomp!
Sorry!
--People are screaming outside. --What's going on?
Hey guys, get out! It's too tight!
You have no interest in the new weapons! You get off!
I'm here because I'm scared!
I don't wanna be alone, either!
Franky, do we have to wait much longer?!
Don't rush it!
It's all set!
I'm getting excited too!
Wait a minute! I need to operate this thing so...
It got more spacious!
What's going on in here?!
Alright, here are the new weapons on the Soldier Dock of the Sunny!
--I'm excited! --What's gonna happen?!
It's time to unveil!
Deadly Venom Squad, go!
Even if you got giant legs or arms,
you're dead meat once you're stung by our venom!
Hold it right there!
The Soldier Dock System!
Channel 4!
--The door opened! --Destroy that stupid ship!
Black Rhino...
...FR-U 4!
The Soldier Dock System!
Channel 4!
Black Rhino...
...FR-U 4!
Cool! It's a cy-bike!
What is it?! Looks so tough!
What did you say about venom?
What the hell?!
Sting it if you can! This steel monster!
It's super cool, isn't it?!
Stop that guy!
All right!
Steel on steel!
I'll take care of it!
Here! Take this!
Hey!
The new number! Channel 5!
Brachio-Tank 5 is here!
It's like a dinosaur! I want it!
It's amazing!
Did you see my great shooting skill?
I bet this thing can do a lot more.
I thought he was a shipwright.
I am Commander Chopper!
I see some enemies at 9 o'clock!
Fire!
You're so cool, Commander!
Hey, you! Fight!
Wow! They're so strong!
There are only 10 of them but they're kicking the asses of 100,000.
The Straw Hat Pirates...
Maybe, they can save us all and Fishman Island for real!
Go, Straw Hat!
Beat Hody!
You're doing great, Straw Hat!
Boss Jinbe!
If you win, I'll let you eat as much as you want at my restaurant!
You can drink as much as you want too, at my bar!
--Straw Hat! --We're counting on you!
Boss Jinbe!
Don't push your luck!
Come on out, Kraken!
No...
It's huge!
There are only 10 of them! Just crush them all!
Then it'll finally be over!
Oh no! They got the mythical monster - Kraken!
Watch out!
Even though the Straw Hats are strong,
they're finished once they get crushed by that thing!
Oh, it's the Kraken! He'll do whatever Captain tells him to!
He's as strong as hell!
See how formidable this deep-sea creature is!
Hey, that's...
What are you doing?!
Kill them already!
I brought you here all the way from the North Pole! You're my slave!
You have to work for me!
You can do it, can't you?
W-Wait a moment!
Fall back!
Hey, if I remember right, that's...
I don't think there are many others!
Huh? You two know him?!
I didn't expect to see him here.
Oh, hey, Surume!
It's me! Surume!
Oh? Don't you remember me?
How could you forget?!
You became my pet for a while. I'm your friend!
Oh no, the Sea Spirit is...
Alright, that's enough. Stop!
Good job!
I can't believe it! You really tamed the monster octopus?
Yeah, I'm gonna use him like experienced people do! Right, Surume?
Let me ride on you again!
He did it!
Luffy-sama!
That tickles! Stop! Surume!
All right, Surume! Let's go!
The Kraken betrayed us!
Stop Kraken!
You stupid octopus!
Go Surume!
Help me, Captain!
Kraken, go that way!
Damn! What's going on?!
The Kraken is totally bonded to Straw Hat!
Listen, Surume! Stay here and protect Wimpyhoshi!
I can't believe you knew the Kraken!
I'm so impressed! You have so many friends!
Yeah?
Um, thank you for doing this, Surume-sama!
There are still a lot of them.
All right! Let's go!
Using their new weapon, Franky, Usopp
and Chopper were making good progress,
until they fell into the trap Daruma,
an officer of the New Fishman Pirates, had laid.
But then, the second of Sunny's new weapons commences its docking!
A wondrous robot emerged!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Iron Pirate! Here Comes General Franky!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!