Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can become Pirate King!
Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
BON VOYAGE!  hito kakera no yuuki hirogete
BON VOYAGE!      Let that shred of courage grow
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
saisho wa minna BARABARA ni egaite ita chiheisen
The horizons everyone dreamed of were separate at first
ima nara hitotsu no bouenkyou de nozokeru
but now they can be seen through a single telescope
kimi no KOKORO madowasu unmei no shoppai KONPASU
A bitter compass of destiny is leading your heart astray
saka te ni kajitoru yo
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
BON VOYAGE!
SHIGARAMI mo kako mo sutete
Toss aside your bonds and your past
bokura nara sore demo waraeteru hazu
We can surely smile despite that
yume o kanaeru tame no namida naraba oshikuwanai
Tears shed trying to achieve your dreams aren't for naught
PRECIOUS IN MY LIFE
precious in my life
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
Upper Yard
Angel Island
In an attempt to obtain gold,
Upper Yard
Angel Island
the crew split up into Nami's escape
team and Luffy's search team.
Upper Yard
Angel Island
They agreed to meet again on
the eastern shore, then departed.
Luffy's team ventured
through the unsettling forest
as they headed for ruins in the south,
but they were attacked by a giant
snake and wound up separated.
This isn't good...
I returned to our course, but no one is coming...
Did I get separated?
Oh, no! I got separated! Huh?! Huh?!
H-Help! Where is everyone?!
Where are they?
I look away for a second and this happens...
Oh, well. I'm sure they'll manage somehow.
I got most of the map memorized, anyway.
It's to the right.
Yeesh, where'd they all go? Am I lost now?
Oh, well.
Guess I'll go ahead and wait at the ruins.
She said "straight south,"
and south is in a warm-ish direction!
This way!
Meanwhile, Wyper and the Shandian warriors
headed for God's Shrine to defeat Eneru.
However, Eneru, who uses Mantra to see all,
let his priests use the entire island
as locations for their ordeals
to begin a game of survival.
The Deadly Reject!
War Demon Wyper's Resolve
When I first met you, I said one
reason I became a soldier-for-hire
was because Blue Sea people
cannot handle sky combat.
Sky combat? What's that?
Hmm. In that case, place that barrel there.
Barrel?
– Watch...
– What're we doing this for now?
You will see.
Try crushing that shell with all your might.
Gently now, Sanji! If you smash a
hole in the deck, you're gonna pay!
Hit it with all your might.
Quit saying whatever you want
when it's not your ship!
Alright, if that's what you want...
Wait! Wait!
You don't need to swing it that hard!
Hey, what're you doing?
I know I told you to hold back,
but you didn't even crack the barrel...
No, I hit it as hard as I could.
I was ready to put a hole in the deck...
Hey!
Yet, it's almost like this
shell absorbed the shock...
Now, point the dial's holes at the empty barrel
and press the back tip of the shell.
You know how to press it, yes?
Click...
That is an Impact Dial.
It can absorb and freely
release shocks given to it.
Normally, they're affixed to the
palms using gloves or bandages.
They're powerful enough that a direct
hit can kill your average person.
Usopp... This is...
Yeah... This is what that dumpling priest used!
It is different from a hit!
Impact!
But why couldn't you have said so sooner?!
That freaked me out, you geezer!
I hear there existed even more
powerful dials in ancient sky islands.
Now-extinct "Reject Dials" that
could release ten times the energy
of these Impact Dials...
But they were a double-edged sword,
as the excessive shock from using
them put the user's own life at risk.
Though, naturally, it seems
they were hardly ever used...
There're shells that dangerous?!
Those're practically weapons!
I thought dials were more common,
everyday objects...
Yes, they are.
But what seems useful can
always be used for evil as well,
depending on who uses it.
Dials are extremely useful,
but that makes them all the more powerful in battle.
For example, even a Heat Dial used to warm food
can turn a spear into a controllable,
high-temperature "Heat Javelin."
A flame-storing Flame Dial,
placed inside a bird's mouth,
can create the truly rare "fire-breathing bird"...
Yeah, Chopper did mention stuff like that!
– And that's "sky combat"?
– Yes.
Blue Sea people unfamiliar with dials
cannot ascertain our techniques.
The same is true for our
many types of artificial clouds.
The warriors of the sky are trained to master them;
those with no knowledge of
them do not stand a chance.
Then is there some reason
behind the "Mantra" thing
that lets them read our
movements ahead of time?
Mantra, huh...?
I'm unable to use it myself,
so I can't explain it very well,
but it is said that "Mantra" is a listening ability.
Supposedly, just by living, people
give off voices from their bodies.
– Voices?
– Yes.
By listening to them, one can allegedly
tell what a person will do next.
With further mastery, you can hear
voices over an even wider area.
The priests can hear all throughout Upper Yard,
and Eneru's powers extend
across this entire land.
And those powers are all too mysterious.
Because of them, the people of this
land have no time to feel at ease.
Have they reached the bottom yet?
Yes. They are already waiting eagerly.
There are the three priests' ordeals,
on top of Commander Yama's
fifty Divine Soldiers...
God. You're waging all-out war.
Is such severity really necessary?
We're only dealing with a few
Shandians and Blue Sea people.
Festivals are more fun the livelier they are.
Plus, you're making light of the
underlying power of sky combat.
Underlying power?
Yes, that's right.
They'll show you soon enough.
Banana.
Now, then.
We have fifty Divine Soldiers and three priests.
Including me, that makes 54 people.
Currently, there are twenty
Shandians heading for the island,
there are four Blue Sea people in the forest,
and four attempting to escape.
No, make that three.
I doubt the old man can fight now.
81 people, altogether!
This will be a battle for survival.
Shall I guess how many will have
fallen three hours from now?
Honestly...
You're so quick to make things into games.
Oh, come now!
Hey, you guess.
Eh?! M-Me?
No, I have no understanding of such things, so...
Huh? What's with you? Don't be a party-pooper.
Just use your hunch.
Okay, then. You guess!
Y-Yes...
Well, the three priests are powerful enough,
but the fifty Divine Soldiers
are all quite strong as well...
So I doubt many of them will be defeated at all,
but the enemy is also strong enough
to compete with the priests...
Given three hours, I suspect thirty people will fall.
Therefore, about fifty will survive...
I see! Fifty, huh?
But don't you think that's a little too optimistic?
You're underestimating this battle, you know...
Then, what do you predict, God?
All right, allow me to answer straight-out.
In three hours, only five of the 81
people on this island will be standing.
What the...?!
My body!
W-What the...?! I can't move!
Hello there, Shandians.
Looking good.
Forgive my rude welcome.
Shura!
Yes, yes. I know my name.
I don't need you all to tell me.
It's unfortunate news for you...
...but Upper Yard's layout has changed
from how it was until last night.
Can't move, can you? That's just fine.
The survival rate is 3%...
...here in the String Ordeal!
The String Ordeal?!
I would say watch out,
but it's too late for that now.
String Clouds?!
Indeed. I'm impressed you could tell.
What covers my area are String
Clouds so fine they can't be seen,
but are so strong in bunches that
they can stop even grown men.
And you pulled them all in yourselves
from the island's entrance.
Look closely. You're covered in strings.
This is what they mean by,
"You reap what you sow!"
Except...
...for one of you!
Let's go, Fuza!
Wyper!
Don't assume you can match me in mid-air!
Watch out! It's a Heat Javelin!
Why would you throw your shield and gun away?! Are you a fool?!
No, he wouldn't...!
If you want a shoulder, you can have one.
An Impact, huh?! Such things can't defeat me!
No, it's ten times the energy.
Reject!
The Upper Yard survival game...
One has dropped out. Eighty remain...
The first battle ends in a great upset...
Shura has been defeated.
M-My word! Shura-sama has?!
He underestimated sky combat, too. The fool!
But is this not cause for distress?!
Two priests, undefeated for six years,
suddenly fall in under two days!
No. It can't be helped that they were defeated.
They must not have had
God's divine protection...
Alright, men! We're up against twenty
Shandians and seven Blue Sea people!
This will be easy.
There is no need to trouble the priests with them.
Go, and wreak havoc to your hearts' content!
The 50 Divine Soldiers of Skypiea
Those who can step over comrades
and keep moving, come with me!
Today... Eneru's head will be mine!
Once we defeat Eneru, we won't need
to revere a single bag of Vearth.
A single bag of Vearth...
Wyper! Are you trying to die?!
Try using the Reject Dial one more time!
Your body'll be blown apart!
So what about my body?
Isn't that called "resolve"?!
These guys can't be beaten
without such sacrifices!
That bastard!
What're you standin' around for?
Braham!
We're behind enemy lines now.
Let's all split up.
There are still two priests out there.
Seems they've changed the locations of the ordeals.
We don't wanna all get caught
in the same ordeal again.
There's no reason to be that stupid...
I'm going on ahead!
Fine! Do what you want!
At least pray for everyone's good luck!
Alright, guys! Watch yourselves out there!
Let's meet at God's Shrine!
Who're you?! What have you done?!
– Heso!
– A Divine Soldier?!
Indeed! By God Eneru's orders,
we've been sent to clean out all of Upper Yard!
Accept the fact there is no escape
from us fifty elite Divine Soldiers!
Taste the wrath of the Axe Dial,
which does not exist in Skypiea!
Out of the way!
Even deeper! Even sharper!
Axe Dial!
Shields have no effect!
♪ The islands in the south are warm... ♪
♪ Pineapple-ple, head all warm,
what a dummy... ♪
A goat? Was that a goat? Where is it?
A goat in a forest?
Aww, man! Jerk got my hopes up!
And I was all excited to see a goat!
Second verse!
♪ The islands in the north are cold... ♪
♪ All chilly-like, head all shivery,
what a dummy... ♪
Oh, it's you!
What are you doing here?
I warned you to leave this island!
Shut up! I can do what I want.
No, you can't.
This island belongs to us Shandians!
Eh? It does? I thought it was God's...
Really? Well, pardon my intrusion.
Third verse!
♪ The eastern... ♪
Wait!
What do you want?!
No, I have nothing to say.
Nor do I want to hear any of your garbage.
I simply want to eliminate you!
Oh.
That's nice and easy to understand, then!
Itsumo no you ni zenryoku shissou
Racing full speed ahead as always
A to Z hashirinuketeku
A to Z, we run through it
Nayandari suru sa shichiten battou
We all have worries and fall many times
Itsuka joushou sureba ii zetchou
But we just need to rise to the top someday
Asahi noboru ano umi no
What could be beyond the sea
mukou-gawa ni nani ga arun darou
in which the morning sun rises?
Koukou to hikaru taiyou no aru houkou sukoshi zutsu ikou
Let's go little by little toward the brilliantly shining sun
I never treat you "bad"
Nankai koronda?
How many times did we fall?
Daijoubu bokutachi wa tashika ni ima ashita ni sa yubisashiten da
It's all right, we're definitely pointing at tomorrow now
Smile! Come back to you, friends
Come back to you, friends
Right, right, right...
Where the hell did Luffy and the others go?
Who're you?!
I should never have come!
The forest has become quite lively...
I ain't the type of guy who'll die when told to.
I accept this survival challenge!
Next time, on One Piece:
Fierce Midair Battle!
Pirate Zoro vs. Warrior Braham
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Fierce Midair Battle!
Pirate Zoro vs. Warrior Braham