Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
A Town That
Welcomes Pirates?
Setting Foot on Whisky Peak
What in the world is with this snow?
It was warm just a little while ago.
All right! Done!
This is the man that fell from the sky, Mr. Snow Barrel!
That's such a crude snowman...
What?!
Look at my soulful artwork,
the Snow Queen!
Whoa! That's incredible!
Okay then! Snow Barrel Punch!
What the hell are you doing?!
Ahh! Mr. Snow Barrel!
How dare you...?!
Damn you! Damn you!
How is this?!
You bastard! Hold it, Luffy!
How come they're so
energetic when it's this cold?
Nami-san! How much snow shoveling
of love would you like me to do?!
Please continue until it stops snowing, Sanji-kun!
Yaay! Nami-san!
Hey, you. Doesn't this ship have a heater?
I'm cold.
Shut up! You guys aren't guests!
Go help shovel snow or something!
Lightning?!
What on earth is going on
with the weather around here?!
It was sunny up until recently.
The next moment, it started snowing,
and now lightning...
The seasons, as well as the weather,
go around randomly.
It's just like what Crocus-san said.
That's how it is in the Grand Line.
It seems that you guys're
clueless about the Grand Line.
You haven't been steering for a while now.
Is that really okay?
I just checked the direction.
Ahhhh!
Wh... What?
What's the matter?
What's wrong, Nami-san?!
Ahhh... No way!
Turn the ship around 180 degrees! Hurry!
180 degrees?! Why're we going back?!
Did you forget something?
The ship has turned around and
is going in the opposite direction!
When I looked away from
the log pose for a second...!
The waves were calm earlier...
Are you really a navigator?
In this sea, you can't trust the winds,
sky, waves, clouds... anything...
The only thing that doesn't change is
the direction that the log pose points.
Do you understand that?
Stop bossing me around in those
cozy blankets and go help already!
Brace the yard!
Receive the wind from the starboard!
Turn the ship 180 degrees to the left!
– Usopp! Take care of the lateen sail!
– Got it!
– Sanji-kun! Take the helm!
– Leave it to me, Nami-san!
You guys! I'm counting on you!
She's such a slave driver.
Hey, wait! The wind has changed.
No way!
It's the first spring gale!
Why?!
Don't just sleep there while
the snow accumulates on you!
Hey!
I saw a dolphin jump over there! Let's go there.
You keep quiet!
The waves are getting high!
I see an iceberg in the 10 o'clock direction!
Nami-san! It's getting foggy!
What the hell's with this sea?!
W-W... We're gonna crash!!
Hey!
Water's leaking at the bottom of the ship!
We have to patch it right away!
Got it!
The clouds are moving fast!
W-Wind's coming!
It's strong!
It's coming!
Unfurl the sails!
That wind is too strong!
If we take it directly, we'll overturn!
Everyone! Eat this!
Let's gather our strength!
You're eating too much!
Oh, crap! The sail is gonna be torn!
Forget about things up here.
Go fix the bottom of the ship!
There's another part of the
bottom of the ship damaged!
Dammit!
Ahhh, that felt good.
Hey, no matter how nice the weather is,
you guys shouldn't be so lazy.
We'd better be on the right track.
You...
Hm?
Why're you guys on this ship?
You're slow!
We're heading to their town right now.
It's called Whisky Peak.
You mean we're taking them back?
We don't owe them anything.
Right, we don't.
Well, not like it matters to me...
Yeah, your faces say that
you're thinking bad thoughts.
What were your names again?
I-I'm Mr. 9.
I'm Miss Wednesday.
Right... Something has been bothering
me ever since I first heard your names...
I feel like I've heard them
somewhere before, or maybe not...
Well, either way...
How dare you sleep comfortably all this time...?
You kept sleeping no matter how
many times we tried to wake you up...
What?!
Don't let your guard down, everyone!
We don't know what else might happen.
I was finally able to realize the danger of this sea just now.
I was able to understand the
reason why it's called the Grand Line.
There's no doubt about it, since my
navigation skills don't work at all.
How blunt... Are we gonna be okay?
We'll be fine!
Things will still work out for sure.
In fact...
Look! Our first journey is over.
It's an island!
So this is Whisky Peak...
But it's really a funny looking island.
Those cacti are huge!
Hm?
Well then, we'll be leaving now.
Thanks for taking us home, honeys.
If we're linked by fate, we'll meet again!
Bye bye, baby!
Huh?
They're gone...
Who on earth were they?
Who cares? We're landing!
There's a river at the front.
Looks like we can go inland by ship.
I-Isn't it possible that there're
monsters or things like that?
It's definitely possible.
This is the Grand Line.
If we come across monsters,
we can just leave the island.
Hold on a sec.
Don't forget that we have to stay
on this island for a certain period of time.
Why?
Unless we store the magnetism
of this island in the log pose,
we can't go to the next island.
Since each island requires a different
amount of time to store the log,
some islands require only several
hours while others require days.
Th-Then even if this is a monster island
that we want to escape from right away,
it's possible that we have to stay
here for days until the log is stored?
That's right.
Well, we can think about that
when it happens. Let's go already!
Luffy's right. Let's go.
It's not worth thinking about it.
No matter what happens, I'll protect Nami-san.
H-Hey, wait. Listen, everyone.
My chronic illness is suddenly...
My "do not go to the island" disease is...
Then we're going in.
– Listen. Make sure you're prepared to run as well as fight.
– No...
Ah, well... like I said, my chronic illness is...
Well, I guess you're not listening...
I wonder what'll appear...
P-Please...
Hey, it's a pirate ship.
Pirates are here!
Huh? Something's moving.
Humans? Humans are there!
Everyone, be careful.
Ahhh, dammit!
Since it's come to this, I've prepared myself.
Monsters or whatever you are, come on out!
Welcome to the Grand Line!
Welcome to our town!
To the welcoming town, Whisky Peak!
F... Far from monsters, we're being welcomed!
What's going on?
Pirates! Welcome to our town!
Hurray for the heroes on the sea!
Whoa! There're lots of cute girls!
Ahh! Look this way! They're handsome!
Maybe pirates are people's heroes after all.
Heeeey!
Welco...
Ma-ma-ma...
Welcome.
My name is Igarappoi.
I'm the mayor of Whisky Peak.
Okay. I'm Luffy. Nice to meet you.
Pops, you went overboard on curling your hair.
Whisky Peak is a town that thrives
on making liquor and music.
Hospitality is the pride of our town.
As for our proud liquor,
it's as bountiful as the seawater.
Would you allow us to throw a party for you
so that we may hear your tales of...
Ma-ma-ma...
...your tales of adventure?
We'll be glad to!
All right!
Three idiots...
Say, by the way,
how long will it take for the log
of this island to be stored?
Log? Forget such boring stuff.
Please just rest after such a long journey.
Now, everyone! Prepare for the party!
Sing to entertain the adventurers!
Party time!!
Then I said with utter coolness,
"Sea Kings, don't you touch my friends."
– Captain Usopp!
– You're so amazing!
– Wow...
Well, regarding the Calm Belt,
even I trembled a bit, though.
– A tremble of excitement, that is.
– Whoa!
– Amazing!
– Cheers to Usopp-san!
Now, please don't hold back, drink up.
No, thank you.
I'd rather not drink alcohol.
Don't worr...
Ma-ma-ma...
Don't worry.
It's a special drink made of prime grapes
that are used to make prime wine.
Its flavor is wine itself,
but it doesn't contain alcohol.
I see...
You're right! This is delicious!
We had a good grape harvest again this year.
Now, to celebrate the harvest,
we'll have our usual toast competition!
That is, you continue to toast and
the last one standing is the winner.
Please join in on our competition.
No thanks. I can't drink that much.
The prize money for the
winner is 100,000 Berries!
Another cup, please!
Zoro! You participate, too!
You don't have money, do you?
What?!
Cheers!
Whoa! Amazing! He finished his 10th cup!
This is it. I can't drink any more.
This girl's downing her 12th cup!
Take that!
More food!
Whoa!
The captain finished a meal for 20 people!
The cook is down!
Please, I can't go on...
Whoa! This young man is trying
to hit on 20 girls at the same time!
What's with this gang?!
It's really a fu...
Ma-ma-ma...
...a fun night!
I'm glad that you all seem to be having fun.
Yes, indeed, I'm very glad...
For that reason, we failed our mission of securing food...
However, we'd like to report that we succeeded
in leading the gang to Cactus Island. Baby.
All right! If we submit this, we somehow
should be able to clear our names.
Right.
I'll drop it in the Unluckies Box immediately.
They'll deliver it for us...
...to the boss...
This is it. I quit. I'm gonna sleep.
Whoa! The young man is finally
down after his 13th cup.
What?! You're hopeless, Zoro!
There're only two left.
They're at the 15th cup.
She's competing against the sister.
You should quit soon, too, for your own sake.
Don't be silly!
I definitely won't quit until I get the prize money.
Ahhh! Thanks for the food.
I can't eat any more.
Three cooks are also down!
Glad you enjoyed it.
I can't drink any more.
I won!!
Ahh, what fun!
She's finally down.
What a nice town...
This is a paradise.
So they wore themselves out
partying and fell asleep...
Sweet dreams...
...adventurers...
Again tonight the Cactus Rocks look beautiful,
dancing under the moonlight.
You're such a poet, Igarappoi... no, Mr. 8.
Oh, it's you guys...
What happened to them?
They've fallen...
...to hell...
Geez... Since they were so stubborn,
I added a little alcohol in their drinks.
Otherwise they might still be
up and having a good time.
But was it really necessary
to put on an elaborate act...
...for just five weak-looking brats?
We should've beat them at the harbor.
This town is already short of food.
Also, we didn't have our hopes up
for the whale meat anyway.
You didn't have to say it like that!
We did try our best!
Calm down. Look at this.
I've checked them out beforehand.
Th-Thirty million Berries?!
Them?!
It's foolish to judge a pirate's ability
based on their looks, Miss Mon...
Ma-ma-ma...
Miss Monday.
S-Sorry.
But we've already settled.
Looks like we can send a good report to the boss.
Confiscate all the money and other
valuables on the ship immediately.
So what about them?
What do we do?
If we kill them, the bounty drops by 30%.
The Government wants to hold public executions.
Go! Capture them alive!
Hey... Sorry, but...
...do you mind letting them sleep?
They're all exhausted from
the journey this afternoon.
Mr. 8! Miss Monday!
The guy with the bellyband escaped
from the room when we weren't looking!
He's over there.
You bastard...!
I thought you were completely asleep!
Swordsmen never make the mistake
of letting their guard down that much.
So, let's see if I've got this right.
This is a nest of bounty hunters.
You dupe pirates who are in high spirits
after having just entered the Grand Line.
Looks like there're about
100 bounty hunters here.
I'll fight you all... Baroque Works!
You bastard!
How is it that you know our company's name?!
When I used to be in a similar line of work,
I was recruited by your company once.
Naturally, I rejected it.
Employees don't know each other's
identity and are called by code names.
Of course, the boss' whereabouts and his
identity are also a mystery, even to them.
Baroque Works is a criminal group that
just faithfully carries out their orders.
Humph...! Was it a secret?
This is surprising...
If you know our secrets, then we have
no other choice but to kill you.
Another gravestone...
...will be added to the Cactus Rocks...
Kill him!
H... He disappeared...!
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Ah yasashi uta nee
Ah, gentle song
Todoke futari no tame ni
Make it there for us
Nami ga saratta chisana suna no oshiro
After a wave washed away that little sand castle
nagareru kumo o miagete naki souna egao
You looked up at the passing clouds with a sad smile
Moshi mo sekai juu ni teki shika inai nara
If you find the world is full of enemies,
senaka o makasete
I've got your back
Shinjiru kimochi o wasurenaide
Don't lose faith
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Ah itoshii hito nee
Ah, my love
Zutto daiteite ageru
I'll hold you in my arms forever
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
The welcoming town is a nest of bounty hunters.
Are you sure that you need
to add only one gravestone?
No one's eating that meat?
I wanna eat it.
It's a good chance to try out
the Kitetsu III and Yubashiri
I got in Loguetown.
Ladies, please come closer.
I'm Captain Usopp!
I'm going to go all-out!
Next time, on One Piece:
Explosion! The Three-Sword Style!
Zoro vs. Baroque Works!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Explosion!
The Three-Sword Style!
Zoro vs. Baroque Works!