Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy was suffering after losing his
brother Ace in the war against the Navy.
The Pirate King?!
Just then, Dark King Rayleigh
appeared before Luffy,
who was barely back on his feet.
Here's my second suggestion.
Meanwhile, the rest of the Straw
Hats learned what happened to Luffy
and realized how hard it
must have been for him.
Contact! The Great Swordsman, Mihawk
Zoro's Obstinate Struggle
This is Gloom Island in the Grand Line -
Gloom Island
the ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
There remains an old castle
from the long-dead kingdom...
which has been occupied
for several years now.
I can't believe Moria-sama died in the war!
You're grating on my ears.
Go somewhere else and cry.
How heartless are you to say
that when somebody's devastated?
Say something nice and bring
me a cup of hot cocoa!
I'm your guest!
I never invited you.
You two were living here without
asking when I wasn't here.
And...
...this article is not credible.
Huh?! Then you don't think that
Moria-sama died in the war?!
I don't know if he's dead or alive
but at least in my memory...
...Moria was alive on the battlefield.
If he's not dead, why did they say he is?
I don't know.
H-How did you get up?!
Stay in bed - you're useless!
What do you plan on doing with those swords?!
Are you going to push yourself again?
You can't beat those baboons.
They'll kill you this time...
Shut up!
It's none of your business!
How could you say that to me!?
Can't you see that I carried
you all the way here?!
Hawk-Eye!
See?! You can't even walk!
Why are you in such a hurry? You're wounded.
Because you told me what happened to Luffy.
How can I stay still!?
He's still alive probably.
But I assume that he's been
very badly traumatized.
Fire Fist Ace...
...died before Straw Hat's eyes.
I didn't even know that such
a huge war was underway!
Are you sure that Luffy's
okay?! Where is he now?!
Tell me more!
I told you everything that I know.
Then I'm sorry for bothering you.
Hey, wait!
Even if you can make it to the shore
without bumping into those baboons,
how are you gonna cross the sea?
If you want a small boat,
there is one on the west side of this castle.
Thank you for everything.
What the hell?!
You fool! I'm not gonna
care about you anymore!
I'll never ever save you!
Although you just lost your brother, Luffy,
I know you'll keep your promise!
That's why I'll get there,
too, at any cost...!
There you are!
I knew you guys weren't
gonna let me go so easily.
Bull Demon: Bold Hooves?!
That was Dragon Twister!
They're imitating my
Three-Sword Style skills!
Hey, you idiots!
How can you be so content to
copy somebody else's skills!
Don't mess with me!
Damn! He can't mess with me!
I've done so much for him!
I hope he drops dead! That'd serve him right!
Why don't you go and look if
you're so worried about Roronoa?
No way! Why should I worry about that fool?!
Well, I don't think that
he'd die that easily.
Look, he was already seriously injured
by the time Kuma blew him away!
So he could lose his life if he
fights against those baboons again.
Damn! Damn! Oh, dammit!
If he dies, I'll be stuck with this guy
who has no interest in cute stuffed animals
and who won't bring me a
bagel sandwich and hot cocoa!
I don't wanna be stuck with
that heartless Hawk-Eye guy!
I can't stand it!
Three Thousand Worlds!
What are you...
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame...
Admirable!
Hey, are you alive?
He must've gotten to the shore by now,
but I don't see any sign of him...
Maybe he's lost again!
Demon...
...Slash!
Stop putting spit on it! Where
did you learn that folk remedy?!
These bastards, they really
make a fool out of me!
I'll never make it to the sea at this pace!
Hawk-Eye...
It's been a while since you left the castle
and you've only made it this far, Roronoa?
The boat that I gave you seems useless now.
Shut up!
I'll just treat them like planks
and swim while hanging on to them.
It's nice that you care about your
friend so much but they're strong.
They're called Humandrills - baboons
that develop by imitating humans.
Humandrills?
They'd be peace-loving, if they
grew up around peaceful humans.
But on this island...
there was a war raging until 7 years ago.
When I came here to live, it still
smelled like blood and smoke
and dead bodies littered the ground.
These baboons were watching those
violent humans as they grew up
and learned how to use weapons and
became warriors of the forest.
Humans can best animals by
using weapons and wisdom.
But when animals can use weapons,
they become this strong.
They make great opponents
for an arrogant young man.
Talking about me?
There's no one else.
It's almost sunset. Come to my castle.
They won't bother you there.
Don't tell me what to do!
I've got to make it to the sea!
I see. Do whatever you want.
I don't care if they're warriors
of the forest or whatever,
I have no time to waste now!
I'm gonna beat every one of them!
Damn! Where has he gotten to?
That's what I thought! He's still here!
H-Hey!
Lazy Bones Island, Hungeria
The Grand Line: Hungeria, Lazy Bones Island...
What is Satan-sama doing?
What happened to the ritual to
curse the Longarm Tribe to death?
It's so quiet.
Believe in him, everyone.
I'm sure that Satan-sama will deal
the diabolic Longarm Tribe a bloody blow!
Everybody, thank you for waiting!
Is the ritual finally over?
That's our Satan-sama!
See, it's finished. As
long as you have this...
What is that?
...you'll be okay!
Well... what is this?
--That's...
--Oh, I know!
Huh?
Listen, everybody!
Satan-sama made us a talisman
which enables us to curse
the Longarm Tribe to death!
Huh?
With this talisman,
even the vicious Longarm
Tribe can't come close to us!
They'll die as soon they see it!
Look, that's...
--I see!
--That's our Satan-sama!
Now everybody, let's put these
talismans up in different places!
Oh no, look... It's not
something like that...
E-E-Excuse me! Everybody!
They're all put up now!
Uh-huh, good job!
--We're safe now!
--Thank you very much, Satan-sama!
--Um...
--Minister, we have a problem!
Th-The Longarm Tribe is here!
They're like moths to a flame.
The Longarm Tribe will be all gone by today!
As I was saying, um, that's not a talisman.
That's a musical score that I wrote!
Huh?
What?!
We're dead!
They're gonna take what little food we have
and men and women, and
do whatever they want...
We have no choice.
No, you have a choice!
Satan-sama!
Everybody, listen to this song.
What is this song?
It's filling my body with energy!
What the hell is this - some kind of spell?
It's hard to tell what those people with just
one joint in their arms are thinking!
Ah? Who are you guys?
From today on, we won't
allow you to abuse us!
Huh?
--We decided to fight!
--Yes! You won't take anything more from us!
We're gonna protect our
things with our own hands!
We're not afraid of anything!
That's it!
They look different from usual.
I don't know what's gotten into
them but... let's beat them up!
Get them!
Thank you very much, Demon King - Satan-sama!
I never even dreamed we'd be able
to put them in a cage one day!
I don't know why but when I heard
the score that you wrote...
...Courage and strength welled up in my heart
and I took up arms and fight
for the first time in my life.
Well, of course.
It ended up not working and you're
the one who beat them up finally.
But the ones who were abducted
came back safely - thanks to you!
No no, I only helped a bit.
Neither gods nor demons will help
those who won't fight on their own.
Since we're in times like these,
I wanted to make sure that...
...you could stand on your
own against evils without me.
How merciful! I think we
can change from now on!
Thank you very much, Satan-sama!
I think I did my duty by them.
Now... I can't believe that news.
Luffy-san, I hope you're okay.
It's so heart-wrenching!
Well - I don't have a heart, but...
Luffy-san, let's sing a song together!
I'm gonna make it there
to save your heart now!
Damn! I can't believe they
have a devil as a bodyguard!
If we could bring these unusual people
with just one arm joint back home,
we could make a fortune by
putting them on display.
Now...
...these Longarm Tribe have
two joints in their arm.
We can make a fortune by
putting them on display!
N-No, wait a minute!
You can't do that! It'd be treating
them the way they treated you!
Huh?
Everybody, listen!
What?! Letting them go?! Then
they'll attack us again!
No, they won't.
I made a devil's contract with them.
Listen, you three.
If you break your promise with me
and commit a wrongful act
in this country again,
I'll eat your heart!!
--Thank you for letting us go!
--We're gonna go home right away!
We'll never come to this country again!
Listen, you guys. Destroying and
stealing only generates hatred.
If somebody did the same in your
country, I'm sure you'd feel bad.
It doesn't matter if you have
one or two joints in your arms.
We're all the same! So let's
be nice to each other!
Devil-sama!
Here we go!
What?!
Why?! What's going on here?!
Let's go!
We don't believe in demons!
You're strong but not so
strong when you get tied up!
--If we bring back this skeleton that moves...
--...We can make a fortune!
Wait a minute! I've got somewhere to go!
Satan-sama!
It's a crisis! Satan-sama got kidnapped!
Everybody, get ready to summon another devil!
That's right! We can call
demons with our underwear!
Luffy-san, just sing when you feel sad!
That's what musicians
are for! So wait for me!
I will... I will be there!
Luffy-san, Luffy-san, before that...
Help me!!
What are you gonna do, Luffy-kun?
R-Rayleigh, what did you just say?!
--Weren't you listening?!
--That's not it!
I can't understand your intent!
You know what's going on in Luffy's mind now.
Depending on your answer,
I won't be able to forgive you!
She's right!
How dare you say a such thing,
knowing what happened to him?
You're a harsh person.
I said that it's a "suggestion."
You must decide, Luffy-kun,
what you want to do.
I don't ever wanna let my friends...
...go through something like that again!
If I do as you told me to,
I can protect my friends?
I think it's worth trying.
But you should realize
you'll have a lot to do.
Okay.
I made up my mind.
I'm gonna go back.
To Marineford!
After learning of Ace's death, Sanji quickly
prepares to return to Sabaody Archipelago.
But then, Queen Iva-san returns home.
The Kamabakka Queendom erupts with joy!
Sanji finally gets to be a man again,
but a new danger is upon him!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Sanji's Ordeal
The Queen Returns to her Queendom!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Sanji's Ordeal
The Queen Returns to her Queendom!