Until I can reach that great sky,
I believe, to that one tomorrow, hey
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one dream
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the good times
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Stumbling into the darkness, fumbling about to find the answer
Freezing up when there's no goal in sight
Umm you and me, yes, in this world where we share our feelings
I feel the beat guiding me, and begin to walk, oh yeah
Share the music, anytime
Share the one dream and believe in each other
Share the good times holding hands
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style
Beginning, expanding, this flavor is beyond imagining
I feel so good throughout my body, I know I can be free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far
Share the one dream, by telling each other
Share the good times and laugh
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall
I'll be there soon, I believe, to that one world, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy was ejected from Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma, a Warlord of the Sea.
Separated from his friends,
he arrived alone at the female-only
empire of Amazon Lily!
Captured by the Pirate Empress Hancock,
Luffy battled in mortal combat
with her younger sisters,
Sandersonia and Marigold who had
eaten Snake-Snake Fruits.
How rude!
Mari! Get him now!
I can't, Sister Sonia.
We are now... being protected...
...by that man!
You said that you'd rather die
than show it to someone.
Hancock's Confession
The Sister's Abhorrent Past
Is it okay, now?
Sister Sonia!
We're sorry, Big Sis!
We're sorry that we lost and
had to be saved by our enemy.
Are you up next?
That's enough.
I don't feel like it.
Oh, yeah?
I hope that she's not damaged.
Alright then,
these people you turned to stone;
turn them back.
What did you say?
You can do something, right?
They were just trying to defend me!
They didn't do anything wrong!
Hey, please?!
Yes, indeed,
I can revert them if I want.
But...
You said that you want
to go someplace by ship.
Yes, my crew's waiting for me.
Oh, that's nice.
But I can only make
one of your wishes come true.
It's either revert them
or help you to get off this island.
Choose one wish and give up on the other!
Snake Princess. You are so...
You can't fool me.
Reveal your true nature, Man.
That's great! Thank you!
That means you're going to help them, right?
Thank you... very much!!
He doesn't hesitate at all.
How is it that a man who has such great Haki
bows his head in order
to save his benefactors...
Maybe, he is...
Big Sis...
Anyway, that man...
I can't believe he defeated the sisters.
Yes, but...
I don't think Snake Princess will forgive him
after he was so rude to her
nor will she forgive the people
who let him in to this country.
Margaret!
Sweetpea!
Aphelandra!
Oh, here you all are!
Great! She turned you back from stone!
I was so worried because you
suddenly started to vouch for him.
She's right.
I was afraid of what would happen to you.
Turned us back?
What happened to us?
I have absolutely no recollection.
Don't you remember?
No I don't...
The next thing I knew, that man
was there and he was really happy.
Oh, I'm so relieved!
I was worried that you were going to die.
No one's here...
Is it all finished now?
Thank you!
Snake Princess!
Um...
Keep dedicating yourself to
your duty to protect our country.
...And that was it.
Great!
When you're turned to stone,
it's hard to remember what
happened before and after.
I'll tell you what happened.
Margaret.
What happened to the man?
What about Snake Princess?
Did she turn him to stone this time?
I don't know that much,
but it seems like he got
summoned to the Kuja Castle.
What?!
Hey, I want to know!
What do you want from me?
Oh!
Is there a meal after the battle?
If that's what it is, I'll be happy!
What kind of food is popular here?
I bet it's some kind of meat!
I should be thanking you.
Thank you.
No, please!
"Thank you" isn't something I can eat!
If anybody had seen what's on our backs,
there is no way that we
could stay in this country.
You may come in.
Come inside, Man.
Inside?
Inside of the curtain.
Oh, is that where the food is?
I'm coming...
Oh, we're not eating.
Hey, what are you doing
with your clothes off?
As always, you are reacting rudely.
But that's okay.
This is the mark...
...that you said...
...you had seen somewhere.
Take a good look at it, again.
Where did you see this?
Do you know the meaning of this mark?
Answer me, now!
It's not something I want to show people.
As I suspected, it's a bit different
from what I've seen before.
I have a friend called Hachi
who is a Fishman...
A Fishman?
Yeah.
And he has a similar mark on his forehead
so I thought it was the same.
I don't know anything about your mark.
If he doesn't know, why don't you tell him?
Granny Nyon!
Where did you come in from?
Be honest, Snake Princess.
You have seen clearly
how tolerant that man is.
Don't be afraid.
Tell him everything that you want to share.
You!
You are a pirate,
Monkey D. Luffy, am I right?
Yes, I am.
How do you know about me?
How can you be so casual
after you caused such
a sensation in the world?
Look at this newspaper!
Just days ago, this man...
...at Sabaody Archipelago
near the center sea,
caused a horrific and grave incident
when he dealt a blow to a Celestial Dragon!
Dealt a blow to a Celestial Dragon?
It is a miracle that he was able to get away
from the supreme powers
at the center sea after that.
And in only a couple days,
he arrived here so far away.
It's all beyond our understanding.
W-Who are you?!
I told you!
I was blown away suddenly.
I have no idea where this place is!
Oh, and another thing -
I don't feel sorry for that Celestial Dragon.
That bastard!
Guess what he did to my friend?
T-Then...
it is true that you punched
a Celestial Dragon.
T-There are still...
...foolish people like that...
...in this world?!
The ones who put their lives at risk
to challenge those celestials...
...like him!
Who are you talking about?
I will tell you everything
including the meaning of the symbol
that your Fishman friend
has on his forehead.
Hachi's mark?
This is...
"The Claw of the Celestial Dragon."
It's an emblem of the Celestial Dragons!
People who were fed by
the World Nobles all get...
...this permanent brand to
show that you are subhuman!
Celestial Dragons?
The three of us were...
...once...
...slaves of World Nobles!
You were... slaves?!
It happened when I was 12...
Starboard, all clear.
Port, all clear, too.
Bow, all clear.
High visibility, all serene!
Don't fall into the sea!
Don't make fun of me!
I've become a warrior!
Okay, okay.
We trust you!
That's our Big Sis!
We'll support you!
I bet you're hungry! I brought a snack!
Hancock?
Sonia! Mari! Where are you?
Three of us were taken
from the Kuja pirate ship...
...and we were sold!
From that point,
all we have are terrible memories
that we don't even want to remember.
We saw men for the first time
and they were nothing but figures of horror.
Sister Sonia, calm down!
The memory haunts us.
W-Wow! H-Hey! That's enough!
No need to force the memories!
You don't have to tell me!
It was awful.
There was no hope.
We kept thinking about death!
Hey! You...
But...
...one night four years later,
something happened that made
the World Government tremble.
"Nobody will challenge
the Celestial Dragons."
That was the cardinal rule in their world.
But there was a man who climbed
the Red Line with his bare hands
and slipped into the Celestial Dragons' Holy Land of Mary Geoise.
He was an adventurer who
later led the Fishman Pirates,
named Fisher Tiger.
In order to free all the slaves
from the town there his fellow
Fishmen were being tortured,
he fought with all his might.
We are free! We are free!
He disliked humans as a species
but he was being fair to all slaves,
and let thousands of slaves
of different species go free.
We prepared to die and ran among the others.
We owe him an immeasurable debt.
Tiger released many Fishmen to the sea,
but ones who were slaves had
a mark that cannot be erased.
Tiger has made the World Government his enemy
and he formed the
Sun Pirates with former slaves
and sailed out into the open sea.
As though breaking a curse,
he changed the Celestial Dragon's
emblem on everyone's bodies...
...into the symbol of the sun.
What you thought was similar
to the mark on my back is
the sun symbol of the Sun Pirates.
Yeah, you're right.
The one Hachi has on his
forehead looks like the sun.
Does that mean he was a slave, too?
It doesn't necessarily mean that he was.
The mark is made in such a way
that it is impossible to tell...
...whether they are former slaves or not.
I'm pretty sure that he once was
a member of the Sun Pirates.
In fact, Fisher Tiger is already dead and...
...the Sun Pirates have split
up into several groups.
Hey, when did you get hurt there?
Oh, this? Don't worry about it.
He has a complicated past, too...
So this is the reason
that the mark on our backs
is similar to the Fishmen's mark.
Okay, I pretty much understand.
Surprisingly, when we were slaves,
we were forced to eat the Love-Love Fruit
and Snake-Snake Fruits
for their entertainment,
and that enabled us to deceive our nation
and preserve the secret.
If you didn't cover up
Sonia's back at that moment,
it would have been impossible
for us to stay on this island.
I don't want to let anyone
know about our past!
I won't stop at deceiving
our whole nation to hide it!
We won't open ourselves up at any price!
We don't want anybody to
take advantage of us again!
I'm scared of being caught off guard.
It terrifies me. I can't take it!
Big Sis...
Ho!
But this is the first time in a long time
that you've shown your emotions like that.
Recently, I've thought
that the Snake Princess
must have turned to ice or something.
Shut up!
You are a traitor who
left the country behind!
You shut up!
You three were miserable
and didn't know how to
return to this island...
...after you ran away from
the Celestial Dragons!
Who brought you back?!
You should be thankful that
I was living outside of this country!
What you are talking about was a small favor.
What did you say?!
Granny Nyon...
I always keep an eye on
you three as a mother would!
And you call it "small
favor", Snake Princess?
Hey, get your hands off of me! Mari! Sonia!
Are you going to...
...look down on me; a former slave?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Like I told you - I hate
the Celestial Dragons!
I like you!
Didn't you say that you had one more wish?
All right!
Where do you want to go?
I'll give you a ride!
For real?!
The Kuja Pirates hold a banquet.
When Luffy is mobbed by curious women,
Margaret saves him and takes
him to Granny Nyon's house.
But there, Luffy finds out that
his brother Ace is in trouble,
and he's forced to make a big decision.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Saving Ace!
Next Stop: the Great Prison"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Saving Ace!
Next Stop: the Great Prison