Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
The Straw Hats have left Fishman Island
and finally reached the New World.
They met a Giant girl named Lily who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit
and decided to help her save her father
- Panz Fry from the Navy's ship. However,
a mysterious group called the Neo Navy threw the situation into chaos.
After finally rescuing Panz Fry, Shuzo and
his clan are hot on the Straw Hats' tails!
Rescue mission accomplished!
Yeah!
Now, bring that food here!
I'll make them my heavenly food!
Really?! Thanks, frying pan pops!
Shuzo-san, I found them! They're hiding behind a reef!
How annoying! All ships, prepare for battle!
Let's blow them up along with the reef!
I-I'm afraid we used up all our torpedoes in the battle earlier
and we're almost out of bombshells too.
No, we still have a torpedo.
We can use this submersible as a torpedo!
We are the proud soldiers of the Neo Navy's flying squad!
We trusted in Master Z and Shuzo-san and got this far!
Shuzo-san! Let us fight with you! Please!!
I'm proud of you guys! I'll care for you to your deathbed!
Fight to your heart's content as a Neo Navy soldier!
All torpedoes, go!
"Z's Ambition! Luffy vs. Shuzo!"
--Pops! --Dad!
What?! What?!
--It's them! --I can't believe this!
Ch-Charge!
You bastard!
--That's not a torpedo! --It's a manned ship, isn't it?
Long live the Neo Navy!
What's wrong with them?!
They're launching themselves like torpedoes!
They must be nuts!
Nice to see you again, accursed pirates.
You can't get away!
It's that guy! How did he find us?!
I used this!
A Vivre Card?!
When you were taking off, I threw it onto the raft!
Ochenta Fleurs!
I won't allow them to die in vain!
He's super crazy!
You damn pirates are the reason that the New World is corrupted.
So all we want is...
...to exterminate you all!
No! If you move too much, your wound will...
Iron Body!
Dad!
Lily!
No, stop!
You escaped death earlier!
But it's come for you again!
Dad!
I'll fight you!
--Luffy-sa! --Go, Luffy!
I won't let you hurt that old man!
A rubber man? Oh right.
You're a pirate too and I'll kill you sooner or later anyway.
Then why don't I kill you first? As you wish!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Finger Pistol!
...Jet Whip!
--Gum-Gum... --Shave!
...Jet Bazooka!
Moon Walk!
Armament!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
--Yeah! --He did it!
Iron Body!
Your Haki is not strong enough to beat me!
What?!
--He uses Haki as well, huh? --This is going to be difficult.
His hands are annoying!
I guess that's all you got!
Gear 3!
Luffy!
You haven't collapsed yet?
How did you like the Haki-wrapped bombshell?
My lovely partner - Beast Cannon Alpacacino!
He's a bazooka that ate a Devil Fruit!
Finger Pistol Five!
Luffy!
I defeated your captain!
Luffy-san!
That bastard!
D-Don't do it!
Dad!
Usopp-sa, could you do me a favor?
Fling me into that guy's body!
What?!
I'll expand myself in his body and break him into pieces!
Okay, I'll do it!
Ready?
Yeah!
Alright, go!
Luffy-sa! No!
Luffy-sa!
I knew your plan all along! So stupid!
All of you, go to hell!
H-Hey!
Not yet.
What?
It's not over yet!
No way!
You fool!
I... I'm gonna kick your ass and...
...eat that old man's heavenly food!
Luffy-sa, here we go!
Whoa-whoa!
Oh wow!
It's super!
What's this? I got horns on my head!
What happened to you guys? You got smaller!
No, you got bigger, Luffy!
Lily slipped into your body and expanded herself!
She did?!
That's right, Luffy-sa!
Oh, there you are!
I was wondering where your voice was coming from!
Giant Luffy! How cool is that?
Yeah! I became a Giant!
How absurd! Even if you get bigger,
you're the same despicable pirate!
Oh, I forgot about you guys!
How could you?!
You bastard!
Don't get carried away!
Giants are too slow - I don't think you can keep up with my speed!
Gear 2!
--Hey! What's going on?! --It's a fast, hot wind!
You pirates are worthless!
And your worthlessness is no match for me!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Jet...
Finger Pistol Ten!
...Spear!
Th-That was too much!
I almost died!
Luffy! Lily!
Thanks, Lily!
Don't mention it.
I'm so happy that I could help you!
Thank you, Luffy-sa!
All right! Now I can have pops' heavenly food!
Uh-huh!
Th-The food is ruined!
You can't complain because you did it.
--Let's go. --No! Food!
We'll get some food on our way and head
for a volcano somewhere. What do you say?
Sounds good.
All right! Let's go!
What should we do about his raft?
We can't load it on the ship.
--Seems like it's not a problem. --Oh.
Super!
I think he made something.
The great shipwright - Franky! Thank you!
Don't mention it! Super!
You bastard! You survived?!
How did you find me?!
Like you did to the Straw Hats,
we secretly put this on Panz Fry's body.
It's a method of tracking pirates that I learned from a teacher long ago.
It's inexcusable for you to drag us Navy soldiers
in for the purpose of killing all pirates!
We'll take you all to Impel Down.
Impel Down?! No way!
We're not gonna tell you anything no matter
how much you torture us!
If you wanna kill us, just do it here in the New World!
No, it's up to the law to decide.
That's how the Navy's justice works!
Luffy-sa! Everybody! Thank you!
I'll never forget what you did for us!
Don't make a big deal out of it.
See you! Thank you for the food!
Don't push yourself too much, you heroic chef!
Yes, thank you! The great doctor - Chopper!
The great doctor? Me?
Compliments like that don't impress me!
Lily! Let's fight together again as Giants!
Uh-huh! You were the strongest Giant I've ever known!
See you again!
All right, let's go!
Yeah!
What I feared most has happened.
SHUZO WILL BE PLACED IN IMPEL DOWN
I should have made myself clearer to him.
I'm sorry!
Do you think the Navy found out what we are up to?
Don't worry.
But...
They won't say anything no matter how horrible the torture.
After all, isn't he a member of our indomitable Neo Navy?
You're right.
Master Z. We will arrive at the First Island soon.
Now, it's finally time to fight! Let's terrify them all!
The last day of the New World is nigh.
We will kill all pirates with our own bare hands!
As the Straw Hats sail the Maubeugemour Sea,
the first island of the New World appears before them.
As the crew marvels at its bizarre appearance,
they receive an emergency distress call
and then head toward the island.
But that will lead them into a battle larger than any they have ever faced!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Arriving! A Burning Island - Punk Hazard!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!