Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
"I've decided to head to Elbaf!"
"What?! Please don't go!"
"I was just kidding. I know how you guys feel."
"So you're coming back, Usopp?!"
"Of course I am, silly!
Geez, you guys must like me so much!"
What the hell is that idiot doing?
Whoa!
Everyone Finally Has A Bounty!
A Pirate Group Worth Over 600 Million!
Yokozuna! I need lumber! Hurry up!
Ribbit, ribbit!
Bring me some, too!
Seriously, those two are extraordinary.
Just as you'd expect from Tom's Workers!
Yeah, we're barely keeping up with them.
It boggles the mind that they
could work at such a crazy pace.
And there isn't even the
slightest fault in their work.
We're not gonna get anywhere by
just sitting here and admiring them.
Let's show them what us
Dock #1 workers are made of!
Yeah!
Yokozuna! Guys! Keep it up!
What's funny?
Well...
I just remembered you used to collect junk
and built a bunch of weird
battleships on this scrap heap island.
You didn't like me building weapons, did you...?
Right. On top of that, they were
used to frame Tom-san as a criminal.
But by looking at this, I can tell...
...that your experience building those
battleships wasn't a waste at all.
Ha! Is that sarcasm?
I wanted to show Tom-san that
the Moron-ky from back then has...
With this ship, going to the New
World is no longer a pipe dream.
Even before Tom-san...
...you can resolutely stand proud!
Iceberg...
I never thought those two would
work together to build a ship.
Ow!
Well...! What the hell are you doing
instead of helping me with work?!
To think that you keep making
unstable stuff like this!
Shut up! It's none of
your business, Stupid-berg!
Seriously, what's with him?!
You should just kick out an idiot like him!
Well, don't say that. He's a fellow ship builder.
His shipbuilding skills are already almost
on par with the craftsmen on the island...
...though what he makes is shaky.
He's just always honest, that's all.
You two will definitely become
world-class shipbuilding engineers someday.
You should be nice to each other.
The way things are going,
it looks like we'll be able to
finish it sooner than we planned.
Iceberg, let me tell you one thing.
This isn't just another pirate ship.
I know. You've put your heart into--
That's not what I'm saying.
The Straw Hats went head-on
against not only Navy Headquarters,
but the World Government.
This is the ship they'll be traveling on.
And you, the mayor of Water Seven,
took part in building it.
If that becomes known, you could be in trouble.
You do understand that, don't you?
Well...
I'll think about it when the time comes.
Besides, did you forget what Tom-san said?
Franky, there's no such thing
as blueprints for a pirate ship.
If the sailors who board a ship put up
a skull flag, then it's a pirate ship.
If they put up a seagull flag,
then it's a Navy ship.
I don't care what you wanna build,
but a man should be resolutely
proud of the ship he built!
So I...
No, Galley-La has been building ships
based on that creed all this time.
But to think that...
...I'm giving you a hand
towards achieving your dream...
Even I feel that... I'm not in my right mind.
It's not like I asked you to
give me a hand, Stupid-berg.
You abandoned your real name
and your body, too, is like that
of a completely different man.
But you haven't changed at all.
You're just the way you used to be.
My dream... Huh...
Give Tom-san back to us!
Stop! Sea train!
Tom-san...
I don't wanna build ships anymore!
I can't love ships that hurt
the people I really care about!
But, Tom-san...
...you're my goal after all!
So I want you to come back
and teach me again...
...because I want to...
...build a dream ship someday, too.
A ship that resolutely and proudly traverses
even uncharted waves at edges of the earth!
A dream ship like that!
This bites... My body... is on fire.
So I'm still alive.
But I wonder if I'll die like this...
I see no one on board.
An abandoned ship, huh?
Scrap wood... Scrap iron...
This place makes me... feel quite at home.
I have to do something
about my disabled body first.
Well... anyway, what's up with
that funny looking body of yours?
Shut up! Since my whole
body became of no use,
I rebuilt my body using iron
scraps and escaped death!
We never change, huh?
Whenever we meet face to face,
we yell at each other.
I still won't forgive you... and you
may feel the same about me, too.
Franky... I'm... really...
...glad that... you're alive.
The hell with "I'm glad that you're alive"!
Just because I'm alive, he ended up
helping me achieve my dream.
You're quite an idiot, too, Iceberg.
"Whoa, Luffy! What a coincidence
to see you in a place like this!
I was just taking a stroll...
but, well, this must just be fate.
What can you do? I'll come
back and rejoin the gang!"
So this is pattern 53.
But not being able to use it
unless they find me is a flaw.
In that case, I should take
some initiative myself.
Yep! That's what I'll do!
What? Why're they all looking so serious?
Yeah, it seems like the crew's gotten
really disorganized and on-edge without me.
Okay, then, for everyone's sake, I'll just—
Pattern 34!
"Ah-choo! Ah-choo!
Geez, that night breeze is cold!"
I'd sneeze loudly so that they'd hear me.
Yep, they're coming.
This is the crucial moment. I definitely
have to act like this is a coincidence.
"Oh, is that you over there, Usopp?"
"Well, I just happened to be passing by."
"You shouldn't stay outside, you'll catch cold.
Come inside and have something warm."
"Oh, yeah? Well, I know
exactly how you guys feel.
After all, you need me, right?
Let's let bygones be bygones!
I'm back!"
Oh, they're going to bed?
The new ship is coming
together quickly, and I haven't yet...
I need to somehow rejoin the gang.
All right, now that it's come to this,
I'll come up with more patterns!
Bro! I brought some food and drinks!
For you Galley-La guys, too! Take a little break!
We brought you cold cola, Bro!
We chilled them good!
Yaay! I was pretty hungry!
Of course, you brought some
of this stuff, too, right?
Iceberg-san! Franky!
Go ahead and take a break.
You guys have been working
without eating or drinking.
There's no way you can keep on going like that!
Yeah, we can take a break later!
Well... then I'll take you up on that offer.
I guess it's not a bad idea for me
to replenish cola and power up.
Replenishment completed! Super... Franky!
--Yeah, he is!
--Yeah!
Franky, what're you going to do
once the ship is completed?
What am I gonna do?
Once you hand the ship over to the Straw Hats,
are you going to be satisfied?
Does that mean you've achieved your dream?
You like those guys, right?
Like I told you so many times,
I have no intention whatsoever
of leaving this island.
I see...
Bro...
Now, I'm gonna go back to work!
Yokozuna, you sit back and relax for a while.
Ribbit.
Paulie, it's you guys' turn now.
When we're so exhausted that we
can't even manage a late-night snack...
Those two are the very
definition of inexhaustible.
Indeed...
Hang in there, Bro!
Let's have a party once the ship is completed!
I'm looking forward to it!
Yeah, me too!
It was a short time, but I had fun with you guys.
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
I finally met someone worthy
of entrusting with my dream.
I couldn't be happier.
As I promised, I'm gonna build an amazing ship!
Just wait, Straw Hat!
Bro...
Iceberg! Why don't you take it
easy and get some sleep, too?!
Why don't you do that?!
Sorry, but I'm feeling super energetic!
Sorry, me too!
Are you watching this, Tom-san?
You were called a legendary shipwright.
Looks like your skills and spirit were
passed down to your disciples splendidly.
A log has been stored!
The Log Pose is pointing to the next island!
Then, all we need now is the ship!
I'm looking forward to it!
Yeah. He told us not to come until it's
done because he wants to surprise us.
Do you guys know where
following that log will take you?
No. Where is it?
It somehow looks like it's
pointing a little downwards.
Of course it is. The next island
is a paradise on the seabed...
Fishman Island!
What?! F-F-Fishman Island?!
Finally?!
What?! What's wrong, Sanji?!
Fishman Island, huh?
I'm not sure how to feel.
Yeah, it reminds me
of what happened in your village.
But, well, they weren't just Fishmen,
but pirates too, right?
Exactly! You really hit the nail on the head, shithead!
Impressive for a dumbass!
Fishman Island is a famous
place in the Grand Line.
Beautiful Mermaids draw arcs
over the water and play with fish.
It's a dream kingdom!
Is that right? That's amazing!
Can't I be allowed to dream?! I'm a pirate!
They do have young ones there!
But it's not easy to get to this paradise.
I'm concerned about it being on the seabed.
Well, we'll see once we go there.
That's not the problem.
Take a look at the front page.
It's a recent newspaper.
What's this?
"Fourteen more ships have
disappeared this month."
What does this mean?
The Devil's Triangle,
also known as the Florian Triangle.
You can't reach paradise without
passing through that area.
In that sea, more than 100
ships go missing every year.
And after they go missing, sometimes
the ships will show up with no crew,
and increasingly, people are seeing
ghost ships with a dead crew on them.
Ghosts?! That's scary!
We can meet skeletons that are alive?!
What kind of imagination do you have?
No! I definitely don't wanna encounter them!
I don't wanna even see them!
Such creepy ships!
What happens in that sea?
Beats me.
Those who encounter trouble
never come back, so I don't know.
It's a dark sea with deep fog. So be careful.
Nooo!
Anyway, it's a dangerous sea
where lots of disasters happen.
Make sure you are well
prepared before you set sail.
Along with the stories about ghost ships--
in other words, wrecked trading
ships and pirate ships--there are...
...legends of treasure ships, right?
Let's find ghost ships!
Leave it to me!
What?! I don't want to!
If the worry's just about getting lost,
don't worry, as we'll have plenty of food.
Treasure ships, huh? I wonder
if they have swords, too.
Pirate guys!
Straw Hat!
What brought you guys here?
Big Bro Franky asked us to bring you guys!
The dream ship has been completed!
They built an incredible ship!
What?! It's already done?!
That was really quick!
Five top-notch shipwrights
worked on it day and night!
Yeah, they did!
All right! Let's head there right away!
Yeah!
Straw Hat...!
Straw Hat!
Franky Family...
What're you guys running that
frantically for? You're out of breath.
To tell you the truth, we came
to ask you a huge favor.
Did you see the wanted posters?!
Wanted posters?
Straw Hat, the bounty on
your head has gotten crazy!
And all the others, too, are wanted in addition!
Me, too?! All right!
Me, too...?!
Me, too?!
Instead of having me explain,
just take a look at these.
All seven of you now have
bounties on your heads!
Straw Hat Luffy, 300-million-berry bounty.
All right! It went up!
Pirate Hunter Zoro, 120-million-berry bounty.
Cat Burglar Nami, 16 million-berry bounty.
Oh, no...
Cotton Candy Lover Chopper,
the gang's pet, 50-berry bounty.
Fifty...?
Devil's Child Nico Robin,
80-million-berry bounty.
Who's this...?
Black Leg Sanji, failed to obtain
a picture, 77-million-berry bounty.
Hey, Sogeking's got a bounty, too.
Fifty...?
W-Well, we sympathize with you, or well...
I'm sure you wanna say all sorts
of things, but, well... please wait.
The favor we're talking about
has something to do with this!
Please take a look at this!
Franky!
Cyborg Franky, 44-million-berry bounty.
Oh, no! Bro's got a bounty on his head!
Oh, no!
That's right. We somehow
were able to get off the hook,
but Bro had no such luck.
If he stays in Water Seven,
his life will be in danger.
If he gets caught again, we're not
strong enough to rescue him!
But he probably will try to stay on this
island because he's worried about us.
So we got together and discussed it.
Straw Hat, please! You can
do it by force if you have to.
Please take Bro out to sea.
He's a pirate's son to start with!
Alright! Let's go get our new ship!
I'm so looking forward to it!
Whoa! So is that it, Luffy?! It's huge!
This is incredible!
Franky! Where are you, Franky?!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The King of Animals that Overlooks the Sea!
The Dream Ship Magnificently Completed!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The King of Animals that Overlooks the Sea!
The Dream Ship Magnificently Completed!