Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
An Outcast's Dream!
Hiriluk the Quack!
Day 3.
Prognosis, the bacteria were reduced to 30%.
Whoa! You're amazing!
Just as you'd expect from a monster!
But what happens if I do this?
Poke, poke...
What?! What're you doing?!
So funny!
Shut up! Go away!
Won't you become my friend?
I really really like you!
Y... Your friend?
Become a pirate!
I'm not interested in pirates at all.
And I never wanted a friend!
If you become my friend,
my other friends will all be happy!
Wait!
Why would I wanna become your friend?!
Don't insult me!
You're definitely funny!
I'll definitely make you become my friend!
In order for you to get a healthy smile back,
I prepared an exceptionally nutritious dish...
Thank you, Sanji-kun.
though you're still painfully beautiful even after what your body's been through...
Good lord!
When did you use my kitchen without asking?
Madam, the roast over there is for you.
It's high in protein and is good for rejuvena-
Ahhh!
I'm not a "madam."
I'm a sparkling single... and still youthful.
You're still 139 years old... right?
Doctorine! Help me!
Wait! Hey! Wait!
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
What're you doing?
This guy's gonna join us and become our friend!
Oh, really?!
I didn't say that!
You did.
– I didn't!
– You did!
Be quiet, both of you!
Wait!
Friend, huh?
How deep a meaning that word has to him...
To ask without knowing that...
There was one man whom he
opened up to when he was alone...
The man's name was Dr. Hiriluk.
He was a quack who gave Chopper
a name and called him son.
Hold it!
Did you find him?!
No! We can't find him!
That darn quack, Hiriluk!
We'll catch him no matter what!
Those're Wapol-sama's orders!
– Yes sir!
Dammit!
You can't go on like this.
Let's call a doctor.
No.
There aren't any doctors in this country...
except for the Twenty MDs who belong exclusively to Wapol...
We'll beg Wapol and call the Twenty MDs.
I'll go.
You don't have to.
I'll examine him.
Hiriluk!
N-No thank you!
Please don't!
A bunch of people you treated
ended up getting worse!
Don't be modest.
I just developed a wonderful
all-purpose drug yesterday.
You're lucky.
Hmm? It's not what you think.
This is a tranquilizer gun.
I use it when the patient's pain is severe.
I... I'm gonna go get the guards!
Please leave!
If you want money, I'll pay!
I don't take money from sick people.
I just want to help you.
Don't! Stop it! I've got a family!
Croak! Croak, croak!
Croak, croak, croak!
Croak! Croak!
Croak, croak! Croak!
Hmm? This is strange.
Did I use a wrong ingredient?
I thought frog extract would work...
Guess it was a failure. Oh man...
S-Sorry...
I didn't mean for this to happen...
Hiriluk! Are you there?!
– Hold it!
Hmm?
Are you happy, young man?
The doctor hunt has come to the final stage.
I hear that you and I are the
only doctors left in this country.
Wapol is trying desperately to catch us.
Even if that wasn't the case,
you're already an outcast in this country...
since you're the worst of the quacks.
I won't get caught by some doctor hunt.
I'll save this country using
medical science one day.
Oh? Didn't you mean to say
"destroy the country"?
There're people on the bridge!
I'll see you around, quack.
I don't wanna see you again,
you thieving doctor.
I'll never get caught!
I'll save as many sick people as possible!
Hmm?
You've been shot?
We need to stop the bleeding
right away or you'll die!
Don't worry. I'll save you!
It's a yeti! Shoot him to death!
I just made an ointment that even
works on broken bones 3 days ago.
You're lucky.
Don't let him get away!
Kill him!
Shoot him!
What are you?
You don't look like a human.
Oh, yeah. You're that yeti that
people have been talking about...
Yeah! It hit him!
It wasn't enough! Finish him!
H... How dare you...
Who do you think...
I am?!
Hey! Wait!
I will never shoot you!
My name is Dr. Hiriluk!
I'm a doctor!
That was Chopper and Hiriluk's first encounter.
So what happened...
to the reindeer taken in by Hiriluk?
What?! You can talk?!
Why did you stay quiet for 3 days?
I thought you'd hate me if I talked...
When I talked to humans the other day,
they shot me...
because it's strange for a reindeer to speak...
You speak, so what?!
I can speak, too... a lot better than you can.
Get out of here! Chopper!
What?
Dammit! It failed again!
Hey, are you okay, Chopper?!
Hmm? Well, you aren't okay
to start with, I guess...
Why are you calling me Chopper?
You're Tony Tony Chopper.
After all, you're a reindeer and have
fine antlers that could chop down trees.
That's a cool name, isn't it?
That's what I'll call you.
Chopper...
Listen, Chopper.
Always observe patients,
and give them proper treatment.
Doing so will save people's lives.
Let's go!
Patients are waiting for me today once again.
Get out of here, quack!
I thought lizard eyeballs would work...
Never come back!
Go away!
Run! It's the guards!
Chopper! We'll use the decoy plan!
What's that?!
Take care!
What?
You almost got me killed!
Oh yeah?!
You failed to die once already!
You clumsy blue nose!
Don't call me blue nose!
Doctor...
Hmm?
This is... the first time
I've fought with someone...
Makes sense...
To fight, you have to have an opponent.
Then... is it your first time for this as well?
Hmm?
I'll give it to you.
It's a gift... as a memento of our making up.
A gift? Making up?
We both go through hardships
as outcasts, don't we?
But don't hold a grudge against humans.
This country is sick right now.
Both the citizens and the king
suffer from a sickness of the heart.
People would probably say that
you can't treat a sick country,
but that's not true.
Once my invention is complete,
this country will be saved!
There used to be a master-thief
in a country in the far west.
He had a serious heart disease.
He went to see every possible skilled
doctor and got treated by them,
but no one was able to cure him.
After being told he'd die,
he passed by a mountain
while frustrated and unsettled.
There... he saw a sight that
he had never seen in his life.
Cherry blossoms!
He saw vivid cherry blossoms
all over the mountain!
And then, he went to see another
doctor and was shocked...
because he was told...
"You're completely healthy."
What?
He was cured!
It was indeed a miracle!
Don't you think?
But this was unmistakably medical science!
By being emotionally moved,
some sort of change
happened in this man's body!
In other words, there's no disease
in this world that can't be cured.
No matter what anyone says about me,
I'll save this country as a doctor!
That's why I raised this skull
towards all the diseases!
Skull...
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
I will save this country as a doctor!
By raising this, I'll fight just like pirates do!
Hey! Reindeer!
Join us and become our friend!
Hmm? Whoa! That looks delicious!
It's cool to be a pirate!
Doctor, what are pirates?
Pirates?
Pirates are incredible guys at sea.
They have large, well-trained
bodies and eyes like an eagle.
Their voices are like a thunder splitting the sky!
Are you... really a pirate?!
Hmm?
Yeah, I am...
Like I've been saying, join us!
It's fun to be a pirate! Pirates sing, too.
What? Th-They sing?
Yeah. And they dance, too!
You call that being a pirate?!
That's right!
And they go on lots of adventures!
Adventures?
So pirates go on adventures then?
Of course!
Pirates risk their lives to go on adventures!
You can meet lots of amazing people!
It's cool to be a pirate!
There're tons of incredible guys at sea!
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
If you do, you'll understand very
well how small your problems are.
This island that you were born on
is like this compared to the world.
Really?
No, it's smaller! Like this! It's true!
Your future lies beyond that sea!
The good times passed in the twinkling of an eye...
And...
The time to bid farewell...
comes for everyone...
It took one year.
Now your treatment is complete.
Your injuries are completely healed, Chopper.
Yes! Thank you, Doctor!
Well then... take care...
What?
Now, leave! Live as you please!
I'm busy with my research!
I no longer have any moral
obligation to take care of you!
Doctor!
I'll never cause you any trouble!
Please let me in!
I'll massage your shoulders everyday!
I'll make you tea and clean the house!
Please! Let me stay!
I don't have any friends!
I have no place to go!
Doctor!
Chopper!
Look at this, Doctor. I'm injured.
Hey, Doctor!
Look at this!
Why... Doctor?
Go... to the sea! Go anywhere!
Don't ever come back here!
Forgive me, Chopper!
I'm gonna... die...
Yeah, you will...
Tell me! How many more days do I have?
Oh? If you're asking me
to examine you, I refuse.
You don't have the money to pay my fee.
Tell me!
You can't kill a person with a tranquilizer gun!
I'll tell you.
You'll die at 5 pm on the 10th day from today.
You won't have to suffer any more.
10 days... That'll be enough...
In 2 days...
In 2 days, I'll complete the research
I've continued for 30 years...
I will... make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country!
Cherry blossoms?
So the research you've continued for 30 years
was about making cherry blossoms bloom?
The miracle cherry blossoms that
saved you, a master thief, long ago?
That's right!
What?
You're a fool.
This is a winter island where it's bitter cold year around.
Cherry blossoms won't bloom here.
They will!
I was a hopeless thug and dying,
but I lived on and was able to
have a profound change of heart.
Every human in this world can be saved!
I'd like to prove it here in Drum,
the land where I was born!
Listen.
What you're trying to do isn't
medical science or any science.
Even if the cherry blossoms bloom,
it will do nothing to human bodies.
Hiriluk!
Chopper! We're alike.
So I will at least teach you before I die...
that there's nothing impossible in this world...
and that you can do anything, too!
But the story of these two
doesn't have a happy ending...
I'll show you...
the miracle cherry blossoms!
Nemuranai kono machi mo Ima dake wa madoromu
Even this sleepless town has dozed off for now
Kyou kara to kinou made
From today forth,
nani ka ga kawatte yuku
something's going to change
Kitto yarinaoseru hazu
I'm sure I can start fresh,
Datte hitori janai kara
since I'm not alone
Soba ni ite kureru dake de
Just by having you by my side,
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru
I feel I can become strong
Doko made ikeru kana
I wonder how far I can go,
mirai e tsuzuku basho
towards the place that leads to the future
Tooku de kagayaite sekai o tsutsumikomu
Off in the distance it shines, encompassing the world
Yoake mae
Before dawn
Hey, Luffy. Are you really listening to-
Hey, where'd he go?!
Geez...
I wonder if he's chasing Tony-kun again...
He's refusing!
That's not true! Are you stupid?!
I've decided to make him join us
and become our friend!
But that's just what you want, right?!
Seriously... I wonder if there's
any medicine that works on fools...
Next time, on One Piece:
Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms
And The Will That Gets Carried On!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms
And The Will That
Gets Carried On!