Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
Hawk-Eye Mihawk!
The Great Swordsman Zoro
Falls on the Sea
– Ugh...
– What'd you just say?!
Nami ran off with the Going Merry?!
What do you mean by that?!
It happened just a moment ago!
What's the matter, Big Sis Nami?
Huh?
You were looking at wanted posters.
Oh... Nothing...
You're impressive as usual.
So you've set your eyes on a big bounty pirate.
But Arlong is the one pirate that you shouldn't go after.
I hear he's super terrifyingly strong...
He kept himself quiet
and out of sight for a while.
But he started going wild again recently.
Well, it's hard to give up on that
twenty-million-berry bounty, though...
This guy's so strong that
there's a shred of possibility
that even we may be killed by a hair...
Huh?
Big Sis Nami?
Uhm, I'm sorry, but could you turn around?
I want to change...
What?! W-Well...
Change? Here? Now?!
May I?
Please go ahead!
True to her looks, she's so bold!
It wouldn't hurt if we take
a quick peek, would it?
Oh, yeah...
Wh-What're you doing?!
What am I doing? Of course, business!
I'm a thief that only targets pirates.
I'll take this ship.
I never said that I became a member.
I just joined forces with them. That's all.
I only spent a short time with Luffy
and the others, but I had lots of fun.
– Tell them...
– What?!
...that if we're linked by fate, we'll meet again.
Big Sis Nami!
H-Hey! We'll be in trouble!
We were more or less asked to watch the ship!
So that's how she took the ship...
We're sorry!
Dammit!
She's making this crisis worse for us!
Kaya gave that ship to us!
Wait! I can still see it!
It's the Going Merry!
Where's your ship?
We still have it here...
Zoro! Usopp! Leave right away!
Take that ship and follow Nami!
Forget about it.
Just give that ship to her.
No need of going after that woman.
I won't accept anyone
but her as our navigator!
All right, all right...
What a high-maintenance captain...
Hey Usopp, let's go!
Uh? Okay...
– Big Bro Zoro, the ship is ready!
Luffy, what about you?
I can't go since I haven't settled
anything at this restaurant.
Be careful.
The situation here isn't normal.
Yeah, I know.
Wh-What? What the hell just happened?
The ship's been split into two!
Look at that!
It's him!
Don Krieg! It's him!
It's the man who destroyed our fleet!
Th... That man!
So that man is...
That son of a bitch!
He followed us here... to kill us!!
We're done for!
Zoro?
Who's that?
The man I've been looking for.
Hawk-Eye Mihawk!
Hawk-Eye Mihawk...
The world's strongest man...
That's the man who sank Krieg's
50 ships on his own in the Grand Line?
Then, the one who destroyed
Krieg's ship just now is also...
But he looks just like an ordinary human.
It doesn't look like he has any special weapons.
His weapon is on his back...
That... can't be!
Did he really slice up that large
sailing ship using that sword?
He's the master swordsman Hawk-Eye...
...the man who stands above all
other swordsmen in the world...
I never thought I'd be able to see him this soon...
It's finally... time to fulfill my promise...
Y-You son of a bitch...
What grudge do you have to come after us?!
Just killing time.
Wha?! Don't mock us!
Wh-What?!
I'm sure I aimed straight for him!
He averted them.
He gently changed the course of the bullets
using the point of his sword.
That can't be true...
Hey! Who are you?!
Three swords... Could it be...
I've never seen a sword moved so gently...
There is no strength in
swordplay based only on force.
Did you use that sword to
slice up this ship as well?
That's right.
I see... You're the strongest...
I came out to sea to meet you.
What's your goal?
To become the strongest!
Hmph... How foolish...
You've got spare time, right? Let's fight!
Th-This guy is Zoro!
Roronoa Zoro of the Three Swords Style!
What?!
Oh, a pirate hunter, huh?
He is?!
Hey, this isn't good, Luffy!
The Going Merry will be out of sight soon!
Hey, Luffy!
Fight? Hmph! How pitiful, weak one...
If you are a competent enough swordsman,
you should be able to see
the disparity in our abilities
even before we cross swords.
Is it your courage or ignorance that
causes you to turn your sword on me?
It's my ambition!
And it's also because of a
promise I made to a dear friend!
Hawk-Eye Mihawk,
the world's strongest swordsman,
and the pirate hunter Zoro...
What kind of fight will it be?
There can't possibly be anyone
who can defeat Big Bro!
Big Bro is the strongest already!
Hey, what's the meaning of that?
I'm no beast that goes all
out when hunting a rabbit.
Even if you're a swordsman who's
earned a bit of a name for himself,
this sea, the East Blue, is the
weakest among the four seas.
Unfortunately, I don't carry any
smaller sharp instrument than this one.
That's enough making fun of me!
Better not regret it when I kill you!
Frog in the well... Know how big the world is.
Demon... Slash!
Wh-What?!
Zoro?!
Wha... Big Bro's Demon Slash was stopped!
Even a big technique that never
fails to blow any enemy away was...
What's going on?!
I... I can't move them! What did he do?!
No one has ever seen through this technique,
and he stopped it using a toy like that?!
This... can't be happening!
Our abilities are this far apart?!
That can't be right!
There's no way that it's this far...
The world's strongest can't be this far!
This can't be happening, right, Big Bro?!
Get serious!
Big Bro!
We can't be this far apart!
What ferocity your swordplay has...
He's taking Zoro's Three Swords Style
attacks with such a small knife...
He's a monster even beyond the monstrous Zoro!
I didn't pursue swordsmanship all this time
to be dealt with by a toy like this!
Zoro...
You're lucky, Zoro. You're a boy.
I want to be the world's
greatest swordsman, too!
If only... If only I had been born a man!
Don't be whining like that after you beat me!
That's not fair! You're my goal!
Zoro...
Promise me!
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
Promise me!
It's a promise!
To become the world's strongest!
I... I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
I'll be the world's greatest swordsman
so that my name will reach heaven!
I promised her... I...
Only to defeat this man...
What do you bear on your shoulders?
What do you desire once you've
obtained power, weak one?
You called Big Bro a weak one?
You cross bastard!
I'll teach you a lesson! He is...
Stop it! Yosaku! Johnny!
Don't intervene!
Be patient!
Luffy...
I can't lose...
Tiger...
That sounds great!
The world's greatest swordsman?
The Pirate King would need
no less than that on his crew!
...Trap!
Are you just going to let me pierce your heart?
Why aren't you withdrawing?
I don't know...
I don't know why, but...
...if I withdrew even a step,
I feel like those various
important things such as pledges
and promises in the past will be shattered,
and I won't be able to come
back to where I am now...
Yes, that's what defeat is about.
Then, all the more reason I can't withdraw...
Even if you'll die?
I'd rather die.
What a strong heart!
So he chooses death over defeat!
Kid! State your name.
Roronoa Zoro.
I'll remember it.
I haven't seen anyone like you
in a while, strong one. Thus...
...as a swordsman's courtesy,
I'll sink you using the world's
strongest Black Blade.
I appreciate it.
H-He took it out!
That's the sword that sliced up the ship!
So this'll be the last hit...
Will it be the world's strongest?
Or death?
Big Bro! That's enough! Please stop!
Three-Swords Style Secret Art:
Fall!
Three Thousand Worlds!
I lost...
I never imagined I'd ever lose...
So this is the power of the world's strongest...
What are you...
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame...
Admirable!
Zoro!!
Don't live so hastily, young man.
– Big Bro!!
Why?
When I decided to become the strongest swordsman,
I decided to devote my life to it.
He's crazy!
His opponent is the real world's strongest!
How it'd turn out was clear.
He should give up his ambition rather than die!
It should be easy...
to give up your ambition, right?!
So this is the power of the Grand Line...
the power of the world!
To think the pirate hunter Zoro
is as helpless as a new-born baby!
Damn you, damn you... Damn you!!
– Big Bro!!
Wh-What's that?
So that brat... has the power of a devil fruit!
You bastard...
Are you that young swordsman's comrade?
You also impressed me for
watching it to the very end!
Don't worry. I didn't kill that man.
What?
Big Bro! Big Bro! Say something!
Zoro?!
Zoro!!
Now, hurry up and get him up on the ship!
This is medicine! Throw it over him!
It's still too early for you to die.
My name is Dracule Mihawk!
Learn about yourself!
Learn about the world!
And become strong!
No matter how many years it takes,
I will hold this seat of the
strongest and wait for you.
Surpass this sword!
Try to surpass me! Roronoa Zoro!
Big Bro! Big Bro, say something!
To think that he got Hawk-Eye Mihawk to say this much...
Kid, what is your goal?
Pirate King!
It'll be even harder than surpassing me!
How would I know when I haven't done it yet?!
He's alive!
He's just unconscious.
– Big Bro!
– Big Bro! Say something!
Zoro?
Big Bro!
L... Luffy...
Can you hear me?
Yeah!
Did I worry you?
You need no less than the world's
greatest swordsman, right?
Big Bro! Please don't talk any more!
Big Bro!
I... I will not be defeated ever again!
Until the day I defeat him
and become a master swordsman...
I'll never... be defeated!
Got any problems with that...
...Pirate King?!
Nope!
You're a good team.
I want to see you guys again.
Hey, Hawk-Eye!
Didn't you come to take my life...
...the life of the East Blue's ruler, Don Krieg?
I was going to, but I had enough fun.
So I'm going home to get some rest.
You may have had enough,
but I'm tired of getting beaten.
D-Don?
Why are you trying to keep him here?
Die before you leave!!
As I expected... he never learns a lesson...
Damn! He escaped...
Usopp!
Luffy!
Go! I'll leave Nami to you!
Got it!
Zoro and I will bring Nami back for sure!
Make sure you get that cook to join us!
When all five of us are reunited, let's go to...
...the Grand Line!
Yeah! Let's do that!
Guys! We ran into some interference,
but the real fight starts now!
We'll take that ship!
Yeah!!
Pops, can I stop doing
chores if I drive them away?
Suit yourself.
Krieg and his pirates are coming!
Honestly, what an ungrateful bunch they are,
when they were given food!
Come to think of it,
there's another ungrateful one
who took treasure and ran off...
You shouldn't worry about it!
Get some rest!
Hey, a weird guy came out...
He's fully armed with shields!
Ow, ow, ow! Fire! Fire!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Deadly Leg Technique Bursts Forth!
Sanji vs. the Invincible Pearl
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Deadly Leg Technique Bursts Forth!
Sanji vs. the Invincible Pearl