Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
The Straw Hats have left Fishman Island
and finally reached the New World.
But not before entering the treacherous Maubeugemour Sea.
What's this weather?!
We're in the Maubeugemour Sea!
Momemomejuban?!
No, "Maubeugemour"!
Also known as the "Ill-Tempered Sea"!
Home to weather conditions you've never seen or heard of before!
Arriving there, they met a Giant girl who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit
and decided to help her save her father - Panz Fry from the Navy's ship.
But I have to save Dad at any cost!
Before they take him to Impel Down,
this is my last chance to save him!
Lily.
Let me help you!
I wanna try that heavenly food that only your dad can make!
However, a mysterious group called the Neo Navy
is trying to kill her father.
Dad!
Consider that our greeting.
Surface and finish them off at once!
Yes, sir!
And a three-way battle erupted between the Straw Hats,
the Navy and the Neo Navy.
Another bomb?!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Move!
A man?!
Outta my way!
Damn!
I won't let you do whatever you like on this ship
while it's under the control of the Navy!
Pops' heavenly food is...
...all mine!
Z's Ambition
A Desperate Escape Plan!
Invade the ship!
We won't let you!
Kill the pirates!
A 400-million-berry bounty, huh? Are you a pirate too?
Yeah.
Then to hell with you too!
Leave it up to me.
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Iron Body!
What a strange technique. Did you eat a Devil Fruit?
I'm a rubber man.
But that wasn't strong enough to break my Iron Body!
Oh yeah?
I said I won't let you do whatever you like on this ship!
Roronoa Zoro!
Thank you for waiting. Let's pick up where we left off!
Advance! Kill the pirates!
Party Table Kick Course!
Get ready to open fire!
He's an easy target.
Dad!
Treinta Fleurs: Strangle!
Robin-chan!
Who on earth are they?!
Oh no! It's a big mess!
Hey, Nami!
I know!
I'm trying to think of the best way to bring back Lily's father!
No! Is that the Thrust Up Stream?!
Bastard! Gum-Gum...
Both Luffy-san and Zoro-san are on the defensive.
Those two must be very strong!
Take this, you monster!
Hey you!
Even though I'm a soul without a body now,
I'm not happy to be shot at!
There's no mistaking it! Damn! Not now!
Thank you for waiting! Nami!
Franky! We have a problem!
The weather's gonna change drastically again!
It's not safe here!
What?!
Everybody, listen carefully!
The Thrust Up Stream is coming soon!
--The Thrust Up... --...Stream?
What's that?
Is it something like the Knock Up Stream
that we rode to get to the Sky Island?!
Yes, it is! But it's not that big!
Oh good!
But it could easily blow away a warship!
What?!
And once it starts erupting, it could appear anywhere around us!
So return to the Sunny immediately!
R-Roger!
Armament: Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
Don't you get it yet? Iron Body!
...Jet Bazooka!
What? Haki?!
One-Sword Style:
360-Pound Phoenix!
Franky! The anchors!
Roger!
You brat!
You have some nerve.
You too!
Sanji-kun! Lily!
Nami-san! I guess she's worrying about me.
It's not safe here!
Something like the Knock Up Stream is coming!
What?!
Did the anchors dig into the raft?!
Yeah!
Then, get away on the Sunny now!
--Okay! --Uh-huh!
What happened?!
Luffy! Silly swordsman!
Let's get away from here with Coup de Burst and her dad in tow!
Alright!
--I won't let you... --...Do that!
Usopp!
Oh no, Luffy and the others!
Don't get in my way!
Th-Th-That was scary!
Yo, super welcome back!
Usopp!
Franky, use Coup de Burst now!
I'm afraid I can't!
Huh? Why?
I didn't notice until I got closer but the raft is too big.
What the hell... Oh, what should I do?
Yeah! That just might work!
What?! Use the eruption of the Thrust Up Stream to catapult us?!
There's no other way!
But you don't know if it'll erupt at the right moment...
Shut up!
Sanji-kun, are the anchors still holding?
Yeah!
Hang on tight now! You have to fly on the raft!
Damn! That was a little off!
Another one's coming.
Nami, not yet?
No!
Not yet.
Now, Franky!
Chicken Voyage!
Coup de Burst!
Luffy!
A flying ship?!
You can't get away from me!
Rescue mission accomplished!
Yeah!
Now, I get to eat that heavenly food!
Um... Don't forget about me!
He got away again.
Once we set our sights on someone, he can't get away.
I can say the same for you guys since you know our secret now!
Go to hell!
We've wasted too much time here.
Let's go after them!
What a fight! It's been going on for 5 hours now!
--They're equal in strength? --No, Shuzo-san has an advantage.
She doesn't have enough strength left.
I know you're suffering. Let me finish this for you!
Did I miss?! No worries. I'll get you with the next one!
What?!
Damn you, Devil Fruit user!
The battle is over.
The winner is Ain!
After that practice match, Ain became Master Z's aide
and I became leader of this flying squad.
But soon, he will find out which one of us is more suited
to be his right-hand person.
Looks like we got away from the Maubeugemour Sea.
The weather is really different from before. It's quiet here.
Yeah, we've come so far! I don't see any ship coming after us!
Of course, you don't! That was an extra-large Coup de Burst!
No one can follow us - even with a high-speed craft.
We can hide behind these reefs and catch our breath for now.
Uh-huh! How's it going there?
He's got a deep wound but...
but he's gonna be alright if he rests for a couple days.
Thank you, Chopper-sa! I appreciate it!
B-Being thanked doesn't make me happy at all, you bastard!
Anyway, I'm glad that he's okay.
So can you make the heavenly food, like now?
Are you a monster?!
Huh?
Why?! Chopper said he's gonna be okay...
You weren't listening to me, Luffy!
I said he needs to rest!
What? What about the heavenly food?
Boy, even if Lily-chan's father were okay,
we don't have anything to make heavenly food out of!
Oh, I got some food!
What?
Where? Lily, where is it?!
There, look!
Oh, there it is! When did you get it?!
When the warship blew away earlier, food was raining down.
I thought "What a waste!" and picked up as much as I could!
Excellent work!
But under those circumstances? How greedy!
Oh yeah!
Dad, Luffy-sa and the others were in danger! What was I thinking?!
I got some sake too.
Excellent work.
Hey!
But even if we have food, frying pan pops can't cook, can he?
Of course not!
I'll cook for...
What are you doing?! I told you to rest!
Ow, ow, ow... It's just for a little while. I'll be fine.
Dad! Do as Chopper-sa says!
Your name is Luffy, isn't it?
Yeah! I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Ow, ow, ow...
Dad!
Listen, Lily.
Dad?
Luffy wants so badly to eat the food that I make.
What an honor for a cook!
W-Well, I understand that. But...
On top of that, they saved our lives.
If I don't return the favor, I should be ashamed of myself as a cook... No.
As a Giant!
Dad!
Now, bring that food here!
I'll make them my heavenly food!
Really?! Thanks, frying pan pops!
No, I have to thank you instead. Thank you, Luffy!
Lily-chan! I'll make something too!
Okay, I'll help him too! I'll carry those bags of food!
Me too!
Sake! Sake!
You go and help them too.
Uh-huh! I will!
Shuzo-san, I found them! They're hiding behind a reef!
How annoying! All ships, prepare for battle!
Let's blow them up along with the reef!
I-I'm afraid we used up all our torpedoes in the battle earlier
and we're almost out of bombshells too.
All right. Then...
No, we still have a torpedo.
No, we don't.
We can use this submersible as a torpedo!
We are the proud soldiers of the Neo Navy's flying squad!
We trusted in Master Z and Shuzo-san and got this far!
Shuzo-san! Let us fight with you! Please!!
Me too!
I'm proud of you guys! I'll care for you to your deathbed!
Fight to your heart's content as a Neo Navy soldier!
All torpedoes, go!
I'm not gonna let you get away this time!
Damn pirates!
The Neo Marines have launched a surprise attack
and the Straw Hats begin their final battle against Shuzo.
Both sides deal blows
until Shuzo reveals his ultimate weapon
and unleashes it on Luffy.
As the shockwave hits the Straw Hats,
Lily takes fate into her own hands and makes her decision!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Z's Ambition
Luffy vs. Shuzo!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Z's Ambition
Luffy vs. Shuzo!