Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
rashinban nante jyuutai no moto
compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
delirious with fever, i take the helm
hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
if the dusty treasure map has been verified,
tashikameta no nara densetsu janai
it's not a legend!
kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
when it comes to personal storms,
biorizumu nokkatte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
omoi sugoseba ii
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
poketto no koin
a coin in my pocket,
soreto You Wanna Be My Friend
and do you wanna be my friend?
We Are
we are!
What's with this restaurant?
It's as if... as if... this were a pirate ship!
We've got trouble!
Pirate Krieg's underling...
This is a restaurant, right?
Sir, do you have money for that?
– Would a bullet do?
– So you don't have money, right?
Eat it.
I found a good cook!
This is a good opportunity.
Damn geezer!
Leave this place with them!
You're no longer needed at this restaurant!
The Strongest Pirate Fleet!
Commodore Don Krieg
Hey, you damn geezer!
I'm the Sous Chef here.
What do you mean you no longer need me?!
You often get into trouble with customers.
You flare your nostrils
the second you see a girl.
You can't even cook a decent meal,
so you're dead weight to this restaurant.
That's what I said.
Say that again...
Also, the other cooks steer clear of you...
So go be a pirate or whatever,
and just leave this restaurant already!
Say what?
If I keep quiet, you just shoot your mouth off, huh? You damn geezer!
The rest I could overlook,
but I'm not just gonna
let you trash my cooking!
No matter what you say,
I'll stay here as a cook!
And that's final!
Just what's the meaning of you
grabbing the owner by the collar?
You idiot!
Damn you...
Quit screwing around...
No matter how hard you try to kick me out,
I'll continue to work here as a cook...
...until you die!
I won't die! I'll live 100 more years!
That geezer is never short of words...
All right, you have permission!
Now you can become a pirate.
No way!
Now... Sorry about that.
I'd like to make up for it by serving
you fruit macedonia, my princess.
Wow, thank you! You're so kind.
– Any time...
– And no apology to us?!
I'm gonna sue you, you stupid love cook!
I'm serving you tea, aren't I?
Thank me for that, long-nose.
Huh? You wanna fight?
I won't go easy on you.
Beat him up, Zoro!
Do it yourself.
Stop! Please don't fight because of me.
– Yes, I'll stop.
– Who said it was because of you?!
– By the way, you know...
– Yes?
The food you have here is delicious...
...but it seems a little expensive for me...
Of course, it'll be free.
Thank you!
– Yours are not free.
– Wha...
You're too predictable.
What are you sitting around for?!
When customers sit down,
bring them moist hand-towels!
Yes, sir.
Well... with this and that going on,
four days have passed...
When can we leave here?
Who knows?
Is he really going to work here
as a chore boy for a year?
What's the problem?
The food is free and it's comfortable here.
For you it is.
Hey, Luffy!
Hmm?
What's going on?!
Let's leave here soon!
Wait a little longer.
I'll try talking to Owner again.
I'm begging you!
Hey, what's the matter?
An hourglass... on each side of the skull...
...to show the threat to enemies...
That flag is... that flag is...
There's no mistake... it belongs to the ruler of the East Blue...
Don Krieg!!
Why... why are the Krieg Pirates here?!
You see it, Patty?! They actually came!
You're gonna get rid of them, right?!
I-Isn't it a mistake?!
This is the Don of a pirate fleet with a
5,000-pirate force we're talking about!
Why would he come all the way here
to get revenge just for one of his men?!
It's no mistake! He's really here!
Hey, this is not good!
Shouldn't we just get out of here?!
What a huge galleon!
What a huge ship!
I wonder if Ghin came back
to repay you for your kindness.
I don't think so...
But it seems strange...
– H-Hey...
– Wh-What the...
Their ship sure is beat up...
It doesn't seem like they
were attacked by cannons...
But then, it's hard to think
that damage is man-made.
Did they come across a tornado or something?
Here he comes...
S-Sorry... Can I have some water and food?
We have money... tons of money...
I don't even remember the last time I ate.
Please... give me some water and food...
Wh-What's that?!
He shows neither dignity nor force.
Is he really that Don Krieg,
Commodore of the grand pirate fleet?
So he's hungry...
C-Captain!
Don Krieg!
P-Please! Help our captain!
He's really about to starve!
He hasn't eaten anything for days!
He'll die if he doesn't eat!
This is good! It's a riot to see
the famous arch rogue Don Krieg like this...
We have money this time.
We're customers!
Don't be ridiculous!
Hey, contact the Navy right away.
What?
He's at his weakest right now.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity!
There's no need to feed him anything.
Keep him under arrest.
He's right! We don't know what
he'll do once his energy's back.
He's done bad things.
He deserved to starve because
of everything he's done!
Once he's back to normal, I bet he'll
attack this restaurant straight away.
There's no need to give
him even a glass of water.
I won't do anything...
Once I eat, I promise I'll leave quietly.
So please... help... me...
Don Krieg, please stop!
Please stop begging!
It's not something you should do!
Please don't do something so disgraceful!
I promise... Please...
I'll take leftovers or anything...
Anything...
Don...
Ha! Are you trying to gain our sympathy?
Hey, out of my way, Patty.
Oh, boy...
S... Sanji-san!
Here, Ghin. Let him eat it.
Sanji-san...
Thank you!
Hey, Sanji! Take that food away now!
Do you realize what kind of man he is?!
He's the man who's called the East Blue Ruler,
the foul player Krieg!
It started in a prison.
He pretended to be a marine soldier
and took over a Navy ship by
killing a senior officer on the ship.
That's how he declared himself a pirate.
He sometimes raised the Navy
flag and entered into harbors
in order to attack the towns and passenger ships.
He also raised a white flag
and then attacked enemy ships...
He did anything to continue winning.
That's how he got to where he is now!
Huh... so he plays dirty.
His real strength is overwhelming as well.
Leaving after eating?
That's not possible with him!
Letting such a wicked fiend die
without help is for society's sake!
What?!
S... Sanji!
Th... This isn't what we agreed, Don Krieg!
I brought you here under the condition
that you wouldn't touch this restaurant!
And that man saved our lives...
Yeah, that was delicious.
I feel alive again.
H-Hey...
Wh-What the hell is going on in there?
We'll see when we go in there.
What?! A-Are you serious?!
Oh? Are you scared?
Wha... Don't be silly!
Hmph!
This is strange...
There's almost no sign of anyone on that ship...
This is a good restaurant.
I'll take this ship.
So... that's what you want...
Ow, ow, ow...
My ship became a wreck,
so I wanted a new one.
You'll get off this ship after you
take care of what I tell you to do.
Wh-What?!
Don Krieg... This isn't what you promised.
There're about 100 of my
underlings still alive on my ship.
They're weak with hunger and severe injuries.
First, prepare 100 meals and water for them.
There're some who've already starved to death.
W-Water...
Bring them over immediately!
Are you telling us to revive pirates
that are gonna attack this ship?!
We refuse!
Refuse? Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not placing an order.
I'm giving you orders.
It doesn't matter who you are... don't defy me!!
– Sanji-san...
– Hmm?
Sanji-san, I'm sorry...
I didn't mean for this to happen...
You son of a bitch!
Look what you've done!!
Hey Sanji! Where're you going?!
To the kitchen.
I have to prepare 100 more meals.
– Sanji-san!
– Sanji?!
– What?!
Right. That's how it should be.
Are you Krieg's spy, Sanji?!
We can't let you go in the kitchen!
We're fed up with your crazy behavior!
Go ahead...
If you want to stop me, go ahead!
I know...
He's an incorrigible rogue... I know that much...
But that doesn't matter to me.
That doesn't matter!
What happens after we feed them...
It's too much of a bother to think about it.
I'm a cook. No more. No less.
If there's someone who's hungry, I'll feed him.
That's all.
It's all right for a cook to be
that way, don't you think?
Patty!
Hey, someone keep him restrained!
Sanji, you sometimes feed customers
I drive away at the back door, don't you?
I'm not gonna say who's right,
but this time, it's your mistake.
I'm not going to let you do
what you want any longer.
I'll protect this restaurant.
Fortunately, we have only one enemy to fight.
Even if it's Don Krieg,
what can he do against us?
This is a sea restaurant where
pirates come and go every day.
We're fully prepared to
serve any kind of customer!
That's...
Are you full now, Krieg-san?
After the main course, how about...
...a piece of iron dessert?!
Meat Ball of Doom!!
Don!
I might've broken the doors.
Owner's gonna yell at me again.
Well, you did it to protect the restaurant.
It's a small price to pay.
What're you gonna do
about those in Krieg's ship?
Who knows?
Maybe we'll spread butter
on the ship and stir-fry it...
It'll taste good, right? You lame cook!
How dare you serve such a nasty dessert?!
This is the lousiest restaurant!
You're damn annoying!!
From all over his body...
Bullets...
Don't defy me!
I'm the strongest!
Steel arms more powerful than anyone's...
A wootz steel-made body
that is harder than anyone's...
And a diamond fist that can destroy anything!
I have all sorts of built-in
weapons throughout my body...
The 50-ship large fleet and 5,000-pirate force!
I've won all battles in the past!
I am the man fit to be called Don!
Out of my way, kid!
When I tell you to prepare food,
all you have to do is obediently follow orders!
Don't defy me!
There's probably enough for 100 meals in this.
Bring it to your ship right away.
– Owner Zeff!
What's with that, pops?
I could've gotten hurt!
Z... Zeff?
Chisana koro ni wa takara no chizu ga
When I was little,
Atama no naka ni ukandeite
I had a vision of a treasure map
Itsudemo sagashita kiseki no basho o
and I always searched for that miraculous place
Shiranai dareka ni makenai you ni
before someone else could beat me to it
Yume sae tsukamenai mama
If the world is going to change
Moshi mo sekai ga kawaru no nara
before I can even attain my dream
Nanimo shiranai koro no watashi ni
then take me to the time when I knew nothing
Tsurete itte omoide ga iro asenai you ni
so that my memories won't fade
Is it really okay to give Krieg food like this?
Yeah. Do something about that, pops!
Okay, leave it to me!
Hey! What're you doing, Luffy?!
Don't go picking a fight with Krieg, you idiot!
That sounds fun.
Gonna fight, Luffy? Need a hand?
Next time, on One Piece:
Protect Baratie!
The Great Pirate, Red Leg Zeff!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Protect Baratie!
The Great Pirate,
Red Leg Zeff!