A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
You're the insolent folks
who didn't pay their taxes
at the harbor, aren't you?
Sanji!
Geez, what are you doing?!
That's the Rainbow Mist!
Professor, where are we?
Ape's Concert.
Ape's Concert? It couldn't be.
W-What's that?!
A ship graveyard, where once
you enter, you can never get out.
Residents of the
Land of Eternity!
The Pumpkin Pirates!
Hey, look! There's nothing but sunken ships,
as far as you can see!
L-Let's give this up. It feels like a
ghost captain might appear at any time.
Really? Ghost captain!
Don't call to them!
Beyond the Rainbow Mist
is the world of the eternal.
The final paradise remaining on earth.
It's filled with treasures of gold and silver,
where people live forever
without aging or going hungry.
That's what's written in this book.
I told you, that's nothing more than a legend.
Professor, you knew that this
place was a ship graveyard?
Yeah.
50 years ago, I got a short glimpse of this place.
If you knew it, then why come?
I told you that, too.
I've been carrying on my research
in order to rescue my friends that
were swallowed up in this mist.
I even became Wetton's dog,
and put up with the finger-pointing, to that end.
Hey!
Look at this!
What's this?
Isn't it awesome?
There's lots, lots more inside the ship!
I'm gonna go explore some more!
Whether this is a paradise or not,
the "being filled with treasure"
thing doesn't appear to be
altogether untrue, huh, Professor?
Those who would disturb the rest of the dead...
W-What's that?!
Leave the cargo, and depart at once,
or else, the curse of the dead shall befall you!
I-I'm s-scared...!
Who's there?
There they are!
Now, hand over the cargo, nice and easy...
Or else...
That was close! You rotten...
Ghost captain...!
There's nothing inside!
They're... ghosts... all... right...!
But that arrow came from over there.
What?
Luffy! Over there!
There's someone over there!
Hey, listen to me, Luffy!
Luffy, I say!
Oh, a bow.
Luffy! Watch out!
Luffy...!
Why, you...!
Special attack: Fire Star!!
What's this?
– Akibi!
– Wait, Rongo!
– Take it easy, Rongo!
Oh, you're just kids, aren't you?
Rongo!
Akibi!
You idiot, stay away! Run!
Gum-Gum...
...I'm Home!!
Yo, thank you for that earlier.
You're welcome.
Rongo!
That's enough!
We are the Pumpkin Pirates,
and Ape's Concert is our territory!
Release my friends, and turn over
the cargo, if you want to live!
A bomb?
Rapa Nui!
Could it be...?
Hey, now, if you use that, you'll blow us all up!
We're all in the same boat!
We live, and die, together!
– Let's go.
– I'm sorry, Rapa Nui. Rongo!
Rapa Nui...? Is that you, Rapa Nui...?
And... Isoka, and Rongo... It's you, all right...
Don't you know me? It's me, Henzo!
We always used to play together,
on Cape Luluka!
Henzo?!
You know them?
Henzo? You don't mean that Henzo!
You idiot, there's no way...
Stay back! I-I'll blow us up! Stay back, I said!
S-Stop!
Kaboom Mark III. I invented it, after all.
It's just a gizmo used for bluffing.
Damn, it's a smokescreen!
What's all the racket...?
You're just now waking up?!
Huh? For that matter, who's the old guy?
Well, it would take a bit of
time to explain it to you.
Hey, they're gone from over here, too.
Who was that just now?
Huh, Pops?
Henzo! Hurry on down!
I-I'm too scared!
Don't be afraid over something like this!
We're the Pumpkin Pirates!
When I grow up, I'm gonna be a real pirate.
But Rapa Nui, your father is a marine, right?
Is he going to let you?
My pop is my pop.
I want to have adventures in places
that nobody has seen before!
Places nobody has seen before?
Sure. There are still lots of things in
this world that nobody knows about.
I want to see them, too.
Me, too. I'll be a pirate, too.
But we'll have to fight with other pirates, too, right?
Someone as weak as I am couldn't do that.
Henzo, you can invent all
sorts of things, can't you?
You'll invent the gear that
we'll need for our adventures.
Hey, yeah!
Okay, I'll be a pirate, too!
You're easy to convince, Henzo!
We were so happy.
Playing as friends, and chatting...
I spent the best days of my life with them.
Every day was so bright,
it doesn't even compare to treasure.
Until that one dreadful event occurred...
Henzo!
Henzo! Are you all right?!
I've perfected the Kaboom Mark III!
You idiot! Don't scare us like that!
You sure do have a lot of false alarms, huh?
Holy crap! The town is on fire!
The town of Luluka is on fire!
– What is this...?
– Our town...
Dad! Mom!
Rongo!
Burn! Burn!
Leave nothing of value!
Kill everyone that opposes us,
the Wetton Pirates! Got it?!
Show the women and children no mercy!
Pirates!
What's this, there are still some kids
who haven't run away, are there?
Listen, guys, once we get to the harbor,
there will be ships there.
We'll take one of them, it doesn't
matter which one, and get out of here.
But what about Dad, and the others?!
You idiot! Do you wanna get killed?!
Go!
Those brats...
The ships...!
Those guys earlier must have sunk them!
Over there! We'll get on that one!
Eh? That one?
There aren't any others, right? Hurry!
What are you doing to my ship?!
Here he comes!
Damn it!
Ker-splash!
You all are ready to answer for this, right?
Hurry, up there!
You think someone like you can handle this axe?
Don't get too cocky, kid.
I'm not a kid!
I'm Rapa Nui, the leader of the Pumpkin Pirates!
– Rapa Nui!
– It's all right! He's just one man!
Let's all join our forces together, and defeat him!
Huh? Captain, are we setting sail already?
There's another one!
Huh? Who are you guys?
What is that?!
The Rainbow Mist!
Hey, hurry and turn the helm!
If we get swallowed up inside there,
we won't be able to get back!
The helm is busted!
Why, you... You'll pay for this!
Akibi!
Don't think you're getting
out of here alive anymore.
Akibi!
Your shoulder's dislocated.
Rapa Nui!
You'll pay for that!
Henzo!
Go back! Turn the ship back!
We can't! The helm is busted!
The Rainbow Mist... The Rainbow Mist...!
Rapa Nui!
Go on! Keep going! Don't worry about me!
Henzo!
I promise, I'll come after you later!
I am a member of the Pumpkin Pirates, after all!
Henzo...
Ever since...
Ever since, Rapa Nui and the others have never returned.
To think that they actually became pirates in a place like this...
Yeah, but that happened 50 years ago, right?
They were still just little kids.
The passage of time within the
Rainbow Mist appears to be different.
One day in here might be equivalent to a week,
or even a year, in the outside world.
W-What?!
If that's true, we have to
find a way out of here fast,
or there'll be no undoing the damage.
Why not?
You are so dense!
The same thing that happened
between those kids earlier and the
old man could happen to us, too!
While we're in here, puttering around,
Nami and the others we left behind
will become old men and women!
What?!
Hey, Pops, let's go back, quick!
Like he said, we don't know how to get back!
What?! Is that right?!
So, there's no way back?
What have you been listening to, Luffy?!
No... There must be a way
They must have said it... three times now!
to get out of Ape's Concert.
Oh, that many times?
Geez, these guys are persistent.
That weapon is a real problem.
You shut your traps! I'll finish you off!
– Lake-sama!
– Are you all right, Lake-sama?
Are you the ones who chucked that?!
No, not us.
For that matter, wasn't he watching?
He is wearing that thing, and all.
I asked you, was it you?!
What if we say it was?
All right.
You're picking it up?!
I have collected your harbor dues.
I now formally welcome
you as a citizen of Luluka.
Ape's Concert, you say?
Yeah.
Some soldiers said they saw your ship enter
the Rainbow Mist, no doubt about it.
From what the mayor says,
it's piled up with treasure in there.
Treasure?!
They say that Ape's Concert is a ship graveyard.
The shipwrecks in there have
untouched cargo all over the place.
The mayor is after that treasure,
which is why he has a scientist,
named Henzo, researching a
way to get into Ape's Concert.
Ah, the old man made this electroshock suit, too.
What do you think? Pretty damn slick, isn't it?
This guy sure likes to talk a lot, huh?
Shouldn't he be content
with just getting the tax?
We can't just stand around here!
We're going in into that mist, too!
Yes, sir, Nami-san!
But once we go in there, there's no coming out!
What good will getting scared do?
Our treasure is waiting for us!
Eh?!
No one is allowed into Ape's Concert
without my permission.
– Grandpa!
– You bonehead!
Grandpa...?
You've got a poor memory.
Aren't I always telling you?
You are to call me "Mayor."
"Mayor Wetton."
Aa hateshinaku tsuzuiteru sora no mukou ni
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
Itsuka mita asu o ima egakihajimete iru
The future that I once saw is now starting to take shape
Jibun ni makesou ni naru hi mo aru
There are days where I almost lose to myself
Sonna toki wa
When that happened,
atataka na basho ga atta
there was someplace warm I could go
Hokoreru mono itsumo kitto
The friends I took pride in always, without fail,
Boku no senaka oshite kureta yo ne?
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Aa hoshi-tachi ga furisosogu kono sora no shita
Ah, the stars are pouring down underneath the sky
Nido to nai ima o hora
This unique moment...
Can you believe that the old man
and those kids were the same age?
Hey, what are you doing, Luffy?
I was thinking that if we get the
ship going, we can get out of here.
Should we be doing that without Nami?!
She's probably upset about being left behind.
She might be a wrinkly old woman by now, huh?
Don't say anything so chilling!
Next time, on One Piece:
Thoughts of Home!
The Pirate Graveyard of No Escape!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Thoughts of Home!
The Pirate Graveyard
of No Escape!