Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has landed on Marineford
to save his brother, Ace, from execution.
Trying to make it to the execution platform,
Luffy breached the barricades with Jinbe's help.
Following him, the Whitebeards boarded a paddle boat
they'd hidden underwater and charged into the plaza.
Gear 2!
You're too slow!
Go across the sea towards Oars!
We have a problem!
Another coated ship is entering the bay!
Sink it like the Moby Dick!
No! Not the boat! Shoot at Oars!
He pulled the boat out of the water!
Through the barricades!
Pops!
Stay back, my sons!
Guys! Rescue Ace and...
...destroy the Navy!!
Garp.
Yeah.
I don't think we can make it through this unscathed!
Luffy at the End of His Tether!
An All-out Battle at Oris Plaza!!
It's curtains for a Devil Fruit user
if they fall into the sea!
If nothing is done, Vi'm gonna really... really...
fall... fall...
fall...
Or not!
"You're not gonna fall?! You got me there!"
What are you doing, Ivankov?
Be quiet please! Vi need to hear what's going on at the plaza!
Huh? You are the one who is making noise!
Ouch! I got hurt!
Vi'm sure that the battle is growing fiercer
on the other side of the wall.
Maybe, Straw-boy is already...
boiled!
Or roasted!
Or frozen!
Yeah, maybe that's what is happening to him!
Oh no! Oh boy!
What are you doing?! We need to hurry!
It's all your fault, Jinbe!
What?! What did I do?!
Yes! It wouldn't have gone like this if you had just beaten them and rescued Ace-boy already!
That was impossible!
Destroy Navy HQ!
Oars, thank you.
Clear the way in front of me!
Alright!
He's gonna do it again!
I have no choice.
Ice Ball!
Whitebeard got frozen!
We got him!
Pops!
Oh no! The vibrations can't be frozen!
Ice...
Admiral Kuzan!
Stabbed with Haki?!
Did it kill Blue Pheasant?!
No! Don't be ridiculous!
Ice Block: Partisan!
Pops, move on!
I'm counting on you!
Diamond Jozu!
We're almost there!
The scaffold is right there!
If only we could gain control of this mess!
We won't let you! You all die right here!
Ace!
I thought the war was over
once the walls had been activated!
Damn! Now Whitebeard
and Straw Hat have made it this far!
Next time, I will catch you!
I will be much much stronger and...
I'll become a Navy...
...ad...
...admiral someday!
I made that promise to him but I haven't changed at all!
Luffy-san!
I've got to fight too!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I, Momonga won't let you pass through here
in the name of the Navy vice admirals!
Vice admiral? The same rank as Grandpa?
Shave!
Moon Walk!
G-Gear...
...2...
Seems like you're reaching your limit! Finger Pistol!
No wonder. He's a rookie after all.
But...
Hmmm?
...he's tenacious.
Garp, don't forget that you're one of us!
All you have is courage.
But, Straw Hat Luffy, if you're not strong enough,
you can't save him no matter how hard you try.
Ace...
H-He is no competition for an admiral!
No way...
Luffy-san!
Kill Whitebeard!
We won't let you!
Why don't you just get lost?
Ace's brother!
Ace...
Whitebeard's command has dulled.
You could've done better than that.
I can't believe that you let that piece of crap...
...who is so reckless, take the lead!
We won't let you lay a finger on Pops!
How touching!
There he is! Straw-boy!
He's there, Jinbe!
Who is it?!
Where is that voice coming from?
Vi knew it! This is exactly
what Vi thought was happening!
It's up there!
Why is that face so big?!
Ivankov of the Revolutionary Army!
Luffy-kun!
Are you still alive, Straw-boy?!
Oh, Vi'm gonna fall, gonna fall...
Or not!
You did!
What are you doing?!
My apologies!
How boisterous you are.
Iva-chan! Jinbe!
Let me go!
O-Old man! I gotta... I gotta...! Let me go!
He has done a lot already. Treat him.
Alright!
You don't need to! There's no time for it!
I gotta go! Just let me go!
Ace is...! Ace is...!
Ace is my only brother!!
At any cost... At any cost, I will... I will...
...save him!
Luffy-kun! Hey!
It looks very bad!
Please, surgeon! Save his life!
Luffy-kun! Luffy-kun! Stay with me, Luffy-kun!
He is nothing but a bundle of energy who just bluffs. Young and clumsy.
But I like fools like him.
Those of you who want to die, come forward!
Watch out, it's Whitebeard!
If I let you wreak havoc, this island won't survive!
Then why don't you protect it?
Take good care of Luffy-kun!
Jinbe, where are you going?!
I'm willing to lay down my life at this place!
Stay away! Don't get caught up!
Die!
Dammit!
N-No way!
What a fragile sword!
We'll make way for Pops!
They're swordsmen, too. But...
...poor losers!
Outta my way!
Move out of my way!
I need to reach Luffy! Don't get in my way!
Oh no!
Boa Hancock is going berserk again!
Slave Arrow!
The number of dead bodies keeps multiplying!
I won't let you bother Pops!
I don't think I taste good.
I-It's not over... yet!
Repel them at once!
They are...
...the allied pirates who came from the bay head!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Yeah, we were expecting you!
Damn! We allowed many of them to reach the plaza!
Uncle won't like this!
It's a melee so a few mistakes can't be helped
but try not to shoot our soldiers as much as possible, Pacifistas!
I'm on my way, Ace!
He's flying!
What are you doing? Shoot him down!
It's not working!
It's alright, just keep shooting!
This is no good!
Go!
Commander Marco!
I never asked you to fight!
The Hero—Monkey D. Garp!
He finally shows himself!
The legendary Navy soldier!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Vice Admiral is on the move!
He'll be the greatest keeper for us!
Old man!
Garp...
If you wanna go further, you have to kill me first!
You brats!
The Whitebeard Pirates slowly begin
to crumble under the Navy's fierce attacks.
When Ace sees his friends injured and falling,
he reflects upon his reason
for existing, and tears come to his eyes.
Meanwhile, Luffy makes a decision to put his life on the line to save Ace!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Power That Will Shorten One's Life
Energy Hormone, Redux"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Power That Will Shorten One's Life
Energy Hormone, Redux