Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Straw Hats landed on Punk Hazard—an island
divided into the Burning and Frozen Lands.
After learning of the island's ruler, Master Caesar Clown's, true intentions,
they are now trying to escape Netherworld, his weapon of mass destruction.
Alongside their newfound ally, the Warlord Trafalgar Law,
they are now on the move to kidnap Caesar,
save the children, and escape from the island.
I have that crazy pirate backing me!
One of the Seven Warlords - Don Quixote Doflamingo!
I said...
...I don't care!
I broke... the gear!
Now,
there is no turning back!
Caesar Crushed!
The Ultimate Grizzly Magnum
The deadly gas, Netherworld,
will fill up the building in five minutes.
The survivors are all heading toward Gate 66
of Building R, their only escape route, however...
Building B, Sanji's Location
The ceiling lifted up just now!
What just happened?!
The gas has started flowing in from the cracks!
This is no good.
--Everybody! Get to Building R now! --Run!
But I'm scared, Sis!
I can't run anymore!
We have no time for wimping out, kids!
Stand up and run!
Don't give up, everybody!
Stand up! Now!
--Captain-chan! --I'm glad that you're okay!
So you beat that bird woman, huh?!
But why are they coming from that direction?!
I thought they were behind us to let us get away!
G-5 is coming this way?!
I told you we were going the wrong way!
That aside, p-put me down! This is embarrassing!
That's a pain! Just stay where you are!
Hey! Who said you can carry Tashigi-chan on your shoulder?!
Zoro! Head back!
--Hurry up, everybody! --This way!
"Broke the gear"?
"There's no turning back"?
That's hysterical.
Realize your place!
Law!
Examination Room
Building B, 2nd Floor
The ceiling's gonna collapse!
Chopper-yan, it's not safe to stay here!
Uh-huh! I've done all I could for now!
Go to Building R now!
Alright, count on us! Let's go, guys!
Yeah!
Mocha! Stay with me! Let's get out of here!
Damn.
How will I eat breakfast tomorrow?
What a horrible turn of events.
How dare you, Law.
This is an upset.
But I know you're going to regret it.
Keep that in mind.
You don't know Joker's past.
And that will cost you your life!
Upstarts like you who have acquired just a touch of fame
can't hope to take over the world.
It's filled with those who are much stronger.
Tell him, Smoker.
All you squirts got is energy.
But this world is much...
Don't worry about me.
Just worry about yourself.
This room will explode.
Goodbye, Vergo the pirate!
Building R, 1st Floor
What was that?
S-Something is falling down!
I know who could have done such a thing!
It must be Law.
What is Vergo doing?!
Master! What's going on?!
--Some of us buried under the wreckage! --Master!
Dammit!
You assholes ruined my "paradise"!
I wonder if everybody is okay.
Gotta take advantage of this confusion!
Roll!
Alright. Now let's look for the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs.
You've got to be kidding!
--The Straw Hat member's gone! --Where did he go?!
Find him!
Building R 2nd floor, can you hear me?
Oh, it's Master!
If Master is okay, we're gonna be alright!
Secret room, come in!
Yes, Master, what just happened?
Open the air vents now!
Let Netherworld flow into this room!
B-But that will...
I'm a gas man. I'm not gonna die.
R-Roger!
Then let's get our fellow soldiers on the 1st floor upstairs first!
I said "Now"!
I said "Do it now"!
Stop complaining and just do it already!
But there are over a hundred soldiers!
I don't care, you idiot!
You guys are just a bunch of guinea pigs!
No one would care if hundreds of you died!
You are the dregs of society!
What are you doing?! Can't you hear me?!
I can find replacements for you fools so easily!
Netherworld is my true power!
That was close!
Now they know who Caesar really is.
Zoro and the others!
They're really in danger!
Could I control the doors from here, by any chance?
Hey! Why're you looking at me like that?
Huh? N-No, I...
Oh, I get it!
Master is trying to fool the enemies!
What?
Oh yeah! You're right!
He must have a plan about the deadly gas, too!
He's not gonna let his people die!
Right, right!
Master is a kind man. It would hurt him
if he finds out we suspected him.
Master! I opened the air vents!
No! The deadly gas!
It's flowing in!
Yes. You should've done as I said from the start!
Dregs shouldn't think!
Now, become my power! Netherworld!
"Netherworld"
This is my scientific power!
It's kicking in.
Look, Straw Hat Luffy! This amazing appearance!
This is my scientific power!
Through this experiment,
two countries have already expressed interest in the weapon - Netherworld.
They are both quite peaceful.
But when humans get serious about defending themselves,
they'll look for any way possible to kill their enemies!
Everybody needs me!
I'll spread weapons all over the world
and become the king of the netherworld!
Look!
Run!
No...
--He killed our fellow soldiers! --What is he doing?!
Master!
Does he really think of us as guinea pigs?
It's amazing if I do say so myself!
Look how fast it works on their nerves!
That's almost an art!
Wh-What... What was that?
Those people are...
Momo, look after Brownbeard.
Huh? Okay!
Hey, where are you going, Straw Hat Luffy?!
Did you chicken out all of a sudden?!
What a pathetic man!
But Building B beyond that path is almost filled up with Netherworld!
There is no place to run on the island anymore!
That goes for all of you guinea pigs, too!
All of you,
die...
...like trash!
That's who Master really is?!
Master!
I trusted him so!
Excuse me. I know you're broken-hearted but could I sit in that control seat?
I wanna save my friends from the gas!
You bastard!
You were watching it, weren't you? Dammit!
Stop! I know you all watched it, too.
Yeah, you're right. We've been terribly betrayed!
We're finished.
Now we know that he was our enemy but...
...we can't run from here!
But so are you people!
Did you just see your captain run from Caesar?!
That serves you right!
He took off leaving you guys behind!
Whoa-whoa, are you dissing our captain right in front of me?
If he were the kind of person who would betray us,
it would've been easier for me.
I would've just run away with my tail between my legs!
Gear 3!
But he never ever stops...
...believing in us...
...so we had no choice but to support him.
We pledged to live up to his expectations as long as we breathe!
Master, please don't...
You people are just crumbs. You shouldn't stand against your master!
Just drop dead like a dog!
--What should we do? --There's nothing we can do.
We can't beat such a powerful man!
--Yes, you can! --What?
You guys should just believe in our captain!
Caesar is...
...the type of person that Luffy hates the most!
H-Help me, Master!
Yes!
I am your master!
I am your savior and I can make efficient use of you good-for-nothings!
Luffy won't forgive Caesar!
Armament; Hardening!
Caesar!
You're back, Straw Hat Luffy!
I don't ever wanna see your face again!
Your death is going to be the climax of this experiment show!
Go to hell!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
Now, drop dead! Behold my scientific power!
Kneel before my power!
Shut up!
Oh yeah, Straw Hat!
You can work under me if you want...
Luffy has crushed Caesar.
The shocking news...
...spreads across the New World in the blink of an eye.
Meanwhile...
...assassins sent by Doflamingo...
...fly toward the island of Punk Hazard.
The storm of a new battle rages!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Attacked!
Assassins from Dress Rosa"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Attacked!
Assassins from Dress Rosa