Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Rainbase
Alubarna
Yuba
Erumalu
Nanohana
Katorea
Spiders Café
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people take up weapons.
The scorching land was now
engulfed in wails of grief,
Rainbase
along with tremendous upheaval.
Yuba
Erumalu
Nanohana
Alubarna
Spiders Café
Katorea
Crocodile's plan was finally being carried out,
and Bon Clay, transformed into the false king,
had appeared in Nanohana.
A rebel army had also risen up.
Meanwhile, Vivi was escaping,
in order to tell Sanji about the peril
that Luffy and the others were in,
having been caught in a trap within Raindinners.
Will Alabasta fall?
Or will it find true peace?
Moment by moment, the hourglass
of fate marks the final hour.
I'm... I'm Mr. Prince!
The Key to a Great Comeback Escape!
The Wax-Wax Ball!
Tony-kun is a decoy?
Yeah. He'll be fine.
Let's hurry, Vivi-chan.
Explain the situation to me.
But Sanji-san, you were
shot earlier, weren't you?
Me?
Hello?
We've caught him!
What should we do with this strange man?!
Where are you? Tell me!
T-The front gate of a casino
in Rainbase, named Raindinners!
All right, nicely done.
That was a star performance.
Now your boss will show up here.
T-Thanks so much.
So, can I go now?
No, sir.
Yeah, guess not...
Look, Chopper.
His friends are starting to crowd around again
in the same place that we were just running wild.
Mm-hmm...
Next, it's whatever I can manage.
That's right.
I'm counting on you.
Who are you?
M-My name is Mr. Prince.
Huh? So then, you're the one
who did all this to my companions?
Whatever I can manage...
My name is Mr. Prince!
What is the meaning of this?
I-It was a man, calling himself Mr. Prince...
Him?!
Bad news! The bridge collapsed!
And that's more or less what happened.
Is Tony-kun all right?
Yeah.
He has some tricks up his sleeve, after all.
I hear something happened over at Raindinners.
They say the bridge collapsed.
You bastard...
Where did you go, Mr. Prince...?
I swear, I'm going to find you, and kill you.
– The water! The water!
– We're gonna die! We're gonna die!
Once this cage is submerged, it's all over for us!
Hey, you stupid gator! Come and get me!
What's come over you, Nami?!
I'm making that guy mad,
to get him to bite the cage apart!
I get it! Great idea!
Come and get me, you stupid banana!
You rotten banana!
No, that's wrong!
I told you, he's basically an alligator,
with a banana on his head.
What?! Would you shut up?
For example, there's the monkey dance, right?
You rotten banana!
Listen to what I'm saying!
What?
For example, there's the monkey dance, right?
A monkey is an animal, but the
monkey dance is a dance, and...
Don't touch that!
Learn something, will you?!
You eat both alligators and bananas, don't you?!
Here he comes!
It's no use!
What a tough cage!
Vivi! Please hurry!
Hey, you guys...
How can you keep so composed?!
You think up something, too!
How much do you guys know?
What exactly is Crocodile after?
That woman who was at Crocodile's side...
She's had a price on her head by
the World Government for 20 years.
The price was over 70,000,000, as I recall.
S-Seventy million?!
S-So what about it?
That's the same price that Crocodile has.
The moment those two joined forces,
this became more than just a simple coup.
This can only develop into a matter that the whole world
will get dragged into, if they're left to it.
The whole world? What do you mean?
That does seem a little far-fetched.
What are you guys talking about?
I don't need any excuse like that to kick his ass!
I see...
So, how are we getting out of here?
It's up to my thighs!
We're gonna die! We're gonna die!
I'm kind of starting to lose my nerve.
This is bad! This is bad!
Tough it out! Didn't Vivi say so?!
Must be hard for you, huh, Vivi?
I'm sorry, I know you don't have time for this.
Damn it!
if only my swordsmanship were better,
this cage would be nothing!
Try as hard as you can not to
make any noise at mealtime.
Bad Manner Kick Course!!
Hey there.
Been waiting long?
Prince!!
Thank goodness.
Stop goofing around and find the key already!
Nami-san!
L-Love me now?
Yeah, yeah, I'm in love,
now hurry and open this up!
Okay!
The guy is an interminable idiot, huh?
Vivi! Way to go!
Here they come, one after the next.
Go, Sanji! Pound them all!
Bunch together as much as you like,
and come get me, you damn bananas.
Anyone with manners as poor as yours,
who would attack a lady,
gets some table manners
beaten into them, but good.
Sanji! There isn't any time for that!
One-second strikes!
No, make that one-instant strikes!
Take out the third one who just came in.
What? You can tell?
Are your ears just for show?
His growl is the same as the one
who swallowed the key, isn't it?
I can't really tell.
Smart thinking, collapsing the
bridge and buying time like that.
There are more of their friends here.
Was that to catch us off guard,
and get to the room?
Probably.
There it is!
The key to the cage!
What is that?!
That doesn't look like a key!
Wax-Wax Ball!!
Release!
What?!
Oh! W-Water! It's water!
It's a miracle!
Hey, it's him!
Three! It's Three!
Mr. 3! What was he doing
in the belly of an alligator?!
I'm alive again!
I thought I was dead there!
That rotten Crocodile!
He may have tried to get rid of me,
but he didn't try hard enough!
The moment I was swallowed,
I squeezed out the last of my
power to create this Wax-Wax Ball.
What's this?
Hand that key over to us!
It's you guys!
What? This key...?
Hold on...
A room, forcefully leaking water...
...an iron cage...
and this key...
I know what's going on, now.
You're Mr. 3, are you?
You startled me!
Are you Mr. 3?
Hand over the key, quietly.
Gleam!
Here comes a long throw!
What?!
I don't know who you are,
but you appear to be on their side!
If you want the key, go find it!
However, whether or not you are able
to find it, I won't be responsible!
You bastard...
What if this person is able
to pick out the alligator
that swallowed the key?
Hmph, it wouldn't do any good.
Even if they were lucky enough to get that key,
the real key is right here.
Let them struggle as hard as they want.
You are bad.
It flew away, it flew away!
That bastard...
That was smart, for coming out of nowhere.
There's no time, Sanji-kun!
That was a good-for-nothing thing to pull...
Just a minute, Sanji!
Couldn't his wax-wax power
make a key to this cage?
Indeed.
Nicely done, candle man.
Let's get moving. There's little time.
Yeah. I'm sure the first route
they took is toward Alubarna.
But there are still so many
bananagators that way!
Aren't there any more?!
That wasn't enough!
Looks like we needn't worry.
And after I had that much
trouble with one of them...!
No, their strength is just abnormal,
so don't worry about it.
Dammit, I can't go all-out,
soaked in water like this!
The walls are crumbling!
Idiot, that's overdoing it.
The passageway is crumbling, too!
Out! We're getting out of here!
Those small fry... They're going to pay!
I'll kill them all, right now,
with my own hands!
What...?
Catch you
later, you
damn gator
Catch you
later, you
damn gator
Hey, you still alive, Luffy?
Usopp-san, wake up!
Good grief, what are you doing?!
Swim, like you're supposed to!
Sheesh, you guys with your abilities
sure bear some hard risks, huh?
Whoa, Smoker!
Hey now, Zoro, what are you
bringing the enemy along for?!
Back off! I didn't want to.
He was this close to dying, after all.
Whatever. Let's just hurry on ahead.
We've lost quite a bit of time.
Vivi-chan, can we still make it?
I don't know.
Nami-san...
Do you still have that perfume
I bought you in Nanohana?
Huh? Yeah. Why?
Put some of it on.
Like this?
It makes me fall in love to the ends of the world!
Come on, get going, seriously.
Roronoa!
Why did you save my life?
Hey, Zoro! Save him!
Huh?! He's our enemy! Leave him be!
If we leave him there,
he's gonna die, you know!
He can't swim!
Yeah, well, I know that,
but he's...
I was just following the captain's orders.
I don't think you necessarily have to thank me.
It was one of his whims. Pay it no mind.
Then, you'd have no gripes with me
carrying out my duties here, right?
See? Didn't I tell you?
That's what you get for saving a marine.
They're here? The Straw Hat pirates?
Yeah!
Captain Smoker is right there, with them!
Let's go back him up!
All right, men! Full speed to Alubarna!
Where is Crocodile?!
Ah, they came around.
Smokey! You want some of this?!
Wah! It's Smoker!
Hey, Luffy, don't do it! Let's get out of here!
Just how serious is he?
This way! Hurry!
Go.
But this is the only time I'm letting you off.
Next time we meet, consider yourselves dead.
There they are!
Don't let them escape!
Come on, let's go. The marines are coming.
Which way is Alubarna?
Over there! Straight to the east!
Hey, Luffy! Hurry! What are you doing?!
Yeah...
They won't get away this time!
You're not unlikable, you know?
Get going, already!
Don't let them get away!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
All right, guys!
Head straight for Alubarna!
itsu demo hanashitakatta
I always wanted to talk about it
hanbun mo ienakatta
I couldn't even say half of it
soba ni iru yo yume wa
I'm by your side,
tsutaeutabi kagayaku yo
I glitter every time we share a dream
sotto kureta egao ga
The smile you gently gave me
totemo ureshikatta yasashikatta
was a very happy and kind one
Glory glory you're my shine
kono namida mo
Because you're here
kimi ga iru kara yuuki ni kawaru
even these tears turn to courage
tsuyoku naritai wakachi aitai
I want to be strong, I want to share with you
kitto tadori tsukeru
I'm sure I'll make it there
It's Crocodile!
Aah! He's come after us!
I can handle him alone!
You guys go on ahead!
That idiot!
Let's keep on moving, to Alubarna!
We're leaving him behind?!
Luffy-san!
We'll be waiting for you in Alubarna!
Yeah!
Next time, on One Piece:
Merciless Mortal Combat!
Luffy vs. Crocodile
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Merciless Mortal Combat!
Luffy vs. Crocodile