Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
You're nothing but the son of a filthy pirate!
Filthy?!
I feel for you.
You must truly hate your great idiot of a father...
...for abandoning his family and village
because of his lust for treasure!
Don't you dare insult my father any more!
Only then will I inherit her enormous fortune!
Hey, you guys! Don't attack that girl!
Expose the Plot!
Pirate Butler Captain Kuro
Our captain's been gone a long time...
Luffy, too.
It was a big shock for him...
He always watches the sea from
the shore when he's feeling down!
– Captain!
Huh? Wasn't Luffy with him?
Where's Luffy?
Wasn't he at the shore with...
Is he still mad about his dad being insulted?
Who knows?
No, that look was different!
Yeah, something must've happened!
Why do you suppose he looked so desperate?!
Hey, how do we get to this shore of yours?
Doesn't this smell like an incident?!
Yeah, something must've happened at the shore!
I think this calls for the Usopp Pirates!
Alright, already!
How do we get there?!
T-Terrible... news...
Terrible news, everyone!
Pirates are going to attack!
Tomorrow morning, pirates are
going to attack this village!
Everyone, run away! Everyone...
What are you all doing?! Everyone!
Alright, Usopp! Enough is enough!
You're gonna pay once and for all!
N-No, it's not like that!
It's the truth this time!
Shut up!
All you ever do is spout huge lies!
If you were as honest as Klahadore-san,
then we'd believe you!
No matter what he does, it won't matter.
Tomorrow morning, Jango.
Attack the village at daybreak!
Damn it!
So he ignored me because
nobody'd believe me anyway?!
Are these to your liking?
They're the ones you custom-ordered
from the eyewear shop...
...in the next town over.
Yes, they're perfect!
I'm sorry for asking you to go all the way there.
It's a present, isn't it?
Yes. Tomorrow is actually
exactly three years since the day...
...Klahadore came to this mansion.
He's always taken good care of me, so...
Klahadore-san will be delighted!
Yes!
Please, hear me out, everyone!
Pirates really are going to
attack tomorrow morning!
If we believed every story you ever told,
we'd have fled the village
hundreds of times by now!
Please, believe me!
We gotta get out of here!
They really are going to kill everyone!
I swear it's the truth this time!
And we're gonna get you this time!
Dammit!
Get him! Don't let him escape!
This is the place!
Our captain always heals his emotional pain here!
It is nice here!
That straw hat guy isn't here...
It's pretty fragile here...
Nami. Don't fall now.
Yeah.
L-Look! There!
What the–?!
There he is!
It's the straw hat guy!
And his butt.
Luffy! How did this happen?!
He fell!
He's a goner!
So that's why our captain...
Quiet!
This guy...
Morning!
Usopp-san!
Thank goodness!
I thought you might never come back...
You gotta run, Kaya!
They're gonna kill you!
Eh? What?
You've been tricked!
That butler is really a pirate!
Hold on. What kind of joke is this?
It's no joke!
I heard it with my own ears!
Klahadore's really a pirate who
weaseled his way into your mansion...
...so he could get your fortune!
He's been pretending to be a
butler for three years straight,
so he could get your fortune!
What are you talking about, Usopp-san?
He said his crew's gonna storm in and kill you at dawn tomorrow!
He's a really bad guy!
You gotta escape, quick!
I admit, he did say too much earlier.
But lying like this...
It's not like you, Usopp-san!
No, it's not a lie...
It's the truth...
It's the truth!
Eh?! They're going to kill Kaya-san?!
Are they really going to attack the village?!
Yeah, that's what they said.
No question about it.
So what were you sleeping down here for?
That's the thing!
I thought I was up on the cliff...
– So how'd I get down here?
– I knew it! Klahadore's a bad guy!
It's no wonder he seemed so creepy!
So that's why our captain ran to
the village with that intense look!
That's great, then!
Now they'll know,
and can run away beforehand!
Talk about stupid bad guys!
Yeah, that's right!
We gotta run away, too!
Yeah! We gotta organize
all our prized possessions...
– ...and hurry!
Oh, no!
What is it?
We need to stock up on food
before the meat shop guy runs away!
That's not the issue at hand here.
Tell me, Usopp-san.
What kind of story do you have today?
Right. Hmm, let's see...
Alright!
This story happened when I was five,
when I fought a giant goldfish
living in the southern sea!
Goldfish? You fought a goldfish?
Yeah! It was so big,
not even a fish tank the size
of this mansion could've held it!
Oh, my!
What first shocked me was...
...the immense size and length of its poop!
It was so big that I landed on it,
thinking it was solid ground!
That sounds fake!
Yeah, it does, doesn't it?
But it's the truth!
So, first off, starting a bonfire to
dry off my clothes was a bad idea.
How come?
Well, you see...
...the goldfish's butt caught
on fire and freaked it out!
Oh, dear!
Though I guess I can't say I blame it.
It was so close to becoming a grilled goldfish!
I... I loved them.
I loved the lies you told...
Yet, why are you saying this?
It's not like that!
I'm not trying to get back at Klahadore...
Why do you say it?
Kaya... I'm...
Is something the matter, Miss?!
You gotta escape, Kaya!
Stop, Usopp-san!
Let go of her!
Just trust me!
You gotta get out of this village,
before that butler gets back!
Stop!
Come on!
This'll all make sense come tomorrow!
But you gotta escape for now!
Please, listen to me!
You're pathetic.
Get away from her!
No!
Please, catch him!
He roughed up the lady of the house!
– How horrible!
– How could he?!
Why...
...won't anyone believe me?
There he is! Get him!
Usopp-san...
Please pull yourself together, Miss!
Thank you for coming, men.
It's truly been three long years.
Once this plan succeeds,
I intend to give you all plenty of the take.
At dawn tomorrow,
destroy the village to your hearts' content!
Who are you?!
I'm Usopp!
A brave warrior of the sea!
I hear you've been unhappy lately!
I'll cheer you up with a story!
Mind your own business!
Please leave! I'll call for someone!
Now, now, don't sweat it!
I'm always meddlesome!
When I was three, my meddling
even led me to save a sick whale!
Eh? A whale?
You bet!
It was huge, and had a really sore throat,
so I went inside its mouth,
but it thought I was food!
Tomorrow morning, Jango.
Attack the village at daybreak!
– Captain!
Oh, hey, guys!
Yo!
You're alive?!
Alive? Yeah, I just woke up!
This guy was asleep the whole time!
Anyways, Captain!
We heard everything!
Let's hurry and tell everyone about the pirates!
Tell everyone?
You're pathetic.
Shut up!
All you ever do is spout huge lies!
If you were as honest as Klahadore-san,
then we'd believe you!
I'm lying like usual, obviously!
That damn butler pissed me off,
so I decided to claim he's a pirate!
Oh!
So you put the straw hat guy up to it, too!
Hey? What's wrong?
I think less of you now.
Me too.
Me too!
Even if that butler is a jerk,
I never thought you'd lie to hurt someone!
We really respected you, too!
I was all wrong about him!
Same here!
Let's go home!
Yeah! It's suppertime!
Wonder what we're having...
Oww!
There, all done!
Why did you tell them that?
Because I'm a liar.
They were never going to
believe me from the start.
I was too optimistic.
Even so, the truth is the truth.
Pirates really are going to come, aren't they?
Yeah. They're definitely gonna show up.
But everyone thinks it's a lie.
They think tomorrow'll be just
another normal, peaceful day...
That's why I'm going to stop the
pirates at the beach tomorrow,
and make sure this stays a lie!
That's the only logical thing
for a liar like me to do!
Even if I get shot in the arm,
even if I'm driven off with brooms,
this is my village!
I love this village!
I want to protect everyone!
You're one hell of a nice guy,
pushing your henchmen away
and going into battle alone!
Just so you know, I have dibs on all the pirates' treasure!
Alright! We'll help you out!
You guys... are going to fight with me?!
Why?
There's a whole bunch of bad guys, right?
"Scared" is written all over your face.
M-Me, scared?!
I'm perfectly okay with
lots of bad guys or whatever!
Because I'm Captain Usopp,
brave warrior of the sea!
Dammit! Dammit! This isn't a show!
These are Klahadore's pirates we're dealing with!
Of course I'm scared!
What's wrong with that?!
I don't want your sympathy!
You guys can leave! Leave!
We ain't laughing!
We're helping 'cause we think you're honorable!
As if we'd risk our lives because of sympathy!
Oh... You guys...
Huh?
Why'd Usopp cover this slope in oil?
It's his Oil Strategy.
What a weird strategy.
But where are the pirates?
What?! They're at the north shore?!
I'll go on ahead!
They're gonna take my treasure!
North, north! Which way is north?!
Damn you, Nami!
Next time, on One Piece:
Clash with the Black Cat Pirates!
Great Battle on the Slope!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Clash with the
Black Cat Pirates!
Great Battle on the Slope!