Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy was depressed after losing his
brother Ace in the war against the Navy.
The Pirate King?!
I'm too weak!!
But at this time, he realized
the importance of friendship.
And he went back to Marineford
at Dark King Rayleigh's suggestion.
The rest of the Straw Hats got a message
through the news about
Luffy's mysterious behavior
and each starting taking
initiatives on their own.
Luffy wants to become
the Pirate King.
I have to improve myself as a navigator!
Hey, Luffy. The Thousand Sunny
still has some life in her.
You're the only captain who can
make it "the ship of dreams."
Luffy, if I can see you again...
I'll give you the greatest
support in the world as a cook
so you can become the Pirate King!
I Will Get Much, Much Stronger!
Zoro's Pledge to His Captain
Grand Line
Sword Mountain Island, Tehna Gehna Kingdom
On the Sword Mountain Island -
Tehna Gehna Kingdom in the Grand Line...
Come one! Come all!
So many people are here!
What is there to see?!
I heard that they found a weird creature.
Now, come and see it! A
mysterious creature show!
No chest! No flesh!
No eyeballs!
It looks almost like a real skeleton!
And it only has one joint in its arms!
I wonder if there is a
creature rarer than this!
Hey, stop lying, you!
Huh? What's wrong with this?
It's not moving at all!
It's just a doll, isn't it?
Luffy-san has made up his mind.
Well, then I have to do something, too.
Hey, skeleton, don't mess with us!
I have to do something!
Oh, now you realize it,
huh? That's right. Move!
We have to show them something!
What can I do to help...
He just told you! It's enough
if you just move! Just move!
What's going on?!
When he saw me for the first time,
he didn't get scared at all and...
...asked me if I wanted to join them.
Putting that aside, you,
join my crew!
Yeah, okay.
For 50 years,
I was just drifting about on the dark water.
Words can't express how
happy I was to hear that.
This man stole my shadow.
Don't act like such a stranger!
If you need your shadow,
I'll take it back for you!
I'm so happy to be alive!
I bet you are!
--Can I join your crew?
--Yes, you can.
What?! So easily...
...He joined!
What?!
I can't explain how bright
you looked to me...
Because 50 years of waiting for a
miracle paid off at that moment.
--We want our money back!
--That's right!
Jeez! I thought he could be
profitable. We have no choice.
We should just force him to...
--What happened?
--Huh?
I-It's moving...
40 degrees!
What?!
Oh, it's so hard!
It's really talking and moving!
--So creepy!
--What is that thing?!
If I try to go further than 45
degrees, I slip, just as I thought!
But when I overcome that...
Maybe I can help Luffy-san more.
No, maybe I have to look for another way...
--He holds a guitar!
--What is he gonna do?!
What is it this time?!
You don't have to do anything!
It's enough that you're a freak!
Alright, a freak! Call me whatever you like!
"Loneliness" is no longer
a part of my vocabulary!
But, everybody, isn't it boring to just look?
--What's this rhythm?
--It makes my heart skip a beat!
Check out my latest single -
Bone to be Wild!
Meanwhile, near the giant bridge in the East Blue...
Giant bridge in the East Blue
What made you change your mind?
Now you agree to go to Baltigo with us.
Well, we're really glad anyway.
Dragon-san has always longed to meet you.
I didn't know there are people like you.
I wish that you guys had
come to see me earlier.
I-I'm sorry!
We didn't know that you
were allied with Crocodile.
Just kidding. I'm just teasing you.
No offense but I'm glad that
things turned out this way.
Let's go! Let's head for Baltigo!
Go and meet your friends
who must be waiting for you
somewhere out there, Robin!
--A bounty of 79 million berries?!
--For an 8 year old girl?!
She's a survivor of the demons of Ohara,
who attempted to destroy the world.
That Ohara?!
I don't know how she did it,
but they said she sank 6 Navy ships.
That's why the price is so high...
She shouldn't be alive!
She's the child of a demon!
Alright, wait there!
Why did you come to help?!
When did I ask you to do that?!
I want to die already!
I understand Robin's enemy very well.
Shoot that flag.
No way!
Are you guys insane?!
You think you can live when the
whole world is your enemy?!
I'm looking forward to it!!
Robin!
I need to hear you saying it!
Say that you wanna live!!
If you allow me to say what I
want, even a little bit, I...
...wanna live!!
Take me out to sea with you!!
Robin-san, come inside. It's cold out here.
I'll stay here. I'm a pirate and
you people are revolutionaries.
I can't trust you so easily.
I can't just go into a
cabin that has no exits.
Please! We don't bear any
hostility toward you!
Let me stay here. This is how I
got through when I was on my own.
I'm sorry. I understand.
Hey, bring as many blankets as you can!
And something hot to drink and eat, too!
But it's all prepared inside...
--Hurry up! And a wind guard and a sofa, too!
--Yes, sir!
Luffy, do you think I can get stronger
by swimming with the flow of the times...
...under your father?
I never thought that I'd
want to get stronger...
...for somebody else.
Meanwhile, on Bowin Islands in the Grand Line...
Grand Line
Bowin Islands
What is it this time'n, Usopp'n?
First, I'll lose weight!
Then, improve my strength!
Oh, you better do that!
And get stronger!
Yeah, that's the only way
to get off of the island'n!
And get much stronger!
Yeah, that's good, too'n!
And get much, much stronger!
Oh? Th-That much'n?!
Much, much, much, much, much, much stronger!
Wow, you've become so serious'n!
You suddenly got with it...
What was it in that newspaper'n?
I received a message from our captain.
A message?
What're you talkin' about? Get on already.
Eh?!
We're friends now, aren't we?
Luffy!
U-Usopp...? You... You came here, too?
Beat him! And we'll all
go back together, Luffy!
Of course!!
I thought...
...that Luffy could become the King
of the Pirates without my help.
We made it here finally!
We'll see this wall again when
we go half way around the world!
And by that time, I'll be
the Pirate King!
But I was wrong.
There are a lot of
enemies who are beyond his power.
Luffy could lose.
He's pushing himself and crying out for help!
That's why...
...he needs my support!
Heracles'n, I wanna get stronger!
I wanna get much, much, much stronger and...
Hey, Master Heracles'n...
What? M-Master'n?
I've been curious about your weapons.
You're strong enough to live
on such a dangerous island.
I wanna learn a lot from you!
Strong? Am I a strong master'n?
Yes, you are a strong master!
And... my name is...
...Heracles'n!
What a cool name!
A-Alright, why don't you sit down, Usopp'n?
Yes, master!
Listen, my pupil Usopp'n!
There are many plants in this forest
called Pop Green, which
grow hostile instantly.
And these are the seeds'n.
Pop Green?
Each of them has an effective usage'n.
Usage'n, huh?
Wait for me, Luffy!
Run, Usopp'n! This forest
will make you stronger!
To make you the Pirate King,
I'll
become the real Sniper King!
Meanwhile, on Gloom Island in the Grand Line...
Grand Line
Gloom Island, the Ruins of Muggy Kingdom
the ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
Please!
Train me as a swordsman!
I'm disappointed in you, Roronoa!
Are you asking your enemy for instruction?
Shame on you.
Get out of here. I have
no time for a boring man.
I think I was overestimating you.
What are you doing? That's just embarrassing.
I wanna get stronger!
You were beaten by the baboons
and you couldn't get to
sea, so you came back here.
I have nothing to teach someone like that.
I beat the baboons.
He beat them?
You're the only one left to beat here!
But I'm not so stupid as to think
that I'm good enough to beat you!
I don't understand.
You still see me as an enemy.
Then why are you bowing to me
and asking for my guidance?
What's the purpose?
I wanna beat you!
You're asking me to train a
swordsman who wants to kill me?
You're weird. And what
you're asking is nonsense.
Even so, what you're doing
is still embarrassing.
Seems like you found something
more important than your ambition.
Hey, ghost girl, treat him.
Hey, don't tell me what to do!
The training will begin
when you're recovered.
Dammit! Everybody keeps
demanding so much of me!
Come on, move it now!
What a clumsy fool.
When a man like you swallows his pride,
it's always for someone else.
"3D" is crossed out and "2Y" is written?
Oh yeah! There is a tattoo on his right arm!
We made a promise to meet again
at a certain place 3 days later.
But we couldn't make it.
So "3D" means "3 days"!
But "3D" is crossed out and "2Y"...?
--2 years!
The meeting will be 2 years
later instead of 3 days later.
And everything else was done
just to get all the publicity.
This is a message exclusively
to us. Luffy made a decision.
Even if we rush now, we're not good
enough to get far in the New World.
We have to stop once and get stronger.
And meet again no matter what!
Hey, I told you to rest!
What are you...?!
That doesn't work!
W-Who the hell are you?!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
The man who's gonna be Pirate King!
Until the day I defeat him and
become a master swordsman...
I'll never... be defeated!
Got any problems with that...
...Pirate King?!
Nope!
There isn't enough time
for everything anyway.
So let's do it.
You said you beat the baboons.
They acquired their swordsmanship
by copying humans.
There are ranks among them
and there is a master.
He is the leader that rules all
the baboons on this island.
That sword is...
He mastered it by copying what I do.
He's different from the
baboons that you fought.
Sounds like fun!
I'm gonna get much, much stronger!
See you at Sabaody Archipelago in 2 years!
The Straw Hats have decided to become
stronger and reunite in 2 years.
Luffy arrives on the
uninhabited island Luscaina,
where he begins training in a new power
in order to face new enemies and adventures
awaiting him in the New World!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Luffy's Training Begins
Meet in Two Years, at the Promised Place"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Luffy's Training Begins
Meet in Two Years, at the Promised Place