Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats reach the New World at long last,
the harshest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
After receiving an emergency signal,
they landed on Punk Hazard,
a strange island divided into two parts—
the Burning Lands and the Frozen Lands.
Sink to your death, Devil Fruit users!
Cut the crap. Let us look inside the institute.
I'm the only one here!
If Straw Hat comes, I'll chop his head off for you.
If that's all you have to say, go home!
I made it out!
One, two, three...
Super!
The Straw Hats?! Children?!
I got out of the building! I can go home!
Oh, you're...!
I was wondering who this villainous guy was! Smoker!
And you, cutie!
This is not good! The Navy's here!
We can't escape from here! Let's look for another exit!
Get inside!
What brought the Navy to such a place?!
I don't know! Just run!
Hurry up, kids! Go to the back!
There should be a backdoor!
Everybody, let's catch the Straw Hats!
Room.
Takt!
No way!
In a Real Pinch
Luffy Sinks into the Icy Lake
Punk Hazard, Center Lake
Luffy's Location
Fire!
Aim at the bottom of the boat!
Let's go back!
What're you talking about, Usopp?!
Advance!
You have no idea what's going on, do you?!
They're trying to make us fall into the lake!
You can't get away from me - Brownbeard-sama!
Who are you, again?
Don't tell me you don't know who I am!
I'm a former pirate with an 80-million-60-thousand-berry bounty!
Brownbeard-sama!
Brownbeard-sama! Sama... Sama... Sama... Sama...
We've never heard of you!
How can they be so ignorant?!
Take this! An angry shot!
Damn, those bastards!
We're gonna fall!
Oh no!
--Yes! He did it!
--That's our Boss!
The boat capsized!
How's that?! Struggle as much as you like
but you'll be swallowed by the water!
It's cold!!
My body's gonna turn to ice in a matter of minutes!
Dammit!
I'm losing my strength...
You could've fought back, Duffy!
Bud you didn't shtop recruiting zem!
Oh no! My mouth is freebing...
Zorry. I give up.
I don't need zem to join our crew.
All right! Let's finish them!
Get ready!
Hey, Usopp!
Hold these two!
I'm gonna slice them up!
Please hurry up... O-Or I'm gonna...
It won't take long!
Huh? Hey, what happened, Roro?!
Sharks!
Why are sharks in a lake?!
Fools!
It's technically a sea.
The fight between Red Hound and Blue Pheasant left a crater just like after an explosion.
And then seawater streamed in from a big crack and created a lake.
Of course, so did a lot of sea life.
Zoro!
Sharks! Scary! Sharks! Zoro got bitten by a shark!
Aim carefully! There is nothing they can do now!
We have no place to go!
Blow them to kingdom come!
What?! I've never thought my life would end like this!
This is it!
Fire!
Huh?
What? What happened?!
Brook!
These winds a raging,
colder than a winter storm:
The underworld's breath.
You bastard!
Oh, did I mention I froze your gun barrels?
So they'll explode if you shoot!
Who are you, skull mask?!
My name is not worth mentioning. It's Brook.
You just mentioned it.
I'm a skeleton who came back from the dead and put my second life...
...in the hands of the Straw Hat captain!
People call me Soul King!
When did he freeze our guns?!
That's unforgivable!
"Unforgivable"? Right back at you!
--You bastard!
--How dare you?!
I refuse to let my crew
die before my eyes yet again!
What?
Before my ice!
He's fast! He sure can fight!
I didn't know they had another crewmember!
But it doesn't matter now!
Because they already became shark food.
See for yourself!
The sharks got their butts kicked!
Hey, where did they go?
We're here!
You're just in time, Brook.
I'm glad that you're okay!
I was chased by a strange thing and happened to come all this way.
Nice try, you part-human-part-animals!
But sharks can't stop us!
We're way stronger than that!
But no matter... how strong we are...
we can't stand the cold!
It's freezing! I'm gonna turn to ice!
"I told you guys..."
"We can't just go to the cold side like this..."
But look. We're lucky.
We should be glad that we ran into them.
Boss, they're right on top of us!
Wait! They look familiar!
He looks good!
I'll take the fourth guy from the right.
All right!
I'll take the guy next to him.
I'll take that one.
The girl at the far left.
What are they talking about?
Their clothes look warm!
"All right... please get me one, too!"
Are they looking to rip our coats off?!
They're terrible! Do they wanna rob us?!
I know! That hat!
He is the rookie of that worst generation from two years ago!
What?!
That's right!
He's Fire Fist's brother!
Whaaat?!
A pirate with a 400-million-berry bounty - Straw Hat Luffy!
4... 400 million?!
Mil Fleurs!
Wh-What is that?!
No!!
Give me your clothes!
You'd better not fight back!
Then I won't have to hurt you so bad!
Oh, my friends. You're in better shape than I thought!
Help me!!
Research Institute, Main Entrance
I told you, Smo-san!
This is why I said I didn't want anything to do with him!
What should we do?!
Hurry up! Hi-ya! It's this way, kids!
We gotta find a backdoor!
Wait!
Go back! It was that man who cut me up!
What? Really?!
Then he may have the rest of your body?!
No, I don't think so!
Then, it can wait!
Wait a minute! Maybe I can get a clue!
We have to find a backdoor!
We can't go back to face the Navy again!
I don't see any exit! Where is the backdoor?!
All right! Super count on me!
You got some kind of sensor on you?!
There's no such thing!
Then why did you take the lead?!
That was that samurai...
Let's go! Let's go!
...And the Straw Hats.
I can't let them escape!
Room!
What is this?! It's like a thin film...
Shambles!
What was that? I felt something weird!
No time to think about it now!
Alright, keep running, brats!
Oh? Did I drop my cigarette?
Follow me!
What is this?!
Hey, this is no time for you to fool around, Sanji-kun!
In this week's episode, I'm super!
I'll find a backdoor in a moment!
What?
--Everybody?
--There's something wrong with you!
Huh? What is it?
Come to think of it, my breasts feel lighter...
What happened?!
These are...! I got big breasts!
I-I turned into a human!
When did it happen? I'm a raccoon dog now?!
E-Everybody, calm down!
Let's do a roll call!
--Chopper!
--Here!
--Franky!
--Yeah!
Sanji-kun?
What?
Nami-san?
You're Nami... aren't you?
Uh-huh!
What is going on here?!
Law, you bastard!
What do you want?
Give us back our ship.
All right.
Really?!
But you can't have it as it is now.
--It's falling toward us!
--Run!
Let's retreat for now, Vice Admiral!
His power is too creepy!
We can't fight him!
I won't let anyone leave!
It's been fused to the rocks of the island?!
He made some sort of strange artwork with the ship!
Damn! We can't make it back to the base without the ship!
The Warlords work for the Government!
You're breaking your contract by attacking us!
Trafalgar!
--We'll report this to headquarters!
--They'll strip you of your title!
Don't worry about me.
Scan!
What's this?! Stop!
Huh? Transponder Snails?
Oh? Mine's gone!
No way... So is mine!
Those are ours!
He took all of our Transponder Snails!
I won't let you tell
headquarters or the Government
about anything that
you've seen on this island.
You stupid pirate, don't push your luck!
Smo-yan!
You ate the Op-Op Fruit and you're the modification man, I believe!
Stay out of his sword's reach!
I got cut!
Huh? But I'm alive!
You guys are in my way! Get out of the circle!
The circle?!
While you're in the circle he created,
you're like a patient on an operating table!
This is his operating room.
He has total control over it and can manipulate anything as he pleases!
He's the Surgeon of Death!
Trafalgar!
If you really wanna do this...
Don't do it, Tashigi!
Your Haki is not strong enough!
Captain-chan!
With Tashigi cut down,
the thugs of the Navy's G-5 unit
were about to face annihilation as well.
But then Smoker intervenes.
The duel between Warlord
and Navy Vice Admiral begins.
Their battle, so fierce that it destroys
everything around them,
suddenly takes an unexpected turn.
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Clash!
Law vs. Vice Admiral Smoker"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
A Clash!
Law vs. Vice Admiral Smoker