Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue his brother, Ace, who will be executed!
Inside the bay, the Whitebeards are trying to get to the scaffold
but the Navy stands in their way.
And at the bay head, the Pacifistas began to attack
the allies of the Whitebeards to exterminate them!
Stop perpetrating this farce, Whitebeard!
I know about your deal with the Navy!
You have their assurance that
the Whitebeards and Ace will remain safe!
You have sold out the 43 captains
of the allied pirates to the Navy...
...in exchange for Ace's life!
You know what you have done, right, Squard?
You thrust a sword into your father's body.
You're such a stupid son!
But I love you, son, even if you are a fool.
So, Squard, treat him kindly.
I don't love him any more than any of the others.
You are all family to me!
He has never changed at all, Sengoku.
He shook us up very well.
How ridiculous to say that I sold out my sons!
He gave the pirates a way out.
I should never underestimate that guy.
If you are a pirate, you pick
what you want to believe on your own!
Those of you who'll follow me,
lay down your life for it!
Be ready! He's gonna run wild!
He's the strongest man in the world!
Engage the Barricades!
Certain Doom for the Whitebeard Pirates!!
Whitebeard's on the move!
Follow Pops' lead!
Clear the way for Pops!
Don't let them come closer!
Fire!
Whitebeard!
Activating the encircling wall!
Do it faster!
Yes sir!
What's wrong?!
I-It seems like...
...the ice inside the bay is blocking it!
Figure out how to fix it!
Yes sir!
What's going on here?
I was told that Pops had sold us,
the allied pirates, out
to the Navy in exchange for Ace
and that that was all there was to say.
Then why does Pops...
...save us and keep fighting?!
It doesn't make any sense!
That's not what I've been told!
Damn Squard, he's been fooled by the Navy and stabbed Pops!
That's so preposterous!
How painful it is!
If this is the truth...
I...
I've done a horrible thing!
I'm sorry, Pops!
I'm sorry, Ace!
Squard!
Can you pay them back by crying?!
They played a dirty trick on us!
That old man is amazing!
He can fight even after being stabbed!
Anyway, I gotta focus on saving Ace!
Luffy-kun!
Jinbe!
Look at that!
They all went up to the plaza
while we weren't paying attention!
Hmmm! I have a bad feeling about this!
But the old man is in the middle of the action now!
There is no time to think!
Yeah! Nothing will stop us!
Is it not ready yet?!
I'm sorry!
The ice is thicker than we thought!
Fire!
You alright?!
It's nothing! Keep moving!
Advance!
The wall isn't activated yet! This is not good!
I'm gonna buy us some time!
Vice Admiral!
I'm not gonna let you
get to the plaza, Whitebeard Pirates!
I-It's Vice Admiral John Giant!
You're standing in my way. Move it.
I lost my balance!
Vice Admiral!
The ground is tilting!
Don't get close to Pops!
It's worse than an earthquake!
Whitebeard!
Ow, ow, ow...
The sea is...
I can't believe this!
Not just the island but the sea is...
...also tilting!
How outrageous that old bastard is!
Luffy-kun!
Jinbe!
I'm going to pull you up!
Thank you! I appreciate it!
Don't mention it!
Doesn't that old man
care about his own teammates?
His crew knew what to do, they evacuated.
Are you alright?
Ouch... Was that the end of the world?
I can't believe it!
So this is what the strongest pirate is capable of!
What deadly power!
But in the name of absolute justice of the Navy,
I can't let you pass through here!
It's coming!
It will reach the scaffold!
Keep going and destroy it!
Hey! Is the scaffold alright?!
Did it reach it?
It didn't hit the scaffold!
What made it veer off?!
Look at that!
3 admirals!
This happened because the walls are not ready!
Your damn ice is blocking it!
Why couldn't you just melt it, Sakazuki?
Damn!
I can't believe that they've repelled Pops' shock wave!
Don't be scared, guys!
Commander Jozu!
Let's charge them while they're off balance!
We cannot miss this chance provided by Pops!
Let's go, Whitebeard Pirates!
Advance!
Seems like they're all very angry.
How scary!
What's going on with the barricades?
I-I'm afraid...
Divert all power from the city!
Pass it on to the walls!
Yes, sir! Right away!
Ace!
Luffy!
I'm on my way!
Ace!
Full power!
Wh-What is that?!
Th-The walls!
We're enclosed!
What the hell is this?!
Take this!
Did it break?!
No, not even a scratch!
This steel wall must be very thick!
These steel defense walls are what
they meant with barricades?!
Damn! Aren't you gonna fight us, Navy?!
Hey, look at those! They're all aiming towards us!
We gotta run!
We're enclosed! There's no place to...
There is a place!
Hey, what's wrong?! It should be fully activated!
I-I'm afraid that the wall
can't lift the giant body of Oars!
It seems like his blood
is running down in the system
and making it less powerful!
Damn the Giant!
Oars! Y-You're...
What a guy!
He is still fighting, you know.
We have a chance to win!
We can't close it but...
...do it, Red Hound!
Meteor Volcano!
He's firing lava fists into the air!
Wh-What's going on there?!
They vanished into the sky.
What's this noise?
What are they?!
They can't get away!
Melt the ice that they're standing on!
The Whitebeard Pirates are trapped in the bay.
As the Navy's concentrated fire continues,
they try to reach the plaza via the path Oars opened,
but the order to execute Ace has finally been given.
What will Luffy do now?!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Execution Order Issued
Break Through the Barricades!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Execution Order Issued
Break Through the Barricades!