This is insanity!
I know of only one man...
who could pull off a stunt like this.
A survivor from the era of
the Pirate King, Gol D. Roger!
I wonder where he’s been hiding
the last twenty years.
The man who was once defeated by Roger,
was later imprisoned,
then cut off his own legs
to slip free of his shackles,
and escaped...
Gold Lion Shiki!
This is a warning to you all.
Fire! Fire!
I wish he’d give up and
pass into legend already...
Has he come back to get revenge
on the world?
I gotta hurry and find the others!
Gum-Gum...
Balloon!
A mantis?!
They just keep on coming...
Seriously, what’s up with this island?
Wanna fight, bastard?!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
I almost forgot...
These animals are seriously tough!
Gear 3:
Bone Balloon!
Gum-Gum...
Gigant Pistol!
That was close!
I hate how I shrink
every time I use that move.
This octopus looks delicious!
What’s that noise?
Who cares?
We got more important stuff to worry ‘bout.
Nooo!
What’s wrong?
Ants?!
Huh?
So they’re after us, huh?!
Franky, aren’t you out of fuel?
Oh, that’s right!
It’s coming back.
Oh, we’re the same!
Are you all right?
Now I see why they ignored you.
There’s no meat on your bones.
Isn’t that just a bit inconsiderate?!
Three-Verse Humming:
Nock Slash!
Indeed, there may be
naught but bones left on me...
But only because as of late,
I have been quite eager...
to lose a few pounds.
But what is the deal with this island?
The creatures have all evolved
in ways I’ve never seen before.
Neither our common sense
nor our power can affect them.
It’s a world where strength is everything.
Survival of the fittest, huh?
Swordsman
Bounty: 120 000 000 berries
Doctor
Bounty: 50 berries
Archaeologist
Bounty: 80 000 000 berries
Shipwright
Bounty: 44 000 000 berries
Musician
Bounty: 33 000 000 berries
Cook
Bounty: 77 000 000 berries
Sniper
Bounty: 30 000 000 berries
Captain
Bounty: 300 000 000 berries
Navigator
Bounty: 16 000 000 berries
Have you decided yet, Baby-chan?
Just let me out of here already.
You’re a strong-willed girl.
I like women like that.
Can you please fix those
obnoxious footsteps of yours?!
Doctor Indigo?!
What’re you trying to say?!
I just remembered
I wanted to show you som—
You can talk?!
Mom?!
That’s obviously a gorilla!
Yeah!
Don’t look at me.
You’re as cold as ice,
Baby-chan!
Why did we...?
One week earlier
What did you say about East Blue?
“An attacking menace...
The mystery of the suddenly-disappearing villages...”
Villages in East Blue are
crumbling overnight.
So far, it looks like
our home islands are safe,
but who knows how long that’ll last?
Luffy, Zoro, Nami and Usopp
are all from East Blue.
Oh, is that so?
Oh, wait...
Weren’t you, too, Sanji?
Well... I was born in North Blue,
but I grew up in the East.
What’s that?
A meteorite?
What is that?!
An island!
Is it flying?! How?!
It’s got a sail!
Is that a ship?
It’s got a skull on its flag!
A pirate ship?
A flying island ship?!
This wind...
We should change course, Luffy!
A cyclone is coming soon!
What? Really?
Then I’ll tell those guys, too!
Hey! There’s a cyclone
coming from over there!
Hey, should he be doing that?
It looks like he’s shouting something...
Pirates?
It seems so.
Heeey!
W-What happened, Luffy?
Nami!
Hey, that’s a Tone Dial!
Does that mean
they’ve been to Sky Island?
Guess we shouldn’t take them lightly.
It doesn’t matter who they are.
Nami!
Sure!
Oh, they know how to use it?
A cyclone is coming!
Steer to nine o’clock from your current heading!
Navigation Team?
No, no, we’ve seen
no sign of a cyclone.
And the mercury meter
shows normal levels.
They’ve changed their heading
to nine o’clock.
They’re moving fast!
A Perm?!
That’s obviously a rain cloud!
You gotta be kidding!
Shiki-sama!
We’ve got to turn to nine o’clock right now!
It’s an enormous cyclone!
Shiki-sama!
Please open the gates,
Never give an incorrect forecast again.
Y-Yes, Sir!
But still...
How can that woman’s meteorological instincts
surpass that of my expert team?
H-How’d he fly down here?
I... I don’t know...
I’m Gold Lion Shiki! A pirate!
And whose voice was that
on the Tone Dial?
That was me...
Oh, quite the Baby-chan,
aren’t you?
I thank you.
Don’t mention it.
Say, Pops...
How can that thing float?
Oh, that?
That’s the power of my Float-Float Fruit.
I can make anything I touch weightless
and control it freely.
There we go...
See for yourselves!
What?
Awesome! Pops!
Make me float too!
Me too! Me too!
I’m afraid I can’t levitate any living beings
other than myself.
Huh? Lame!
By the way,
I’d like to host you at my base.
As a sign of my gratitude.
You’ll come along, won’t you?
Nah, we’re good.
We’ve gotta get to East Blue.
Luffy?
Hey!
What about our adventure?!
We can just start over!
The guys back home might be in trouble.
Don’t you wanna help?
Uh... Well...
That settles it, then.
Are you serious?
I-I see...
Y-Yeah, guess you’re right.
That’s best.
There you go.
Thanks, but no thanks.
I’m really starting to like you guys!
I see. So you’re from East Blue, huh?
Of course you’d worry, then.
Very well!
I’ll take you there with my power!
Really? Thanks!
Pops, you’re such a nice guy!
Of course I am.
Can he really do that?
Right! Prepare for battle, guys!
Aye!
Wait till we get there!
We’re so high up!
This feels great!
Do you even know what
“Prepare for battle” means?
Why, indeed...
You ought to show a little more concern.
That coming from
the laxest guy on board?!
I see something!
This is amazing!
Are all these islands floating
because of your power?
Yeah, that’s right.
Once I make something fly,
it remains airborne.
That island’s huge!
Here we are...
Well, then...
This is Merveille!
A perfect island for you adventurers!
Explore to your hearts’ content!
Hey!
And there we go!
Your navigator is mine!
Nami!
Luffy! Everyone!
Shiki-sama!
A new strand has evolved!
Please, have a look!
A guitar?
It’s obviously a bird!
Yeah!
You piece of shit!
Hey, wait!
Was that your new evolution?
Yes... It’s a type that
specializes in electric attacks...
What do you mean, “evolution”?
Hmm? Oh, yeah.
Since I intend for you to join me,
I suppose I can tell you.
These islands have long housed animals that had
evolved in ways nobody had ever seen before.
This was caused by
a plant by the name of IQ.
It stimulates the animals’ brains
and triggers adaptation to their environment!
Once I realized this,
I harvested every IQ on the island!
We’ve lived on this island
for twenty years, and, at last,
we’ve managed to
distill a drug from the IQ!
We call it SIQ!
If we inject this into the animals,
they evolve in ways that enhance their fighting strength!
Repeated injections make them
more aggressive still!
Because of that,
this island is filled with ferocious beasts!
That’s horrible...
Why would you...?
You’ll see soon enough.
That is, if you join me, of course.
Like I said, I will never—
...say no!
Before long,
you will surely plead me to take you in.
I’ll tell you everything
once you’ve made up your mind.
Being in my crew entitles you
to certain favors, you know...
Huh? You want me to
give the woman to you?
That is entirely out of line, you creepy gorilla!
What a shock! For a minute,
I thought you were my grandma!
Just how ape-like is your family?!
Yeah!
So it’s those animals’ fault that
the others haven’t come yet...
Nami-swan!
Again: Stop shouting!
It’s a bug!
Robin-chwan!
Seriously! Quiet!
It’s a bird!
Nami-swan!
Seriously,
you’re just wasting your energy!
Robin—
Oh, shut up already!
I’m falling! I’m gonna die!
That was close...
Look up!
Up! Above you!
Sanji-kun!
Concasser!
Damn cat.
Yes, perfect!
Exactly as I told you to do!
What now?
What the hell?!
I wish they’d
give us a break already!
Good, we made it!
Chopper,
lend her your fur coat.
I guess I should. She looks cold...
You think I can take off my fur?!
So you’re awake?
H-Huh?
What were you doing out here?
Huh? Well...
You see...
Never mind that.
We’d better get outta here, fast.
I’m sick of the snow.
We’ve been stuck here for days.
You should be able to get out of
the Winter Zone in half a day.
It’s that way!
Look!
This whole time,
I’ve just been following Zoro’s directions...
I... I just happened to mess up!
If you cross that river,
you’ll reach my village.
Thank you for saving me.
My name is Xiao!
I’m Zoro.
I’m Tony Tony Chopper.
T-The gorilla spoke!
She fainted!
So people live on this island, too?
You’ve noticed it too, Usopp?
Huh? Yeah...
This village...
has no young women.
That?!
You awake?
I was so surprised
when you two fell out of the sky.
You’re lucky to be alive.
Thanks!
Thank you, Madame.
Oh, you don’t have to call me that...
What’re those feathers on your arms?
These? We don’t know why,
but all the people around here have them.
Really...
Does this village have
a food shortage?
Everyone’s so thin...
Yeah...
The men and girls all get their food
at the royal palace, after all...
Those who can’t work
end up living out here.
What? That’s just awful!
If we try to resist Shiki,
we’re done for, after all.
Shiki?!
That’s right.
We’re all his subjects.
And...
Hide, you two!
What’re you doing?!
Huge! What is that?
It’s a mobile surveillance snail.
Everything that surveillance snail sees
is transmitted directly to the palace.
We’re always being watched.
If we try anything to oppose Shiki,
we’re immediately killed as an example for the villagers!
Where’d that come from?!
It’s the smell...
It smells so bad here, my nose is burning.
You can’t smell it?
It’s the Daft Greens.
Our village is surrounded by trees called Daft Greens,
which protect us from the animals.
All the animals hate this smell.
Yeah, I’m sure they do...
So plug your nose.
Let’s go.
Is this it?
Yeah.
Even with my nose plugged,
I can still smell it.
Yeah. It does smell kind of bad.
Now you notice?!
You shouldn’t sniff it too much.
It’s poisonous.
Now you tell me?!
I keep telling you not to
wander past the Daft Greens!
But...
I wanted to save Grandma...
Xiao...
You don’t need to
endanger yourself for my sake...
But... If I don’t do anything...
You’ll...
Thank you so much, you two!
I’d like to pay you back...
We just happened to see her.
That’s right.
And she helped us, too.
Anyway, what sickness is that?
It’s called Daft...
It’s a sickness where paralyzing, green bruises
appear on your body.
You catch it from inhaling
too much Daft Green pollen.
The only cure for it is made from IQ...
but we’d need more than one...
So that’s why she
went out there on her own.
I’m sorry...
It’s not your fault!
It’s Shiki’s fault
for hogging all the IQ to himself!
Shiki?
Did you say Shiki?!
Until twenty years ago, there was balance
between humans, plants, and animals.
But he ruined all that!
I wish they’d just leave already...
and go to that “Sea of the Scheme”.
Can’t you do anything to cure her?
I’ve never seen this sickness before.
I might just end up making it worse.
Still, it looks like we’re safe from those animals
as long as we’re here, at least.
Yeah...
It still stinks of Daft Green here...
but when I think about that,
I guess I can handle it.
I wonder if the others
are all right out there...
Yeah, me too.
Let’s take a quick break,
and then we can go look for them again.
Yeah...
I’m so exhausted!
Something’s strange here...
My body feels so heavy.
Of course it does!
We hardly slept at all
these past few days...
Oh, it’s just you.
Sanji! Usopp!
It seems like all the captains
have arrived in port.
Good. The plan will commence
as soon as I’ve briefed them.
So tonight is the night?
Tell the men from the island
they can go home.
Are you sure?
I promised them, after all.
But only send one of them.
We’ll grant them some hope
before despair.
The higher a man stands,
the more amusing it is to watch him fall, right?
Boss Shiki!
You can talk?!
It’s an emergency!
The girl has escaped!
What?!
Looks like she figured out the pool in the royal palace
is connected to the sea!
How careless of us.
We can’t let someone
as skilled as her get away!
Have all our troops start searching.
We must find her!
Yes, Sir!
That hurts!
Seriously...
Stop.
Still, you saved me. Thanks.
But where am I?
It’s the Sunny!
Oh! There’s the Sunny!
Luffy?!
Nami!
I’m so glad you’re safe!
Nice job escaping on your own!
Don’t come this way!
Where are the others?
I haven’t seen anyone else.
This place is huge!
I never thought you’d be
the first one I’d find!
Anyway, eat!
This scorpion is delicious!
Ain’t that right, Billy?
No, thank you!
Who’s Billy?
This guy.
‘Cause he goes “Bzzzt!”
biri
Right?
I see. Since you’re a rubber man,
electricity doesn’t hurt you.
So now that we know where the Sunny is,
do we wait for the others?
Or do you want to
search for them?
Search for them!
This crayfish vehicle is amazing!
Damn right it is!
It’s a custom transport I designed!
Call it Zarley Davidson!
Yes!
Zarley Davidson! Zarley Davidson!
I can see something up ahead.
A village?
Looks like it.
I bit my tongue.
Though I do not have one...
Dammit, I told you
not to go backward!
It’s trembling.
It’s useless.
He won’t listen to me at all.
Hmph, I guess we have to walk.
Huh? What’s up?
There’s a village down there!
Those trees were around
Shiki’s royal palace, too!
You can’t handle that smell?
Really?
I assume surrounding a place with those trees
makes a safe zone where the animals won’t attack.
Then maybe the others are there, too!
I’m so glad you’re safe, Nami-san!
I’ve been so worried about you
this past week, I could hardly sleep!
He really didn’t sleep one bit.
Robin-chan is still missing!
You’re so damn noisy!
Anyway,
I’m glad you’re all safe!
Huh? Even more showed up!
Oh, my. Looks like we’ve got
quite a crowd here.
If you’d like,
please come inside and rest.
Nami.
You should go take a nap.
Huh? Sure...
Wake up, Xiao!
Make some room for her to rest!
Yes, Mom...
I’ve found her, Shiki-sama!
Yes, now let’s go
get our navigator back!
They’re not here...
But seriously, there’re so many pirates here...
Is someone planning to go to war or something?
It looks like they all have an Eternal Pose,
so I assume they were invited.
Oh, excuse me...
Would you please let me
see your panties?
Like hell I will!
What’s that on your arms?
Huh? Oh, these?
We think we’re
trying to become birds.
Birds? You really think you can just
become something like that?
Um, your panties...
You’re from the Straw Hat crew, right?
Are you guys gonna exchange a toast of brotherhood with Chief Shiki, too?
Yes, that was the plan.
Why has Chief Shiki
gathered so many pirates together?
“Why,” you ask?
Don’t play dumb with me!
You’ve read the news, right?
This!
That’s...
Mom! Grandma! Big news!
What did you say?
It’s true!
Xiu-chan’s dad came back!
The others will
come back soon, too!
We can see Dad and Sis again!
Is it true?
I’m not dreaming, am I?
So you’re saying...
That’s right! Shiki is leaving!
He’s taking the animals with him
to the “Sea of the Scheme”!
To East Blue!
I see.
So you’re from East Blue, huh?
You’ll see soon enough.
Before long,
you will surely plead me to take you in.
Become my navigator, Baby-chan!
Being in my crew entitles you
to certain favors, you know...
I never thought I would have hope again...
It’s like a dream!
I know. The sooner he goes
to East Blue, the better!
Luffy!
Yeah, that’s right! This was just a warning
for the World Government and the Navy!
In other words, Shiki’s...
I mean, the Chief’s goal is...
To annihilate East Blue,
and turn the whole world on its head!
Once tonight’s meeting is over,
he’s gonna take those beasts to East Blue!
But that’ll cause tons of deaths!
Don’t mind that! It’s all to
make the World Government surrender to us!
Can you believe he invited us?
You can say that again!
Right!
Let’s make another toast!
Cheers!
Hey, you guys! Do you really think
you take part in the meeting dressed like that?
Put on something
more appropriate!
So there’s a dress code?
I understand.
Anyway, listen to this!
I heard we’re going to see
a demonstration tonight!
A demonstration?
Yeah! He’s gonna destroy
the only inhabited village on the island!
It’s really pretty exciting!
An inhabited village on this island,
and it’s gonna be...
Luffy?
Stay back, Nami!
Baby-chan, I found you!
Shiki!
You sure are cold, Baby-chan!
You really hurt me
when you just left without a word!
Shut up, you damn bastard!
You’re the one who tricked us
and took Nami-san from us!
There’s no way I’d let
such a fine woman get away!
If you didn’t want me to take her,
you should have protected her properly!
Though, by now, I’m pretty sure
that woman won’t leave me anyway!
Ain’t that right, Baby-chan?
Damn you!
Hey, Steering Wheel!
Don’t think I’ll let you get away
after hurting my friend!
Really? What’re you gonna do?
I’ll beat the crap out of you!
Luffy!
Go on! Try to hit me!
Gum-Gum Sickle!
Sure-Kill Firebird Star!
72-Pound Phoenix!
Arm Point!
Hoofprint Roseo: Metel!
Poitrine Shot!
You’re a pretty good team.
You actually forced my hand.
But now...
I’ll have to finish the job, won’t I?
Sanji!
I’ll start with you!
Rocket!
Oh, were you saying something?
Not really.
You really believe you can match me?
How annoying.
I’ll take you all on at once.
He’s up to something!
Lion’s Threat: Earth Bind!
Gum-Gum...
Cannon!
Cook!
Armée de l’Air Power Shot!
Sure-Kill Atlas Comet!
Good aim.
But you waste your time!
Three-Sword Style, Bull Demon: Bold Hooves!
You’re not even worth killing.
Zoro!
Damn it!
Gear...
Luffy!
Everyone!
I’ll let them sleep in the dirt for a while.
These guys are so clueless.
It really gets on my nerves.
And here you finally understood what was going on
and were about to come back to me...
Am I wrong?
What happened in East Blue...
It was your doing, right?
Yeah, that’s right.
Please...
Please don’t hurt my friends or East Blue
any more than you already have!
You’ve got it backward.
Didn’t I tell you? That being in my crew
would entitle you to favors?
The greatest threats to me right now
are those cyclones.
I’m sure you understand how important
a skilled navigator is.
A memento for them?
Don’t be a fool.
My sister gave me this bracelet
when I left my hometown.
If I join you,
will you spare East Blue?
Well, of course.
I’m a man who values his companions above all else.
Which means I’d never lay a hand
on a crewmate’s homeland.
Don’t get any stupid ideas, Nami!
Usopp!
You’re still conscious?
Are you gonna surrender yourself to him
to keep your homeland safe?
Luffy would...
never let you do this by yourself!
What do you mean,
he’d “never let her”, you brat?
It seems you don’t
understand your situation!
Wait! I understand!
Please, don’t hurt my friends!
Will you give me your answer, then?
Hmm, Baby-chan?
Usopp, this is the only way.
I’ll protect East Blue.
So just forget about me
and continue on your journey.
Don’t do it, Nami!
I’ll be fine.
Stop it!
I can survive anywhere!
Don’t be a fool!
Who’d accept something so—
Usopp!
Sheesh, what a noisy little brat!
Now, Baby-chan,
let’s hear your answer.
I’ll...
join you.
Oh, will you, now?
Please...
let me join you.
Really?
Then let me welcome you,
my skillful new navigator!
Learning that there are enemies you can’t beat
means you’ve matured.
I’m no kidnapper.
Even we pirates
have a sense of honor.
I’ll let you leave a parting message for
the crew you’ve been through so much with.
That’s a fine farewell.
Cuts off all the loose ends.
Your crew should understand, too.
Well, that is, if they even manage to
drag themselves out of there!
All right...
All hands to your stations!
Commence the operation,
as planned.
Oh, welcome back.
Yeah.
Hey, what’re you doing?
Get in here.
The more I look at you,
the more beautiful you get!
Look.
You made the right choice.
Savor the relief of knowing that your hometown
won’t suffer this fate.
Hurry! Hide underground!
Awesome! The monsters are
devouring that village!
I’d expect no less from Chief Shiki!
He knows how to play dirty!
I’m just having a little fun.
All I did was remove the border of Daft Green.
I’m not interested.
I’m going back to my room.
What?
I thought she’d react
a little more strongly...
Damn. We didn’t make it.
It’s just like the picture
in the newspapers.
This is horrible.
So all of East Blue
is gonna end up like this?
Straw Hat!
If you’re here, say something!
Luffy-san!
Are you here?
Straw Hat!
Luffy-san!
What the hell happened?
Let’s hurry and dig them out.
Yes!
Shiki was behind
what happened in East Blue?!
Yes.
So he’s gonna use those monsters
to wreck our homeland?
Damn bastard.
He played us all for fools.
Nami...
followed Shiki,
in order to save her homeland.
We...
were saved by Nami.
Xiao! So you made it?
We hid underground.
Anyway,
about what you were just saying...
You’re from East Blue?
Is she from there too?
Yeah, that’s right.
What have I done?!
I said that I wished Shiki would just go to East Blue,
right in front of her!
How could I say
something so terrible?!
I was happy too!
Xiao, what’s that?
I just found it over here.
Let me see it for a second.
Sure...
You guys’re amazing, Xiao!
Even though your own village was messed up,
you’re still worried about Nami.
I’ve never met anyone
as nice as you!
You’re not bad people at all.
Shiki is the bad one!
I’m gonna send him flying!
So cheer up, okay?
What’s that? A Tone Dial?
Yeah, it’s the one Shiki had.
Please, just let me leave you in peace
and walk away.
It’s Nami’s voice!
I’ve decided to join Shiki’s crew
to be his navigator.
Shiki is a legendary pirate.
You have no hope of beating him.
Even if you come after me...
you’ll only end up losing your lives.
I leave you with this...
What the hell is this?!
What’s she thinking,
leaving us with this message?!
C-Calm down!
No hope of beating him?!
Don’t just decide that on your own!
He just beat you all at once,
didn’t he?
What was that?! That was...
I wasn’t...
Really...
I said calm down!
Stop it already!
Damn it!
Hey, Usopp. Let us hear it again.
Uh, sure...
Please, just let me leave you in peace
and walk away.
I’ve decided to join Shiki’s crew
to be his navigator.
Shiki is a legendary pirate.
You have no hope of beating him.
Even if you come after me...
you’ll only end up losing your lives.
I leave you with this...
My elite troops continue to gather.
It’s time, World Government.
Has it really been twenty years?
Twenty years since
my legs trembled like this...
Okay. I understand.
I’ll go right away.
He understood me!
I get it.
So you’re planning to get rid of the trees
and lure the animals here to attack us?
Were you planning this all along,
Baby-chan?
After you finally said you’d
agree to my terms, too...
There’s no way you’d
honor my request...
My homeland, ruined...
My friends,
in despair over the terrible news...
I don’t want to see
either of those happen!
You were far too rash.
Did you miscalculate the potency
of the poison these spores release?
A pirate can’t be going on about
“family” and “homeland”!
If you let things like that
hold you back,
you’ll only be throwing
your life away!
If you’re unfortunate enough to
still be alive after the meeting ends...
I’ll allow you to
continue on as my navigator!
I’ve got nothing against
cheeky women.
I’m glad to see
you’re all here, men!
We will now share a drink
to commemorate you becoming my subordinates!
Bear in mind,
I will show no mercy toward traitors!
Now, let us set sail,
to the “Sea of the Scheme”!
To East Blue,
the Sea of the Tragedy!
Yeah!
Let’s go, Franky!
Right. Hold on tight.
Coup De Burst!
Y-You’re kidding, right?!
Who’d be crazy enough to
storm the royal palace with a ship?!
As you know,
East Blue is the weakest of the five seas.
There is no one important enough there
to be missed if they’re killed,
so ravage it to your heart’s content!
This is the birth of
the Gold Lion Pirates!
Yeah!
Shiki-sama!
What do you want now?!
I’m sorry, but there’s
something you must know!
Eight men? Well, shoot them!
We tried...
Huh?
You call that a dramatic entrance?
Watch and learn!
Wha-?! Hey, wait a second!
So it’s you?
This is a surprise!
Is it true you’re gonna attack East Blue?
Well, yeah.
Is Nami safe?
Yep, she’s doing great!
You sure are raising a ruckus,
but the eight of you don’t really plan
to fight all these guys, do you?
First that delusional woman believed
she could save her homeland by sacrificing herself.
And now a suicide squad
comes to join her in death?
You sure are stupid.
Huh?
Nami didn’t come here
to sacrifice herself.
She broke through the front lines,
bringing the fight to you!
Now get ready, Gold Lion Shiki.
Because we’re the main battalion!
Hmph. No more bullets?
There’re still quite a few
of them left.
It was just a little greeting.
That was more than enough.
Usopp! Chopper!
Go look for Nami!
Got it!
Shoot these prancing fools!
Slaughter them all!
Chief Shiki!
Come to the room in the back!
Sure.
Take down their boss!
Lullaby Flanc!
Have you done something...
to my friend?!
Chief!
Don’t get in the way
of my captain!
Didn’t he just tell you
to make way?!
Billy?
Did you do this?
I have a favor to ask...
Please listen...
Please... just... listen!
Rapid Fire Star!
Chopper, can you smell her?
It’s no use. I can’t smell anything
with all this Daft Green in the air.
Dammit...
Found her! Nami’s over there!
Nami!
Will you take this with you?
Have fun!
I’m all right... Don’t worry...
I won’t let my precious homeland...
be destroyed.
Just a little further!
Wait for us, Nami!
We survived, somehow...
W-What about Nami?!
Nami!
Nami, hang in there!
Are you all right?
I’m gonna save you right now!
These bruises are the same as
Xiao’s grandma had!
We’ve got to hurry and treat her!
I-Is that...
Could it be...?
Why now,
when we’re in such a hurry?!
We’ve got to hurry and
get Nami out of here!
Nooooo!
What?
Three-Verse Humming:
Nock Slash!
How is she, Chopper?
It was really close,
but she’s finally started breathing again.
We have to do something soon...
Billy!
The only thing that can
cure this disease is the IQ!
And they said that
Shiki has all of them!
What?!
Where does he keep them?
How’s Nami?!
She’s all right.
Shiki!
You’ve really done it now, girl!
You must really want to die!
I’m sick of you!
No matter how hard you struggle,
I will crush East Blue!
W-We’re surrounded!
Lion’s Threat: Imperial Earth Bind!
Die in the depths of despair!
Damn!
Damn it all!
Luffy!
You’re still gonna fight?!
Nami! I’m gonna send this guy flying,
then we’ll all go back together!
Luffy...
Leave this to me!
Take care of Nami!
A-All right!
Get him, Luffy!
Wherever you run,
you’re still doomed to die!
You’re not gonna
decide our fate!
Jet Pistol!
Billy! Help me out!
I’m not letting you go to East Blue!
You’re getting on my nerves...
I can’t hold back when fighting
men from East Blue!
What is this place?
They’re all IQ.
He’s using the moonlight
to nurture them.
That’s the smell of chemicals!
So this is where they’ve been
researching IQ?
Which one should we give her?
It’s one of them!
You’ve got the scent of chemicals
all over you!
You’re a scientist, aren’t you?
Indeed, and quite a
talented one, at that.
Hand over the Daft medicine!
Why would I, fool?!
Is this what you’re after?
I always carry one with me, just in case.
What? Then it’s easy.
We just have to take
the medicine you’re carrying, right?
Out of my way.
I’ll finish him off myself.
Zoro!
So you followed me
all the way here?
Right, take him down!
We need the medicine he’s got!
You’re gonna finish me off?
You’re just some no-name from East Blue!
Besides, it’s not like the world would care
if we crushed that one, useless sea!
Chemical Juggling!
Burn!
I can’t keep up with him!
Zoro!
Are you all right?!
So how do you like the power
of my Chemical Juggling?
I don’t have time
for your acrobatics!
What?
Mass Juggling!
Take this!
Zoro!
He took it head-on!
Demonic...
Nine-Sword Style,
Asura!
If being born in East Blue
makes me a no-name...
Chemical...
Then what does make you,
who is just about...
Juggling!
Piercing Drill!
...to fall by my blades?
Zoro’s so cool!
What is he, immortal?
Chopper!
It’s the antidote!
I’m going back!
Take care of Nami!
Sure!
Hey, that’s the wrong way!
I would expect no less from you.
Sheesh,
there’s no end to these things!
Over there!
Is that...?
Robin-chan!
What?!
You’re gonna take Robin-chan
as your bride?!
You damn, perverted gorilla!
You can understand
what he’s saying?!
You’ve really done it now,
you damn perverted gorilla!
You’ve put your hands on a lady,
right in front of me!
You’re in my way!
Robin-chan!
You guys don’t even know
who you’re messing with.
What ocean
were you gonna conquer?
Do you have any idea how many ladies
there are in East Blue?!
Diable Jambe!
Venison Shot!
That’s the taste of East Blue love.
Oh, no, Robin-chan!
Are you all right,
Mademoiselle?
Yes... Thank you.
Dammit, how dare you
steal the best part?!
I’m gonna fillet you, you bast—
Though I have no flesh
for you to fillet.
Our first priority is Nami’s safety.
Usopp?
Yeah, that’s right!
I can hear Chopper’s voice, too...
Where am I?
Nami!
What a relief!
You’re finally awake?
Looks like the antidote worked.
You came to save me?
Of course we did!
And it’s not just us, either!
Zoro, Sanji, Franky, Robin,
Brook, and Luffy...
We’re all here!
Thank you!
Hey, hey, this is no time
to be crying!
I know!
We’ve got to defeat Shiki,
or East Blue will be...
This is...
Stop!
Nami, what’s wrong?
A storm is coming.
Huh?
The air pressure is dropping.
I’m sure there’s a large
storm cloud nearby!
We’ve gotta go back
to the royal palace!
What?!
Billy! Are you okay?!
It’s time we settled this!
Slicing Wave!
You’ve met your match, kid!
Navigation Team,
calling Shiki-sama!
What is it?
Move the island to the east!
A storm is coming!
A storm?!
W-Was that all right?
N-Nami, are you sure?
Yes, I’m sure.
But is it really safe
to fly straight into the storm?
Of course it isn’t!
But we have no other choice!
This should do it.
Now, then...
I suppose that’s pretty painful
for a Devil Fruit user.
Your youthful optimism
isn’t gonna save you this time!
East Blue and that girl...
They’ll both die in the depths of despair!
You can watch from hell!
Lion: Scattering Valley!
What’s that?
A Perm?!
What?
The monsters are running away!
It’s a storm!
This island is headed straight into a storm!
What?!
You guys!
We’re escaping to the sea!
The sky’s starting to look
pretty nasty.
Those monsters were victims, too.
This drug turned them into
what they are now!
I can’t forgive that!
I must say... Physical labor
can be back-breaking...
Oh. In my case it would be particularly bad
if my back really broke.
Billy, can you still fly?
I’m gonna kick his ass!
Carry me...
to the heavens!
So persistent!
Shiki!
Nami! Don’t be reckless!
It’s Nami!
Everything ends here!
We’ve prepared the explosives!
Huh... Explosives?!
That’s right!
Your royal palace, your factory, and your island...
They’re all ready to blow!
We’re putting an end
to all your schemes!
You gotta be kidding me!
Nami-san!
You’re just a group of kids!
Don’t think I’m about to let you destroy the plan
I’ve worked twenty years for!
Take this!
Sure-Kill Heavenly Dragon Star!
Go!
Enough of your fireworks!
Billy! Save Nami!
Nami-san!
What about me?!
Billy!
Damn you!
Shiki! You’re fighting me!
Gear 3:
Bone Balloon!
Everyone!
Hurry aboard Lion-chan!
What’s that?!
How are you still alive?!
Get hit by the lightning and fall!
You’re the one who’s gonna fall, Shiki!
I’m not letting you go to East Blue!
You fool!
That’s...
Here it comes!
Take him down!
Luffy!
I am the man who will
conquer the ocean from the sky!
I will never let you touch...
my crew...
or the sea...
for as long as I live!
Gigant Thor...
Axe!
Has a man from East Blue
really foiled my plans again...?
Roger?!
Time to fly!
Hold on tight!
Coup de Burst!
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
Luffy...
Billy?
Billy!
Luffy...
Luffy?!
W-Where is he?!
All right!
Thank goodness he’s safe...
I’m so relieved!
He did it!
Now East Blue is safe again!
But he doesn’t look like
much of a winner right now.
Nope.
You got that right!
That’s...
They’ve been freed
from Shiki’s power.
What about Xiao and the others?!
Hey! Look at that!
Thank goodness...
Nami!
Nami-san!
What’s wrong?
Hey! Nami!
Islands are falling down on us!
Run away!
We have to get out of here!
Hurry!
There he is!
It’s Gold Lion Shiki!
Capture him!
Don’t tell me...
This is their doing?!
Our target is the Straw Hat Pirates!
Prepare to fire!
Yes, Sir!
That’s right.
The Straw Hat crew.
The Straw Hats?
We’re still gathering information.
We’ll make a detailed report in the coming days.
Is that so? I understand.
So, we accomplished nothing...
In any case, I’m glad.
You recovered a lot faster
than I thought you would.
Ah, but you still shouldn’t
push yourself too hard!
I’ll be fine.
I want to breathe some fresh air.
Really?
Then, let’s go!
The others will be happy, too!
Everyone! Nami’s awake!
What?
Nami-swan!
Are you all right now?
Yeah, I’m fine.
I’m so glad you’re better.
Excuse me, Nami-san.
May I see—
Cut it out!
You’re so harsh!
Shut it!
Hey, Nami!
What’s this supposed to mean?!
Hey wait, that’s...!
Don’t go saying ridiculous stuff like, I can’t beat Shiki,
or that we’d all die, or whatever!
Sure, we were all buried
in the ground back then, but...
I was just hungry at the time, so...
That’s what I thought too!
I don’t believe this!
We’ve traveled together for so long,
yet you don’t trust us at all!
I’m disappointed in you!
Luffy...
What’re you talking about?
What do you mean, “What”?
Don’t tell me...
You didn’t hear it?
Nami had no choice
but to say it like that.
Yeah, I thought so too
when I heard the last thing she said.
What “last thing”?
You’re really hopeless.
Of course, to me it sounded
like a message of love.
And it was mainly directed at you,
the densest one...
We can just play it again, right?
Hey, wait!
Oh, yeah.
It doesn’t matter now!
It’s embarrassing!
Be quiet!
It’s all over now,
so just throw that thing away!
Hey, don’t throw a valuable Dial away!
I was gonna use it again!
Hey! Nami!
Don’t throw it away!
Please, just let me leave you in peace
and walk away.
Wait!
I’ve decided to join Shiki’s crew
to be his navigator.
Shiki is a legendary pirate.
You have no hope of beating him.
Even if you come after me...
you’ll only end up losing your lives.
I leave you with this...
Please, come and save me.
kuyanda tte ato no matsuri
Forget your regrets; It’s all in the past
mou kinou ni te o furou
Bid farewell to yesterday
saa tabidachi no toki wa ima
Now it’s time to depart
omotaku shizunda ikari o age
Raise the heavy, sunken anchor
congratulations!
Congratulations!
ima mune ni takanaru fanfare!
A fanfare resonates within my heart!
mou guradeeshon wa
The infinite colors
mugen de nou ni kamifubuki yo mae!
dance in my mind like a rain of confetti!
kakugo naki mono wa sare
If you have no resolve, then leave
atedo nai rurou no tabi
We embark on a journey of blind wandering
nobody knows koukai no matsuro o
Nobody knows how our voyage will go
chotto matte to iwareta tte
Even if you tell me to hold on
docchi ikun da to towareta tte
Even if you ask me where I’m headed
“kotae wa itsumo kaze no naka” ni arun desu ne
“The answers always lie within the wind,” isn’t that what they say?
itsu no ma ni ka otona ni natte
Before we know it, we will become adults
ukkari shite matomo ni natte
We’ll slip up but end up decent in the end
ushinatta takaramono o sagashi ni ikou!
Let’s look for the treasure that we’d lost!
kuyanda tte ato no matsuri
Forget your regrets; It’s all in the past
mou kinou ni te o furou
Bid farewell to yesterday
saa tabidachi no toki wa ima
Now it’s time to depart
kaze o yonde dekai ho o hare!
Read the wind and raise the sails!
chotto matte to iwareta tte
Even if you tell me to hold on
docchi ikun da to towareta tte
Even if you ask me where I’m headed
“kotae wa itsumo kaze no naka” ni arun deshita kke!
“The answers always lie within the wind,” wasn’t that what they all said?
kitto kyou mo anata no hitomi de
Even today, within your eyes
boku mo shiranai atarashii boku wa
I’m sure the brand new me, whom I don’t yet know
guruguru tabi o shiteru
continues to travel ‘round and ‘round in circles
itsuka daremo ga otona ni natte
In time, everyone will become adults
chakkari shita otona ni natte
We’ll grow up to be prim and proper
ushinatta takaramono o sagashi ni ikou!
Let’s look for the treasure that we’d lost!