It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement—there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail—let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag—together, we're one
One
Piece
Team Foxy wins yet again in the
second round of this second fight!
Now you've lost two crewmates.
One game remains, and you can only
take back one crew member at most.
So, even if you do beat me in this next game,
you've already lost one crewmate for good!
The Captains Square Off!
The Final Combat Round!
Now then, Boss!
Choose your bounty, if you please!
You're the second one I choose!
Oh, Choppy! I won't leave you ever again!
Robin!
Don't cry, Doctor.
Hey, things are looking pretty bad!
What are we gonna do, Luffy?!
Don't worry! We'll just do
another Davy Back Fight!
Another one?
Forget it.
Say, shall I tell you why we Foxy Pirates
are known as the mightiest of all?
--Heh. Says they're the mightiest.
--After losing to us twice.
Don't be like that...
We had five three-coin games
with the Fang-Frog Pirates
today before we ran into you.
Many of us are hurt. We're exhausted,
both mentally and physically...
We're ready to call it quits.
So we won't agree to any more fights,
however much you want one!
Knowing when enough is enough--
when it's time to quit--
is why we're the mightiest!
Wh-Why aren't you saying anything?
What a joke.
Acting like you're the
underdogs here... Are you an idiot?!
Is that what you call the "mightiest crew"?
What a bunch of Peanut crap.
How can you be so laid-back?!
We can't choose between Chopper and Robin!
Are we just gonna let 'em keep 'em?!
Don't be stupid! I'm gonna get both back!
And how do you plan to do that?!
What a pain. Maybe I
should just chop 'em all up...
Uhh, this is a game, you know. A game...
Hey, "Boss"! I have an offer...
Huh?
What do you say we bet
five people on the next game?
--Hey, now! You can't just decide--!
--No, let's leave this to her.
Come again?
This game is all about taking
crew members you want, right?
Well, we want those two!
There's no point to this if
we can't get 'em both back.
Huh?!
So, if we win the next game,
you'll give them back to us.
And if you win, all five of us
will join your crew too.
What do you say? It's a pretty
good deal if you ask me...
This girl has some serious guts
to try and bargain with me...
Those two clearly have enormous power...
This one and his strange
implements could be useful...
And most valuable of all is this
guy worth 100 million berries!
All right! Two is way too cheap, though!
I'll bet 500 people!
If you win, I'll give you 500 people,
including those two!
Wha...? Why 500?
Oh, my! Our boss has made
the "Hellish 500-Man Wager!"
Will Straw Hat accept?!
We don't need 500 people!
Are you stupid or something?!
You idiot!
We're so close to making a deal!
Don't back out now!
The Merry can't carry 500 people!
Getting Chopper and Robin-chan
back is all that matters!
Five or 500, it makes no difference!
Oh.
Do you accept?
Yeah! Of course!
Incidentally, should the losing
team not have 500 people,
the remainder will be made up
by the team's descendants.
In other words, your children,
grandchildren, and great-grandchildren
will be forced to swear loyalty to
the Foxy Pirates until the total is met!
Children...?
Daddy!
Yes! What is it?
They've suddenly added a
strange condition to the mix...
We don't have much of a choice.
You just have to win! Understand, Luffy?!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
It's nice that you're raring to go and all,
but I should warn you now
that it's impossible to beat me
in the final combat round.
I suggest you all ready yourselves!
What?! I'd never lose to you in a fight!
How many times must I repeat myself?
A fight and a game are two different things...
Foxy!
At last, it's time for the final combat round!
First order of business:
establishing the battlefield!
The two competitors spin the cannon!
And then...
...wherever it stops will be where--!
Hold on! That was clearly not normal!
The battlefield has been set!
By sheer coincidence, it's on
the deck of our own Sexy Foxy!
Coincidence, my butt! You idiot!
I'll now explain the rules of combat!
Everything within 50 meters
of where the cannonball landed
is part of the battlefield!
In other words, it's a 100-meter-wide circle!
Weapons are allowed, as well as
anything else within the circle!
Only the two competitors
are allowed inside the circle!
Knock your opponent out of
the circle and you win! That's it!
Note that the air and water inside
the circle still counts as in-bounds!
F! O! X! Y!
Foxy!
The Flower Cheerleaders
are currently on the stage
performing cheers for our boss,
while an opening fight is
being held aboard the Foxy!
Additionally, the Association of Stalls
is selling limited-edition
Davy Back Fight merchandise,
so be sure to check them out!
We don't need any of this! Just get started!
--...please!
--Okay! Limited-edition Foxy pins!
"Foxy Pins"
Don't buy their junk!
--Excuse me. Where's the participant...?
--There! Just take him already!
What are you so mad about?
Sheesh! Why isn't anyone taking this seriously?!
It really ticks me off how their boss
is dictating the pace of everything!
I dunno, it's probably just 'cause
they've gained so many crew members...
They clearly have more than enough now!
All that matters is that Luffy wins, Nami-san!
I'll go buy us some drinks! Go on ahead!
Hey, you two! Come on over here!
Here! For you!
--How much is it?
--It's on the house!
Oh, thank you.
Oh, yeah! Even if Luffy loses,
they'll all be part of this team too!
We won't have to go our separate ways!
But if that happens, Captain
won't be our captain anymore.
We'll all be serving under a new boss...
--The Pirate King...
--...will be me!
You guys better work hard for me!
Yeah...
Say, Luffy's going to win, right?
All seven of us are gonna get
to continue our journey, right?!
Let's pray it turns out that way.
What the hell?! Why does popcorn
and a cola cost so much?!
If you don't like it, don't buy it.
--Lower it 80%!
--Get outta my face!
What is all this?!
This is the dressing room.
It's a gloved fight, so choose anything you like.
Awesome!
Wow, this is more like a costume
room than a dressing room...
Look at all this stuff! And I can
use anything I want, Usopp!
Hey, how about this? Does it look good?
No... This is it...
The boundaries are in place!
This ends the opening entertainment!
Thank you for your patience!
Now for today's main event...
Combat! The bell will ring shortly!
Hurry to the spectator stands, everyone!
What's happening?
The sky is turning dark...
Nami-san! Where are you?! Say something!
Watch where you're walkin', crappy cook.
This time we're being treated to
a captain-versus-captain battle!
--Beat 'im up, Boss!
--We're counting on you!
First, in the left figurehead corner...!
A man who takes on all challengers
and boasts a legendary, undefeated
record of 920 wins and 0 losses!
Boss!
Our boss, Silver Fox Foxy!
All right...
Listen up, Luffy. You ain't your old self no more.
That hairstyle arouses a man's true wildness.
Some ask if the champion makes the afro,
or if the afro makes the champion...
Not even modern science can explain it.
Luffy... With an afro on, your punches
will have some serious firepower.
--Where's Straw Hat?!
--Did he wimp out on us?!
Let's do it, Pops.
Oh, yeah!
And in the right corner, hailing from East Blue!
The leader of a miniscule pirate band
with a 100-million-berry bounty...
..."Straw Hat" Monkey D. Luffy!
Wow! The afroed Luffy is all
fired up in the right corner!
Lookin' sharp, Luffy!
Are you kidding me?
Luffy looks so cool!
He certainly does.
Both fighters have stepped onto the battlefield!
Can Straw Hat successfully
knock our boss out of the circle
and protect his crew and pride?!
Or will our boss's legendary undefeated
streak strip him of everything he has?!
This final and fateful combat
round of the Davy Back Fight
is about to begin!
But first, a word from our sponsors.
Hey, Straw Hat! Nice fashion!
Your butt is as good as kicked!
Keep your arms tucked in and
show 'im your golden right punch!
Yeah!
Whoa! His brotherly soul is burning red-hot!
Letting Usopp be his corner man was a mistake.
I wish he'd take this seriously...
Hey! Not too shabby!
What a wild style!
Quite admirable, even if you are my opponent!
I wouldn't act so confident
if I were you, Champion!
He's liable to bite your head off!
Better watch out!
All right, corner man! You're in the way! Scram!
Whoa! My job as corner man is over already?!
Corner man, out!
Get goin' already!
You're absolutely right!
There's no need for me to remain
here either! I'll leave as well!
What? The stands are...!
Oh, cool! I didn't know they did that!
Now then, Straw Hat Luffy.
Let's have some fun!
This entire ship is our battlefield!
Rampage to your heart's desire!
We have plenty of skilled shipwrights, you see!
By sheer luck, this bout is taking
place aboard the Sexy Foxy!
What kind of deadly struggle
is about to unfold?!
The two pirates are now all alone
inside the spacious battlefield!
--Boss!
--Keep your undefeated streak going!
Win, Luffy! You hafta win!
His beam! Watch out for his beam!
Excitement fills the stands!
It's plunder or be plundered!
500 people are on the line in this final
combat round of the Davy Back Fight!
It's one match only, with no time limit!
--Luffy!
--Boss!
Silver Fox Foxy versus Straw Hat Luffy!
It's a head-to-head battle between
these two pirate powerhouses!
The fate of everything hangs in the balance!
Here comes...
...the starting bell!
--Let's do it!
--Yeah!
--Gum-Gum... Pistol!
--Slow-Slow Beam!
Only my fist is slow!
You're not so tough! You're all show!
What?!
Come back!
Slow-Slow...
Oh, no!
Just kidding!
Wha...?!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Luffy!
He's floating! He's slow even when falling?
I told him to watch out for that!
Talk about lame!
Now beat 'im, Boss!
Aww... Crap...
What's the matter, Straw Hat?
Ready to throw in the towel already?!
Say...
...what...?
Nine-Tails Rush!
Oh! Our boss unleashes a
fierce attack right off the bat!
Straw Hat is helpless to do anything!
Huh? He isn't even budging...
No, that's not true!
The effects are slow too, that's all!
That was just a little "hello."
The punches themselves
didn't hurt you too much.
That much is obvious to me, rubber man!
Darn... it...
Well, your thirty seconds are about up!
--It's hitting him all at once!
--Oh, no! He's going overboard!
Luffy!
Crap! The Slow-Slow Beam is
more dangerous than I thought!
Beams sure are nice...
Guess I shouldn't stretch more than I need to...
Where'd that jerk go?!
Damn! I won't get hit by that anymore!
Come out, Split-Head!
Please don't take your anger out on the ears!
A-Another Slow-Slow?!
Welcome to my ship!
Why, you...!
He got me!
Calm down, will you?
I'm trying to show you some hospitality here...
Those cannonballs have been Slow-Slow-ed...
If you can ride one, then I can too!
Oh...! I wouldn't ride that one if I were you...
Oh, or that one.
Told you so!
What is this? What's going on in the fight?!
Hey! Robin!
Can you see anything from up there?
Nothing but smoke!
Darn it...
Man, he's wrecking his own ship...
I'm just getting started!
Slow-Slow Foxy Face Bombs!
Freaky!
Huh? Pin badges? They're
bigger than the one I bought!
Of course we are! We're bombs!
You are?! Yikes!
Huh? A bomb just talked!
I'm... the real deal!
Sorry, Straw Hat...
...but I upgraded my gloves!
And the Face Bombs'
30 seconds are just about up!
Oh, yeah! Luffy! The body! The body!
Oh, Usopp!
Hey, what's happening with the fight?
Dunno. Beats me.
Are you serious?!
Luffy... Oh, no...!
We're setting off toward the distant orange horizon
Today's winds are blowing
across the morning sea
I can't sleep
The kind of passion I saw this very morning
cannot be stifled by anyone
Hope, frustration
and much more might come our way
but for now
we can just start from scratch
Some time ago, we had a dream
in which we followed our aspirations
so we'll raise our hands high
and embrace the shining sun in our hearts
We're going to make it to that place
Get up! Get up, Joe-- err, come on, Luffy!
--Do a No-Guard stance, then a double-cross!
--Who are you pretending to be?!
Now! Remember the eye of the tig--!
Not you too, Robin!
--Pops... I'm gonna be pure white ash...
--Don't burn up! Fight!
I'm having fun! Come on, Straw Hat!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Full-Blast Slow-Slow Onslaught
vs. Invulnerable Luffy"
--I'm gonna be Pirate Ki--
--Nope, I am!
Huh?!
Full-Blast Slow-Slow Onslaught
vs. Invulnerable Luffy