Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
This is your punishment.
There is no way to neutralize the
amount of poison you have absorbed!
What do you think you're doing to...
...Bon-chan?!
Leave Bon-chan...
...alone!
After fighting the Army Wolves,
Luffy and Bon Clay lost consciousness
and a mysterious man named Inazuma
rescued them and took them to...
Welcome to...
Impel Down—Level 5.5!
It's a secret garden for prisoners!
New Kama Land!
Heehaw!
Luffy's Treatment Begins
Iva-san's Miraculous Power!!
You're wonderful!
Heehaw!
Is he...
Heehaaaaaaw!
...Iva-san?!
Vi got a bit too excited...
and now my anemia is...
Iva-sama, are you alright?
is... is...
isn't bothering me at all!
That was a joke?!
You sure fooled me!
You're Iva-san, aren't you?!
Oh, dear?
Am Vi that popular?
Hey! Calling him Iva-san
is so disrespectful!
She's right!
He's the king of the New Kama—Iva-sama!
Iva-sama! Iva-sama!
Iva-sama! Iva-sama...
Hush, now, candies!
Don't sweat the small stuff!
It's just a little thing!
They can call me whatever they want!
Even "Dooky" is fine!
No, don't call me "Dooky!"
Then why did you say it?!
You got me again!
H-He is the miracle worker?!
The one that I worshipped for so long?!
Not "Dooky!"
Emporio Ivankov!
You were the queen of
Kamabakka Queendom, weren't you?!
15 years ago, my father who was
once king of a country himself...
...went to Kamabakka Queendom and...
...came back as a queer!
Aak!
Because the king became a queer,
both his country and family were ruined
and I fell from my princely status
to become a lowly pirate!
I'm glad to have found you!
You'll pay the price for ruining my life!
No! No!
Don't do that! Where did you get that thing?!
Watch it!
Watch it Vi tell you!
Vi'll die! Vi'll die!
If you shoot me with that, Vi'll die...
Vi'll die...
Or not!
You're such a character!
You were pulling my leg?!
Death Wink!
Yes! That's how Iva-sama blinks!
He was able to turn back that
bullet with only a wink?!
Emporio Female Hormone!
What did you do?!
You bastard! Don't tell me it's...
Your father wanted to become a woman!
What's wrong with that?!
Oh no!
I'm gonna lose it!
Two mothers and one daughter!
What's wrong with that?!
It's your family!
No! Please don't...
...do it!
What?!
What happened?
Way to go!
You can become a woman or a man,
heehaw!
Even a fairy!
You can become whoever you want!
Don't you think so?!
The border called gender!
Vi... No, everyone here,
heehaw!
We've all crossed that border!
So we're the new human race!
New Kama!
This is the garden of freedom -
New Kama Land!
Heehaw!
Iva-sama! Iva-sama!
Iva-sama! Iva-sama! Iva-sama!
He transformed a man into a woman!
He is a miracle worker! What great power!
Welcome to our New Kama Land!
Heehaw!
I'm so embarrassed!
Heehaw! She's embarrassed!
She's still got a long way to go
to become a New Kama!
Bon-boy?
The miracle worker, Emporio Ivankov!
It's my honor to meet you!
I'm glad to see you! I'm so glad!
If you don't mind, I have a favor to ask you!
A favor?
Can you save my friend's life?!
He was poisoned by Magellan!
No antidote can help him and he's just dying!
I'll do anything for you if you'll save him!
Are you talking about Straw-boy?
Bon-boy?
Huh?
Do you know why you've been treated already?
Oh yeah! When did you do it?!
We're just prisoners!
We don't just take in and care for anyone who we find injured.
We're just not that nice!
Vi treated you because Straw-boy begged me to.
Straw-chan begged you?!
We've been watching you guys on the monitor.
Straw-boy,
Vi can't believe you made it this far.
Nobody's ever been as lucky as you two!
Bon...
Bon-chan tried to help me
and got bitten by the wolves!
Take care of him!
I beg you! He's my friend!
You wouldn't say something
like that when you're dying.
So some friendships can't
be ruined even in a prison.
When someone begs you like that,
you gotta do it unless you're
a demon in human skin.
Straw-chan!
Straw-boy's treatment
already started ten hours ago!
Really?!
But, in a rough way...
Hey! Those of you born after the 90's!
These are old-fashioned bamboo stilts!
You gotta try these! It's fun!
I mean, I made these with wax,
so we should call them wax stilts!
How much longer can they keep this up?!
Go away now!
It's not good!
We gotta get off of this floor
in order to lose them!
Just keep running!
Tell me somebody! Where's the exit?!
What's going on here?!
Is this the treatment?!
He's been screaming for ten hours
since we put him in this chamber.
It'll be two more days before he is treated.
What?!
Ten years of your life.
Vi'll have to use ten years of
your future for this treatment,
Straw-boy.
Alright!
But there's no guarantee
that it's gonna save your life.
At the moment you have
zero chance of survival
and all Vi can do for you
is raise it to two or three percent.
And then it's up to your will,
if it's possible or impossible to survive.
If the poison takes over, you will die.
But if your will wins out...
you will survive!
Alright now, have a nice trip
to the shadowy valley death!
Emporio...
Healing Hormone!
10... 10 hours?!
Straw-chan has been screaming
like this for 10 hours?!
Your will and hormones,
these are the vital forces of the human body.
They bring out the power to heal oneself!
Vi have drawn out his latent
immunity and modified his body...
to enable him to battle
with the deadly poison.
There is a lot of destruction and recovery raging at an extraordinary speed inside his body.
He will only survive if he can make it through the pain!
W-What?!
You can take a look inside if you want.
Where... Where is it?!
Straw-chan...?
H-He's gonna die!
It's gonna tear up his body and
it's gonna be all messed up and...
No, he's already dead!
How could you?!
Help Straw-chan! Please! Help him!
Untie the chains and stop him bleeding!
T-That's horrible! Please!
Please do something!
Shut up!
Vi'm helping him right now!
We're talking about a life!
Huh?!
Do you know what it means
to save a life that is beyond saving?!
Vi'm no God!
Miracle worker, you said?!
Vi don't care what you call me, but...
Vi won't waste my time saving fools who can't even save themselves!
Even with nations that were about to suffer economic collapse, or be torn apart by wars,
all Vi did was draw out
their will to live.
Miracles only happen
to those who never give up!
Don't underestimate miracles!
Ace!
Time until Ace's execution:
hours!
Luffy fights the poison treatment himself.
The chance of survival is so slim,
it would be a miracle for him to survive.
Trusting his friend,
Bon Clay continues to cheer for his survival.
And then, the time of Ace's
execution is finally at hand.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Believe in Miracles!
Bon Clay's Cries From the Heart"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Believe in Miracles!
Bon Clay's Cries From the Heart