Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After being separated from his friends,
Luffy comes to rescue his brother Ace--
who has been captured by the Navy
by sneaking into Impel Down - the
greatest prison in the world!
After running into Buggy on Level 1,
Luffy went on to Level 2, the Demonic Beast Floor,
where he joined up with Mr. 3
- a former Baroque Works agent,
and together, they all
headed to the lower floors!
It looks like there's a lot of fun
going on in the outside world!
Jinbe, Fire Fist, just so you know,
there are dozens and dozens of silver
medalists in the world who in the end didn't win...
...against Whitebeard and Roger
all holding back their tears.
Chief Guard Saldeath's Trap
Level 3: Starvation Hell
Monitor room! We are at the scene on Level 2.
Can you see the image?
Yeah! Keep us updated!
Roger that!
Impel Down Level 2
Demonic Beast Floor
What happened here?!
This hole is big enough for even
the Sphinx to fall through!
What does Straw Hat Luffy want?
Look! This is bad!
The prisoners on Level 2 are all
free! How did they get the keys?!
Are they responsible for this, too?!
Those guards are in trouble!
Let's hear it for Captain Buggy!
He's our savior!
L-Level 2 reporting! We need backup, pronto!
The prisoners are...
Send Blugori to Level 2!
We've just received word of
Straw Hat Luffy's intent!
You did?! From whom?!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku at
the Headquarters sent word!
The invader - Monkey D. Luffy and...
...the condemned prisoner - Portgas D. Ace,
those two are brothers!
What?!
Then, he came here to rescue Fire Fist Ace
before the public execution?!
Yeah, that's exactly it!
That explains why he keeps going down!
We were focused on Whitebeard's attack!
If he pulls this off, the
tide will turn against us!
Inform Warden Magellan at once!
And get the riot on Level 2 under control!
"Navy"
What's so funny, Garp?!
We're standing at a crossroads that
could change the whole world of the sea,
but he keeps causing problems,
one after another!
At Enies Lobby...
That symbol represents...
...the unity of over 170 member nations
in the four seas and the Grand Line
which is to say - the whole world!
Now, do you realize how big the
organization that is after her is?!
Now I know the enemies Robin has.
Sogeking!
Shoot the flag.
Understood.
My new weapon - The giant
slingshot called "Kabuto"!
Let me show its power!
Sure-Kill! Fire Bird Star!
Agh! No!
And the time with the Celestial Dragons...
You annoy me, too!
All of this has been unprecedented!
And this time,
he's meddling with a prison where
no-one's escaped for 20 years!
Ever since the abhorrent Golden Lion,
a prison which has never been breached,
known for so long as a robust  and
iron-tight great fortress - Impel Down!
He has disgraced its name by being
the first to penetrate its walls!
How could he be your grandson, Garp?!
He sure has accomplished a
lot! I'm proud of my grandson!
Damn Bartholomew Kuma!
He said that he took care of the
Straw Hats at Sabaody Archipelago!
I knew that he was lying!
You weren't going to trust the
word of a Warlord, were you?
Anyway, I wonder how he got through
the Navy's impregnable defenses...
Maybe he just flew in!
Cut the crap! If you weren't
known as the hero of the Navy,
I would have made you take full
responsibility for your family, Garp!
You can take this old man's life but the
situation is far more serious than that!
It's not funny!
This has all been
the Navy's blundering!
Do you realize how much Tsuru and I
worked to deal with the aftermath?!
Hey, that's mine! Give it back!
Shut up!
Ouch!
Ow, ow, ow...
Ow, ow, ow!  This floor is like a frying pan!
Are we in the desert?! It's so hot!
Why is it so quiet?
Level 3! Oh, I never wanted to come here!
Straw Hat! I'm doomed along with you, again!
Oh! Looks like the lion's taking a cat nap!
I was talking!
This is especially difficult
for me and my wax powers.
It's really big!
Where are the stairs?
I don't know.
He can't stand here for much longer.
Alright, let's just go.
How long do we have to walk
until we get somewhere?!
Chatting won't do anything but waste energy.
Wow! Grilled chicken is served!
Don't be ridiculous!
That's a hummingbird that fluttered down
from upstairs and got grilled in the air.
How hot is it in here?!
It's cooked perfectly! Yum-yum!
How can he...?!
I'd prefer the lion from
upstairs be barbecued.
Who wants to eat an animal
that speaks like a human?
How can you have an appetite
at a time like this?
Oh! There are some cells!
So what? It's a prison!
That's why you're an idiot!
We can hide from the sun in there
and it's definitely cooler than outside!
Oh yeah! You're so smart!
Of course I am!
Mr. 3, you better make some keys!
Yeah!
There's no place to hide...
Hey, can we just get in...
Isn't it a miserable sight?
Prisoners on this floor
were once all tough
criminals with more than 50-million-berry bounties.
The heat from the Inferno Hell underneath...
...along with depriving them of food
and water has made them half dead.
This is Level 3 - the Starvation Hell!
Now you know why this floor
is covered with sand.
Don't tell me it's...
Chances are the sand that
you're stepping on now
is the remains of a
prisoner who has dried up.
If we stay here too long,
we will become like them before we know it.
We have to get away from here while
we still have sweat to spare.
Let's go to Level 4 in hurry!
Seriously?!
Hey, not that way! We gotta
take the stairs on the left.
Oh yeah?
--No, we should take the pass on the right.
--Stop confusing me!
The targets are proceeding to the back.
I see. Just keep watching.
Let's do it as we planned.
Haven't you been able to
contact Warden Magellan yet?!
--Not yet!
--What about the Blugori?!
They headed off to catch the
invaders with their commander!
Damn! The security of Impel Down
shouldn't fall to pieces this easily!
Why...
...are we back where we started from?!
Looks like we went in a circle.
Quit being so relaxed!
I told you that we should go right.
I hope we make it to Level 4 soon.
--I told you "I'm not going!"
You have to guide me!
You said that we were
gonna save Ace together!
We never said that!
Stop imagining things as you want them to be!
Didn't you say you would?
They are in!
Alright, draw the net!
Yes, sir!
I'm going on my own then!
Ah?
What's this?!
Oh no! It's a trap! They got us already!
It's made of iron!
I can't use my Chop-Chop Fruit power!
Of course, it contains Sea Prism Stone!
They're gonna torture us for
attempting to break out.
We're goners.
We got the invader - Straw
Hat Luffy and two others!
--What do you mean "two others?!"
--Don't antagonize them, Buggy-kun!
It's over.
Damnit! I gotta rip this net!
There are guards and Blugori here!
--Put the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs on them!
--Roger!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Who're you?
I'm Saldeath.
Cell death? You don't look that old though.
No! You're not listening.
I'm Saldeath.
So, you're a monkey, right?
No! Get it right! It's my name!
Give up.
Chief Guard
Saldeath
[Blugori Commander]
It's no use holding out.
There's no place to get away...
...in this closed underwater prison!
It's lucky you were caught by me.
Because there are four Jailer Beasts
prowling around on the floors beyond this.
What?!
He's right! I don't wanna
face them and the warden!
If only we have gone the right way there...
Oh no. We were watching you
but no matter which way you choose,
you would have ended up here.
Oh, is that how it was?!
Vongole bianco!
Oh, Chief!
Pasta?!
Soup spaghetti!
He's onto pasta now!
We're gonna get squashed!
--Spaghetti!
--The Sphinx is awake!
Oh no, he's gonna break the net!
Don't let those three,
especially Straw Hat get away!
Deep-fried noodle!
Noodles, again!
He must've been going through a phase!
Yeah!
This is great! Now, we can run!
Get them!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Oh? Where'd they go?
Hurry up, Mr. 3!
I can't move quickly due to this heat...
Ah! They climbed up the net!
Straw Hat!
If you see Ace, tell him
that I said "hello" and...
"let's have a drink if I
ever see you again alive!"
Be a good little live bait for us, stupid!
I was happy to see you were
alright but... Alright! See ya!
Thanks for helping me!
Ugh! How sweet!
Ouch! It's heartbreaking!
Stay sharp! He is a pirate with
a 300-million-berry price!
Now is our chance to run!
Alright!
I don't have time to fight you all!
Buckwheat noodle!
Oh no! He's still around!
You bastard!
He's gonna run! Chase him!
Where are the stairs to go down?!
We'll soon arrive at Fire Fist Ace's floor.
Finally. It took a long time.
It couldn't be helped.
That floor is filled with notorious criminals from
all over,
not just Fire Fist.
It is not the place one can enter casually.
We're doing this as a favor for a Warlord.
It's my request.
You have to grant it, right?
Yes, I have to!
By the way, there is a prisoner
who was once a Warlord like you.
You don't have to worry. I
just want to see Fire Fist.
I won't do anything improper.
You better keep it that way.
It's hot...
We'll be safe here! They're
after Straw Hat as we wished.
They closed up the staircase going up.
It's already too much for me to stay here.
Un, deux, faint!
Un, deux, come on!
--Un, deux, faint!
--Who's singing?
Un, deux, come on!
Un, deux, faint!
You know, this world is
about a man and a woman!
But when you're queer,
you're a little of both!
That's why we're the greatest!
The greatest!
The queer way is the greatest!
The queer way!
The queer waaay!
Impel Down beefs up security
after its series of incidents,
sealing the only way in and out.
Luffy and the others are
completely trapped inside.
Unaware of the dilemma he's in,
Luffy continues toward Ace's floor,
and unexpectedly encounters
an old friend along the way...
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Unleashed Swan!
A Reunion With Bon Clay!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Unleashed Swan!
A Reunion With Bon Clay!