Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
After learning about the ruler of the island - Caesar Clown, aka the Master's motive,
and all while trying to escape Netherworld,
along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar,
save the children,
and escape from the island.
Did you just say something?
Who the hell are you?!
Who are you?!
A Small Dragon!
Momonosuke Appears
Momonosuke?
Team Luffy
Basement of Building C, Garbage Dump
That is my name.
I heard that name before somewhere.
Where was it?
How do I know?
It must be somebody else.
More importantly, you...
...stop drooling!
You can't eat me!
If you try to eat me, I'll eat you first!
Behave yourself!
Momonosuke (Dragon)
Oh?
Maybe "Momonosuke" is stuck on a dragon's body
and he's talking with his farts...
Hey, where are you?!
What are you doing?!
Here we go!
He's torn in half! I'm sorry!
Oh, I'm finally separated from it-bu!
I'm not talking with my farts!
How rude!
What are you talking about?!
Come to think of it, that dragon
was bigger
and we already ate it.
Who are you then?
What?!
An eel is talking to me?!
Stop drooling!
I'm not an eel!
You're starving, aren't you?
Don't be ridiculous.
Samurai warriors don't get hungry
after just ten days of fasting.
Ten days?!
Who are you and why are you here?
I'm Luffy.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
P-P-P-P...
P...
You must be joking.
Pirates are big, heavyweight men.
They are more violent and strong-looking.
Anyway, eel, how can I get out of...
It's Momonosuke!
So you're from somewhere else, too, aren't you?
All I know is there are so many sick children here.
I don't even know what kind of island this is and what happened to me.
It all began when I happened to stow away on a ship.
I tried not to be so friendly
but those children were kind to me.
They're giving out food.
Aren't you hungry?
Shut up!
I don't want any!
I am a samurai!
I don't accept alms!
They were very nice to me
but I was on edge so...
I got you some food.
I said I don't want any!
You better eat something.
We're all separated from parents so we must stick together...
Nobody can understand how I feel!
Biscuits Room
I am "Master" Caesar!
Come on in!
This is your playground from today!
There are many giant children!
Are they sick, too?
You can count on me!
I'll treat you all at any cost!
Hi!
We're all friends from today!
Thank you!
Hey, what about you?
What's your name?
I don't have
a name.
Here.
Have some snacks.
I don't want any!
Candy?
A few days later
Hey, is it true that one of the kids escaped?
Yes but everybody on the boarding list was accounted for.
That's strange.
In any case, let's split up and search.
How can I get out of here?
Hey, you!
You were on the same ship with me.
Do you remember me?
Oh, so your name is Momonosuke-kun.
This is a "secret room" where no one is allowed.
You're so annoying.
Don't get involved with me.
Why?
Because...
There is no reason!
I'm just looking for an exit.
I'm gonna get out of here.
There is something I need to do.
I know it's hard but every child here is going through the same thing.
Everybody wants to see his or her father and mother as soon as possible.
All of us came here from different islands to be treated
but everybody feels the same way.
There are so many things I wanna do
if I could just get back home!
Everybody is friendly at the Biscuits Room and it's fun there.
You can forget the pain.
So why don't you eat something, Momonosuke-kun?!
Well, but...
Hm?
What's wrong?
Oh no, somebody's coming!
Let's go, Momonosuke-kun!
The door to the secret room is open!
Come on!
Don't worry about me!
Just go!
Anybody there?!
Wh-What is it?!
Who is it?!
A d-dragon?!
What's going on?
I don't know.
M-Momonosuke-kun...
Look!
If I remember correctly,
there was a man-made Devil Fruit that Vegapunk created here.
I heard it was a failure.
Yeah, I heard so, too.
That pain in my chest I felt suddenly -
I thought my heart was gonna explode!
I had trouble running before.
What happened...
So I am originally a human.
You ate a Devil Fruit, huh?
And it made you an eel man, maybe?
Eels don't have horns.
Then why don't you turn yourself back into a human.
What?!
I-I can turn myself back to myself?!
How?!
I don't know.
I'm not a Zoan-type.
By the way, I wonder how high this ceiling is.
I can't even see the hole that I fell through.
I want to get out of here, too,
and tell those children the truth!
I happened to hear something!
That Caesar guy was talking...
We have another group of good obedient kids.
The other kids are growing bigger without problem.
But, after all, this is an experiment to see the limitations of drug dosing.
I don't think they can take it that long.
I assume they'll all be dead in five years.
So we need to find more kids.
Well, experiments come with failures.
It's a necessary sacrifice.
Those stupid kids can help the world's greatest scientist -
Master Caesar Clown
and do good for the world!
Even if it's a short life, they have to be happy with it!
Don't you think?!
I thought he was a doctor
but he is actually a bad man
who is going to let the children die!
And the kids have no idea.
Here.
Have some snacks.
I know it's hard but every child here is going through the same thing.
Everybody wants to see his or her father and mother as soon as possible.
I feel sorry for them.
If I don't do anything,
I should be ashamed of myself as a samurai warrior!
I was on my way to tell the children but I fell down here
when I tried to hide in a trash can.
Caesar!
Alright, Momo,
I'm gonna climb up there.
I'll take you with me!
What?!
How are you gonna climb that high?!
I'm gonna climb the wall.
Hold onto me!
What?!
Don't worry about the children.
My friends are on their way to help them.
Really?!
They always keep their word!
So don't worry!
Okay!
What I thought was right!
You are not an ordinary...
...pirate.
What's the matter?
What happened?
Are you too hungry?!
Hey, stay with me!
Stay with me! Stay with me!
Stay with me! Stay with me! Hey!
Stay with me!
Stay with me! Stay with me! Stay with me!
Stay with me!!
Wh-What?!
What's going on?
Hey, what's the matter?!
H-Hey!
Hey, wait!
We're...
flying!
Pathway to the Examination Room
Building B, 2nd Floor Interior
I wonder if Nami and the others are doing okay without me!
Well, at least Zoro is with them!
I'll save you at any cost
so wait for me, Momonosuke!
Brook!
Let me know if you see the
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs that Robin told us to find!
I'm sorry, corpse-dono!
I have to depend on your sorcery!
Count on me!
I just need to look for samurai-san's son
and some Sea Prism Stone handcuffs, right?
Let's check the other side of that wall.
Was his name Momonosuke-kun?
I bet he is a boy who dresses like samurai-san!
Hey! Where are you?!
Building D, S.A.D. Manufacturing Room
My Armament Haki surpasses your ability by far.
I think you're smart enough to know
that it's useless to fight against me.
Smoker.
Or are you trying to avenge those dumb-asses' death?
They're not gonna die that easily -
they're not that weak!
Even though they're misfits,
they're still Navy soldiers!
Shave!
Don't mess with the Navy!
I didn't know you cared so much about your men,
Smoker-kun.
Building B, near the Biscuits Room
Everybody, this way!
Get to the Biscuits Room where the children are!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
You guys are too slow!
The deadly gas is right behind you!
If you don't wanna die, run faster!
Hurry up!
Ouch!
Brother, don't kick me!
Ouch, brother!
Come on, everybody!
Hurry up!
Don't kick me!
Ouch!
The Black Leg brother is gonna kill us before the deadly gas does!
Don't be a baby!
He's crazy!
Hurry up!
If you wanna save the children,
go to the Biscuits Room now!
Biscuits Room
Building B, 3rd Floor
It's cold! The whole room is in a blizzard!
I just took off my coat!
What is a Snow-Snow Fruit?!
Damn that snow woman!
Everybody, stop!
You shouldn't eat the candy!
Mocha, run!
Wait, Mocha!
Give us the candy!
No! You all have to come to your senses!
You can't have it all to yourself!
Stop running!
I'll try to hold them, if even for a little while.
Don't do that.
Robin!
Are you alright, Robin?!
Oh!
You're Pirate Hunter Zoro
with a 120-million-berry bounty!
You three, go stop those kids!
She's a Logia-type.
I'll take care of her!
Even while he's at the mercy of Monet's ability to freely manipulate snow,
Zoro still tries to let Nami and the others escape, despite the relentless attacks.
It's then that Monet transforms into a terrifying monster
and the situation worsens.
The crew find themselves backed into a corner.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Mortal Combat in a Blizzard
The Straw Hats vs. the Snow Woman"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Mortal Combat in a Blizzard
The Straw Hats vs. the Snow Woman