If you are —
a pirate
a pirate among pirates
a pirate among pirates among pirates
a pirate among pirates among pirates among pirates —
Then gather your steadfast crew
And set sail for our island.
The name of the island is...
Omatsuri Island?
Yes.
Omatsuri Island.
I've never heard of this island before.
It's a trap.
No doubt about that.
Why do they call it Omatsuri Island?
Do they hold festivals there or something?
I'll read the rest.
"Omatsuri Island is the only pleasure
island resort in the Grand Line."
"As its name implies, every day is a festival."
"You will also enjoy our many spas and beauty salons."
Spas and beauty salons?
What is that, place? It sounds fabulous!
"Your nightlife will be filled with beauties from around
the world and a selection of fine beverages."
Beauties?
That's a great island!
"Dinner will be a full course of exquisite cuisine.”
Exquisite cuisine?
What's that?
What kind of food is it?!
I’m telling you it's a trap.
Eh, a trap?
What a load.
Omatsuri Island sounds wonderful!
Everything is perfect!
You can tell it's a good island just by its name!
I guarantee it!
Come on! It's gotta be a trap!
Geez!
What d'ya wanna do, Captain?
Nightlife!
Listen, guys!
Hey, Luffy.
What kind of food is it?
Luffy!
Are you listening?!
Nami, read that first part again.
Huh? Okay.
"If you are a pirate among pirates
among pirates among pirates..."
"Then gather your steadfast crew and set sail for our island."
Alright!
I've decided!
We're going to Omatsuri Island!
The reason is, of course...
Because we're pirates!
—Baron Omatsuri and the Secret Island—
This is certainly a lively island, but...
We're here!
Or...
Is the festival over?
Has there ever been a time when
I navigated to the wrong island?
Who the hell would want to
vacation on a deserted island?
I guess it would be ideal for a hermit or something.
Jeez, you're such a loudmouth.
Huh? You say something?
That's odd.
What is?
There were flowers drawn on the map, right?
But I don't see any flowers on the island.
We've been duped.
Okay, let's get going.
Huh?
Do you hear something?
This way!
Spas and beauty salons!
Beauties of the world!
Exquisite cuisine!
T-This is...
...everything we'd hoped for!
Come into my arms, my finely selected beauties...
Hey, what gives?!
Look!
They've all got leaves growing on their heads!
Yeah! Them too!
And them!
What are these guys?
First it's leaves, and then a flower!
A flower?
Pirates!
Courageous pirates who traverse the Grand Line!
Oh! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Luffy!
I congratulate you on reaching Omatsuri Island.
My name is Baron Omatsuri.
Baron Omatsuri?
Yes!
I am your host — the master of this island!
It’s coming, it's coming!
You have faced a long and perilous journey.
Please enjoy your well-deserved rest.
It's coming, it's coming!
You may enjoy yourselves to your hearts' content!
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming!
But before you do, you must...
...undertake the Ordeal of Hell!
Ordeal...
...of Hell?
...of...
...Hell?
I knew it!
Um, I... I have a question!
What is it?
The note said something about spas and beauty salons...
Spas?
Beauties from all over the world and
a selection of fine beverages...
Beverages?
What about the exquisite cuisine?
Exquisite cuisine... Exquisite...
We're leaving!
Hold on, hold on, hold on!
Pops! What's the Ordeal of Hell?
Move it!
The Ordeal of Hell is a test of strength!
Countless many have failed to endure the
task and fled barefoot from this island.
That sounds great!
If you do not have absolute trust in your crew,
you would be well advised to leave this island!
Don't be stupid!
We'll accept your challenge!
Luffy!
Luffy, think about what you're saying!
What would we gain from accepting this?!
Even if there was something, we don't
have any obligation to participate.
That's right, Luffy!
It's dangerous!
I know we don't have to, but I wanna try it!
Hey!
See? I told you so!
I told you this was a trap!
Is it?
It's the Ordeal of Hell!
That's right.
We don't know what'll happen!
Yeah.
Luffy!
What?
Why are you always so carefree?
It doesn't matter if it's a trap
or not. You guys can handle it.
Besides, I trust all of you.
Oh, you're a sweet talker, Captain!
Hell...
Hell, eh?
I'd like to see what this is all about.
Zoro!
Count me in too.
I'm a bit interested in the Baron.
Robin!
Oh, well...
I'm up for it.
Jeez, that leaves me no choice.
Let's just get this over with.
Um...
Luffy!
If you're going for this, then I'm with you!
H-Hey!
Fine! Then l'm in too!
So all of you will be participating?
Very well!
Prepare the Ordeal of Hell!
Huh? W-What?
I will now reveal the Ordeal
of Hell that you will undertake!
It is...
It is...?
Goldfish Catching!
The rules for Goldfish Catching are simple!
The team that captures the largest
goldfish in three minutes wins!
By the way, this paper dissolves easily in water!
And now, allow me to introduce my valued
confidant who shall be your opponent!
Go forth, Muchigoro!
Aye!
Yo! I'm Muchigoro!
What did he say?
Mutsugoro, like a mudskipper.
He looks more like an eel.
Maybe he's a loach.
He's just an idiot.
No! My name is Muchigoro!
Baron Omatsuri's first mate, Muchigoro!
Yep, an idiot.
Now, which one of you will compete?
Here, here, here, here!
Me, me, me, me, me!
Hold on.
Let me handle that Muchigoro or Sushigoro
or whatever his name is!
Oh?
Weren't you shaking in your boots about
the Ordeal of Hell just a second ago?
He got a burst of confidence after
hearing it was Goldfish Catching.
Hey, Tamegoro!
I'm Muchigoro!
You'll regret being my opponent!
You will be facing the man known as
the master of Goldfish Catching...
Me!
Master?
Really?!
Yes, really
Awesome!
You're awesome!
Yeah, awesome!
It's not a lie, right?
Please say you're lying!
I'm lying.
Lying?
It was a lie?
Yes, a lie!!
You lied again!
Darn it! He tricked me!
See? He's an idiot.
Muchigoro! Don't let them build up momentum!
Ah! l'm sorry, Baron!
We shall now begin!
Ready...
Go!
What's that?
What's that?!
That's my cute pet, Rosario-chan.
Look at that!
Laugh at them, Muchigorol
They are nothing but feeble cowards!
Rosario-chan is a good kid who
would never do anything bad!
Hold on!
What's the big idea?
Oh? I told you it was Goldfish Catching.
How are we supposed to catch that?!
Just put the goldfish in the bucket.
He certainly didn’t mention this.
He duped us!
This is getting pretty interesting!
No, it's not!
Pass.
The rest is up to you, Nami.
Hey, wait! Master!
Oh, fine! Ill do if if I have to!
Forget it!
Nami-san, look out!
What?!
Rosario-chan!
Nami-san.
Did you witness my kick?
Zoro, pass.
Me?
Jeez, I guess it's up to me.
Katanas are not allowed in Goldfish Catching!
You damn fish!
What?!
Hey!
You tried to cut my Rosario-chan into pieces!
Whaf did you expect me to do?!
I'm gonna try! Pass me the net!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
His arm stretched!
Then he...
He has the power of a Devil Fruit!
It tore!
There's no way you could catch that
huge goldfish with that tiny net!
You are absolutely correct.
Muchigoro, show them!
You have to catch Rosario-chan with THIS!
No fair!
Why is he using that?!
Who said you had to use this net?
I only said that the paper dissolves easily in water!
Well? Do you remember?
H-He duped us again!
One minute left!
You have one minute left!
Rosario-chan, be a good girl and come over here!
Well done, Muchigoro!
Thank you, Baron!
Oh.
So there were never any rules to begin with.
She's eaten a Devil Fruit too?!
Rosario-chan!
Crap! It's gonna fall on us!
Run for it!
Chopper!
I can handle this!
10 seconds!
Game over!
The Straw Hats win!
Win!
Yeah!
Good job, Chopper!
Chopper?
Chopper!
Luffy!
I'll save you!
I-I thought I was a goner.
Thanks, Luffy.
No, no, it was nothing.
Hey!
I'm the one who saved you!
Sanji-kun, how long were you in the water?
How long is it gonna take you guys
to remember that you're Hammers?
You morons.
Anyway, guys!
We...
...won!
We won!
I'm sorry, Baron!
I'm so useless! I've brought disgrace to your name!
That was easier than I thought!
They call that the Ordeal of Hell?
Congratulations!
Wait! This contest is not yet finished!
We just finished it.
You must now undertake the next ordeal.
I will not allow this travesty to go unpunished.
How dare you make my Muchigoro cry!
Hold on!
You never said anything about this!
He lost. Just accept it.
Silence!
The matter is settled!
You will do as I order you to do!
What're you talking about, Pops?
You're taking this sore loser thing a bit far.
Another ordeal?
Sounds like fun!
Let's try the next one too!
Luffy!
Luffy, we came to a resort!
We're not here to play warrior!
Do you hear me?
Okay, guys!
We're gonna win the next one too!
You numbskull!
You'd better not lose!
Nami, you're coming too!
You numbskull!
Hey, hey...
Where are you going, Nami?
If you like those Ordeals of Hell so much,
you can do them by yourself!
Count me out.
Hey, hey, Nami!
Nami!
Huh?
By the way, where are we?
Are we lost?
Then... where did we leave the ship?
We don't know anymore!
Hey, hey, hey!
I think it's this way.
No, it's gotta be that way.
Slow down!
Everyone stay calm.
Let me see...
Where are we?
We don't know!
Then there was no point in bringing this map!
Huh? What's that?
It looks like someone was having a picnic.
On this island?
There's no accounting for taste.
Leave that stuff alone!
Anyway, let's keep moving.
That's right.
We have to reach the beach first.
We'll get there eventually.
Nami, let's go back.
Shut up!
Nami!
I told you to shut up!
Ah, we're almost out of the forest!
I've been expecting you, courageous pirates!
Oh! Flower Guy!
W-What?
We can't enjoy our vacation!
We can't get off this island!
The only thing we can do is...
The Ordeal of Hell!
Part two!
Ladies and gentlemen!
I shall now announce the next ordeal!
It will be...
Be what?
Ring Toss!
Ring Toss?
Each team has two boats with two people aboard.
The first team to ensnare all of
their opponents in rings wins!
Let me now introduce my confidants, the Four Wise Men!
The leader, Kerojii.
The main striker, Keroshot.
The repairman extraordinaire, Kerodeek.
And the youngest and only female, Keroko!
What?
Are they seriously calling this a competition?
They're a bunch of old geezers!
From our point of view, you're a bunch of snotty kids.
Snotty?!
You've got some nerve
You may be right, but what's with the attitude?!
She's angry.
The girl has a short temper and lacks maturity.
Well excuse me for having a temper!
That's my personality!
And what's with that attitude?!
My, my. I'm quite tired. Can I go to sleep?
Don't sleep!
Are you serious about this?!
You're pretty arrogant about
being a little younger than us.
I'm not a little younger!
I’m way, way younger!
Now then, who among you will enter?
Me, me, me, me, me, me!
Me-!
Let me handle this!
Nami got fired up all of a sudden.
If Nami-san is entering, maybe I should too.
Robin-chan, will you enter too?
Give it a rest, would you?
I didn't invite you.
Who would accept an invitation from you?
Half-Wits are better off on the sidelines.
Who do you think you're talking to?!
Who else would I be talking to?!
Calm down, guys! Stop, stop, stop!
A city?
Look over there!
They can't keep up with us!
Toss a ring, Nami!
I know!
No way!
They're so fast!
There.
It's about time for us to attack.
They're passing us.
That's right.
What's with them?
Alright, we're ahead of them!
Get the rings ready!
There’s something I can't figure out.
Huh?!
Why am I stuck on a boat with a guy who waves
sticks around all day instead of Nami-san?
Huh?!
It's time to attack!
Roger!
Why him instead of Nami-san?
I wanted to play Ring Toss too.
Let them handle it.
We can rest in the meantime.
What hit me?
What? What?
Who's there?!
Where are you?!
Stop hiding and come out!
There you are!
Hold it!
Hey, wait!
I said hold it!
Hey, stop!
We'll catch up and get back in the game!
Back in the game!
Prepare to attack!
Preparing to attack!
Commencing attack!
I can't see where we’re going!
Dammit! I'm getting hungry!
Wrong idea!
We can get out of the smoke if we pull ahead!
Here, meat! Here, meat! Here, meat!
Old people shouldn't eat stuff like that!!
And you two get this!
What was that?!
Stop that!
Are you all comfortable?
Please enjoy yourselves to your hearts'
content until the match is over!
Thank you.
Oh, how very kind of you.
I lost the last match.
I'll do anything you wish.
That is a law of this island.
Is that so?
Then let's have a toast.
I'm on duty.
Oh? I thought you would do anything I wished.
As you wish.
A toast to this slightly odd resort.
Cheers.
It's strange...
This may be a resort,
but there's no one here except us.
Mr. Doctor?
I'm gonna explore a bit.
I'll be right back.
What the hell are you doing?!
I am happy that you could join me.
Huh?!
I braved many dangers to reach this mansion
and make you a wonderful proposal.
Many dangers?
Allow me to introduce myself!
I am the Captain of the Toothbrush Moustache Pirates, Brief!
I‘m a brave man who has organized a resistance
movement against Baron Omatsuri's tyranny!
Huh?
You've got snot hanging off your nose.
This is a toothbrush moustache!
It's proof that I'm a part of the Toothbrush Moustache Pirates!
By the way, we have a special greeting among our crew.
Watch this!
Moustache!
Well? Cool, huh? You try it too.
What's wrong?
You do it like this!
Moustache!
What’s your proposal?
Oh, that's right.
You have six crewmates with you, right?
Ah?
I saw them. They really are a superb team.
Yeah, that's right.
They are wonderful crewmates.
Naturally!
Their teamwork is perfect!
That's nothing!
That's the thing. Listen to me.
Will you join my crew?
Will you all join the Toothbrush Moustache Pirates?
Hey, did you hear me?
I'll say it again!
Will you all join the Toothbrush Mous...
Please, no violence!
No.
Why would we want to be in your crew?
Everyone has that attitude at first.
But, if you stay on this Island, you
change your mind before long.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Beware of Baron Omatsuri.
He separates crewmates.
Flowers?
Who are you?!
Who are you?
Me?
Hey, let me go!
You accursed minion of Baron Omatsuri!
How dare you do this to us!
Surrender!
Take this, and this, and this!
Well, will you say uncle?!
You vile otter Merman!
Take this, and this, and this!
I’m not an otter!
Please don't hit me!
Papa?
Stay back!
Papa won't lose!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I won't do it again!
Please forgive me!
Who are you?
l'm not one of Baron Omatsuri's minions.
Then does that mean you're a pirate?
What a coincidence.
We're pirates too.
Our family, the Tearoom Pirates, are
pretty obscure as far as pirates go.
Oh, the kids behind me are my daughters and my son.
Cute, ain't they?
They all try to be good kids.
We heard this island was a resort,
so we came here to have a picnic.
But it was all a lie.
There's no way we could catch that huge goldfish.
And then?
We ran away.
But my kids still believe their Papa is strong.
And since you seem like a reasonable
person, I need to ask a favor of you.
Would you let me beat you up in front of my kids?
You just have to pretend!
But...
Please!
In return, I'll tell you all of this island's secrets!
Secrets?
Yes, secrets!
You just have to pretend! Pretend!
Hey! Give yourself up!
Please don't hurt me!
Hey!
I surrender!
Papa! You're strong, strong!
Strong, strong, strong, strong!
That’s right!
Papa's strong! Strong, strong!
Papa's strong, isn't he?
This is pretty fishy.
I have a feeling this is a big, fat lie.
What are you saying?
As if it could be a lie!
Listen well.
You can't trust this guy.
How dare you talk about your father that way!
Shut up, old man!
How dare you call me an old man!
Call me Papa!
Stupid.
How dare you call me stupid!
Alright, we’ve caught up.
What the hell is that?!
Now it's my turn!
Hey, get closer!
Shut up! I know!
Got them.
Damn!
Dodge the bullets!
How am I supposed to do that?!
Hey! Wait, wait!
I told you to dodge the bullets!
Dodge them yourself!
He's good.
Got you!
Dammit!
What?
Watch where you're going!
You idiot!
Why don't you do it yourself!
That's what I'm doing!
I'm looking straight ahead!
You're facing the wrong way, you green-tea head!
Green-tea head?
Damn, you...
You... you question!
Question? That doesn't make any sense!
It's your eyebrow!
Are you trying to ask me something, Question?!
Hot, hot, hot! Hot!
The hotter the coals,
the more delicious the food
will be in your mouth.
Usopp, do something! Don't you have any ideas?!
I would like to help,
but putting out this fire
seems too great a task.
Are you imitating him instead of thinking of a plan?!
You’re trying my patience!
A good idea!
A good idea?
...is hard to think of.
I'rn drawing a blank.
You useless lump!
A rescue box?
What's this? There's another one.
Those boxes have things to help
you out when you're in trouble!
Hey! Shh, shh!
Oh, I get it!
There's something we can use to our advantage!
What's inside? What will I get?
You get handmade cups!
How am I supposed to use these?
They must be for this!
Okay, what's in this one?
What?! What's this?!
Hey, hold on!
Usopp!
Hey, where are you going?
Usopp?
No way...
He ran away! He ran away and left you alone!
Kero, kero, kero!
His crew's worth
does not compare to his own.
He is above you.
Tough break, kid.
Kero, kero, kero!
Yeah!
Alright!
This is awesome!
A flower?
Yes, a flower.
I don't know of any flower that grows only on this island.
Besides, I'm so drunk that I need to take a nap.
Please try to remember instead
of avoiding the question.
I-I think...
Think what?
The Lily Carnation...
Lily?
What is that?
It grows at the highest point on the island...
Excuse me!
The Lily Carnation.
Hey, jerk!
Wait!
You've really pissed me off this time.
I've had enough of your attitude, you green-tea freak!
That's my line, Question!
Hey!
Don't ignore us!
I bet that scared you, you little brats!
Shut up!
Sorry for making you wait.
Yeah.
I'm sorry I let him break it!
It's alright.
Repairs complete! Power up!
Shut up!
Alright, let's finish this.
Yeah.
Not again!
No problem!
Shut the hell up!
Alright, that takes care of them.
Let’s do this then.
You two idiots over there!
Nami-san!
Hurry up and ring them!
Oh, that's right.
Nami-san, sorry for making you wait!
Get me down!
You!
I shall warn you once.
Your elders may surprise you.
Do not drop your guard.
I am Kerojii.
You almost kicked me!
Damn!
You're the one almost killing people!
Kerojii, nice!
It's your fault for being in the way!
Move aside!
No, you move!
No, you!
I don't care who does it, just get him!
You almost hit me!
Guys!
I told you to stay out of my way!
What?!
Guys, above you
Were the rabbit to die,
the fox would be lonely
and deeply distraught.
That was close.
What's this?
Oh, my. I missed one.
Hey, no, you didn't. He pushed me...
Making excuses? That's pathetic!
I can take this guy myself!
Even when the two of you couldn't?
I can fight better without someone holding me back.
Holding you back?!
Hey, how long are you going to keep fighting?!
If you don't pull it together...
Kerojii is strong.
He's been playing this game for decades.
Could you all just act your age?!
Kero, kero, kero, kero!
What's with these old geezers?
Pirates?
That's right.
Baron Omatsuri and his men used to be a pirate crew.
Oh, you're right.
They really were pirates.
I found this while wandering around the island.
A paradise like Omatsuri Island could never exist.
This is a pirate's island.
But...
Why is a pirate drawing other pirates to him?
A pirate gathers pirates, makes them undertake
ordeals, singles out the strongest ones...
Why's he doing that?
Good question.
I thought it was pretty strange too.
You don't know?!
I'm sorry!
Anyway, I have to tell the others...
Huh?
Now that I look at it, there's something
strange about this wanted poster.
Well, young'un, what happened to all that energy?
Shut up!
Just wait! I'm about to cut you to pieces!
Three-sword style, eh?
Oni...
The foes are vanquished.
This contest has now ended.
Victory is ours.
Wait right there! Aren’t you forgetting someone?
Usopp Pound!
Did you see that?
That was Usopp's mid-air attack.
You guys are the worst!
Yo, Nami!
I'm glad you-
That hurt! What was that for?!
For backstabbing me earlier!
Backstabbing?
What're you talking about?
That's your speciality, ain’t it?
You'd better remember what you did back there.
You say something?
I told you to remember it.
Guys... What the hell happened?
Don't laugh when you just lost!
Look, they're setting off fireworks
to celebrate your victory!
Flowers of the sky,
blooming in passing triumph.
Ephemeral lights.
I've got it!
Take a good look!
The Baron is the only one on this
poster who looks younger!
Oh, you're right.
But what does that mean?
Well...
I think...
You want to know if I saw anything from the sky?
Yes, perhaps a flower?
A flower?
A flower, hmm...
Come to think of it...
Come to think of it, where did Chopper go?
Oh, he told Robin he'd be back soon,
so he should be back soon.
Hey, does anyone know where Chopper is?
I just said he said he'd be back soon!
Ah? Where's Chopper?
I said...
Nobody asked you!
Hey, Nami!
How long are you gonna stay mad?
Please do something, Mr. Captain.
They've been like this for hours.
Why are you arguing?
I thought your pirate crew got along well.
Eh, spare us the wisecracks.
I will now entertain you all with a private dinner party.
A dinner party?
W-What, what?
I present to you the outdoor iron-griddle restaurant!
A performance, eh?
He's spreading oil!
Nothing special about that.
He's fast!
Nothing special there either.
Looks yummy!
Kid, you're in the way! Get lost!
Luffy, I'm about to make you a shitty meal 100
times better than what this fatty is making.
I don't have any ingredients for you to use!
Then I'll just...
...take yours!
Yeah, yeah!
Yeah, yeah...
Miss.
Where are you going?
I'm getting some fresh air before I eat.
In the middle of the banquet?
I thought that a flower would complement the decor.
Is the specimen on my shoulder not to your liking?
The Lily Carnation.
Prithee, of what do you speak?
The kind goldfish keeper told me about it.
A species which grows nowhere else in the world.
A magnificent flower.
Sanji-kun!
Lookin’ good!
Do your best!
Keep it up, Sanji!
Go, go!
Sanji-kun!
What's wrong with Nami?
Jeez! There was nothing to get so angry over!
What did I do anyway?!
Dammit!
Ouch!
Good evening 'pu.
Who's this guy?
Your hat's cool 'pu.
Give it to me 'pu.
Give me your hat 'pu.
Why should I give you my hat?
Don't be so selfish!
Give it to me 'pu!
Get real!
Gimme 'pu!
Wait, what's with all those "pu"s?
Oh, you just made fun of me.
No, no, I didn't mean to make fun of you!
You're making fun of me!
Yeah! You're making fun of me 'pu!
Another "pu"!
Ah, you made fun of me again 'pu!
You made fun of me ‘pu!
Aren't you overreacting a bit?
I won't forgive you 'pu!
Why's that?
I won't forgive you 'pu.
Oyster sauce!
Seaweed flakes!
And with a dash of red, pickled ginger, my
Omatsuri Island yakisoba will be complete!
Bon appetite!
W-What are you doing?
Thanks for the ingredients
W-What?
Super-thick sauce!
A layer of mayonnaise
And...
As the veil-like bonito flakes dance in
the air, my modanyaki is complete.
That's how it's done!
Im... Impossible...
H-H-Hot!
Robin-chan, did you see?
I have proven my mastery-
She's gone!
Nami-san, behold.
A demonstration of my love consecrated in...
She's not looking!
Jeez, I've had enough of this.
Time to eat!
Whoa, hot!
I can't take any more.
I've been drinking since this afternoon.
Are you saying you won't drink the
wine a woman like me pours?
That's not it.
Sitting with a gorgeous doll
like you, I could drink all night.
Gorgeous doll?
You tease!
Don't make me blush!
By the way, who's that flower guy?
Is he the king of the island?
And is he filthy rich?
What did you just say?
No one calls the Baron "flower guy"!
Say that again and I won't be responsible
for what happens to you!
He's a great man.
He's strong and courageous!
And he's kind!
He’s the greatest of the greatest
of the greatest of men!
You might have said a few too many "greatest"-
No!
Even that isn't enough to describe
what a wonderful man he is!
I've worked for the Baron all these
years because I love him!
By the way, why are you drinking
with me instead of your crewmates?
Why?
I wonder...
We've never fought like this before.
Did something happen?
No.
I just thought to myself that
I wanted to hear about Muchi.
Muchi?
What's Muchi?
Your name's Muchigoro, so I'll call you Muchi.
I'm Muchi.
Yep, Muchi.
Please call me Muchi.
Hey, Zoro! Wake up!
This is great!
What? Dinner?
All right, let's eat.
You were asleep, so you can go hungry.
Huh?
Anyone who doesn't cheer for me
doesn't have the right to eat.
Robin-chan! Where are you?
Dinner is served!
What a jerk.
Robin-chwaaan~!
Huh?
That's right, Nami.
We used to be pirates like you guys.
Our pirate crew was called the Red Arrows.
The Red Arrows?
We were an incredibly strong pirate crew!
With the Baron as Captain, we had to be.
I'm sure the Baron could even beat Roger.
Roger? Which Roger are you talking about?
Tell me I'm not hearing this!
You're a pirate and you've never heard of Gold Roger?
Gold Roger? You mean the man who
started the Great Pirate Era?
So you do know him.
Have you ever met him?
There's no way I could have.
Wasn't he executed ages ago?
Executed?
Gold Roger's been dead for over twenty years.
What are you talking about?
That's impossible!
I mean, I met him just recently.
Recently?
Yes.
Before that stormy night...
That storm was terrible.
Stormy night?
Hey! What are you talking about, Muchi?
Muchi?
As I thought, this ship was run aground by a storm.
There is no doubt that this is the Baron's ship.
But this is strange.
I thought I would find it here.
If you really want to see it, I'll show you.
The secret flower.
The Lily Carnation.
The flower of death and rebirth.
What is that?
The flower you have sought.
That's a flower?
You call that a flower?
Muchi, what is it?
What happened on that stormy night?
Tell me, Muchi!
Mu...
That can't be!
That thing... That thing can’t be a flower!
Hey, Captain!
Quit stuffing your face!
Robin-chan's gone!
Robin?
She said she was going to look for a flower.
A flower?
When was that?
Would it take this long?!
Where's Usopp?
I don't know. He should be around...
Usopp's gone too?!
Chopper isn't back yet either.
Damn.
That's bad.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Don't give us that half-baked garbage.
What the hell were you doing?
What?
I told you to keep an eye on them!
They aren't kids! I can't keep
tabs on them all day long!
Three of our crewmates disappeared and no one noticed?!
But...
Luffy.
What are you going to do?
You're the one who got us into this.
Sanji-kun...
You're the one who decided to come to this island!
Stop it! This isn't the time!
That's what caused all of this!
Luffy... this is your fault.
Me?
Muchigoro.
The dinner party is over!
The Ordeal of Hell will now resume!
Everyone, take your positions!
DJ, come forth.
Good evening 'pu.
I'm DJ Gappa.
Pleased to meet you 'pu.
Hold on. Where are Usopp and Robin-chan?
And Chopper!
We want to see them now.
Did you just ignore me?
Hey! Did you just ignore me?
Shut up, kappa!
K-Kappa?
That hat's Usopp's!
Give it back 'pu!
You bastard. What did you do to Usopp?
Don't worry.
Your friends are still on the island 'pu.
If you want to see them, try and find them 'pu!
So you’re the one who's behind this!
Calm yourselves.
You will learn their fate after the next ordeal.
Don't give us that crap!
Give them back now!
The ordeal comes first.
Don't screw with us! Those three come first!
The ordeal will come first!
This is getting us nowhere.
I'll go find them myself!
Sanji-kun, wait!
I'm not about to bother with your Ordeal of Hell now!
Zoro!
The fools have gone off without
knowing what this ordeal entails.
There are no rules in this ordeal.
My one hundred sharpshooters will hunt you.
If you believe you can escape them,
You are free to search for your crew
or do whatever else you wish.
Luffy, what do we do?
Luffy?
Luffy!
You may begin!
I'm going by myself.
Aren't you going?
Is the pirate captain abandoning his crew?
Is that all your crewmates mean to you?
Give my friends back!
Very admirable!
You have nowhere to run!
Straw Hat!
Dammit!
What's that sound?
How are we supposed to look for anyone like this?!
You can't get away 'pu!
I said you couldn’t get away.
That's what you get for making me mad 'pu.
That's freaking hot!
What are you doing, you stupid brat?!
Demon...
Slash!
What?!
You just cut me.
But I didn't die. I'm not even bleeding.
Why?
Shit!
What kind of trick did you use?
Trick?
How's that?!
What trick?
That's impossible!
W-What's going on?
DJ, are you okay?
I'm sorry 'pu, Baron.
But why do I never die when
pirates shoot and cut me 'pu?
Because you are strong.
I don't understand 'pu.
I'm so much weaker than Kerojii, Muchigoro,
and the rest of the crew.
You are strong too.
That must be it!
That's right.
Straw Hat's the only one left 'pu.
I promise I'll catch him 'pu.
What's wrong?
I feel dizzy.
But it happens all the time 'pu.
I don't feel well.
I wonder if I overdid it.
Let's take a nap.
When you wake up, you'll be the same
cheerful old woman you always are.
Yes, just like always.
W-Where is everyone?
I can't see anything.
It's pitch black.
You're awake.
You!
We meet again.
You're the guy with the snot!
It's a toothbrush moustache!
What am I doing in this hole?
Excuse me for living in a hole.
I've dug trap doors and tunnels all over the island...
So that I can escape from the
Baron's vile clutches whenever I need to.
You fell into one of them.
You're lucky to be alive after facing the Baron.
I don't have time to sit around here!
I have to go
Wait!
My friends are waiting for me.
I told you to wait!
Bye!
You won't be able to get out of here so easily.
The tunnels are connected to each other in a complex network.
I'm the only one who knows how to get out.
Then tell me!
Oh! Welcome to my secret base!
It's been so long since I've had a guest.
Do you like goat's milk?
I don't want any!
Well?
Will you reconsider that proposition
to join my crew?
No!
Don't be so stubborn.
The Toothbrush Moustache Pirates are
currently recruiting new members.
Are they your crew?
Huh? That's right.
These guys all look like you.
Yeah, because we're crewmates.
Come to think of it, you're the only one I've met.
Where are the others?
Are they in another base?
I'm alone right now.
I am currently the only member of
the Toothbrush Moustache Pirates.
I can still see it in my mind.
The day my precious crewmates
were attacked by the Baron.
The day they were swallowed
by that gigantic monster...
Huh?
I thought I was hit by an arrow...
I'm scared.
I'm scared!
Don't be afraid! Don't be afraid!
Papa's here, so there's nothing to be afraid of.
I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
I've kept you waiting, Lily.
It's time to eat.
Get away!
Daisy!
Papa!
Papa, save me!
Daisy! Daisy!
Daisy!
Now's your chance!
Get out of here!
Go! Hurry!
Mr. Reindeer!
Hurry!
I see. Your strength is as magnificent as I'd expected!
This is the first time I have offered Lily someone
with the power of a Devil Fruit!
Damn! Let me go!
Let me go!
Daisy!
I told you to get away.
What are you kids doing?
Come quickly!
Papa! Save Mr. Reindeer!
You're strong, right?
Show us how strong you are!
Papa!
What are you doing?!
Papa, stop!
Papa, why?
He saved Daisy!
Let me go!
You coward!
Yeah.
I am a coward.
Show me more!
That was splendid! Show me more!
I love seeing a pirate crew fighting amongst
themselves more than anything else!
What's wrong?!
Won't you quarrel anymore?
The Baron once told me something.
"When I see crews like yours, anger fills my chest."
"I want to separate you."
"I want to chop them up one by one."
"I want them to experience the same pain I have."
The same pain?
I don't know what his true intentions are.
But, the Baron does indeed loathe the
sight of pirates with strong bonds.
You cannot fight him alone.
That is what he wants you to do.
Then what should I do?
That's...
Baron!
Don't think you've won!
My friends will come to save me!
They're gonna beat you to a pulp!
Your crew will not be coming,
no matter how long you wait.
You're lying!
They'll come!
That was no lie.
You will not be rescued.
No, they'll come!
I believe in them!
I said they will not and they will not!
They'll come!
I'm sure of it!
Stop saying that!
I am telling you they will not come!
Nami!
Sanji!
Usopp!
Robin!
Zoro!
Guys!
My crew, my crew, my crew, my crew...
That's all they ever talk about.
You will nourish Lily well.
What's wrong, Straw Hat?
This is wrong.
I shouldn't be sitting down here.
Hey!
Hey! Wait, Straw Hat!
Thanks for your help.
Straw Hat!
Don’t go alone!
Huh?
Baron!
What am I doing here?
Baron.
Oh, Muchigoro.
I see you're awake.
I feel like I've been having a long dream.
I'm sorry, Baron.
No, no, it's quite all right.
I only want you all to be your cheerful selves.
Cheerful?
I'm always cheerful!
Look at me!
Did you see that?
I saw it, Muchigoro.
No, I'm not done yet!
That's enough.
Now go back and join the others.
Roger that, Baron!
So you've come, Straw Hat.
How foolish of you to face me alone.
This voice...
Okay, let's go.
Daisy.
Quietly, quietly.
Straw Hat!
Wh-Who are you?!
Pops, where's Chopper?
Are you referring to that horned river otter?
Then...
Pops.
I've got two things to tell you.
First, Chopper isn't a river otter — he's a reindeer.
Second, I'll never let you hurt my crew.
Never let me hurt them?
Your crew consisted of six, correct?
Just before you arrived,
That number went down to five.
What did you say?
Before long, the others will disappear into Lily as well.
What did you say?!
Yet you say you won't let me harm them?
Youll never let me hurt them.
Unforgivable...
I won't forgive you!
Gum-Gum...
One arrow.
What happened to your determined spirit?
Dammit!
While you struggle, another one
of your crewmates is disappearing.
S-Stop it!
Robin!
Who will be next?
I see. The cook.
You bastard!
Gum-Gum...
Two arrows.
Sanji!
Only three left.
If you don't hurry, there won't be anyone left.
Stop it!
Gum-Gum...
Since you can't see, I'll just tell you.
The man with the phallic nose has just died.
Usopp!
What will you do?
Will you fight me with just your left leg?
Gum-Gum...
The other woman has just disappeared.
N-Nami...
You can no longer move in that state.
The very last of your crew is starting to fade away.
Zoro!
Straw Hat.
Your swordsman is dead.
You have no crewmates left.
You are utterly alone on the vast Grand Line.
Alone?
I feel much better 'pu!
Pupupu, pupupu, pupupu no 'pu!
Alright! Speed this up!
M-My friends... Give them-
Does it hurt to be without friends?
You have lost all of them.
That reality will never change.
What are you going to do now?
If you decide to go on, a life of suffering,
despair and loneliness is all that awaits you.
Or will you decide to follow your crew?
Let me paint you a picture.
Almost every captain has chosen
death over living in solitude.
That is a wise decision.
One man cannot be a pirate alone.
Now I will ask you again.
What will you choose?
Life or death?
As I thought, being alone is too
painful for you to endure.
Then die.
What?
Baron!
You again!
I won't let this man die!
Fiend!
Where are you aiming?!
Here! Here!
That impudent...
How is he?
He's hurt pretty bad.
Hey, Straw Hat!
Hey, now!
Open your eyes, Straw Hat!
Straw Hat!
My friends...
It's my fault.
What are you talking about?
Where's your determination?!
Corne to your senses!
You're their captain, right?
You have to stand up!
Listen to me, Straw Hat.
Your crewmates probably aren't dead yet.
She can hear their voices calling you.
Are you Luffy?
Mr. Reindeer is calling for you.
Chopper is?!
Where?
From where?!
He's not here!
No, I can hear him.
There are other voices too.
Four.
Five.
"Luffy! Luffy!"
See, even now.
Really?
Unfortunately, I am also unable to hear them.
But that child was repeating your name
even though she had never met you.
That much is certain.
Daisy, was your hearing always this good?
I...
Where are you?!
Where are you hiding, Straw Hat?!
You can't just reeklessly charge at the Baron's arrows.
Use the underground routes I dug.
I'll back you up.
Just do as I told you and rush
toward that strange flower.
You...
You forgot this.
Don't let the Baron's lies affect you.
Listen, you aren't alone yet!
I wanted to tell you that.
You still have a chance to save your crew.
And...
I'm here with you too.
If you understand, then go!
We don't have much time!
Hurry!
What's with' that weird pose?
You're talking about life and death
with your finger up your nose?
That's just weird.
Hey, shut up!
This is the Toothbrush Moustache Pirates'
time-honored, sacred greeting!
How dare you!
There you are!
You're only running away!
Got you!
Straw Hat!
Jump in the hole ahead to your right!
Then keep going and don't stop!
Well done, Straw Hat!
Have you still not learned your lesson?!
Now stay in that hole!
Baron...
Don't mess with me.
If you think you can just rob people of their friends and crewmates, you're dead wrong!
As of now...
I'm one of his crew!
His crew?
How delightful!
Straw Hat!
Listen well!
This man who claims to be your crew was once
the captain of a pirate crew that I annihilated!
A man who pleaded for mercy!
A man who wretchedly shook in fear
at the thought of being alone!
Why would you let such a pathetic
insect be part of your crew?!
S-Straw Hat...
I warned you.
I won't let you hurt my friends!
Friends?
Moustache!
Hey!
Go help Mr. Reindeer and the others!
Guys, I'm coming!
Hang on!
He did it!
Now he can rescue Mr. Reindeer and the others!
Something's wrong.
The voices are coming from somewhere else now.
Where are Zoro and the others?
Where are they?!
Right here.
Die.
Straw Hat!
Every single one of these arrows symbolizes a
day of loneliness I endured after that storm.
They are the number of regrets I have suffered from
suddenly losing every one of my beloved crewmates.
Have you had a glimpse of what I have endured?
Straw Hat...
l-lt's over.
Don't lose!
Mr. Reindeer and the others are calling for you!
"Luffy, you can do it! Luffy, you can
do it!" They're cheering for you
So... So don't lose!
Luffy, Luffy... Luffy... Luffy... Mr. Captain... Luffy...
What?!
My friends...
Give them back.
Give them back!
Luffy?
Yes, just like that!
Daisy, can you really hear their voices?
Papa can't hear anything.
To tell you the truth, I heard everything you told
Mr. Reindeer behind that grave earlier this evening.
My hearing is just naturally adept.
I can hear even the faintest sound.
But I pretended not to know.
You're always trying so hard to keep us happy.
Daisy...
But I believe that you really are strong!
Of course.
Papa is strong.
Papa!
Don't give up, Papa!
Papa, shoot!
Shoot!
Liliy!
Lily!
How could this happen to you?
But now, Muchigoro... my crew... my crew will...
Unforgivable!
Muchigoro, Kerojii, DJ, Kotetsu...
My friends, please don't go!
Please don't leave me alone!
Without you, I am...
I am...
Baron, we're sorry for leaving you alone for so long.
Kerojii...
Thanks for remembering us all this time 'pu.
We're really happy 'pu.
DJ...
But, you should have forgotten about
us after we died on that stormy night.
Muchigoro...
What are you saying? I am...
We don't mind!
That's why you should have found some new friends.
New friends?
Look. Like them.
Straw Hat!
I thought I was gonna die!
You're alive!
Thank goodness!
Guys...
Are you hurt?
Why are you worrying about us?!
It's a miracle that you're even alive!
Brief, I couldn't have done it without you!
What are you saying?
That's my line!
And that guy too.
Me?
I didn't do much.
By the way, where are my friends?
Mr. Reindeer!
Daisy!
Chopper, you're quite popular.
I don't know what happened, but I slept well.
By the way, where are we?
Take a look! It's the sunrise!
It's so bright!
Is that Luffy?
Oh, it is!
Luffy!
What are you doing, sleeping out here?
How many people?
We're are so frail.
I long for the courage to face the gods.
The destiny we've been given is too dull and quiet.
Drifting and floating, we'll keep on goin'!
I want to tell somebody...
...there is no night that will not turn into day!
Until we grow up... Until that day comes...
...we'll take the long way 'round!
The secrets of the world await you!
Yes! Even if you're too old to dream.
O, Sky! O, Sea! O, Stars! O, Wind! O, Clouds!
O, Father! O, Mother!, O, Friends! O, Great Earth!
I want to see everything there is to see!
I want to see all this world has to offer!