Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hody's merciless plot puts Fishman Island in unprecedented danger!
The giant ship, Noah, has just lost its power
and is starting to fall towards the island again!
What?!
About Hody Jones...
I found out who he really is!
Hody is...
...a monster who was brought to life by our environment!
The New Fishman Pirates are a group of monsters created from an ancient grudge!
What did you go through in the past?!
Answer me, Hody!
What did humans do to you?!
Nothing.
We were chosen by heaven to punish humans...
...and granted powers!
Their hatred is...
...not rooted in their experience or true beliefs.
They have no substance!
They are completely "empty"!
"Back to Zero! Earnest Wishes for Luffy!"
Their hatred is not rooted in their experience or true beliefs.
They have no substance! They are completely "empty"!
Empty? What does he mean by that?
Hey, you guys, you got to keep moving! Get off of the island!
You can see the shadow of the Noah up in the sky already!
--Hurry up! It's gonna come within range soon! --I'm hurrying!
How much longer? How much inflation do we have so far?!
87%!
Make it in time! Make it!
Hurry up, Wimpyhoshi!
Hody-sama looks even more terrifying than before!
Humans are lowly creatures.
Remember, Hody.
They are evil.
This is it! We're doomed!
Since the Pirate Era began, we've kept losing our friends day after day!
Humans have kidnapped some young Mermaids
and sold them to the Human Shop!
We're all doomed! Fishman Island will fall!
--Damn humans! --We have to kill them all!
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them all!
Damn! Humans!
They get on my nerves!
Oh, you got stronger-ch!
Wow!
It's great! We have a hero!
He blew up the Human Shop sacrificing his life! Pay him your respects!
Let's not forget his death!
Hero?
That serves you right, humans!
This is awesome!
Yeah.
Heroes are cool-ch!
Dosun!
Arlong-san sank another human pirate ship!
This is a crusade!
Ages ago, the filth we call "humans" envied the chosen and gifted Fishmen
and feared our existence.
And...
...they decided to persecute us.
Humans were everywhere in the world, like maggots.
So they exploited their only advantage - their number,
and drove us down to the seafloor.
Listen, everyone! Never forget our grudge against the humans!
Humans know and fear that their reckoning day will come!
And that's when we'll make them pay!
Never forget our history.
Feel the disappointment of the dead.
Take over their resentment.
Hold a grudge against humans!
There is this human named Rayleigh who I knew for a long time
and he's different!
He doesn't make a face even when he sees me...
Hody?
I don't like your story, Hachi-san.
It makes me sick.
Humans are afraid.
Take over the resentment. Okay, Hody?
Remember, Hody.
They are evil, lowly creatures.
Hate humans.
Hate them. Hate them! Hate them!!
This is terrible!
Tiger-san, the hero who freed the slaves, has been killed by humans!
What?!
So Tiger was not the chosen hero.
Who are you people?! Go away!
I heard you gave your blood to humans.
So what?! There was a human who was dying so...
Dad!
Even the members of the royal family are crazy in this country.
She wants to forgive humans.
Screw that!
Did you hear about Jinbe-san joining the Seven Warlords?
Only the Arlong Pirates keep the purity of the Fishmen.
We need a hero.
This country...
...needs a hero.
Otohime-sama has been shot!
You see? That's what humans do!
They show no mercy even to someone like
the Queen who was so friendly to them!
If the royal family won't seek revenge out of pride,
we'll never trust this country again!
We don't need such a spineless country!
The leader of those disgraceful ones has been punished by heaven!
Those villains who want to forgive humans must die-dosun!
It's time for our revenge!
Heaven chose us finally and granted us power.
--Don't tell me it's... --That legendary drug-ch?!
I can't believe you got it-dosun!
Can you make a lot of it, Zeo?
I'll try.
The people of the Fishman District who are
disappointed with the country will come together!
This is a crusade! Get ready!
Prepare to kill as many humans as you can until your own death!
We were chosen...
...to inherit the duty of vengeance!
The reckoning day will come!
Evil lowly creatures - humans!
We're devoting our life to this vengeance!
It was too late!
I don't know when but we lost contact with the Fishman District
and they've become something like an isolated, dark side of Fishman Island!
We pretended not to see the twisted hatred building up in that lawless ditch...
...in the deep water!
--Hey you! Where are you going?! --Let me go! The Noah is...
No way!
I filled my mother's shoes and collected signatures
but I was only dealing with superficial matters.
But I thought I was making a progress!
I know it's hard but...
...you can't plant your anger and resentment
toward humans in children's minds!
It was too late!
People like them are the ones that my mother feared the most!
Brother-sama!
We should have fought within ourselves first!
We should have fought our own feelings toward humans!
Mother was...
Mother was killed by the grudge growing on Fishman Island!
It was too late! People like them are...
...the ones that my mother feared the most!
We should have fought within ourselves first!
We should have fought our own feelings toward humans!
Mother was...
Mother was killed by the grudge growing on Fishman Island!
Maybe she knew it!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Don't get angry on my behalf.
Don't let resentment or hatred get the better of you for my sake.
But a part of me held that resentment
and hated humans for killing my mother!
Prince...
Dead people take their regret to the grave.
So a grudge is an illusion that the living create and they alone cultivate it!
Because I hated humans - even a bit, I overlooked the
resentment in the Fishman District
and when I finally noticed, it had become too powerful and beyond control!
If nothing is done, Fishman Island will...
...destroy itself through its own hatred toward humans!
Be careful!
Unlike the bubble protecting the island, this one can overshoot the ship!
It has to surround the Noah! It can't go too far!
Straw Hat! Please!
We don't need the past! Reset our history to zero!
Wipe out those phantoms who shut the island away from the sun!
Okay, now!
Go!
Bring Fishman Island back...
...to zero!
Shut up, Fukaboshi!
The Fishmen's grudge will last forever!
Brother-hoshi.
As long as you let me handle it my way, don't worry.
H-Hey! Those guys fighting against Hody's crew at the plaza are...
--Yes, it's the Straw Hats! --And Boss Jinbe!
What?!
--Luffy-chan's voice! --Oh yeah!
Yes! It's in the bubble!
Our minds were made up when we arrived at the plaza that,
along with Jinbe, we wouldn't let anyone harm the island!
Leave it all up to us, Brother-hoshi!
We're friends, right?
I cannot believe we suspected a human like him!
Hey, what's wrong? Don't stop!
We have to run! Hey!
--I'm gonna stay on the island! --What?!
Me too!
--Me too! --I'm not gonna run either!
--Luffy-sama! There is air on the Noah now! --Yeah!
You can't get away from me!
Hody-sama!
Wimpyhoshi! Stay with me! I promise I won't let you be hurt!
Okay!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-sama!
Take this! The Wings of Ikaros!
Wings?
That's not tsubasa (wings).
That's tsuba (spit)!
Squid!
Ink?
It's too bad for you-ch!
That was my alter ego made from squid ink!
Don't underestimate us officers of...
Franky Fireball!
Oh, I don't wanna become a dried squid-ch!
Yes! General Franky's new attack!
He shot a fireball from his stomach!
Huh?
You breathed it?!
How could you drop your guard-gaban?!
Heavy Point!
T-shot!
Heavy Gong!
He stopped my hammer with his bare hand?!
Ow... Maybe this transformation is not suited for a fight against a hammer!
Hey, Chopper!
That was the form that gave you the most
human-like look but now you look like a monster!
I don't care now.
I wanted to look like a human because I wanted friends.
Now I wanna become a monster who is helpful to Luffy!
I see.
Smiles make me wanna slice!
Bring the strongest swordsman on Fishman Island!
You're not even able to kill my boredom.
Straw Hat!
It's all over now!
Weren't you listening?
I won't let anyone harm Fishman Island!
It's finally time...
...for the climax of the Straw Hats' battle in Conchcorde Plaza.
And on the Noah, Hody, transformed into a living weapon...
...mercilessly attacks Luffy.
In order to fulfill his promise to Fukaboshi...
...Luffy puts everything he's got into his fists in order to crush Hody!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Luffy's All-out Attack! Red Hawk Blasts!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!