Until I can reach that great sky,
I believe, to that one tomorrow, hey
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one dream
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the good times
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Stumbling into the darkness, fumbling about to find the answer
Freezing up when there's no goal in sight
Umm you and me, yes, in this world where we share our feelings
I feel the beat guiding me, and begin to walk, oh yeah
Share the music, anytime
Share the one dream and believe in each other
Share the good times holding hands
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style
Beginning, expanding, this flavor is beyond imagining
I feel so good throughout my body, I know I can be free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far
Share the one dream, by telling each other
Share the good times and laugh
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall
I'll be there soon, I believe, to that one world, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy is heading to the
Great Prison - Impel Down
to rescue his brother Ace, who's
been captured by the Navy.
Meanwhile, his friends have
been sent to separate islands.
The Crew's Whereabouts
An Island of Giant Birds and a Pink Paradise!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
M-My shin! You kicked my shin!
Why couldn't you get it, you blockhead?!
I require at least 100
kilograms of food per meal.
Anything less than that won't suffice.
Do you want to be turned to stone again?!
N-No! I'm very sorry! I'll be careful!
Bring her another meal to replace this one!
Here, Luffy! Bon appétit!
It's extremely delicious!
When I'm fed by you, the food tastes
sweeter than it actually is!
Oh, I'm glad!
...A-And that's how it'd all play out!
What're you doing over there in the corner?
Aren't you gonna eat? This
Sea King ham is good as hell!
I-I-I'm okay! You eat it!
I'm totally satisfied as I am!
Damn! I can't see anything.
The curtain's closed.
Yeah, it's totally covered! Oh,
there's an open space here!
Love-Love Beam!
Something wrong?
There were two bad-mannered rats
so I just taught them a lesson.
I see!
T-This is...
This must be a warning!
If we ever try to look into her
room, she'll do this to us!
She's scary!
Meanwhile, a few days ago...
On an island in the South Blue...
Luffy!
Everybody!
Oops!
Why isn't anybody here?
Did they kill them?
That can't be it! I won't believe it!
Everybody!
Chopper!
Luffy!
Everybody!
I wasn't scared at all when you guys
weren't there. I really wasn't!
Ow!
Ouch! Stop it, Luffy, Usopp!
I said stop, damn it!
Ouch! You jerk!
What are these birds?!
They're huge!
Are you gonna eat me?!
I-I can't move my body!
I gotta run!
Oww! Stop it!
Oh, my head is spinning!
No! Let me go!
You bastard!
What's wrong with this island!
Is this a dream?
Please tell me this is a dream!
No, stop it!
Stop it!
I am not your toy!
It's over... right?
What is this place?
Isn't there anybody here?
Luffy!
Everybody!
I'm the only one on this island.
What am I gonna do?!
I'm thirsty and hungry...
If only Luffy and everybody else were here,
even on a deserted island like this,
we'd have a banquet!
Banquet, banquet!
Maybe I'll never see them again...
I can't take it!
Where is everybody?!
Luffy... Everybody...
Oh yeah!
There's this!
We made a promise to meet up
where this Vivre Card leads us!
Luffy and others will be there!
I know that nothing can stop them!
I will make it!
This is no time to give up!
I'd eat anything to survive
to see everybody again!
This fruit is bitter!
But it's juicy!
This one's too sour!
Gotcha! I need some meat, too!
But this doesn't look so appetizing.
No, I can't expect too
much on a deserted island.
Wow! You can't run!
You can't get away from me!
Who the hell... hit me?
Ouch!
Why is it so hot?
Am I gonna be dinner?!
Wow, it's so rare to find a raccoon dog!
We'll cook raccoon dog hot pot!
I rather get some birds
and do chicken hot pot.
We would've done it, if it were that easy.
We'll just have raccoon dog for now.
Stop it! I'm a reindeer!
Then it looks like we'll
have reindeer hot pot!
Oh wait, did it just say something?
Do reindeers speak?
Let me go! Just let me go!
I-It's a crisis! We tried to
sneak into the birds' nest
but they caught us!
The birds are coming!
Let's shoo them away!
--Let's go, everyone!
--Let's go!
H-Hey! Wait! Set me free before you go!
Looks like the birds are stronger!
Oh no!
Augh! Ow! Ow!
Ouch! Ouch!
Those birds treated me like a toy
and the humans tried to eat me in a hot pot!
What's wrong with this island?!
One legend suggests this
island is a treasure island.
This is Birdie Kingdom,
where birds reign supreme.
What is Chopper's fate?!
Behold! A dream island in the Grand Line
called Peachy Island.
"Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan,"
"how are you both doing?"
"Right now, I'm... I'm..."
A few hours earlier
W-Where am I?
Damn! This is all because of that Warlord!
Excuse me! Mister! Mister! Are you all right?
Mister! Mister! Are you all right?!
I can feel something...
and smell something sweet.
I'm in the hands of a beautiful woman!
Is it... Nami-san?!
No, is it Robin-chan?!
No, I must be dreaming.
But it's doesn't matter. I
just wanna be here forever!
Oh, w-wait a minute!
What's this?
You forgot your handkerchief! Oh?
So it wasn't a dream?
Elizabeth?
Anyway, where the hell am I?
Don't tell me that I'm in heaven!
Her name is Elizabeth...
If this is heaven,
is she an angel?
Oh, my heart aches!
Why is my heart beating so fast?!
This...
must be love!
I can see that romance is blooming!
Sanji-san!
Wait!
Oh no no!
Nami-san and Robin-chan are waiting for me!
No but...
I gotta say thank you to her!
I'm not the kind of guy
to forget his manners!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Forgive me for being unfaithful!
Elizabeth-chan! Oh?
This house has the same
design as this handkerchief.
Well then, maybe this is Elizabeth's...
Is Lady Elizabeth here?
My name is Sanji. You were
looking after me a while ago.
I came here to return your handkerchief...
Isn't that a bit cruel, Elizabeth-chan?!
No, don't rush it.
She's a shy, naive girl.
I got to be cool - have patience.
I'm really sorry about the
way I acted back there!
Your hand was so attractive
I couldn't help it!
Excuse me for being so forward but
may I make it up by cooking
something for you?
You can tell me whatever you want to eat!
I may not look it, but I'm a good chef!
Ah, this isn't working.
Do you like to cook?
Oh yes! I love cooking!
Then, do you like clothes?
Clothes?
Yes, yes, of course!
Unlike some stupid swordsmen,
I care about how I look!
Really? You like clothes?
Yes!
Then what about dresses?
Dresses?
I got it!
She keeps asking what I like because she...
Maybe she has a thing for me!
How's this dress? Do you like it?
I like dresses! I like them! I love them!
I'm really fond of it!
How about flower prints?
Flower prints! They're wonderful!
They are really cute!
All right...
Finally, the door to
Elizabeth-chan's heart has...
You have a good taste, Elizabeth-chan!
Don't be shy! You've already
opened up the door of your heart.
Sanji-san!
Now, don't be afraid and
just come into my arms!
Elizabeth-chan!
I think...
...this will look good on you!
Oh, ow, ow, ow...
Despite your appearance, you're
very strong, Elizabeth-chan!
I-Is this a dream? Then it must be...
...a nightmare!
I thought that you were one of us!
You were suffering, weren't you?
You don't have to pretend anymore!
Yes, this is a free country!
Now, put this dress on and open
up the door of your heart!
I-I-I don't wanna open anything!
Wait!
This island is known as
the second Maiden Island.
Everything is pink here.
All people and animals
who come to this island
have girlish hearts.
This can't be heaven!
Hey! Wait!
--Aren't you one of us?!
--You are one of us!
Shut up! Don't come after
me! I told you I'm not!
"Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan,"
"how are you both doing?"
"Right now, I'm..."
"I'm..."
--Wait!
Why don't you wait, man?!
Why should I? Stupid!
Welcome to Kamabakka Queendom!
"Right now, I'm..."
"...in hell!"
In a certain land where snow silently falls,
the people have been forced to
work day and night for 700 years.
What has Robin seen there?
Around the same time,
Usopp is about to be eaten
by mysterious plants!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Crew's Whereabouts
Bridging the Islands and Vicious Vegetation"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Crew's Whereabouts
Bridging the Islands and Vicious Vegetation