Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war
against the New Fishman Pirates,
who held a grudge against humans
and plotted to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom.
In the end, Luffy managed to defeat Hody,
the New Fishman Pirates' captain, in an intense fight.
Ultimately thwarting his plot. However...
Have it your way, instead of Fishman Island,
I'll have my vengeance against you all!
Monkey D. Luffy. I know your name now.
Come to the New World!
Sure, wait for me there.
There's some business I want to settle with you, too.
I can't leave it in your hands - that's too dangerous!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
...and make Fishman Island my territory!
You insolent brat!
Difficulties Ahead
A Trap Waiting in the New World
--Here you go. --Oh, thank you!
It's kelp tea - a special product of Fishman Island.
It aids in digestion so do your stomach a favor with it.
It's good! How thoughtful of you, Minister of the Right!
You are treating us most graciously - I hope we're not imposing!
No, no!
There are no words to express my thanks to you all, so...
We have to say goodbye to this island soon.
Do not mention saying goodbye, "Nose"pp-sama!
No, don't cry! I'm sorry!
And my name is Usopp.
Oh, where did Franky go?
He left to learn how to operate the ship.
Seems like he needs to learn a little trick to ascend.
So... this is the list of treasures that were stolen from the chamber.
There are so many! The Tamate Box, again...
Tamate Box?
In the vicinity of Candy Factory Town
Damn Straw Hat!
I can't believe he kicked me out!
But,
I have so much treasure in my belly.
I'm gonna buy, like, 100 pirate ships and kill the Straw Hats in the New World...
T-T-The treasure!
It's all gone!
I can't even buy a hard candy now!
Oh my treasure-chan!
Where is it?!
How is everything-jamon, Jinbe?
Are the members of the Sun Pirates doing well?
Yes. In fact, they have too much energy and they are a bit out of control.
But I cannot believe they accepted it.
Even I was surprised when I heard about it-jamon.
I had never expected the Sun Pirates becomes Big Mom's allies.
Is it going well?
I have to say that while she is not a reasonable person she lets us
do what we like.
Well, I was worried because it must be hard
for a man like you to work under somebody...
...other than Fisher Tiger.
You don't have to worry.
I don't mind working for someone.
Plus, in the New World,
the best you can do to protect your crew is
ally yourself with one of the Four Emperors.
Oh yeah? It seems to me like you
are doing it for the benefit of Fishman Island.
Even after Whitebeard's death,
this island remained safe under Big Mom's name because you
connected us to her.
No, it's just a coincidence.
We are supposed to protect the island
but we are wanted pirates so...
However, Your Majesty!
I am thinking about breaking away from Big Mom.
Oh, are you going to accept Luffy-kun's invitation?
Hey, Jinbe.
Join...
...my crew!
Yes. I've made up my mind.
But the pirates' world is all about obligation and honor.
Our contracts are made by exchanging cups of
sake and a verbal agreement - no documents.
So we have to be really determined when we terminate a contract.
My concern is that there is a chance
that Big Mom will turn her anger toward this island.
Boy... You do not have to feel responsible for everything-jamon, Jinbe.
If that is going to happen, so be it. I have a plan-jamon.
We just welcomed 70 thousand rowdy
fellows as new soldiers from the Fishman District today.
So do not worry about us-jamon.
And if we lose Big Mom's Jolly Roger as protection,
there is another one that I want to use!
A skull with a straw hat on-jamon.
I see! I like that Jolly Roger too!
King-sama!
W-W-We have a problem!
What is it, Minister of the Right? Why are you in such a rush?
I just remembered something serious!
Relating to giving all the treasures to Luffy-kun and the others.
If they find them, could you to tell them to return the Tamate Box!
What are you saying?!
I will not tell them to return something I already gave them!
But...
What?! It will explode if someone opens it?!
Why did you rig it with explosives?
Well...
After the contents of the Tamate Box were stolen 10 years ago,
I thought, in case another thief comes, we have to teach him a lesson.
So we set up a box-full of explosives to explode when someone opens it.
Since I am in charge of the treasure chamber and the Tamate Box...
All right. All right.
If Luffy-kun and the others come back with the treasures,
give them the reason and ask them to return it to us.
I am sorry.
But what if they open it before they get here...
That is my concern, too.
King-sama, Minister of the Right! Luffy-sama and the others just came back.
Oh, so they are okay?!
I am so relieved. I guess I was just worrying too much.
What?!
All the treasures?!
To Big Mom?!
You gave them away?!
She said she was gonna destroy the island if she couldn't get her sweets!
Can you believe how crazy she is?! I mean - if it were meat, I could understand!
But don't worry!
I really stood up to her!
You stood up to one of the Four Emperors?!
You talked back to Big Mom?!
Wow! You are so tough, Luffy-sama!
That's not the point!
"Nose"pp-sama is scary!
My name is Usopp!
Okay, I'm sorry!
Boy, that's not good.
I have to break away from Big Mom before it gets complicated.
You guys should not do anything to make Big Mom angrier!
We won't! We're all gonna get killed since she's one of the Four Emperors!
Hey, this is pretty bad, Minister of the Right!
I can't believe it!
If they gave the Tamate Box to Big Mom and if she opens it herself,
she will take it as Luffy-kun's challenge to her!
That is a big problem-jamon!
Well, he had no choice though.
What's done is done.
I guess it was a tit-for-tat situation so you couldn't help fighting with her.
You're right! No matter who she was, I'd...
Nami-san...
Why...
...did you give all the treasures away?!
That's what you're focused on?!
--I'll punch you! --You already did!
All right! Leff's go thew the New World!
We have no future ahead of us!
This is it! We're doomed!
Meanwhile, near the Candy Factory...
Dammit! Somebody took all the treasures before I knew it!
Who did this? I'm gonna kill him at any price!
With a mountain of treasures
and the secret of the Mermaid Princess as presents,
I know that person will like me!
Oh, a crowd!
Who are those two carrying heavy loads?
Straw Hat Luffy! How dare he challenge Mama!
Mama must be really mad-soir.
I wonder what's going to happen-vous plait.
The tea party is 4 days from now.
Let's stop by at some island and get something really sweet. Grr!
We have to ease her anger even if just a little bit.
I think that's the best we can do-soir.
Luckily, we have so many treasures-vous plait.
Those are my treasures! I'm sure!
Who the hell are they?! I will bury them alive!
I stole those treasures! Give them back to me!
--That's... --He looks familiar to me. Grr!
Oh, here he is!
His name is "Wet-Haired" Caribou. A rising rookie.
Oh, he's got a 200-million-berry bounty.
H-He's worth 200 million berries?
It's too late to beg for your life!
Swamp-Swamp...
...Gatling Gun!
I'll fill you with holes!
Mr. Pekoms!
What is that?!
A turtle?
You're a Devil Fruit user!
Of course I am!
But you're just Zoan type, aren't you?
Drop dead!
Logia Devil Fruit users who think they're invincible often die young.
Half-boiled challengers always disappoint me-soir.
Let's go home-bon, Pekoms. Mama is waiting.
He beat a guy with a 200 million bounty in a single blow!
As I recall, Mr. Pekoms has a 330-million-berry bounty.
Over 300 million?
That is how strong the pirate group led by the one of the Four Emperors can be?
Will Luffy-san and the others be okay?
We are totally heroes now!
There's the Sunny!
Franky's there!
Looks like he's ready to go!
Hey, Franky!
Here we go finally!
Meanwhile, on the sea near the Red Line in the New World...
An urgent report from the headquarters!
Several coated ships are emerging from the seafloor at high speed!
Everyone, man your posts now!
I repeat!-- Everyone, man your posts now!
That's...!
A-A pirate ship!
Fire!
Hurry up! There's one more at two o'clock!
Pirate ships are emerging one after another!
What's going on?
Don't try to gain her favor like that!
Shut up! Go away!
I just got freed from hell at last! I don't wanna die here!
Here comes a big one!
The captain is in danger!
I'm gonna embrace her to keep her safe!
Let me take that important task!
Hey!
Not again!
Nice! That's my Captain-chan!
What beautiful swordplay!
It's not just the swordplay that's beautiful!
You guys, be serious!
You all know how to ward off bombshells!
If you don't use that skill now, when are you gonna...
Captain, you're talking to a mast!
I cleaned your glasses!
Thank you.
She's so cute! She's like a flower in the filth of G-5!
I will die for you, Captain-chan!
Me too! Me too!
We're in a battle! Stop fooling around!
Otherwise, you'll get killed!
I'm sick of you G-5 guys!
5th Grand Line naval base, G-5 Captain Tashigi
I can't believe you guys are Navy soldiers!
Don't take me lightly just because I'm a woman!
We're not taking you lightly!
We're just falling for Captain Tashigi's cuteness...
There! You're taking me lightly!
You have to realize that you're Navy...
Shut up, Tashigi!
I'm interrogating someone here.
I'm sorry, sir!
I see.
So you all were captured by Hody Jones, a pirate from the seafloor.
That explains why
there was no rookie passing by Fishman Island for a month.
Captured? No, he enslaved us!
But when Hody and his clan started a civil war, a group of pirates defeated them
and freed us!
A group of pirates?
Yeah, but I'm not gonna tell you who they were!
Idiot! Just tell them!
They're not just Navy soldiers - they're the G-5!
They'd fish for sharks using a pirate as bait
or make a bonfire using pirates as kindling!
They're the Navy's craziest outlaws
who won't even obey orders from the headquarters!
You have no idea what they're gonna do to us!
And of all men, we were...
...caught by the infamous "Ashen Hunter" Smoker!
5th Grand Line naval base, G-5 Vice Admiral
"Ashen Hunter" Smoker
Vice Admiral Smoker! Can I take them?
No, don't!
I'll tell you! So help me!
The group of pirates who beat Hody and his clan was...
...the Straw Hats!
I know.
Fool!
With both excitement and uncertainty...
...the journey to the New World is finally underway.
The Straw Hats acquire a new Log Pose...
...and say their goodbyes to Shirahoshi and Jinbe.
To fulfill his promise to Shanks...
...Luffy finally sets off...
...on a new voyage.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Setting Sail at Last!
Farewell, Fishman Island"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Setting Sail at Last!
Farewell, Fishman Island