Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Broggy-san!
Now, then! Accelerate, Candle Service!
Turn these people into wax figures!
My hands won't move!
I don't wanna die this way!
Can't we do something?!
Hey, old man.
Whadya say we crush these guys together?
I'll fight alongside you and your fighting spirit!
Don't be stupid!
What can you possibly do?!
I'm gonna kick your asses, just so you know!
What?
These guys spoiled the old giant guys' duel!
Master Broggy!
We've taken on your frustration!
Usopp...
For now, could you bust this pillar for us, Luffy?
I leave the rest to you.
Alright, no problem!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Break the pillar, Luffy!
A Hex on Luffy!
Colors Trap
Zoro! What are you doing?!
If I'm gonna be solidified, I prefer this pose.
This is no time to be playing around!
I'm not playing.
Anyways, do something about your leg!
It's painful just looking at it!
Then quit looking at it.
You're the idiot who suggested
cutting our legs off in this situation
so we could escape!
That ain't true!
I was gonna cut 'em off so we could fight.
That's even stupider! Get serious!
Just shut up!
Honestly! You have no common sense!
We still haven't even escaped from this situation,
yet neither of them seems
to sense the danger at all...
Hey, runt.
Is that all the struggling you got?
Yeah.
Looks like it's someone else's turn now.
I see...
Mr. 3.
Those people don't seem concerned at all.
I could say the same about you,
Miss Golden Week!
Urgh!
Hey. If you're gonna do a pose,
now's your chance.
Don't put me on your level.
Mr. Bushido!
Please be more serious about this!
I'm always serious.
More like stupid.
– Like you're one to talk!
– It seems we're being mocked!
This is truly displeasing!
Ever since he showed up, they've been...
It couldn't be!
Alright!
He hardly seems to be that reliable of a man.
Mr. 3!
We'll finish him off.
Finish him off?
Don't be silly.
Just look!
He showed up here alive and well
because your attacks don't work.
At the very least, he's at a level
that's too much for you to handle.
You two can take care of the others!
I think I'll add Straw Hat Luffy
to my wax figure collection...
You guys are too damn annoying!
You've gone a bit too far!
Give yourselves up!
Small fry.
Let's do it!
Alright! Preparations are complete!
We got your back, Luffy!
Did you say something?
Now you're mine!
Candle Lock!
What is that?!
– Luffy-san!
– Damn. He's already gotten caught?!
Idiot!
What's this? It's heavy, like a mallet!
How simple.
Now for your hands!
Oh! This is perfect!
Candle Lock!
Whoa!
Old giant guy!
Sorry to bother you!
What?! What's he up to?!
Gum-Gum...
...Mallet!
He did it!
Yahoo!
Lucky! The mallet on my legs broke, too!
Huh? Huh?!
I'm alive...
We survived...
That didn't help things at all!
Whew, that was dangerous!
Why didn't you guys run?
We can't move! Isn't it obvious?!
Oh? Really?
But you guys told me to break the pillar!
Were you lying?
Is it really a good idea to put our
lives in his hands, Mr. Bushido?!
Don't look at me.
That's the only choice we got here.
Plus it looks like my arms are stuck now.
Please be serious about this!
Hold on... It feels like my body is hardening more and more now...
I can't move at all now...
Fools! With the candles closer,
your hardening has sped up!
Now you can become wax figures even quicker!
That guy thinks he can act
all smug and arrogant!
Hey! You guys are gonna be wax figures?
That's what we've been trying to tell you!
Just destroy this set, Luffy-san!
R-Right! Okay!
I told you, I won't let you interfere!
Wax-Wax Arts! Harpoon!
Exploding Star!
That was rather bland.
You don't use very good gunpowder.
He ate the Exploding Star!
This is bad. It really is fast.
– Good thing I posed beforehand.
– You idiot!
Luffy-san! Please, hurry!
Alright!
That pumpkin's the bad thing, right?!
Hang on! Gum-Gum...
It's no use!
Candle Wall!
...Bazooka!
Hey, you! Don't get in my way!
That would be my line.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't
interfere with my creative activities.
Candle Lock!
I got a mallet!
Gum-Gum...
Oh no! Candle Wall!
...Mallet!
Hurray! Hurray!
– Mr. 3...
– Impossible!
Luffy!
Hurry and break this set while there's still time!
– No.
– Quit joking around and hurry!
No.
This is no time to be acting stupid!
Luffy-san! Please!
What should I do?
I don't feel like saving you guys.
What are you saying?
Colors Trap.
Hey! Luffy!
There's no time!
Do something about this thing already!
Yeah... I know.
– Then hurry!
– Yeah, Luffy!
I know, but...
But I don't feel like saving you...
Why do you keep saying that?!
We're the ones who're about to be wax figures!
Understand?! We're about to die!
Yeah. But for some reason,
I just can't get motivated.
This isn't a motivation problem!
D-Dammit! What's happened to him?!
Our friends're gonna die if he doesn't hurry!
I'll bring him back to his senses!
Let's go, Karoo!
W-When did you...?!
Give it up.
He's already fallen into a trap.
That's right. See where he's standing?
Where he's standing?
Let's see here...
What's that?
There's a strange black pattern...
What's so important about that?!
You're right. It's nothing. It's just paint.
Paint?
In other words, both you and them are goners!
Karoo! Let's just run for now!
He's planning to escape on the bird!
Let's get 'em.
Sprint at full speed!
Hey, you! Wait!
I haven't gotten on yet! Karoo!
Hey! Alright! Stop! Let me get on!
What's the point in being scared of me?!
Miss Golden Week!
This is your doing!
Colors Trap: Betrayal Black.
Touch the black paint,
and you'll want to betray your friends,
no matter what they say.
What does she mean?!
What happened?! Explain!
She's a "realist painter" who can
even create real colors of emotion!
Eh?!
Her refined sense of color
can manipulate people's minds
through the use of her paints.
Manipulate?! That's not good!
That simpleminded idiot is already easy enough to manipulate!
Then doesn't he just need
to get away from that paint?
Luffy! Get away from there!
No, don't!
Luffy-san! Whatever you do,
do not move from that black circle!
I'm begging you!
Vivi! Why?!
We don't want you to save us at all!
No.
I get it.
You made him do the exact
opposite of what you said...
Huh?
I-I was kind of weird just now!
Luffy-san! Hurry!
Alright! I'll save you right now!
But never mind you guys!
I just wanna laugh!
– Why?!
– Why, you...!
Now what?!
Colors Trap: Laughter Yellow.
You know you're not supposed to move.
Now it's on his clothes!
Luffy! Hurry and take off that clothing!
N-Never mind that!
I just feel like laughing!
Not good!
If it keeps raining down at this pace,
we won't last one more minute!
Did you guys come here to play?!
Look! When Usopp ran into him,
the paint on his back smudged!
Did I wind up doing something again?
Hey, you! Knock it off, you jerk!
Was Laughter Yellow funny?
Shut up! Are you stupid?! Stupid!
Anyways, I gotta break that pumpkin!
Gum-Gum...
Colors Trap: Bullfight Red.
...Bazooka!
Where are you aiming?!
You're not allowed to break it!
You'll make Mr. 3 angry!
What is this?!
Just as bulls rush at red capes,
you feel the urge to attack
that Bullfight Red mark.
Too bad.
I can't stand you anymore!
Get out of here!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
Having fun?
It's no good.
This isn't his kind of fight.
All his power is useless!
Now to finish it with this!
I'll mix the Laughter Yellow on
your back with Sadness Blue...
Colors Trap: Tranquil Green!
Such nice tea...
You idiot!
So... What happens now?
See? I told you you should've posed!
Too bad for you!
How can you still be so calm about this?!
Damn, they run away fast!
Nose Fancy Double Cannon!
You missed! Way to go, Karoo!
My turn! Special Attack: Lead Star!
We gotta go back to Luffy and the others again!
We're getting nowhere, chasing them all around.
Yeah.
I didn't want to use it on such small fries,
but there's no dodging this.
A .44-caliber, six-shot flintlock revolver.
A new South Blue model.
It can fire continuously,
and if I use it, the bullets are invisible.
Luffy's acting that way because of
that paint the bad guys mentioned!
They're related somehow!
There was also some on his back
when I crashed into him earlier!
No doubt about it!
If I can just do something about the paint...!
Hurry!
Ahh. Such nice tea...
Such nice...
Luffy! What are you doing?!
Such... nice... tea...
What are you doing, you idiot?!
sekai wa yake ni hirokute
The world is awfully big
doko ka ni takara ga atte mo
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
tenmongakuteki kakuritsu
the odds are astronomical
guuzen ni tayotteita tte hajimaranai
So relying on dumb luck won't get you anywhere
dakara
So even...
dare ni tomerareta tte
...if someone stops me
kage de warawareta tte
or laughs at me from the shadows
fune wa mae e susumu yo
the ship will continue forward
Bon voyage!
hottoite yo
Forget about them!
baka wa shouchi no suke da yo ikanya nara hyoue
I know I'm a fool, but I gotta go
muri na yume hodo kaccho ii yabou
The crazier the dream, the cooler the ambition
baka wa shouchi no suke da yo tatakau zou
I know I'm a fool, but I'm gonna fight
tooi umi hodo kitto ii tengoku
The farther the sea, the more heavenly it surely is
yarudake yareba donna suiheisen mo
Do everything you can, and you'll get
chotto chikazuku
a little nearer to any horizon
Luffy! They've only just hardened!
There's still time to save them!
– Really?!
– We're gonna save you now, guys!
I'm counting on you, Karoo! Run around!
I refuse to let anyone else die!
– It'll be hot, but endure it!
– Wake up, everyone!
It's damn strange.
Why hasn't anyone come back?
Next time, on One Piece:
Time to Fight Back!
Usopp's Quick Thinking and Fire Star!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Time to Fight Back!
Usopp's Quick Thinking and Fire Star!