A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
How is it from the sky, Pell?!
I searched every corner of the rooftops
of the buildings near the Square,
but I saw no preparations for the cannon anywhere.
Then... it might be from
somewhere inside a building...
I'll search all of them!
Okay!
I don't feel any anger against you...
You know why, Nico Robin?
How silly... We were a team for four years.
I knew you'd pull something like this.
Water?!
If you get wet, a knife can stick in you, right?!
He dodged it! Where'd he...
I'll forgive you for everything, Nico Robin...
...because I've never... trusted anyone...
from the beginning.
That's right... That place can...
Special Attack... Red Serpent Star!
The Nightmare Draws Near!
This is the Sand Sand
Clan's Secret Base
Crocodile!!
Where are you?!
What's with this place?
It's falling apart!
There's no mistake!
The cannoneer must be in there!
I finally figured it out!
Is he really in such a place, Vivi?!
If this dust devil is part of the plan...
...it should be a place where
they can still hit the target...
And it also has to be an open space
where a large cannon can fit
and yet can't be seen from the sky.
Look!
This place is unexpectedly large, isn't it?
Why don't we make this place our secret base?
Yeah!
There's nowhere else I can think of!
Okay! Hold on! Everyone's headed here.
So we'll leave a message...
I'm gonna go on ahead, Usopp-san!
What?! W-Wait, Vivi! W-Wait!
Hurry!
Ah, okay.
All right! The princess! We found her!
She led us right to her!
There're still some members of Baroque Works...!
Urk! We signaled the enemy, too!
That's Usopp's signal.
But why is the palace that far?
Good, it's close!
I wonder if they found the cannoneer.
They must have! Hurry!
Usopp...! Noise...!
So this is... this is the...
Now! Let's go, Vivi!
Okay!
Th-They ran away!
Stop!
It took so long... to make it this far...
But the end... has finally come...
This land is mine!
You...!
I've cornered you, gator!
Why are you alive?
No matter how many times I kill you,
why do you stand up to me?!
Well?! Straw Hat!
How... did he survive and come here...?
Who on earth is he...?
Straw Hat...
Just how many times do you want to be killed?
You still haven't returned...
what you took away...
What I took away...?
Is it money...? Fame...?
Trust...?
Lives...?
Rain...?!
What do you want me to return?
There're so many things that I took away.
The country!
The country? You say funny things...
I'm just about to take this country...
by becoming its king.
When we got to this island,
it was already gone.
Her country was gone...!
I'm going to persuade the Rebel Army
because I want no more shedding of blood!
Up until just recently, it was
a thriving city full of greenery!
Please, Vivi-chan! Stop those fools!
If this is really her country...
What's wrong... with not wanting people to die?!
Just one look at this kingdom and even I can tell...
...what most needs to be done!
As if putting your single life on the line is enough!
I don't have...!
I don't have anything else
that I can put on the line...
At least try putting all of our
lives on the line together!
Aren't we friends?!
If this is really her country...
she should be... smiling more!
Even if you talk cool, when you don't
have water with you, what can you...
This can't be... Kicking me without water...
If only you hadn't come to this country...
Alabasta would've remained peaceful!
Isn't it just heartrending?
Love for the kingdom will be
what destroys the kingdom.
Crocodile!
Wai...
Could it be... you're using...
...your blood...?!
Sand can be hardened by blood, too, can't it?
From Rainbase... to the palace...
and to the underground mortuary temple...
I'll reward you for your
persistence in challenging me,
even after living through hell twice...
You bastard...!
...as a pirate...
It seems that you want to
beat me up no matter what.
And I'll also admit that you're
an annoying enemy to me.
It came off! What the...
It's a poisonous hook.
I see...
As a competent enough pirate,
you seem to understand
that a duel between pirates
is always a fight for survival,
and that there's no such thing as "playing dirty."
When the explosion happens up there,
this place will probably
collapse in one breath as well.
This is the last time.
Let's settle it once and for all!
The smoke was in that direction, right?
No, was it this way?
What?! Marines?!
Look! It's Roronoa Zoro!
Dammit! I didn't realize that the Navy showed up in this town...
When I don't have time...
I guess I can't help it.
I'll settle this in three seconds.
You...! Why are you in a place like this?!
What the heck are you doing?!
That's what I'd say!
Roronoa Zoro!
We knew you weren't good with directions,
but this is worse than we expected!
Go back! If you go north at the last corner,
you can get to the Square!
Go back and turn right! Not this way!
Are you stupid?!
Stupid?!
Hurry up!
Go!
Wh-What?! What's going on?!
Run! Run, Vivi!
Usopp-san! I can't...
Wait! Hold it!
Th-Tha... Thank...
We'll assist you!
Please stop the explosion of the Square.
Now, hurry!
Thank you! Hurry, Usopp-san!
Ah... Yeah!
All units! Continue to assist them...!
With all your strength!
Yes, ma'am!
Me, go to Alubarna?
We're chasing after the Straw Hat pirates, right?
Or...
You decide what to do when you're there.
You just follow your sense of justice.
Whatever happens, I'll accept responsibility.
Hurry! Hurry!
We wasted quite a bit of time!
I don't know why they did,
but if the Navy hadn't helped,
it would've been worse!
Idiot! Don't look aside!
If the attack isn't stopped,
the casualties will be a lot worse!
Right!
The attack can't be stopped by praying!
In two minutes, are we gonna
be winners or dead bodies...?
We still have a minute and a half!
Yes!
You've got us all!
There they are! Vivi! Usopp!
Nami-san! Tony-kun!
What's going on?! The Navy helped us!
Did you find the cannoneer?!
We haven't confirmed it yet,
but there's no mistake!
I must've looked at it many times,
but it was my blind spot.
The cannoneer is over there without a doubt!
What?
What?!
The clock tower...
I see! From that place, he can
get a good shot at the Square!
If only Pell would get here,
we could stop the attack.
Pell...!
We don't have time.
If I'm not mistaken, the smoke rose around here, but...
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit... Hey, listen.
I just shot down a big bird using this ribbit-ribbit gun.
My blunder...
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Who in the world is he...?
Crocodile treated even our kingdom's
proud warriors like worms, and yet...
You were skewered...
buried alive... and dried up...
Even you, who stood back up after all that...
...won't be able to survive this.
Game over...
The poison will pass into your system soon.
You don't understand anything!
I wonder what happened...
I don't see Pell anywhere...
Say, Vivi. We can't go up that high
within a minute all by ourselves!
Pell! Where are you?! Hurry!
In any case, we should hurry up, too!
We have no choice but to use the stairs!
– Where's the entrance?
– Hey!
Hm?!
Nami-san! Vivi-chan!
Why are you up there?!
Why? You left a message
under the smoke, didn't you?!
It said "clock tower."
That's why I came up here.
What should I do? Where's the cannoneer?
He's at the top! Top!
Go up from there and beat him up!
Hm? Hm?!
Hey, I looked all over for you guys!
Zoro! You too?!
What're you doing there?
That's what I'd like to say!
Well, Navy guys kept saying,
"go north," "go north,"
so I came up here for now...
"North" and "up" are totally different, you know!
But in any case, good job!
Go up from there and destroy the clock tower!
No!
What?
They can't go inside the
clock tower from where they are.
Other than entering from the sky,
the only way up
is the stairs in the back on the first floor.
But Zoro can destroy the tower wall and...
We don't know if the cannonball
can bear that kind of shock!
We have no choice but to
go up the stairs after all!
Wait, Vivi!
What?
I've got a good idea!
Ribbit... ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
Hey listen, Mr. 7. I know that this is
our last mission. Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
That's the plan.
According to the plan, we have 30 seconds left.
What's that?!
Mr. 7! Miss Father's Day!
Doko ni mukatte hashireba
Which direction should I run towards
Motto suteki na ashita ni aeru?
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
Kaji o totte mune ni shimatta
I took the helm and opened the
Kiseki no chizu o hirogeta
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
Sora o mezashite yume o sagashite
I aimed for the sky and sought out my dreams,
Michi ni mayotta toki mo aru
though at times I got lost
Yume ja nakute kimi to deatte
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
Suteki na jibun o mitsuketa
I discovered the wonderful person in me
Chiisana yuuki kara
With just a bit of courage,
ookina mono te ni shita
I gained something grand
"Negai" o ima koso "chikai" ni kaete
Now's the time for my "wish" to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Mirai no monogatari o egakou
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
Atarashii kaze ni subete no omoi nosete ima...
I'll put all my feelings in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
Doko made mo oikakete Shining ray
I'll chase after you wherever you go, Shining ray
Looks like more weirdoes showed up.
So if we take them down,
the attack will be stopped, right?
Hey, Nami. What're you gonna do by stacking us up like this?
Just shut up and do what I say!
We've only got 20 seconds!
Sink or swim... But we have no choice...
We'll put it all on the line
in the time we have left!
Next time, on One Piece:
Magnificent Wings!
My Name is Pell, Guardian Deity of the Country
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Magnificent Wings!
My Name is Pell,
Guardian Deity of the Country