Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil
and Zoro, Usopp and Brook got caught by Hody at the Ryugu Palace.
I'm gonna go to the Ryugu Palace to save my crew and kick that Hody guy's ass!
I said "Don't do it"!
"Something Has Happened to Hody! The True Power of the Evil Drug!"
It's time for the decisive battle!
Well, as soon as we cut the King's head off, the morale of his army will be shattered
and then it's over!
Which means we'll have a new king soon!
I can't wait!
Meanwhile, at Candy Factory Town in the center of the island...
CANDY FACTORY
Daruma-san, w-what are you...?
--He's chewing the wall of the factory... --W-What powerful jaws!
My fangs itch!
You fools!
I don't want some trendy cappuccino and cake for my happy snack time!
Do I look like a yuppie?!
I-I'm sorry, Daruma-san!
Do you want me to bite your flesh off?!
My favorite snack is the bones of big fish! And don't ever forget it!
Y-Yes, I'll be careful from now on!
That's okay. I'm gonna go chew up the royal family and their soldiers now!
See you at Conchcorde Plaza!
We all have to be there! Don't be late!
What should we do about the citizens?
Weren't you listening to what Boss said?
He said "No more stepping on her picture."
Leave them alone! They know what's waiting for them!
The New Fishman Pirates have...
...4 shark Fishman officers including Hody,
and 1 giant squid Fishman.
Plus, they have a blue-ringed octopus Merman as a bodyguard,
who is the best swordsman on the island.
Our only hope is the Neptune brothers.
I believe in the Princes!
Kotsun...
At Waterwheel Town in the north of the island...
WATERWHEEL TOWN
--The Princes are heading to Conchcorde Plaza! --What's gonna happen to this country?
I don't know. All we wanted was friendly relations with humans.
Why should our lives be threatened?
I can't believe they're gonna execute the King.
Can't we stop them by taking these guys as hostages?
Hostages?
No, that's not gonna work. Boss Hody is a ruthless man-kotsun.
Even if you try it, he'll just cut us off and go on as planned-kotsun.
This is not good. Because he got beaten by the Princes,
Dosun-san's power level went down to "kotsun."
He needs the Energy Steroid.
All right.
He's always been like that-kotsun.
He has too much pride-potsun.
"Potsun"?
He doesn't like Fishmen who do business with human pirates-posun.
"Posun"?
Those Fishmen who transfused blood to wounded humans,
he punished them by attacking them in the dark-tosun.
"Tosun"?
Humans' blood is tainted-tosun.
Both giving them blood and getting their blood...
...degrades our Fishman blood-dosun!
He's back to "dosun"!
Those Fishmen who support the horrible humans are...
...getting in the way of...
Be quiet!
...Our noble intentions-dokan!
He exceeded "dosun"!
He broke the chain!
You bastard!
The soldiers got blown away!
Damn Fukaboshi! I'll get even with you-bokan!
I'll beat you to within an inch of your life next time-zugan!
Let's go, guys-bagon!
To Conchcorde Plaza, the execution ground-gaban!
In front of the Fishman Cultural Hall in the south of the island...
FISHMAN CULTURAL HALL
Who did you say is drunk?
You are, Hyouzou-san!
Get yourself back together! You can't fight like that!
No worries, no worries! This is my treat!
What are you talking about?!
We have to fight Neptune's army which is being led by Fukaboshi now!
In the worst-case scenario, the infamous Jinbe will be there too!
Hey! Stand on your feet!
It's no good. He's as slippery as a sea cucumber.
I can't believe how many degrees your head can spin around.
It's not spinning! You're too drunk!
Boy! I bet you can't even hold your sword!
No, I can!
Hey, stay away from him!
Hyouzou will slice into anyone when he gets drunk!
He will... slice?
He sliced his friend!
That wasn't enough!
I wanna cut more!
H-Hyouzou-san!
Go to the plaza now and slice up the Neptunes to your heart's content!
Oiaiyonohoniaiu!
What are you talking about?!
At the Marine Shopping Mall in the east of the island...
MARINE SHOPPING MALL
We're former soldiers of Neptune's army! We won't let you do whatever you want!
What?! He disappeared!
What the...
Take this!
He disappeared again! How can he do that?!
What can you civilians do now? Nothing!
Zeo-san can change his skin color like a chameleon and camouflage himself!
It's even hard for us to figure out where he is!
I-It's impossible for us to beat a guy like that!
Your only hope is...
...the Neptune brothers.
But they'll die soon just like the others.
Which means you folk have...
Oh, a bug!
Kill it!
What happened? He stopped talking.
Is the cockroach dead?
Yeah, it's flattened.
Wh-Which means you folk have nowhere to run.
There's nowhere to run!
He kept his nobility! He's not known as the Noble of the Fishman District for nothing!
Is he pretending as if nothing happened?
It's like a revolution.
Later today, at Conchcorde Plaza,
the Neptune family will die and the new king will rise.
Now, let's go to the plaza!
Captain Hody! Wh-What's the matter?!
--It's nothing. --But...
Hey, bring it to me now! As much as we have!
It? No way!
You better not take more Energy Steroid!
That's too much!
Do you want your head to get smashed?! Just shut up!
Captain! We got King Neptune already!
Victory is within our grasp! So you don't have to do that!
He's right! Don't push yourself too hard!
I'm running out of time! I said "Get out of my way"!
I won't! I said "Leave it up to me"!
Why can't you understand even after I've explained it?!
Shut up!
I don't give a damn about the history between Fishmen and humans
when my friends are in danger!
That is why! That is why I want you to wait!
They both wanna help the country and their friends.
Why do they have to fight?!
How long will it take to Conchcorde Plaza?
"WATERWHEEL TOWN" TO "CONCHCORDE PLAZA"
Less than an hour!
It's not the actions of a sane man to go through the trouble of
executing the King at the plaza!
I think they just wanna lure you Princes out!
I don't care!
I am looking forward to it, rather. I won't let them hurt my father!
And I won't let our people's minds close again, not after they were just opening up!
Now I know why Jinbe always had his eyes on Hody!
And they are the reason we haven't seen human pirates around the island these days!
I wonder if Shirahoshi is still in the Hard Shell Tower.
I can't help worrying because we don't hear anything about her-fa-so-la-ti-do!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama, what do you think about the Straw Hats?
Madame Sharley said they will destroy this country.
They did not seem like they had bad intent.
That's what I thought.
Straw Hat is Jinbe's friend and the Mermaids at the cove didn't speak badly of them.
Those Mermaids sure have an eye for people!
But this is not the time to think about those things!
Yeah, that's right-la-ti-do!
Summon all soldiers from all over the country! We will save the King at any cost!
Yes, sir!
Much!
At Fishverly Hills in the northeast of the island...
FISHVERLY HILLS
Damn!
I can't believe that we are still struggling against just one sea monster!
There is something not right with this sea monster!
You damn fools, it serves you right! Good job, Sea Bear!
The Energy Steroid worked too well!
C-Calm down, Sea Bear! That's enough!
Those soldiers are barely alive. So it's over, Sea Bear!
Use this! Sea monsters don't like fire.
Stop!
Much?
Ikaros-san's body is contorting!
Is it some kind of curse?
Put out the fire-ch, you fool!
Oh, crackle, crackle...
Fire? What about the fire?
I'm gonna become a piece of dried squid-ch!
No way, fool!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I know you were trying to roast me and eat me with sake. I'll kill you-ch!
Who would do that, fool?!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Ikaros-san once had a best friend who was a giant squid.
One day, he went too close to the sun and became a giant dried squid!
That's why when Ikaros-san sees fire, he...
Daidalos!
He's a Fishman. He's not gonna be like his friend.
Daida...
Be careful hereafter-ch!
Oh no!
That Dried Squid Spear is always waiting for its chance to turn back into a normal squid.
So once it gets stuck in someone, it'll suck all fluid out of his body!
Ika!
Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika...
That's awful! He's pummeling that guy who got dried out!
Ikaros-san, that's enough!
Don't we have to go to the plaza already?!
Much! You're right!
It's too late. He already became a dried squid.
Minister of the Right! Look up!
Is that Hody and the others?
I don't see Hody but I see some men from the Fishman District!
They're heading to the plaza!
Damn, those bastards!
Look! The King-sama is on board!
King Neptune-sama!
Help us!
Great Knight, perform a miracle to save us!
Don't call me Great Knight.
I can't save my citizens--look at me!
How pathetic!
King-sama!
We are the King's army but we can't even protect the King?!
Then, what are we here for?!
Ikaros-san! There are only 2 hours left until the execution!
Come with us to Conchcorde Plaza!
What happened to Captain Hody-ch?! I know he's there-ch!
Why doesn't he even come out-ch?! Much!
Well...
That drug enhances your strength but takes years off your life.
You shouldn't take it in the first place-jamon.
Shut up!
Captain Hody said he got cut by the pirate swordsman and it hurts!
Cut? The Boss got cut?!
So he kept taking the Energy Steroid to kill the pain!
And he ended up... I mean, we told him to stop!
Captain Hody!
I can't... breathe!
My body is gonna explode!
Much! Is it a side-effect-ch?! So that drug could kill you as I thought-ch!
Th-That's...!
Hey, what's wrong, Sea Bear?!
He's acting strange!
Although all these sea monsters are under Captain Hody's control,
I've never seen them get so scared!
--C-Captain Hody?! --Are you all right?!
Why shouldn't I be all right?
Captain Hody!
Oh, I see some soldiers from the army!
Water Shot!
Facing the destructive power of Hody's new form,
Neptune's army is defeated.
The citizens have only one hope remaining...
The three Neptune brothers!
They rise to face Hody, and their battle begins!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Battle is on! At Conchcorde Plaza!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!