Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has landed on Marineford
to save his brother, Ace, from execution.
At last, in their effort to reach the execution platform,
Luffy and the Whitebeards have breached the barricades.
As an all-out battle between the Navy
and Whitebeards rages at Oris Plaza,
Luffy charges toward Ace.
Damn!
Even you can't win out against
the onslaught of time, Whitebeard!
That's what I was afraid of the most!
If you have an unguarded moment,
you will lose the fight!
Marco!
You can't look away like that!
Should I be the last voice you hear before you die?
Pops!
If I'd be able to do all I could...
I'd be happy to die!
Let me fight, Iva-chan!
If I can't fight now
and if I can't rescue Ace, I...
I'd rather take my own life afterwards!!
Let me have the strength to fight for now!
All right!
Do whatever you want!
Luffy!
Ace!!
To Live Up to a Promise!!
Luffy and Koby Collide!
So slow! What's taking them so long?!
I'm sorry for being late!
I brought two executioners as replacements!
Finally! Hurry and get ready!
Yes, sir!
Straw-boy, once again,
you better keep in mind that the next time you drop, you won't be able to bounce back!
The Energy Hormone is just fooling your body!
It isn't repairing any of the damage!
I...
I won't fall again!
What?! Another foolhardy statement!
Look at them!
Wait!
They're trying to execute Ace again!
Oh, well, my words can't change
Straw-boy's mind under these circumstances!
All Vi can do is keep them from beating him!
Straw Hat?!
Straw Hat is coming!
Kill Straw Hat!
Leave it to me!
I'm gonna finish him!
It's not over! I won't let you pass through here!
If you wanna advance...
...You gotta beat all of us!
We'll show you the spirit of the Navy!
Heads up!
Death Wink!
Ten points! Vi'll back you up!
Thanks, Iva-chan!
Luffy-san...
You're...
Koby!
That day...
I've decided to become Pirate King,
so if I die fighting for that,
that's fine with me!
Do you suppose I can do it, too? If I'm prepared to die for it?
Do what?
Do you think... even I could join the Navy?
Navy?
Yes! Catching bad guys is my dream!
It's been my dream ever since I was little!
If I hadn't met Luffy-san,
I couldn't have become what I am now.
That's right! In order to live as a Navy soldier,
I have to fight to change myself!
Because this is a battlefield!
I have to commit myself towards killing him!
Gum-Gum...
Shave!
I'll become a Navy...
...ad...
...admiral someday!
Whoa! Oh, I mean...
I-I-I'm sorry! I got carried away!
It's embarrassing! I wanna crawl in a hole!
After I met you, I became emboldened a little bit...
Koby!
You wanna fight me, right?
Then, of course you have
to become such a heavy hitter!
Do you think I can become an admiral?
Next time we see each other, we'll be much stronger!
And much greater!
Why?
They know that it's just a wild dream
that makes me lightheaded at just the thought of it.
Then how can they believe in it?
...Bullet!
He's as strong as I thought!
It's useless. I have to become much much stronger...
Hey, Koby!
Damn!
What is it this time?!
You guys are...
the Kuma impostors!
Monkey D. Luffy.
Oh no! What a pain in the ass!
Hey you, watch out!
Boa Hancock. The Seven Warlords.
Abort attack. Friendly operative.
That's right! You guys are on the same side!
Thank you, Hancock!
She's the Empress, right?
How do you know her?
Luffy! He called my name again...
Thank you, Hancock.
Every time he calls me like that, I'm so...!
Hancock.
Yes.
Hancock!
Yes!
Hancock.
Move aside, Boa Hancock.
I don't want you to call my name!
Magma brat!
P-Pops...
I-I'm on my way!
You are off guard!
Take a couple more of these and get yourself a good rest!
Pops!
Things don't always go the way you want!
Of course, Marco the Phoenix regenerates!
Hey! It's your turn now!
Sea Prism Stone?!
Commander Marco!
It looks painful!
Commander Jozu has been beaten, too!
They even beat our commanders one by one...
They're falling apart! The Whitebeard Pirates!
Old chap!
You Fishman monster!
Grr! Let me go!
Now move it!
Everyone, beat Whitebeard!
Pops!
"Justice"
Stay away!
They think that they can beat me...
...this easily!
I don't need any help because I'm...
I'm...
I'm Whitebeard!
H-He's a monster!
Don't hesitate! He's wounded!
Everybody, follow me!
Yes, sir!
Did he call me wounded?
That's ridiculous! I won't die from such a small wound!
I won't die from... such a small...!
I know...
...what will happen...
...if I die!
Then, you know,
I can't allow myself to die until...
...I see a bright future ahead for my sons!
Right, Ace?
Pops!
You dotard!
What is it?!
W-What are they doing?!
Guarding the back of Whitebeard?!
Are they willing to die with Whitebeard?!
You guys don't have to understand!
We'll defend Pops' glory!
That's too thoughtful, you fools!
Pops...
Captain Squard, let's go and fight with Pops, too!
Captain? Where are you going?
Don't come with me.
I'll pay the price in my own way.
If you wanna see the future,
I'll show you now, Whitebeard!
Do it!
Ace!
It's no use!
Do you think that I can't stop you for doing it?!
See it for yourself, Whitebeard!
Don't do it!
Don't do it!!
I'm on my way!
Hey, was that...?!
Conqueror's... Haki!
Hey, come on! For real?!
That was surprising!
That brat...
Luffy unconsciously used Conqueror's Haki
and stopped Ace's execution.
But the Navy, wary of his display of latent power,
combine their efforts
in an attempt to eliminate him.
Just then, Iva-san finally reveals his last trump card!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Scaffold at Last!
The Way to Ace Has Opened!!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Scaffold at Last!
The Way to Ace Has Opened!!