Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the Paramount War against the Navy,
Luffy was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
Sabo who became brother to Luffy and Ace...
...has been brought home by
his father, a member of the nobility.
I'll do as you say. I'll
live as you want so...
...please don't hurt these two!
I'm begging you. They're very important
to me, they're my brothers.
We all have to keep quiet about the plan!
What if someone outside the
town finds out about it?
We're special! If you're
from a noble family...
Run! Ace! Luffy!
The Fire's Been Set
Gray Terminal in Crisis
Wait! Stop!
Of course, I know. What about it?
They're setting boxes of oil and explosives all over Gray Terminal.
A-Are you alright?
Outta my way!
I-I have to tell them!
Hey you! Watch out! You have to be careful.
Ouch!
--We got him!
--Hey, relax!
Ace! Luffy!
Huh? Burn down Gray Terminal?! Why are you doing that?!
You fool! Don't scream! We can't
let anyone else know about this!
This is serious! I gotta tell everybody!
He's a bad guy just as I thought!
I told you to not to scream.
Hey, hold them down.
I'm not the mastermind.
There was oil and explosives in the boxes
that you guys carried yesterday and today.
And there's gonna be a massive
fire that no one can escape from.
--No...
--Are you out of your mind?
Even punk kids like you two are freaking out?
But now you know about the plan.
We can't let you go.
I want to ask you something before the fire.
Say, you two, do you have a
treasure hidden away somewhere?
Get in here!
You've given me nothing but
trouble! You're such a bad son!
I was right to adopt another
child just as I thought.
Open up, dad! I gotta go!
There are people that I have
to help! Dad! Dad! Open Up!
I...!
Edge Town
Shut up!
H-Hey! Look at that!
Something's wrong with Gray Terminal.
Isn't it burning?
This is the best game I've ever played!
B-B-Boss! Boss! You gotta see this!
What are you screaming about?
--The sky in the north, look!
--Is it the town?!
No, closer than that!
Must be Gray Terminal! It's on fire!
Midtown
What's going on? It's like a wildfire!
It's never happened before!
It's dangerous - evacuate Edge Town!
Edge Town, Great Gate
All residents must head to Midtown!
Leave the lifesaving and fire
extinguishing to us military!
--We made it to the Great Gate!
--We're safe now!
Wh-What are you doing?!
We only protect the residents here!
--No way!
--How can you do this?!
--Let us get in!
--Help us, please!
--Everybody, wake up!
--You gotta run!
--The fire is spreading all around!
--We can't stay here!
It's no use, give it up!
You gotta flee your home!
Oh! The fire has gotten to the shore already!
The entrance to the forest is ablaze, too!
Damn! Where should we go?! We're stuck!
Burn everything, guys!
When we complete this task,
my long-cherished dream will come true!
You're right.
We don't give a damn
about the other people living here.
But even if this place is so crappy,
it's good enough for us to hide in, King.
I'm aware of that, Bluejam.
But when this is over, you
no longer need to hide.
I will make you and your friends
nobles by my authority.
Will you really?!
The king will give us titles
and we'll live in the High
Town as privileged nobles!
We better get moving.
Let's get to the Great Gate!
The military is waiting.
Captain, we left the brats in the hideout...
Forget 'em. They could've joined my crew
if they told me where the treasure was.
Fools can't live long anyway.
But it's closed, Captain!
Don't panic. They just don't
want other people to get away.
The plan is for me to give them a sign,
then they'll open the gate.
It's me, Bluejam. Open up.
Hey! Don't you hear me?!
Is this...
Captain, could it be...
Hey, you guys, what are
you doing?! Open the gate!
The plan was you let us
evacuate from here, right?!
This is not what we agreed to! You bastards!
What happened to your promise, King?!
You said that you'd make us nobles...
You set us up? King!
Dammit!
Did you hear?
Bluejam, a pirate in Gray Terminal, started the fire.
That's what I thought!
No one else would do that.
He did it to try to keep the observers
from the World Government away.
How terrible he is!
It's hot! It's hot!
Yes!
Damn! We didn't wanna be involved in this!
We can't get away! I don't wanna die!
I'll leave you behind if
you don't stop complaining!
It's not hot.
Whoa, it's hot! No, it's not.
The fire is everywhere outside!
I can't breathe.
Yes, I can!
The air is hot!
No, it's not.
It's gonna be alright! I'm here with you!
Call the police! Sabo did it again!
Hello? Hello?!
What are you doing?! You have to evacuate!
Open the gate!
What are you talking about?!
You brat!
Take him away!
Ace! Luffy!
Run!
Stay away! Stay away from the lock!
No!
Ace!
Luffy!
--Be a good kid and evacuate!
--Don't give us any trouble!
A-Ace... Luffy...
What happened to you, boy?
O-Old man...
The royalty and nobles
are... behind the fire...
Believe me...
This town smells worse than Gray Terminal.
It smells like rotten people!
If I stay here... I'll never be free!
I'm...
...ashamed of being born a noble!
They finally made a kid
say this! Goa Kingdom!
I know how you feel. I was
born in this country, too.
But I still don't have enough
power to change the country.
Old man, you really are
listening to me, aren't you?
Yes, and I'll never forget.
Run, Luffy!
No... No way!
I can't believe it!
Captain, there's no chance!
There's no way to put out the fire!
We gotta give up the ship!
We can't flee to the sea!
Damn the King! How could he do this to us?!
I'll show that bastard!
Honestly!
It's so annoying that the sky
in the south is bright even in the night.
We are sorry, your Majesty.
Let us close the curtain.
Say, daddy, why are the people in Gray Terminal not humans?
Why do they have to get burned?
As the phrase goes, "As a
man sows, so shall he reap."
Think about it.
They could have avoided their
fate just by being born nobles.
Born nobles?
You're right! They should have
chosen to be born nobles!
They're stupid!
Now, enough about those people,
you have to study for tomorrow.
You better go to bed.
Okay!
Good night.
--There's no way on this side!
--We keep losing ground.
I don't wanna die here!
I wonder if those old men escaped safely.
This is no time to be concerned
about other people!
Damn! I don't even know where I am!
Who said that you could get away, you brats?!
Bluejam!
Why are you still here
after setting the fire?!
You were supposed to have escaped by now!
Shut up, you little shit!
We're hopeless, you know.
We have an unforeseen dilemma.
Humans are strange creatures, aren't they?
When you hit rock bottom,
you can't stop laughing.
They are acting weird.
Luffy, let's go!
Don't let them!
We worked together - we're friends!
We have to die together!
We don't wanna die with you!
Not in a million years!
You're so cold.
Come to think of it, you haven't told
me where you keep your treasure.
I'll save it for you before the fire
gets it. So tell me where it is.
Your life is in danger and all
you care about is treasure?
If you don't care, then tell me where it is.
You've gone mad.
If you're not gonna go
get it, it'd be a waste.
If nothing is done, it's gonna be
reduced to charcoal like my ship.
What a waste.
Don't be ridiculous! That treasure is...
Alright, I tell you!
Ace! You and Sabo spent a lot of time...
Sabo would understand!
What matters the most now is your...
What matters the most now is our lives!
Ace...
We keep our treasure from
last 6 years in this tree.
I see.
Don't cry!
It's alright. This is not the end.
What are you doing?! I told you where it is!
You're right. This is not the end.
Which means you could be lying.
You gotta come with us.
No way! Then it's gonna
be too late to escape!
Why don't you guys go on your own?!
You don't wanna mess with me now.
I'm determined to make a come back,
even if it means stealing from kids
so I can take my revenge on nobles.
And your brother is one of them.
They think they're so special
and look down on others as if we're trash!
Sabo doesn't think like that!
He's the same as them, fool!
He was with you both just to feel superior!
That's not true!
His parents are loaded.
He doesn't
have to worry about anything!
It was just a pastime for him.
He was looking down on you guys
and laughing to himself holding his nose!
Stop talking bad about Sabo!
Yeah, Sabo just wants to be free!
You little shit!
Luffy!
I'm gonna kill you!
Let go of me!
Don't touch Luffy!!
Luffy! You okay?!
What did you do?!
Dammit...
You creepy brat!
Do you wanna make a fool out of me, too?!
Shut up, you scumbag!
You bastard!
Ace!
Don't do it!!
Ace and Luffy are cornered by Bluejam!
Trapped among the flames with no escape,
Ace stands his ground and
prepares to fight alone.
Meanwhile, left behind in High Town,
Sabo finally takes action
to go after his dream!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Where Can Freedom Be Found?
The Boy's Sad Departure"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Where Can Freedom Be Found?
The Boy's Sad Departure