Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Bon Clay who was saved by
Ivankov of New Kama Land...
...has just learned that Luffy's
treatment has already begun!
Don't underestimate miracles!
Believe in Miracles!
Bon Clay's Cries from the Heart
M-Miracles?
Yeah!
But it will take a truly tremendous miracle for Straw-boy to survive!
I believe in Straw-chan's will!
I believe that miracles can happen!
B-Because it's Straw-chan!
I believe that he can do it!
Then, stop panicking!
We have to trust him and wait!
So Vi ate the Horm-Horm Fruit
and now Vi can control people's hormones.
Vi can change their sex, body temperature, skin color, growth and emotions!
Vi can remodel people from the inside, Vi'm like an engineer of the human body!
Vi can feel that you're
like the candies here...
except they've all
transcended sex completely!
Some men you see
could have been women...
and some women
could have been men!
That's some kind of miracle!
That's some kind of miracle-able!
That's right!
He changed that man to a
woman by injecting hormones!
Umm... But I still can't believe
there's a place like this in a prison!
I must be dreaming!
It's not a dream!
It's a dream land!
All of these candies were lost prisoners
who made it here by luck!
You see—there are entrances
to New Kama Land on every floor!
There's one at the bloody
mountain of needles,
and in the lair of beasts!
Or in the burning hellfire!
Even in the mortuary.
We use those passages
to get everything we need!
Jailers would never think
there was a paradise like this in hell.
But we always know
what's going on out there!
Because we've got a Transponder Snail that's the same model as the jailers'.
So we know everything
going on inside this prison!
And we steal newspapers from garbage cans so we know what's going on outside, too!
We enjoyed watching the adventures of the first invader—Straw-boy...
as well as you and the others!
We had so much fun!
Where are we in the prison?!
How did you find a space like this?!
Oh, this place wasn't always here.
Vi heard that there was a prisoner
with a hole-digging ability
and with that candy in the lead, they built this prisoners' paradise a long time ago!
This place is like an ant farm that's been created by digging tunnels into a rock.
It's right in the middle of Level 5 and Level 6!
Wait a minute! Level 6?!
Something like that exists?!
Well, it's not widely known but...
Level 6 is where the true villains are kept!
Every one of them is condemned to life without parole!
That's Level 6—the Eternal Hell!
Exceedingly cruel crimes are often
covered up by the Government.
As are incidents that'd harm
the reputation of the Government.
For example, you guys rampaged all the way to Level 4
but if you'd tried that a little while ago,
it wouldn't have been so easy.
Because there was another
threat in this prison!
He was the Jail Manager
of Impel Down—Shiryu of the Rain!
He's as strong as Warden Magellan.
If you think about how little
Magellan actually works,
Shiryu was twice as troublesome.
A-As strong as Warden Magellan?!
Impel Down was iron-tight with those two!
Jail Manager Shiryu of the Rain...
What do you think you're doing, Shiryu?!
What do you mean?
The prisoners are not here
for your amusement!
No one cares whether or not these vermin die!
I can't overlook your actions any longer!
If anyone finds out what you've done here,
it will disgrace Impel Down!
Now I must exercise my authority
and put you under arrest!
He massacred prisoners on a whim.
Something had to be done.
So they imprisoned him on Level 6
because he was so dangerous.
I've never heard about this!
I know it happened before I got here, but—
Down there are also pirates like the world's most dangerous woman—Catalina Devon,
"Great Battleship" San Juan Wolf,
"Heavy Drinker" Vasco Shot!
These are names that'd
make anyone shiver in fear!
Their most brutal crimes never even made it into the papers.
Those are the kind of legendary pirates
who are imprisoned on Level 6.
Your former boss is there, too!
He's just as crazy as the others!
What?! 0-chan?! Crocodile?!
You guys were Straw-boy's enemies on Alabasta, right?
How interesting!
It goes to show that anyone
can become friends!
You're right!
There is also a Warlord of the Sea—
First Son of the Sea Jinbe!
And the guy that Straw-boy snuck in here for.
He's the second division commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates—
Portgas D. Ace!
Vi heard it over the radio!
They are brothers, right?!
Yes, Straw-chan said that the only reason
he came here was to rescue him!
It's miraculous that he snuck in.
But he's going to have to give it up!
He has to save himself first!
Today's the day that Ace-boy
will be executed—at 3 p.m.!
Vi think that they're gonna take him
to Navy Headquarters in the morning.
That means Ace-boy will be taken
out of Impel Down in seven or eight hours!
Straw-boy's treatment will take two more days!
Even if he survives, he'd need three more days
of sleep to recover his strength!
So when he wakes up,
everything will be over!
But can he even take
two more days of that?!
Vi told you that the possibility is low
and that he needs a miracle to make it!
You need to rest, too!
Eat something nutritious and go back to bed!
Vi'll take you to a quiet room you can sleep in.
I'll stay with Straw-chan!
Hey, don't bother! He's...
There's little hope!
What are you gonna do?!
S-Straw-chan!
Hang in there!
Straw-chan!
I wonder how he's doing.
All he can do is wait.
Hang in there!
Hang in there! Straw-chan!
Hang in there! Hang...
Hang in there! Hang in there!
He's been doing it all this time?!
That's so stupid! That won't do anything!
You're right! Let's go!
Hang... Hang in...
Hang... Hang in there!
Can't you find...
...even one queer?!
Look for him again!
He's not back yet.
Is he still doing it?
He must have given up already
and probably went to sleep!
I'll go check!
I'll go!
Me, too!
I can't hear it anymore.
See, I told you!
He gave up and...
Hang... Hang in there!
Hang in there!
Hang... in... there!
How long will he keep wasting time like that?!
Hang... Hang in...
S-Straw-chan...
That fool!
Hey, you alright?!
Take care of yourself first!
We gotta treat him!
Keep your hands to yourselves!
Let him do whatever he wants!
But...
Bon-boy wants to struggle
and fight alongside Straw-boy!
Even if there's only a sliver of a chance,
he believes in Straw-boy,
puts his life on the line
and shouts himself hoarse!
S-Straw-chan!
They're both beyond their limit already but...
they're trying to create a miracle!
For more than 10 hours,
S-Straw-chan has been fighting against
his own destiny for his life in this way!
Then I... I...
I shouldn't give in, either!
Hang... Hang in there!
Hang in there!
Hang in there, Straw-chan!
Straw-chan!
You have to live!
Hang in there!
--Straw-chan!
--Hang in there!
Hang in there!
Hang in there-able!
Straw-chan!
Hang in there!
"Warden's Office"
Warden!
I just heard from the canteen staff on Level 5
and they said that Straw Hat Luffy has...
...disappeared!
What?!
V-Vice Warden Hannyabal!
What are you doing here?!
Hang in there!
Hang in there! Straw-chan!
Ace-san, I don't know anything
about that woman but...
...I think that you better
assume she's lying.
So you're saying that she came
all the way to here just to lie to me?!
Well, I'm sorry.
But, to tell you the truth, Jinbe.
My brother would do something like that!
He does stupid things!
Since we were kids,
he always made me worry, that fool!
Finally, the day has come!
I hope that we can get
rid of him successfully!
I don't want any wars in Impel Down!
Warden Magellan will be here any minute.
I-It's blood!
No more screams...
The treatment is excruciatingly painful from beginning to end!
If his screams have stopped...
How sad!
But he fought bravely for twenty hours!
Straw-chan...
What... What?!
Food!
S... Straw-chan!
Yeah!
Straw-boy! I—
Impossible!
What's going on?!
It hasn't even been one full day yet!
Warden! Warden Magellan!
Good morning!
I've got very bad diarrhea...
Please hurry.
It's time to move the
condemned prisoner - Portgas D. Ace
Bring more food here!
Keep it coming! Cooked or not!
The amount is what matters!
Hurry up! Just leave it close to him!
Wow! He's taking in food like a sand pit trap!
How long will he keep eating?!
He's been eating for
30 minutes at a steady pace!
He ate several days worth of
the food supply for Kama Land!
What amazing vitality!
He's coming out!
What kind of creature is that?!
That's not the form of human being!
I'm...
...recovered!
Thanks to Ivankov's treatment, Luffy has miraculously recovered
and intends to save Ace by himself.
Once Iva-san learns that Luffy is the son of the Revolutionary--Dragon,
he decides to lend Luffy his strength.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Luffy Returns!
Iva-san's Escape Plan Set in Motion!!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Luffy Returns!
Iva-san's Escape Plan Set in Motion!!