Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy and others had been captured by Largo,
captain of the Amigo Pirates,
with his Net-Net power.
Even if you are a rubber man, I will
not let you get away with it, senor!
But Boss, the big beetle, tried to
sacrifice himself to save the island...
Wait!
Can't you hear what I'm saying!
Boss, after shedding his skin,
then cut down the nets which
held Luffy and the others.
Oh no! It was too soon to
shed his skin as I thought!
Crying or screaming won't help anymore!
We got your guardian angel as you see!
It's not over yet!
We won't let his last breath...
...be wasted.
Thank you, Giant Beetle!
Now, it's showtime!
Movie Tie-in Special
The Battle is on! Luffy vs. Largo
What can three burned men
and some weak sea idiots
with pathetic weapons do...
...at this last moment?!
It's obvious! We want the Giant Beetle!
Boss!
Give him back!
Thank you!
Go ahead, make my day!
Zoro! Cut that net!
Okay.
How stupid are you?
You know that your sword
is too dull to cut my net.
We'll see about that!
Lion Song!
No way!
We gotta fight, too!
Wait a minute!
Gear 2!
Sanji! Shoot me over there!
Alright!
Get ready, Net Man!
Why should I?
Armee de L'Air Assault Gum Shoot!
Jet Bullet!
Get the rest!
Alright!
Big Bro got taken down?
No, he was just off-guard! He can't
have been beaten by that kid!
To be recognized by Big Boss Shiki...
Did you get hurt, maybe a bit?
Now I remember!
That straw hat!
You have a 300 million
berry price on your head...
You're Monkey D. Luffy, aren't you?
Yes, I am!
It's hard for me to take a young man's life
but the sweet sound of your death
cry will be worth 300 million to me.
Mucho Burning Net!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Lance!
Mucho Sticky Net!
The jungle is a poor place to
fight! I need to get out of here!
Bastard! He's running away!
Of course!  That's why
they call it "weak sea!"
People from the East Blue
are quick at running away!
No. A smart lady from the
East Blue figured that...
...two of us are enough to beat you all.
Hey! Why are we running?!
We're all ready to kick their butt!
Ouch! Don't be stupid!
You can't confront them!
He's right!
You can only do what you are
capable of at times like these...
...even if that means using your brain!
You! Hurry up!
Don't tell me what to do, Pirate!
Do you want them to have
the beetle and the island?!
If not, you have to do as I say!
Are you sure...
Are you sure that I'll get Boss
back if I go along with you?!
Yes!
Are you ready now?!
Yeah!
We're all in agreement?!
You two are enough for us?
What a big mouth!
The only thing they've got going
for them is their numbers.
Do you want me to protect you?
Are you kidding me?  You
just watch your own ass!
Guys! Let's...
...Get them!
--Ouch!
--W-What happened?!
Don't mess with us!
Fool! Aw!
Get out of here!
What are they doing?!
Take that!
Surprised?
The caves here are all connected
to different parts of the island.
It's a waste to just use them as an
escape route for when an enemy comes!
Alright! Get down, everybody!
Thunder Bolt...
...Tempo!
Oh no!
Let's get them all at once!
What's going on here?!
Stop it!
Sure-Kill Egg Star!
Augh! It stinks!
Nice!
They're great!
You think you can make a fool out of me?!
You can't get away with it!
What the hell?!
I'll kill you all!
Oh no!
Boss!
Screw you!
Out of bullets?!
What have you done?!
As a requiem for my brother,
I will take your life!
Here on the beach, with an expansive view,
you'll find it hard to elude me, I'm sure!
Oh yeah? But I'm sure you can't beat me!
How stupid you are!
Bring it on, senor!
Oh? What's going on there?!
--It's Luffy!
--Seems like he's fighting.
Jet Pistol!
No shock! Net Body!
W-What's that?!
Sorry! Your attack won't hurt me anymore!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
It's not working! How long
are you going to do that?!
Until you get blown away!
Luffy's attack isn't working!
He must be a Devil Fruit user!
That's not good.
Alright, let's finish it up.
This is for my brother!
A requiem of a death cry!
Mucho-Mucho...
...Full Net Body!
--Luffy!
--Luffy-san!
Now, you're captured!
You will never break this net!
What now?!
It's a submarine, isn't it?
It's being used as a pirate ship?!
Looks like it.
Now, I have a prize worth
300 million berries!
Gear 3:
Bone Balloon!
W-What are you...?!
Stop it!
Gum-Gum...
...Gigant Pistol!
Oh no!
Augh! Luffy!
I got it!
I'm coming to save you, Luffy-san!
What?
Oh, wait--I seem to have
forgotten I can't swim!
I thought I'd die here!
Even though I'm already dead!
Thank you, Giant Beetle!
Ow, ow, ouch! What do
you think you're doing?!
You bastard! A few minutes ago,
you could barely breathe fire!
I can't take it! Let's fight right now!
No! Wait until I get down!
Ah no!
Ow, ow, ow... You bastard!
--Those two...
--Ow, nice one!
are they gonna fight forever?
Dunno.
You haven't won yet!
Dad...
There you are.
Can I join?
Why are you here?
I heard there was an orange plantation so...
What a view!
My dad used to love this place.
And so did I.
Look, Yoko! This is my favorite
place in the whole world!
Yeah! I love this place, too!
I really really love it!
Yeah? You really love it?
Burn everything up!
Take all the treasure and food!
Kill all who resist!
Dad! Dad!
Yoko!
Hurry and escape from this island!
No I won't! Because I love this island!
I love the view from the orange plantation!
You said that you love it, too!
You're right.
You save...
...t-this island from now on.
Dad!
Together with the island...
...live strongly!
I was like you.
I really hated pirates.
What?
Then, why did you become one?
Well... I'm not sure why.
Nami!
You're one of us now!
Uh-huh!
But Luffy is not the kind of
pirate that you think he is.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Let's make it clear which
one of us is stronger!
Shut up! I don't care!
I just wanna fight him!
Is that it?!
Yeah, I think I see what you mean.
Yeah?
Uh-huh.
He's too stupid and naive to be a pirate.
I agree.
It's quiet. Did they finish fighting?
Oh yeah.
I wonder how Boss did.
What do you say? Do you give up?
He says "No, I won!"
What?!
Alright, that's it!
It's time to go back to the sea!
What're you talking about, Nami?!
We're not through yet!
It seems like it only takes a half day to
record the magnetic wave of this island.
So we better go now before it resets.
Nami-sama!
Luffy!
Thank you for saving our island!
No problem!
Giant Beetle! I'll be back someday so,
let's continue where we left off!
Promise me!
I thought that they were
specialists in trapping.
But I'm afraid we've lost
touch with the Amigo Pirates.
It seems as though it was
impossible for them to defeat
the monster that you created.
However, one escapee doesn't affect
the execution of my plan at all.
These monsters will help
me to conquer the world!
Let's declare war against the whole world!
Shiki the Golden Lion's
supreme plan will begin!
Luffy and the others defeat the
Basilisk and press on through Level 2,
but more beasts impede
their path one after another.
Meanwhile, another pirate is being
held in the same prison cell as Ace.
His name is...
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Warlord in Prison!
Jinbe, First Son of the Sea"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Warlord in Prison!
Jinbe, First Son of the Sea