Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and in order to move on
to the next stage, the New World,
they return to Sabaody Archipelago!
The Navy Has Set Out
The Straw Hats in Danger
Sunny!
We made you wait two long years.
I'm glad you're safe!
Look at that beautiful woman over there!
Is that our super archaeologist...
Robin?!
You haven't changed a bit, Franky.
Oh, I've changed alright, silly!
Just look at this body!
It's the stuff men's dreams are made of!
Behold the greatest transformation of all time!
I'm beyond human comprehension!
Well, you're right about that.
I have no idea what you are.
Hey, hey, you mean I'm a pervert?
You're far too kind!
So this is the ship's new coating.
It's like jelly.
That's right! Rayleigh's a genius!
Now we can sail the depths of the sea!
What incredible engineering!
I went to see Rayleigh already.
You went to the bar?
What number were you?
I'm the eighth.
Luffy will be the last one.
That's great.
Then we'll be heading out real soon.
I've finished with maintenance.
Installed all the new weaponry too!
I'm looking forward to it.
By the way, where are the others?
Usopp and Sanji came by already.
Usopp went to get fuel
and Sanji's stocking up on food.
I see.
Actually, on my way here,
I came across this.
Did you know about this?
What do they mean by "Soul King"?
About Brook?
Yeah, I knew.
They sell his TDs everywhere.
He's emerged a dazzling star!
Having traversed the dark seas of despair,
he's standing on a glorious stage
being cheered on by an army of adoring fans!
He might not...
want to be a pirate ever again.
Grove #33, Sabaody Dome
...King, mysterious...
He's nothing but bones!
Afro on the skull!
Girls love the contrast!
If you wanna make out with her...
Got milk! Got milk!
You need calcium more than protein!
Captain!
Captain Luffy!
Damn!
Luffy!
I missed you guys so much!
Hey!
Luffy!
Franky!
Nami!
Sogeking?!
So cool!
You guys sure changed a lot in the last two years!
I bet you're a lot stronger now!
Right?!
It's the Straw Hats.
What are they doing on the street?
Well, what happened was...
Try to avoid eye contact.
You wouldn't stand a chance against them.
Damn it all!
What happened to you, exactly?
I don't know!
I felt a chill run down my spine.
What kind of trick did he use?
Oh, right!
We ran into some trouble ourselves.
The thing is, Cocoa got...
Uh, I mean... Nico Robin got...
What did you say, Zoro?!
Nico Robin got kidnapped?!
We're so sorry.
And it happened right in front of our eyes too.
Yeah, yeah!
It's terrible, Luffy!
They might be kidnappers!
Like that time with Camie!
Who did it?!
We have no idea.
Captain!
It was probably somebody with a grudge
against Nico Robin who mistook Cocoa for her.
That's possible.
They do look just alike.
So it worked against us this time.
Hey, what are you whispering about?!
Whatever.
Forget her.
It's her fate.
What?! Okay, Captain.
What?!
Hey, Luffy!
Robin's been kidnapped!
I've been thinking,
what is this creature?
Is that a joke?!
Even if it is, you shouldn't
joke about things like that!
How can he speak?
Is he a stuffed animal?
Take it back, Luffy!
Oh, shut it!
Anyway, have the 100 pirates we recruited here
assemble at Grove #46!
The man with the long nose,
that woman with long orange hair,
and that brat with the cloak and the huge backpack...
Find those three
and make them regret attacking Straw Hat Luffy!
Roger!
Remember not to kill them before we've brought them here.
This is the perfect opportunity
to show them how formidable we are!
Alright, let's go!
Hold on, you guys!
Did you hearts completely change
in the past two years?
Luffy!
I... I... feel so sad...
I can't help crying!
Again, what is this creature?
What's gonna happen to Robin?!
Why is no one saying anything?!
Huh? How can you talk?
Toys these days sure are well made!
Dammit! I misjudged you guys!
I'm gonna save Robin even if I have to do it alone!
Wait for me, Robin!
What happened?
An internal feud?
That's...
There's no mistake!
The Straw Hats look different than they did two years ago
but nobody else would keep such a strange creature for a pet.
They're...
definitely the Straw Hats! They're alive!
Reporting from Grove #47!
Straw Hat Pirates confirmed!
Grove #66, Navy Base
The Straw Hats intend to gather their recruits...
"Crew Wanted"
here, at Grove #46!
Great work! Roger that!
Evacuate the civilians immediately!
Aye aye, sir!
The pirates are gathering at Grove #46!
The target is the Straw Hat Pirates!
We will now enter the Lawless Lands!
All hands prepare for battle!
Blockade Groves #40, 42, 44!
Reinforcements from G-1 will arrive shortly!
S-Sentomaru-san!
I'm going ahead of you guys!
And I'm taking PX-5 and PX-7 with me!
What?! You're deploying Pacifistas?!
Of course!
Are you taking the Straw Hats seriously enough?
It's been two years since the war.
They're definitely a lot stronger than before!
They're far superior
to the rookies gathering on this island!
We never found out...
Lord Kuma's true intentions two years ago.
But even after he lost his personality,
seeing how he continued to act so strange
I knew the Straw Hats would come back
to this island one of these days!
Now let's go!
Oh, it's moving!
It must be this way.
This is what happens when you messed with me.
Damn!
Run!
There sure are a lot of pirates around.
Hmmm, maybe I should put it on after all?
I'm telling you give me a better discount!
I-I can't do that, ma'am!
You're asking me to sell
this many clothes at half price?
That's just...
Hey, Nami!
You can buy as many clothes
as you want on Fishman Island, right?
We should be getting fuel now!
No way!
Here! I'll buy these too,
so give me a 90% discount!
Noooooo!!
Hey, hey, your haggling skills have powered up
these past two years as well, I see.
Hey, Mosshead!
You gotta stay with me!
Don't want you getting lost.
Huh? Who do you think
you're talking to, Bearded Brow?
What'd you just say?
Oh! Something smells good...
Oh, this looks delicious!
Hi!
Try some!
Oh, how dazzling!
There's a lady right in front of me!
Oh? That bastard! Where'd he go?!
If I'm gonna fish I'll need a fishing rod.
Oh, a fishing goods store!
He's gone... Damn that guy!
Robin!
Where'd they take you?!
Dammit!
Dammit! Dammit!
Dammiiiiiit!
I can't believe those guys!
What happened to them?!
Luffy, Zoro, Nami, Sanji, Franky...
They used to care about each other so much!
But they didn't even care
that Robin's been kidnapped?!
What jerks!
What's the point of all my hard work
these past two years?!
Who was it all for?!
Hey, Chopper!
Hey!
Over here!
It really is you, Chopper!
Usopp!
Look at you!
You've grown!
I bet you're really comfortable to ride now!
How have you been?
Uh-huh!
He's right!
You're so much fluffier too!
Long time no see, Chopper!
Huh?
Nami?
Yes?
Oh yeah!
I'm glad to see you again too,
but we've got trouble!
Something terrible's happened to Robin!
What?! Those guys were impostors?
So that's why there were two Namis?
Oh, come on...
Robin's been on the run
from the Government for twenty years.
Do you really think they could just stuff her in a bag
and carry her off?
I see!
I thought something seemed different!
She didn't smell right either!
Now... I'm getting mad!
What's wrong with those guys?!
Pretending to be us!
They'll pay for this!
If they're impersonating us,
it's like we're...
famous, those jerks!
Why are you so happy?
It can't be helped.
Luffy's exploits were hard to ignore.
I better work on my signature!
I already have one!
Look, we're famous in a bad way, okay?
Hey, Chopper!
Chopper!
Honestly! Right when we thought
we'd caught the pet of the real Straw Hats!
Ouch! My side hurts!
What?!
That strange creature was a survivor
of the real Straw Hats?!
Why didn't you tell me?!
Hurry up and bring it back!
What?!
It's impossible!
How are we supposed to find it?
We completely lost sight of him
and Sabaody Archipelago is massive!
Ouch! My side! It hurts!
I can't keep running!
Let's walk! Let's just walk!
Hancock was right,
I'm better off with the mustache.
She told me not to cause any trouble.
Hey, look! Isn't that the brat with the cloak
and huge backpack Captain was talking about?
Brat?
Isn't that just a cheery old man?
Hey, it's you guys!
Hey, buddy, we need you to come with us.
If you just come along quietly,
we're not gonna hurt you.
But our captain is very angry.
You're not gonna live long either way.
What? Are you too scared to talk?
I knew it! You're Sanji, aren't you?
And you must be Zoro!
It's been a long time, huh?
H-Hey, it's been a while... hasn't it?
Y-Yeah! Anyway, let's go!
Sure! Are the others here already?
Sorry I kept you waiting!
Do you think he's mistaking us for someone else?
Who cares?
We just have to take him to the captain!
I'm going to the shore.
I wanna go fishing.
No, you can't, shithead!
Why not?!
You're not my boss!
Why should I listen to you?!
I'm not walking with you because I want to!
You're a huge pain, but if I let you keep wandering around the island, you'll just get lost!
You Stray Moss!
The others will be here any time now,
so just shut up and follow me back to the ship!
Damn you!
No. 7 telling No. 1 what to do?
What?! You're ranking us in the order we got here?!
You got here first by chance! Don't get carried away!
Sure, sorry... No. 7.
That's it! I'll gut you like a fish!
I spent two years in hell training my legs for this!
Bring it on!
I'll cut you in half!
Grove #46, the Straw Hats' meeting spot
Reporting from Grove #46.
The rookies joining the Straw Hats
are showing up one by one.
I can confirm the identities of four captains.
"Gashed" Albion
Bounty: 92 Million Berries
A bounty of 92 million berries.
"Gashed" Albion.
Lip "Service" Doughty
Bounty: 88 Million Berries
A bounty of 88 million berries.
Lip "Service" Doughty.
A-And the super rookies...
"Wet-Haired" Caribou
Bounty: 210 Million Berries
The captain of the Caribou Pirates,
A bounty of 210 million berries.
"Wet-Haired" Caribou!
"Blood Splatter" Coribou
Bounty: 190 Million Berries
And his brother, the co-captain,
with a bounty of 190 million berries,
"Blood Splatter" Coribou!
The Straw Hats slowly gather on the Sunny,
but, lured in by the actions of the Fake Straw Hats,
the Marines raid Brook's live concert.
Amidst the confusion, Brook starts singing
his last song as the Soul King.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Big Guns Assembled
The Danger of the Fake Straw Hats"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Big Guns Assembled
The Danger of the Fake Straw Hats