Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Luffy got to Level 6 along with
the queen of New Kama Land Ivankov
but Ace was already gone!
You better not resist because it's useless!
Luffy!
Your brother is also a pirate! There's
no way that he'll walk out of here alive.
I wished that she was lying!
Why did you come, Luffy?!
It's simple but their plan defeated us!
We're confined to Level 6! There's
no way for us to get out!
They'll hand over Ace-boy to the
Navy Headquarters at any cost!
You need to give up on him!
I mean, you need to trust Whitebeard.
He's not gonna give up on one of his
own! He'll definitely do something!
--I'm going!
--Huh?!
I'm gonna go to Navy Headquarters!
If I give up now...
...I'm gonna regret it!
But first of all, how can
you get off of this floor?!
If you wanna get out of here, set me free!
I can create a hole on the ceiling!
What do you think?
Crocodile!
It's been a while!
Straw Hat!
The Ultimate Team Has Formed
Shaking Impel Down!
I thought that there was no
reason to get back on the street
but Whitebeard and the Navy
are gonna start a war?
It's my chance to finally
bring down that old man!
This war has piqued my interest.
And with my power, you and
I could get out of here.
It's not bad, huh? We both get what we want.
Screw you!
--You're the man who messed up Vivi's country!
--That was a long time ago.
I lost interest in that country.
Let's release him, Straw-boy.
His power will aid us greatly.
What?! Iva-chan! If you
knew what he's done...
You wanna keep going, right?!
If you wanna make it to
Navy HQ,  you need him!
Ivankov!
Long time no see, Croco-boy!
Y-You know him?
Just a passing acquaintance! I met
him when he was just a rookie!
Don't worry!
I can bring him under control
in case he tries to betray us.
I can't trust him at all!
But I know one of his weaknesses!
Hey, if you so much as say it...
Oh? Do you wanna take that tone?
If you like, I can just
reveal your past here.
But, if you just shut up and help
us, I keep the secret for Y-O-U!
Heehaw!
You bastard!
Why don't you release me, too?!
Me, too! I have something against Whitebeard!
Let me out, too!
Shut up!
Death Wink!
Have mercy on me!
Take me with you! I can help you for sure!
I have known Ace-san ever since
he joined the Whitebeards!
He always told me about his brother!
I was arrested because I objected to the war!
I wanna save Ace-san, too! So please!
Let me die for him!
Such a strong bond between a Warlord
First Son of the Sea Jinbe and...
...the second division commander
of the Whitebeards--Portgas D. Ace!
I never would have guessed!
-- Alright.
-- Are you sure?!
We don't know about him
and how dangerous he is!
It's okay! Let him out!
Thank you!
--Hey, I'll thank you, too!
--Have mercy on me, too!
Shut up! Death Wink!
A Warlord and a former
Warlord both on our team.
Two of them? Who is the other one?
I appreciate this! Now I can be of some help.
Maybe you can stop the war between
the Whitebeards and the Navy
but it's a waste of time.
Because I'm gonna get that old man anyway.
I won't let you even touch good
old Whitebeard, Crocodile!
Then, do you wanna just fight me here?
Croco-boy--your secret past?
Alright, we don't have much time!
We're gonna just break out by force!
Heehaw!
Straw Hat, Ivankov, Inazuma,
they're all Devil Fruit users!
Don't forget the Prison Bullets!
We've reached Level 6!
Move in!
What's this stone thing?
N-No way!
Are they still here?! Go look!
Do you really think that they stayed
here after making that hole, stupid?
S-Shiryu, the Jail Manager!
See, you guys? You can't do
anything right without me.
You're doing your job so poorly!
This is a huge mess and the
embarrassment of Impel Down!
The three that you're looking for
released Crocodile and Jinbe and...
...climbed up through the hole to Level 5!
Tell Magellan now  that I
can help him if he wants!
No, that's...
W-What?!
They took Crocodile and Jinbe?!
Yes, they're not in their cells!
No! Does it mean that I thought
that I confined them to Level 6
but that I've been outsmarted?
There're now five of them and
they're on Level 5, right?
That's right!
Do you think that  I'm
responsible for any of this?
Warden Magellan is
convoying Portgas D. Ace
so I think that you're
responsible for all of this!
I'm responsible for all of this?!
Alright, I'm gonna fight, too!
All jailers must go back to Level 4!
Sadie-chan, Saldeath!
Go to Level 4 with all of your people now!
I'd risk my own life to become Warden!
I mean, risk your own lives to stop them!
Are you ready, Bon-boy?
Y-Yes, Iva-san!
You sure?
Emporio Energy Hormone is just
for you to recover for today.
There'll be after effects!
I know! Go ahead!
I mean if you don't, I can barely move!
Oh yeah! You're right!
You got me there!
Emporio Energy...
...Hormone!
Oh! I injected it into
your crotch by mistake!
New Kama Land!
Bon-chan! Don't die!
Are you ready?
Even if we manage to get to
the  front door of the prison,
we'll still be in for a fight!
There's the Calm Belt all
around us which is impassable!
We have to steal a Navy ship to go to Navy Headquarters!
We just need to get more
people to fight with us!
To be honest, we already have a lot but...
...only a few of you can
make it  to the top floor!
If you are captured, you'll
be tortured to death!
So if you wanna survive,
you need to set free as many prisoners
as you can from levels 1 through 5!
If we can start a riot,
we'll keep our foes busy!
We have to steal the keys and set
as many as we can free on our way!
Let's unleash mayhem in Impel Down
such as has never been seen before!
Heehaw!
Let's go, Straw-boy!
Oh?
He went ahead.
What a free spirit! Heehaw!
Let's catch up with him, candies!
Wait! Please somebody stop me!
I'm going way too fast!
It's faster than usual!
The hormone is working overtime!
Yeah, but it must be  nice to move like that.
It's not always nice!
The biggest trouble in the history
of Impel Down is now gone!
Back to your posts and
clean up the mess inside!
It's before 10 in the morning!
The execution is at three in the afternoon.
They'll definitely do it on time!
If Whitebeard is going to do something,
he'll do it hours before that!
Ace should already be on the ship!
The war could begin anytime now!
But he's not gonna get killed until three!
Which means that we still have a chance!
Doors can't stop me!
I'll turn it into sand with my right hand.
Let's see how Crocodile's
Sand-Sand Fruit power works!
He can turn into sand and control it.
With his right hand, he can
suck any type of moisture
so people and plants will wither
and rocks and land turn to sand!
T-They're coming!
T-This is Level 4!
The prisoner who escaped from
Level 6 - is a Warlord Jinbe!
This is the Inferno Hell!
The intruder--Monkey D. Luffy!
It's hot!
A former Warlord Crocodile!
They're here! So we will fight!
Shoot!
Stupid! Use the Prison Bullets!
Crescent Cutlass!
Shoot the Prison Bullets!
Gum-Gum...
...Rain!
Fishman Karate:
W-What was it?!
What's happening?!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
We're no match for them - an
infamous rookie and two Warlords!
D-Don't stop!
Hold out until backups will get
here! We're outnumbering them!
Get out of our way! We're in hurry!
Let's just go!
You fools! Shoot them up!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
What's up?!
--Vice Warden, this is Level 4!
--You did it?!
No, actually...
Please come help us!
H-Hurry up! Damn it! Dash!
Camisole!
Long johns!
T-back!
--Pantyhose!
--Briefs!
--Leggings!
Bra!
Bloomers!
Bloomers! Briefs!
Briefs!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Here comes the funny part!
Damn! Why're they hanging out
here? Those underwear fetishists!
They're so relaxed!
Finally we got to Level 2!
If they find us, all of our efforts will come to nothing!
But their farts really stink!
Oh yeah!
You!
I'm sorry.
--S-Smells like burdock...
--Sorry...
Wow, the key! We can get out!
Thank you very much!
Oh, you're C-Crocodile!
I'm thinking about breaking out
but I need some assistants.
Do you wanna come with me?
Mr. 1!
I'll come with you because you asked me.
I was just starting to get bored.
Trying to break through Level 4, Luffy and the others rush forward.
And the prisoners on Level 2 begin to riot.
Impel Down is engulfed in chaos.
And to make things even more crazy,
an unknown ship shows up.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Even More Chaos!
Here Comes Blackbeard Teach"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Even More Chaos!
Here Comes Blackbeard Teach