Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
Zeff and Sanji's Dream!
The Illusory All Blue!
Ghin!!
No matter how incredible he was
in the past, he's now a mere cook.
It's easy to blow his brains out.
You want to save this man, right, Sanji-san?
Please, leave the ship without a fight.
I don't want to kill you.
Leave the ship?
No way!
Man, do you look stupid, you damn geezer.
If you're like that, you can't set a
good example for the fighting cooks.
Hmph!
I don't need a lecture from a little brat.
Where do you get off calling me
"little brat," you damn bastard?!
Quit treating me like a kid already!
That darn Sanji...
He sure isn't gonna forsake Owner, is he?
Ghin! Point that gun at me.
Are you stupid?! You'll die!
Maybe...
Sanji-san... Why?!
If you want to die so bad,
I'll kill you in a refined way...
Don't move if you don't want
your Owner's head blown off.
The Absolutely Natural Pearl... Surprise!
Sanji! Why aren't you dodging?!
If I did, that damn underling
would pull the trigger.
Why? If you abandon this restaurant,
everyone's life will be saved.
It's a no-brainer, isn't it?!
This restaurant is that damn geezer's treasure!
I took everything away from that damn geezer...
His power...
His dream...
So... I don't want that damn
geezer to lose anything else!!
Sanji! Watch out!!
Pearl... Cymbals!
Sanji!!
The All Blue?
Yeah!
It's a legendary sea.
It's definitely out there somewhere!
Don't be silly!
Though there is a legend like that.
Well, we're seafaring cooks, so we've
all dreamed of that sea at one point.
Right?
I'll definitely find that sea some day!
You say you'll find it, but...
Do you know what kind of place
the All Blue is to start with?
Yes, I do! Don't insult my intelligence!
The East Blue, West Blue,
North Blue, and South Blue...
A sea where fish from all four seas live...
That's the All Blue.
To seafaring cooks,
that's an irresistible paradise!
That's my dream!
Oh, yeah! There's all sorts of seafood
from all over the world in that sea.
Cooks would be itching for
the chance to show their skills!
Yeah.
It's worth risking your life to look for that sea.
– That is, if such a sea exists...
– What?
There's no way a miracle sea
like the All Blue could exist...
It's obvious if you just give it a little thought...
It's probably a big lie told by some
daydreaming cook somewhere...
Now, enough with the silly stories.
Go collect plates, Sanji!
Ahh... How wasteful... leaving this much food...
This one has barely been touched.
I was sure they'd like it.
Customers these days sure are pampered.
You guys stop eating the customers' leftovers.
I ditched food that looked rotten earlier.
Saying things like that shows you're
still just halfway to being a cook.
Don't forget we're seafaring cooks.
The sea is an unpredictable place,
so it's best not to waste food.
Why don't you have some, too, huh?
I don't want it!
Everyone, please calm down!
Calm down!!
Pirates!
Pirates?!
That ship is... The Cook Pirates...
Red Leg Zeff's ship!
So they came back from the Grand Line!
I take it you're the pirate captain Red Leg Zeff.
How can I help you?
Steal!
Steal all the valuables from them!
Dammit! I'm not gonna be killed!
I'm not gonna be killed by bastards like them!
Whoa!
What's this kid?
Hey, kid. Don't swing things
like that around. It's dangerous.
I'm bleeding. It's a serious injury.
Shut up!
I'm not gonna be killed by bastards like you!
Sanji!
Stop it! Don't fight back!
Seems he's got a death wish.
Kill that brat already!
I don't want to die!
If I'm gonna be killed by you bastards,
I'd rather kill you first!
Sanji!
Boy, you did it, Captain.
You have no mercy.
I'm not gonna die!
I...
I will find the All Blue some day!
He said "All Blue"!
What an ambitious goal!
Captain, tell him... that it didn't
exist even in the Grand Line.
That idiot!
He's still spouting that nonsense...
I'm not gonna...
I'm not gonna be killed by damn
pirates in a place like this!
Captain! Let's withdraw!
This storm is bigger than we expected!
Okay, guys!
Hurry up and take the treasure on board!
We're withdrawing!
Sanji!
Dammit!
Captain!!
That damn brat!
Why'd you do that for just one brat?!
So you've come to, little brat?
You're very lucky.
Pirate! Ow, ow, ow...
There's no way you can move!
Whose kicks do you think you took?
What about the ships?
Who knows? The sea was very rough.
I wouldn't be surprised if they
were completely destroyed.
We're the only ones who washed up here.
There's no fruits or animals
on this rocky mountain.
There're at least fish in the sea,
but since the rock has
been curved by the waves,
we won't be able to come back up
once we go down. Isn't that sad?
Hmph! It's all your fault!
I'll kill you!
Just keep complaining.
We have no choice but to wait for help anyway.
If no one comes, we'll just
dry up and turn into skeletons.
A skeleton?! I will...
That bag over there is your share.
What?
That's the food that luckily washed up here.
It's 5 days worth of food
at most if you eat normally.
Use your head and eat.
Good thing that we're both cooks.
Wait a second! Is that your share?!
It's huge... at least three times as large as mine!
Of course! I'm an adult.
My stomach is larger than yours.
You should be grateful that
I'm even sharing food with you.
Don't expect any pity from me.
You damn geezer!
You watch the other side of the sea.
As soon as you see a ship, let me know.
Until then, we won't be in contact at all
because that'd be a waste of energy.
Good luck.
That damn geezer!
I'm not gonna let him know even if I see a ship.
It'll be fine.
I have 5 days worth of food.
If I have 5 days, there'll definitely
be a ship or two passing by.
But just in case, I'll divide
them up for 20 days for now.
If I have 20 days, there'll be a ship passing by for sure.
It'll be all right.
I'll definitely survive. It's easy!
No ship passed by today.
That's all right. I'll just have to
be patient for a couple more days.
I don't wanna die...
This is the last piece of bread...
It's gotten moldy...
Ahh... How wasteful... leaving this much food...
You guys stop eating the customers' leftovers.
I ditched food that looked rotten earlier.
Why don't you have some, too, huh?
I don't want it!
My last piece of bread...
I wonder... if that damn geezer already died...
He's still alive...
And there's food, too...
There's still that much...
There's that much food!
I'll take it no matter what.
It was all his fault to begin with!
I want to live!
What did you come here for, little brat?!
Did you see a ship or something?
I came to steal your food.
If you think you can kill me, go ahead.
I'll die if I don't eat anyway.
To think you to have this
much food all to yourself...
What?
Didn't I tell you that we wouldn't
be in contact until we saw a ship?
Why? This is all treasure...
It's odd that we can't eat
when we have money.
Hey... This bag is filled with treasure...
What is this?!
What's the meaning of this?!
Where's your food?
You didn't eat anything until today?
Hey! Say something!
What happened to your leg?
That time...
So it wasn't a dream...
In order to save me, you...
What about the food?
Did you give me all the food you had?
That's right.
Without that leg, you won't be
able to be a pirate any more!
I guess...
Why? I didn't ask for your help!
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
Why? Why did you?!
Because you... you had the same dream as me.
The All Blue...
But... even your men said it doesn't exist...
Of course it does!
When the time comes, head to the Grand Line.
The All Blue surely exists there.
As you see, I can't be a pirate any more,
but this time, you can go and find it.
H-Hey! Geezer, don't die!
Don't just do as you please
and die as you please!
I wonder...
I wonder how many people
died cursing the sea...
...the grandness of the sea...
I've experienced crises like
this where I couldn't eat.
And each time I wish...
...that there was a restaurant
in the middle of the sea...
Restaurant?
Yeah. I was thinking that if
I could leave this place alive,
I'd build a restaurant as my final purpose in life...
All right, then, I'll help you do that.
So don't die!
Ha!
It's impossible for a weak little brat like you!
I'll become strong, too!
So... don't die!
Hey!!
Help!! Help the geezer!
Help the damn geezer!!
Hey!! Hey!! Hey!!...
That damn geezer gave up
his leg so that I could live.
Wha?!
I... I can't repay the damn
geezer for his kindness
unless I risk my life for him, too!
Why do you get up... Sanji-san?
In order for this place to be
a restaurant as long as possible...
That idiot... Is he trying to get killed?
You damn brat!
Ha! That's such a refined line.
But this restaurant will be closed now...
...and it will change into a pirate ship!
Stop it, you idiot!
Keep your hands off of them!
What's he trying to do?!
Gum-Gum...
...Battle-Axe!!
Though they call themselves the
strongest pirate group in the East Blue,
it was just because they had so many pirates.
That's all. Right, pops?
You talk very candidly.
Look.
It seems like Ghin can't defeat Sanji, either.
Not quite.
What're those weapons that
look like skewered dumplings?
He wasn't an underling?
Next time, on One Piece:
Cool-headed, Cold-hearted Demon!
Pirate Fleet Chief Commander Ghin!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Cool-headed,
Cold-hearted Demon!
Pirate Fleet Chief Commander Ghin!