All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
After learning about the ruler of the island - Caesar Clown's motive,
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni,
along with their pirate ally - the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar, save the children,
and escape from the island.
What a shame.
Why are you trying to attack the weak ones?
How did the gas flow in?!
I thought the door was closed!
Is it leaking from somewhere?
Really?!
If so, this building is no longer safe!
We have no time!
Let's split up to look for the Sea Prism Stone Handcuffs!
You've been only defending yourself
without even trying to attack. Why is it?
Could it be what I think it is?
To be honest, I didn't think I could beat you but...
...maybe I can.
I'm gonna stay here!
What?!
What are you thinking?
I think you need my help here!
What?
"Showing Off His Techniques! Zoro's Formidable One-Sword Style!"
Alright! Let's go, G-5!
Let's go save the children like Captain-chan said!
Yeah!
I can't believe there is another Logia eater besides Caesar!
That cute harpy-chan was a Devil Fruit user?!
How awful!
We can't handle her!
Black Leg brother!
Why didn't you help us when she was attacking us?!
Don't be such a baby! I don't kick women!
Then what would you do in a life-or-death battle?!
I'd choose death!
That's ridiculous!
They're all so different even though they're in the same pirate crew!
That Pirate Hunter guy looked like
he'd chop up anybody without mercy.
Yeah, yeah.
Surprisingly, he has a soft side too but he will find a way out!
You can count on him.
Don't worry about Tashigi-chan, either!
What we have got to do
is save those damn children to impress Nami-san, Robin-chan, and Tashigi-chan!
Yeah!
All for the ladies!
NEAR THE EXIT OF THE BISCUITS ROOM
Why don't you go with them?
I'm free to do whatever I want!
I don't need you here!
You're free to think whatever you like!
Well then,
am I free to take care
of you first since I'm a pirate, Navy soldier girl?!
You can't do that.
What?!
You're not gonna cut me...
…or that woman!
You don't know that!
That's what I was just thinking.
I was right.
Well then... I'm in a hurry, so...
Why aren't you finishing me off?!
Is it because I'm a woman?!
It's humiliating that you won't fight seriously in a game played
in earnest just because men're physically stronger than women!
I'm sure you don't understand the feeling
that I wish I was born a boy!
I don't carry a sword for pleasure!
I don't like your very being!
Listen! Your face!
It looks exactly like my close friend's who died long ago!
On top of that, you started saying the same thing she used to say!
Don't imitate, you copycat woman!
What?! Stop talking like a child!
You view women as inferior!
You don't really try to fight us!
You won't kill us!
Maybe you're not gonna lose but you're not gonna win either!
That's why I had to stay here!
If I let this Logia eater go after my people, there will be carnage!
Are you looking down on me?!
Yes, I am.
Oh!
Do as you like.
My duty is to keep her from going after my friends, too.
I just wanna keep her away from that path.
How can you take it so easy?
Don't you know that we're out of time?!
You better run, too!
Don't drop your guard. She's willing to kill you.
He's right! Thank you for sharing his weak point!
Even though you can use Haki,
it's not so hard for me to gnaw you to death!
How annoying!
But even if Haki allows you to sense a Devil Fruit user's true form,
you can't catch me unless you can keep up with me!
Isn't that right?!
I thought so.
You're a cold man.
This? Coming from a snow woman?
Pay attention!
Do you like snowball fights?
Snow Rabbit!
Shave!
You're Smoker's right-hand girl.
Maybe I have underestimated you a little bit.
I wonder how he is now.
I know he's pretty strong but Vergo is more...
You don't have to worry about Smoker-san!
You people can't beat him! Not in a million years!
I know that better than anybody!
How scary.
Snowstorm.
Whoa-whoa!
Why is it chasing me?!
B BUILDING - USOPP
Don't follow me!
Alright. It's not gonna be safe here
and I gotta find the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs already!
That was close...
What is this place?
It's dark and I can't see anything!
And it's cold!
The handcuffs... Where are the handcuffs?
I hope there are no monsters in here!
Oh! Oops!
Excuse me, Kin'emon-san!
Where are you hurrying off to?
Corpse-dono! I heard children's voices - they were close!
What?! But that doesn't mean you can leave me here!
The poison gas is coming this way, too!
Momonosuke!
--Oh, children! --Who are you?!
Do you kids know Momonosuke?
He is my son!
--I'm scared! --What?
Wait! Just wait!
What?
There are so many of them!
Momonosuke! Is Momonosuke here?!
Answer me if you're here!
There were still this many kids?!
Alright!
It's dangerous here! Everybody, get to R Building!
A skeleton!
How could you say that? But I'm glad they're fine!
Go to R Building now!
Hey, are you looking for Momonosuke-kun?
Mocha!
Give us the candy!
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - A PATH IN THE BACK
Stop! You can't have it all!
Konbu! Doran! Everybody!
I know it's hard but you can't have it!
There she is! Mocha!
Robin! Hold the children!
Cien Fleurs!
What?! The hands again?!
I'm sorry! I had to do this.
This will ease your pain a bit.
Sis!
Mocha!
Mocha! Don't let them have those candies!
Keep running!
Uh-huh!
Chopper-chan, I'm not gonna give up!
I won't give up - for everyone's sake!
I'm not gonna let anybody have it!
THE BASEMENT OF C BUILDING - A GARBAGE DUMP
Hey, are you alright?!
I'll take it from here, Momo!
Wait for me, Caesar!
I'll say hi to your people for you
and tell them "She died a tragic death."
Sword Snow - Skin Sword!
Wh-What happened to my shoulder?!
What are you doing?! Let go of me!
If I let go of her, she's gonna bite off my shoulder!
I can just shred it to pieces if you prefer!
You talked so big but took so much time.
Time's up.
I have to go now.
I thought he wouldn't cut women.
But he just tried to cut me!
You've underestimated me, snow woman.
When you thought you couldn't beat me,
you should have run.
Of course, there are things that I don't wanna cut.
But...
...let me ask you something.
Have you ever seen a fierce animal you were sure would never bite?
Because I haven't.
Wh-What?!
I can't move!
One-Sword!
He's gonna cut me!
Great Dragon Shock!
Are you two happy now?
He cut her!
How insulting!
What?
Is she still alive?!
He didn't use Haki?
Is this how he shows his mercy?
I guess she can't control her body.
Because she's frightened by his overwhelming strength
and the fact she could have died if he had used Haki!
I've never seen anyone beat somebody like this!
When the Straw Hats disappeared for two years,--
I wonder where they were and what they were doing.
Just how strong have they become?!
Ro... ro... noa... Zoro!
I won't let you get away!
Sword Autumn Rain!
You lose.
What was that?!
You didn't try to kill her after all, did you?!
See, like I said, you're...
I didn't ask you to do that. So shut up.
If you hadn't killed her, I would've.
Don't lie! It's not fair! I already cut her!
You didn't have to do that.
But...
Good job, Captain Eyeglasses.
You stopped her from going after anybody.
You can take the credit.
Why do you always talk like you're greater than me?!
Because I am.
What's wrong?
It's nothing. You can go ahead.
Hey, hey!
Monet... Huh! How useless!
Straw Hats! Make your way to R Building already!
That's where you'll meet your demise!
I can't wait to see you suffer
from the gas and groan, as my test subjects!
While holding the candy, Mocha desperately tries to get away.
But then the crazed children surround her.
Just when the children almost successfully take the candy,
Mocha makes a surprising move,
making Chopper's heartbreaking scream resonate.
Next time, on One Piece:
"To Save Her Friends! Mocha Runs at the Risk of Her Life!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!