Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made a raid on Navy HQ to rescue his brother, Ace, who was to be executed!
But his struggle ended in vain
and the historic Paramount War
at Marineford has ended.
Landing at Maiden Island
The Harsh Reality Falls upon Luffy
West Blue
A pirate ship is approaching Lascamp, West Blue!
All their ships are already engaged!
The nearest bases in that area are...
The 80th division will send back-up!
This is South Blue,
requesting confirmation of location!
Dammit!
I thought pirates would be afraid of us
after killing Whitebeard
and winning the war at Marineford!
Instead of laying low,
they're wreaking havoc everywhere!
What's gotten into them?
Pirates have started raiding Lascamp!
We lost touch with the site! Send back-up!
I repeat, send back-up to Lascamp!
Load up supplies! Let's head for the Grand Line!
New World, Foodvalten Island
Two weeks after the Paramount War,
people started seeing effects around the world.
Y-You can't come any further! Don't come into our town!
You heard the news, didn't you?
Then you know that this island
is no longer Whitebeard's territory.
This symbol is meaningless now!
That's right! Whitebeard is dead!
Listen, and burn this into your mind!
The man who rules this island, from this day forward, is me—
the pirate Brownbeard!
The war ended with Whitebeard's death
and the victory of the Navy.
But contrary to what the Navy thought,
the situation has only grown more tense all over the world.
Meanwhile, not too long ago,
Hancock, Jinbe and the others decided
to head for Maiden Island
to harbor the unconscious Luffy
and joined up with the Kuja's ship.
Big Sis!
Snake Princess-sama!
Sorry that I made you worry,
Sandersonia, Marigold—and you all!
Thank you for your warm greeting!
We are all too grateful
for your great work as Warlord!
Alright then, my duty
to support Straw-boy ends here!
Heehaw!
Do you mind if I leave the rest to you, Jinbe?
Yes. I can't swim very well right now anyway.
The least I can do is see that Luffy recovers fully.
Though I don't know how much help I can be.
It was a curious turn of fate for us to meet.
I agree.
Although we were both locked up
in the greatest prison in the world—Impel Down,
if it weren't for Luffy-kun,
we would have never met each other at all, I suppose.
We both tried really hard to keep up with Straw-boy at Marineford, didn't we?
It's hard for me to say goodbye to you
but I have sweet candies waiting
for me to come back to my kingdom.
Please take good care of Straw-boy!
So long, Straw Hat!
Thanks for giving us our freedom!
Our dream can finally come true because of you!
Give him our regards when he wakes up!
I hope we meet again someday!
Hang in there!
Don't die on us, Straw Hat!
Okay, let's go!
To the New Kamas' homeland and our mecca!
To the Kamabakka Queendom! Heehaw...
We have to head for Maiden Island, too.
And so, the pirate ship carrying Luffy
arrived at Maiden Island—Amazon Lily,
the female-only empire where men are forbidden
and where the Kuja,
a tribe of female warriors, live.
Snake Princess-sama!
Welcome back!
I'm so glad that the princess is safe!
There are men on that strange ship in the back!
Look! There's only women!
So it was true that it's a female-only island!
They snuck in during the Snake Princess' triumphant return?! Unforgivable!
W-Wait!
It smells nice!
I feel lightheaded!
This must be heaven!
Hey, you guys.
You gotta go back in, otherwise you'll die.
Everyone, stop! They're not our enemy!
Snake Princess-sama!
Luffy is on that ship!
He's suffered greatly, mentally and physically,
during the battle at Marineford.
Now he lingers at a point between life and death!
Luffy's here?!
Ladies, carry Luffy to Kuja Castle
as soon as possible!
I'm gonna look after Luffy...
Wait a minute, Snake Princess!
Granny Nyon!
It's fine if it's just Luffy.
But we can't allow the men on that strange ship
to step foot onto Maiden Island.
It's against our country's policy!
Then, let's just allow the doctor
to come with him. That way—
No!
We can't allow any men to come onto the island, even if he's a doctor!
This island already has many good doctors!
Well, I don't care either way but...
...do you have medical equipment
and technology on par with my ship?
If his wound opens up, he's gonna die.
Take Straw Hatter if you don't care about that.
Luffy's gonna die?!
If that were to happen... Oh, I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
It's obvious that we can't save Luffy-kun without this man's help.
If he can't come in, we have no choice.
We must go somewhere else.
Impossible! We'd be attacked by Sea Kings!
Even if we get away from them, the Navy might find us at any time!
What should we do?!
Oh, well... We'll only do it as an exception but...
...you can stay in the bay area.
The Sea Kings won't attack you there.
Then, I'll stay with them to look after Luffy...
No!
Damn Granny Nyon!
You keep rejecting everything I say!
Luffy! Get better soon, alright?
Just by looking at Snake Princess-sama,
I can tell that Luffy is in critical condition.
Luffy...
Maiden Island, Rocky Bay
Two weeks have passed.
Law's group dropped anchor in the bay...
...and is working hard to treat Luffy's wounds.
How much longer do we have to stay confined in such a small space...
You can say that again.
There's only one thing to look forward to here.
Guys, sorry to keep you waiting!
It's meal time.
Finally!
Here it is.
Good food is the only silver lining to all of this.
Agreed!
Here you go!
Thank you...
Please don't push and wait for your turn.
Aphelandra!
Don't talk to the men!
Luffy is the only exception
due to the Snake Princess' orders.
Don't forget!
Okay!
Come on, it's no big deal! Right, Aphelandra-chan?
I'm not gonna say it again!
We're sorry!
Excuse me.
Is Luffy awake?
I see.
It's up to Straw Hatter's spirit.
Whether he's willing to live or not.
Margaret, let's go already!
Coming!
I'm sorry! Please take good care of Luffy!
Margaret, how many times
must I tell you not to talk to them?!
I'm sorry!
Amazon Lily, Kuja Castle
Big Sis...
Luffy...
You never change! Luffy!
You never do as I tell you...
...and always get yourself in big trouble!
Don't do it...
Don't do it!
Stop that, Straw Hat!
Do you wanna destroy the ship?!
Ace...
Luffy-kun!
Where's Ace?!
He's uncontrollable! Calm down, Straw Hat!
What will happen if we leave him like that?
Well, simply put—
As I said when we got here,
if his wound reopens, he could die.
Yes, now's our chance!
Let me go, dammit!
Stay still, Straw Hat!
Shut up! I have to look for Ace!
I told you that Fire Fist is...
I said "let me go"!
Where's Ace?!
Ace!!
Damn! He's out of control!
It's Luffy!
We have to tell Snake Princess-sama!
Snake Princess-sama! Snake Princess-sama!
Luffy woke up!
Luffy-sama?!
Really?!
I'm glad. I wanna see him right away!
You can't, Snake Princess!
Everybody here wants to see him.
If you go see him alone, you'll set
a bad example for the rest of the nation!
This is an island forbidden to men.
Merely allowing those men to anchor in the bay
is an unthinkable violetion of our laws.
I know that, but...
Before that, Big Sis, you need to eat.
She's right, Big Sis!
You've barely eaten since you returned!
That's right! Luffy must be starving!
Make a mountain of food!
He needs plenty of nourishment to recover!
Yes, with pleasure!
I'll help too! Ladies, we must make haste!
Yes, Snake Princess-sama!
I should just let her do this.
She just wants to prepare some food...
Then I'm gonna...
...take it to him!
So you're going?!
We promised that once he gets better,
Luffy alone can enter the kingdom.
Wait just a bit longer!
I won't wait! I am an empress! No one tells me what to do!
No, you can't!
This island has upheld these laws for generations!
Honestly! You've been infected by such a powerful virus!
To think that the fearful
Pirate Empress has become love sick!
But—
First Impel Down and then Navy HQ.
That's like an ant diving into a hurricane!
Returning him alive
is something only a god could do.
What do the heavents want from that man?
Hey, pass me the wrench.
Okay, here you go.
Hey, think you can fix the ship?
Yeah, I'll manage.
That aside, where'd Straw Hat go?
Jinbe's gone, too.
Don't ask me.
You know, they say any man who enters
Maiden Island turns to stone and never comes back.
It might just be worth risking your life for.
According to Aphelandra-chan,
only a small portion of the women were at the port.
The female-only island I've always dreamed of!
I wish I could take a peek inside!
You'll be killed, you idiot.
I wonder if there are female bears here...
It's the Maiden Island!
Sorry.
There's only human women! Only humans!
I'm really sorry!
Where am I?
Maybe it was all a dream...
I'm sorry, Luffy...
I couldn't make it all the way.
Go away! Go away!
Luffy!
No!
Go away! Go away!
If I don't escape death...
I'm sorry but could you look after my brother?
The war is over!
Ace-san is...
Don't say it! Don't say anything!
I've already pinched my cheek hard enough it started to bleed!
If it were a dream, I'd have woken up by now!
It's not a dream, is it?
Ace is really dead, isn't he?!
Yes, he's dead!
Hey grandpa, who's Ace?
Ah, you see...
...he's going to be your big brother from now on.
Luffy, next time we meet,
we'll both be legendary pirates.
See you at the top!
Ace!!
Next week is a special collaboration with Toriko!
Those Barbecue Pigs are scary!
Whew, I'm stuffed!
That was tasty!
Apparently there are lots more of these things!
Really?!
That's what Toriko said!
I wanna go home!
Okay! We're going with Toriko!
What?!
Next week, the special Toriko x One Piece
collaboration episode!
The Strongest Tag-Team!
Luffy and Toriko's Hard Struggle!
"The Strongest Tag-Team!
Luffy and Toriko's Hard Struggle!"
Don't miss it!