Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy comes to rescue his brother Ace
who has been captured by the Navy
by sneaking into Impel Down - the
greatest prison in the world!
Ace-san.
What did she just tell you?
She said that my brother's here!
Swan Arabesque!
It's been a long time! Straw-chan, it's me!
Warden Magellan's Strategy
Straw Hat Entrapment Completed!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
...Gatling!
Spin, spin!
The following prisoners seem to be
helping the invader - Straw Hat Luffy:
Prisoner number E-8200:
Pirate - Buggy the Clown.
Prisoner number D-0464:
Former Baroque Works agent -
Galdino, A.K.A. Mr. 3.
Prisoner number C-9915:
Former Baroque Works agent -
Bentham, A.K.A. Mr. 2 Bon Clay.
Straw Hat Luffy and Mr. 2 Bon Clay
are now in District N on Level 3.
The Blugori are having
trouble subduing them!
Hey, Bon-chan! How can we
get to the lower levels?
There are stairs at the opposite side!
Nice! I'm so glad to see
you, Bon-chan! Thank you!
You needn't thank me!
We were destined to see each other again!
It seems like they're heading
to the staircase to Level 4.
Meanwhile, we lost track of the other
two, Buggy the Clown and Galdino - Mr. 3.
There is a riot going on Level 2 and
the invader is still on the loose!
This is getting interesting!
This is a good way to kill time!
They'll get caught and it'll be over soon!
--Thank you for being understanding.
--No problem.
Here is your cloak.
--Thank you for everything.
--M-My pleasure!
By the way...
Y-Yes?
Earlier, there was a report of an intruder.
Yes, it seems so.
But Impel Down is truly iron-tight.
Now that we have Warden Magellan in command,
I assume that it'll be over soon.
That's good.
Why would you want to sneak into hell?
That guy must be crazy.
Magellan has a deadly power.
Don't get caught, Luffy!
What's Saldeath doing?
The Blugori can't beat
Straw Hat and Mr. 2 so...
...he went to Level 2 to break up the riot.
Why was there no report before
things got this out of hand?!
You weren't paying attention because
you were crazy about Hancock-dono.
I didn't pay attention?
No, you didn't. As Warden, you
need to take responsibility.
Warden!
Can I see the prisoner now?
Okay, let's go! I'm ready to go!
W-Warden! Don't you realize
how serious this is?!
You're stupid.
If only you had checked on it at the time...
Warden! Stop sighing!
I didn't pay attention?!
Or - maybe you did pay attention!
Have the guests left, Warden?
Oh, Sadie-chan!
Salute the commander!
We're ready to go hunting...
What do you say?
You're just the person! Do
you have somebody on Level 3?
Minotaurus... happens to be there!
That's good but there are many
places to hide on Level 3.
It's hard to corner them.
Let's leave the riot to Saldeath and...
...summon all the other forces
of Impel Down to Level 4!
Roger that!
If they manage to escape from Minotaurus
and come down here to the Inferno Hell,
I'll execute them with my own hands!
This great prison Impel Down
is not to be trifled with!
It's hot!
The air is so hot up here.
It's unbelievably hot!
We have no choice.
This is the safest place to be.
But we gotta figure out how to get to Level 1
because we don't have much time!
Oh... I'm totally out of spit!
Are we gonna die like this?
What happened here?
I don't see any of the guards
who were here a while ago.
It's so quiet. Maybe we're dead already.
I have a bad feeling about this!
S-Straw-chan! This is not good!
What's this creature?!
I've never seen moves like those before!
It's Minotaurus!
Minotaurus?!
A cold-blooded Jailer Beast!
A monster that tosses people
around like garbage!
That's who it is!
Jailer Beast
Minotaurus
A monster?! A Devil Fruit user?!
How do I know?!
Bon-chan!
Ouch!
What speed!
Straw-chan, watch out!
Wait just a Fouetté!
I-I can't breathe!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Bazooka!
You alright, Bon-chan?
I almost died!
I saw the great heavenly
garden of Oh Come My Way!
You're very strong, indeed!
I'm sure that the monster's still alive
but I think he must be pretty hurt. Oh?
Oh no no! Fume, fume, fume!
My make-up's been ruined!
Cosmetics, cosmetics! I need some cosmetics!
Plus, pointe shoes and
clothes and weapons and...
...drinks and tears and Oh Come My Way!
I wanna get going now!
I'm thirsty and hungry!
Don't rush, Straw-chan!
It's too-too easy to go down
to Level 4 from here, actually!
Oh, really?!
Yes! It's too-too easy! Much too-too!
--There it is, Straw-chan!
--Heh?
Climb this big wall!
All the way to the top?
Yes! But don't just barge
in! Watch your step!
Alright!
Ow, ow, ow, ouch!
What the hell?! It's hot
like a heated iron pot!
A heated iron pot?
It's something like that,
Straw-chan! Your hand alright?
Here we go!
Ouch!
Ow, ow, ow... Ouch!
Here, Straw-chan! You should
take a look at this!
There's a huge amount of hot air and smoke!
It's hard to even stand here!
Right! But...
...this is Level 4 - the Inferno Hell where you wanna go!
Inferno? Is it down there?
Yes! As you mentioned before, Level
4 is exactly like a giant iron pot!
Once you go down there,
you'll see a boiling pool of blood
and the blazing sea of fire!
The heat on this level is
nothing compared to down there!
We can just jump down from here...
...but if you land on the
wrong spot, you'll be fried.
You're gonna have to risk your life
just to go further from now on!
Bon-chan!
You said that there's
someone that you wanna see.
Who is it that you wanna see
at the risk of your life?
People call him a miracle.
He was imprisoned on a baseless
charge. He's known as Iva-san!
He's the queen of Kamabakka Queendom,
the pink paradise of the Grand Line!
Every queer looks up to this world's
greatest queen of all queers!
The queen of all queers?!
There's a queen for queers?! Wow!
Yes, there is!
I wanna see him even just for a
little bit and rescue him if I can!
Hey! What're you, nuts?! Why're
you bringing him back again?!
You said you were gonna break out!
Straw Hat!
I knew you'd want to come with me!
No one wants to follow you to hell!
He smashed into us while we were hiding!
I dunno why!
--Oh, I knocked him your way.
--Oh, okay... No, it's not okay!
I don't wanna run anymore!
I should've...
I should've let myself
get caught rather than run away!
Stupid monster!
Minotaurus! I'm gonna die!
That leaves me one choice!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Do you remember the Buggy Ball?!
The powerful and special weapon that
I used to make you scared as hell?!
No.
You don't? You can't be serious...
I'm sure that you remember the Buggy Ball!
You were there when I blew up the
whole town with just one shot!
Ka-boom! Remember the ka-boom?!
I think it's hard to forget
something that was so shocking!
No.
Um... Well...
I mean...
There is this big and powerful
cannonball called Buggy Ball...
It's kinda like my special weapon...
Buggy Ball?!
I assume that you have a lot of confidence
in it because you put your name on it!
Yes, I have!
And I made it smaller without reducing
its power so I can carry it around!
--It's called Muggy Ball!
--You changed the name!
Anyway, you take this! The
special weapon - Muggy Ball!
Wow! Cool!
You did it!
It was a piece of cake!
Now, you remember it, Straw Hat?!
Damn! He's still alive!
We can beat him, Straw-chan!
Hey, 3! You sure that you can't
use your Wax-Wax powers?!
--It'll melt in 3 seconds!
--That means you can use it!
Fly, fly, I'm flying!
"Oh Come My Way" Kenpo...
...Memoir of that Winter Sky!
Ready, Straw Hat?!
--Candle Lock!
--Alright!
Gum-Gum...
...Mallet Rifle!
We did it!
We beat the hell beast!
Alright, let's keep it
up and go on to Level 4!
This is Level 4.
All of our forces are rallied
under Warden Magellan!
Stay away!
Luffy!
Buggy and the others want to escape,
while Luffy wants to proceed to Level 4.
In a stroke of good (or bad) luck, an
accident drops all of them into Level 4.
But waiting for them there is
Warden Magellan, who has amassed
all the forces in Impel
Down together to stop them!
Next time, on One Piece:
"All Forces Have Gathered!
Battle on Level 4—the Inferno Hell"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
All Forces Have Gathered!
Battle on Level 4—the Inferno Hell