All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
They learned about the ruler of the island and the puppet master
of Land of the Dead - Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate ally - the Warlord -
Trafalgar Law, were drawn into a climactic battle
which ended with Caesar's defeat.
However...
Goodbye, Young Master.
I know you will become...
...the Pirate King.
Goodbye, Smoker!
What happened, Monet?
Young Master...
Weapon-morphosis!
Revolver Girl!
Oh! It doesn't work!
It just made me itchy!
Alright, we're almost there!
Go faster!
Is it still safe there?
Which means the island and those squirts haven't been wiped out.
You two.
Take care of that guard.
I'm on my way!
"Capture Caesar! General Cannon Blasts!"
THE SEACOAST OF PUNK HAZARD
Now, with that much ordinance, he must be...
What?!
I am an invincible Iron Pirate!
Super!
Even a Pacifista would take damage from that!
What is that bastard?! Why does he stand in our way?!
Because you guys are trying to steal my cola!
Cola?! What is he talking about?!
Cola is my energy source!
So what?!
What's wrong, Weapon Woman? Aren't you gonna transform?
I liked those looks on you!
Then I'll show you!
Weapon-morphosis!
Flying Disc Girl!
Here we go-dasuyan!
That's nothing!
Weapon-morphosis!
Oh? What is it this time?
Fire Girl!
I'm gonna finish you off with this one-dasuyan!
Oh! Ouch! Ow, ow... Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Burn up-dasuyan!
Fire Girl's "flame of love" burns any enemy - it's the most...
Just kidding!
General I'm-Okay!
What?!
N-No way!
Come on, Fan Man and Weapon Woman!
The tunnel is gonna collapse!
Don't collapse before we get to the exit!
Even if we can make it out, there's the gas to deal with!
Hey girl, can you really generate wind?!
Are we gonna be okay?
Hey, hey!
Those of you who don't trust Nami-san, get off!
No, I'm gonna kick you out!
You're scaring us, brother.
We'll be counting on you, Nami!
You're our only hope now!
Trust me!
What is that iron soldier?! Nothing works on him!
I can't let you have my cola!
I said we're not interested in your cola!
He's keeping us too long! We got to take care of him already!
Let's do it, Baby 5!
No one's ever warded off this attack of ours!
No matter what you try,
super nothing will work!
We're gonna chop up your body!
Weapon-morphosis!
Feast your eyes on this weapon that I'm swinging...
Sickle Girl!
Okay, I praise you...
...for your power - you made it through this General body!
But this is like a mantis going up against a warship!
The Thousand Sunny will conquer the whole sea someday.
And I'm gonna give you a taste of
its ultimate secret weapon although you guys don't deserve to see it!
This is a land-based version of Gaon Cannon!
I call it...
General Cannon!
Who is he-dasuyan?!
Why is he preventing us from recovering Caesar?!
Pops! Hold my hand! Hurry!
Isn't that Caesar who's lying there?
How did he get there?
We can't fail! No matter who you're working for!
Whoa-whoa, I can't believe it! They are so tough.
Don't think that we're just ordinary underdogs.
In the name of Joker...
...We're gonna recover Caesar no matter what it takes!
So what you're trying to do is...
recover Caesar over there, isn't it?
Go, truck!
We're almost there!
Alright, we can make it...
What?
Look! The deadly gas is everywhere at the exit!
N-No!
The gas is coming from both front and back!
We have no choice but go through that!
Sis, save us! Please!
Please!
Get us out of here!
Sis, please! Help us!
You can't turn your back on a child crying for help!
I'll keep my word at any cost!
Let's go!
Sorcery Climate Baton!
Gust Sword!
Let's get out!
Keep the wind going, Nami!
The gas will be everywhere outside, too!
I'll accomplish the mission from Joker at any price!
Although I'll kill him when I get back!
You iron soldier!
We won't let you mess with us anymore-dasuyan!
We made it out!
What?!
Yeah!
Oh? Why isn't the gas here?
You've made it here finally! I was getting tired of waiting!
Wow! Look at that!
It's the General!
What?
Super!
--It's a robot! --The ultimate one!
--Wow! Cool! --That's what we boys love!
Yeah, isn't it?!
Buffalo!
Are you Baby 5?!
Law! Are you really going to stand against Joker?!
You traitor!
Joker is still saving the "heart seat" for you!
Who are they? Are they your friends?
No.
They're my enemies!
All of the Straw Hats and the Navy G-5! Odds are against us!
Wh-What's going on, Baby 5?
In any case, we gotta take Caesar to the Young Master!
They took Caesar and ran!
Alright, I got it!
It's a sniper's work to take down a flying enemy!
--Those bastards! --Whoa-whoa!
Usopp said he can handle it.
Don't underestimate our sniper.
Even his nose is too long.
The last part isn't necessary!
No way! If we let them get away, our plan is...
You allied with us, didn't you?
You saw what I did earlier. I need you to trust us a little bit.
Allied? What are you talking about?
I've been running around all this time so...
...I feel like attacking now!
I'm not afraid of enemies who are far away
and have no intention to fight!
On top of that, they're wounded and turning their backs on us!
Alright! Let's just do it!
Now I give you some water.
Okay, let's do it!
Grow Up!
Chomping Grass on Black Kabuto!
Now, eat up and get your fill!
Be careful, Buffalo! They're up to something!
You have to watch my back, Baby 5! Neither of you can fly so I have to!
Let's complete the mission!
What?!
Okay! You need me, don't you?
I'll defend you with my life!
Go! Weather Egg!
Something's flying this way!
Now, hatch! Thunder-chan!
Thundercloud?!
Buffalo! I have a bad feeling!
I can't go any faster than this!
No, you can't get away!
The Science of Weather!
Thunderbreed...
No!
...Tempo!
Baby 5! Damn, she got hit!
Here is a final blow! Go, Chomping Grass!
Special Attack - Charging Shooting Star!
Go!
H-Hey, Buffalo! You got to protect me.
I can't move myself!
O-Of course! Don't underestimate me.
I'm a member of Don Quixote's family!
I'll complete a mission at any cost!
Idiot! What a good-for-nothing!
You can't hit me, fool! I'm a gas man!
I-I must make it to Dressrosa with or without them!
You can't run! The last ammo is...
Wh-What is this?!
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
Alright, I caught him!
That serves you right, Caesar!
You can count on me when an enemy turns his back...
Alright!
All right. the initial phase is accomplished.
See? They are strong, aren't they?
Wait for me!
Squirts!
I overslept.
Which way is Punk Hazard?