Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
After learning about the ruler of the island -
Caesar clown, aka the Master's motive,
and all while trying to escape Land of the Dead, the weapon of mass destruction,
along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar,
save the children, and escape from the island.
Jet Spear!
The floor!
What tremendous hidden strength he has.
But falling through here
will land him in the slide to the garbage dump deep underground.
He'll never be able to come back up unless he can fly.
I didn't expect him to sabotage himself like that.
Goodbye!
It didn't work!
I was pretty sure that I could take my heart back from Caesar.
But I didn't expect you here.
Vergo!
It's Vergo-san to you!
I'm in the middle of something.
Does it have to be now?
Vice Admiral Smoker.
"Fists Collide! A Battle of the Two Vice Admirals!"
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - BISCUITS ROOM
Mocha, those sweet candies are for everybody, aren't they?
Stop fighting.
Share and eat them together as usual.
No!
We shouldn't eat them anymore!
You're a difficult girl.
Hey, what have you done?!
Yeah, we don't have any time for you!
How could you say such a thing?
I know about you people so well.
The infamous Straw Hats.
I'm happy to see you.
Who the hell are you?!
I'm Monet, a Snow-Snow Fruit eater.
Usopp! Brook!
I'll try to restrain the children here!
You two, go find some Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs?!
Why?
Luffy asked me to find them!
I don't know why but...
You can count on me to find things!
I'll come with you!
I have to find Momonosuke!
All right! Let's go!
D BUILDING - THE "SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
What are those?
This room's really disturbing.
That's none of your business.
Hey, why are you looking away?
I haven't given up yet.
I'll take care of you later.
Why don't you just shut up and grovel on the ground?
Vergo.
I don't want the soldiers to know the truth about you.
They admire you like a father.
It's a serious breach of trust.
I can't believe
you're Joker's dog.
It's too late.
I just saw them a few minutes ago.
What did you do to them?!
I don't remember.
Vergo!
You're heating up, Smoker-kun.
Don't tell me
you're worrying about those Navy misfits.
I'm a base commander.
I can do whatever I want to my good-for-nothing subordinates.
Plus, you're gonna have to die anyway
since you know who I really am now.
Even if you've known them for a long time
and even if you're a base commander
which I don't acknowledge now,
once we're out of the base,
an unit commander is responsible for the troops' life.
Don't lay a hand
on my men!
B BUILDING - THE G-5 AND SANJI
What's going on here?
Ouch! Ow! Ow!
There is no place to step!
What happened here?!
Hurry up!
Carry the injured and let's go!
We gotta protect Tashigi-chan!
Stop it!
Don't be so friendly!
He's our enemy!
That's just how people would define our relationship!
But pirates are free!
When you gave the Vergo impostor a blow, brother,
you looked so cool - even I could fall in love!
Yeah, you looked so hot, brother!
Shut up!
I said I don't need support from guys!
Stop calling a pirate "brother"!
The tank exploded!
It caught fire!
Hey,
that's not good!
There is a crack on the outer wall!
Another explosion!
What the hell!
Run, guys!
Huh? What's wrong?
You look pale.
The gas is flowing in from the outside!
The deadly gas from earlier!
What?!
Run if you don't wanna die!
No!
This B Building is very big
but it'll be filled up with the gas in no time!
Stand up already!
Tashigi-chan, you have to lead them!
If you lose your way, you'll die!
Don't go the wrong way!
Black Leg!
Come on, guys!
You're gonna die if you're too slow!
Everybody! This way!
R BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - THE SECRET ROOM
They're so dumb!
They let Land of the Dead in themselves!
But...
...letting them die there won't help
bring my experiment show to completion!
Hey, close the gates to Building C and D!
Yes, sir. What about the one to R?
Keep that one open.
I want to lure them into the first floor of R Building.
They're trying to get to R Building - gate 66 anyway.
I don't want them to take an unnecessary side trip
so let's just guide them!
C BUILDING - A GARBAGE DUMP
That was awful.
Where am I?
It's broken.
So is this a garbage dump?
I guess I fell all the way down to the deep underground.
I'm hungry!
Come to think of it, I had been running for so long!
Isn't there something to eat?
Damn!
It's all garbage!
Be careful, you insolent fellow!
I really don't like this room!
The "secret room" on the second floor of R Building.
I didn't wanna come to this shitty room.
But I can't let the Straw Hats do whatever they like.
They pushed it a little too far.
I've got Joker on my back.
Once they come this far, I'll kill them all perfectly!
Master!
We have been ready to fight since yesterday!
So why did you summon us here
to the former office of that despicable Vegapunk?
Vegapunk is also an enemy to us
since he caused the accident four years ago!
Isn't there anything we can do?!
Shouldn't we fight them?!
No, you shouldn't.
You people are the best soldiers I have!
I don't want you to shed your blood for nothing!
M-Master...
All right. Let me explain about the plan.
When we close the gates to C and D as I said before,
the only open paths left
are the ones connected
to the first floor of R Building which is below this room.
The Straw Hats, the G-5, or the children.
Doesn't matter if they're our enemies or not,
the only place those survivors can get to is going to be the room below.
There are some air vents on the first floor of R Building.
So we can let the air from outside - that is to say, Land of the Dead - flow in.
And then there is no turning back.
Who can survive that?!
When we close all the gates,
it will become a big gas chamber!
We're gonna broadcast what's going on in that room
for all the underground brokers in the New World!
So they will see what I'm capable of!
P-Pardon me for asking this, Master Caesar.
Did you create that deadly poison gas?
Yes, I did.
It's like Vegapunk's poison gas
that spread all over the island after the accident four years ago.
So it freaks us out, to be honest.
It's horrible.
Master?
This is...
...an avenging battle of science!
My people!
That day,
I tried to stop...
...the mad scientist -
Vegapunk!
"No! If such a weapon explodes,
what's gonna happen to the people on the island?!"
"Stop it, Vegapunk!"
But the accident happened.
On top of that, he still lords over us
as the head of the science department of the Navy!
And he's considered the world's greatest scientist!
I can't tolerate it!
He's the cruel man who hurt you all!
Do you think it's right that people still call him the No.1 scientist?!
Master!
That's why I want to prove them wrong!
I didn't want to make a weapon of mass destruction
but I want to show them that there is a greater scientist here!
That I am the greatest scientist in the world!
When the Navy acknowledges it
and when I become the top of the science department,
my dream will come true.
I can use my scientific knowledge to bring peace to the world!
Master!
I'm sorry, Master! We should be ashamed for suspecting you!
You're the savior after all!
Master!
Thank you! Thank you all!
Stop it, Caesar!
You have to abort the experiment now!
If such a weapon explodes,
what's gonna happen to the people on the island?!
Shut up, you boneheads!
Where do you think you are?
This is the Navy's research facility!
The Navy wants to kill as many pirates as they can
and what they need is a weapon that will do it for them!
That's not true!
They don't want a weapon that would also kill civilians!
You're so dumb!
It's called collateral damage!
Those who get themselves involved must be stupid!
If we blow away everything,
we can bring peace to the world.
You're so...
You want to say I'm cruel?
You've got to be kidding me!
You're using the damn prisoners
as your guinea pigs as if they're real trash!
What's the difference?
The incumbent fleet admiral, Sengoku, is too soft.
But Admiral Red Hound would want a weapon that I make.
If you finally get it, then go away!
You're disturbing me.
Vegapunk must be jealous of me because I'm such a genius!
I heard he failed to turn people into giants again.
You can't make people bigger in a short period of time unless you use magic.
So I kept telling him:
He should just go kidnap some kids
who are still developing
and try every drug he can think of!
Caesar...
That's it! That's it!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Don't fight!
Do you think you can talk to me like that?!
I'm almost finished making a weapon
that you guys have only dreamed of!
Vegapunk! What's going on here?!
You're dismissed from the science department, Caesar.
Your eccentric behavior is intolerable and I can't protect you anymore.
Screw you!
Don't do it, Caesar!
Fools!
Vegapunk, the Navy, Straw Hat, and these guys right here,
they're way less intelligent than me -
they're all dumb as a brick!
Now, let's do it!
The gate between C and B is closed!
The gate between D and B is closed!
No one can enter Building C and D from B Building now!
Run like hell!
Did you just say something?
Who the hell are you?!
Wh...
Who...
...are you?!
Deep within the depths of Building C, which is said to be inescapable,
Luffy finds himself in a desperate situation and is then greeted by a small dragon.
The dragon calls himself a warrior and has overcome a strange fate.
Because of their chance meeting, Luffy decides to take action.
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Small Dragon! Momonosuke Appears!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!