Soo gooood!!
Seconds!
Sorry, it's going to be a bit more 'til they're ready.
Those ones look fine to me! Gimme those!
Like hell I will!
The essence of barbeque is in roasting it perfectly!
Learn to be a little patient, would you?
You bastard! Gimme back my meat!
Ah, I've got a nosebleed.
Brook, you bastard!
What the hell are you looking at?!
Here I go!
The meat ready yet?
What?
I thought I told you it's not ready yet!
I'm sorry...
I've seen the error of my ways!
Match, set!
I guess it's our loss, huh?
Winner...
Team Nami and Chopper!
What?!
Using Devil Fruit abilities is against the rules.
Ah, that's too bad.
Yay~!
Nami,
Your prize for winning. As promised.
Thank you for your patronage.
I can't wait...
Until we get to Gran Tesoro, the City of Dreams!
Especially the amusement park!
It has more than just an amusement park!
A giant shopping mall with the latest, cutting-edge fashion...
A colossal theater and amusement park...
An enormous luxury hotel and spa resort...
And to top it all off...
The casino!!!
It's got it all!
I see!!
Then, I'm going to head straight to the luxury hotel and stuff myself at the buffet!
I hear they have an all-you-can-eat imperial banquet open 24 hours a day!
Just what kind of delicious food is waiting for us?!
Not to mention, the unique show the dancers will put on for us.
I'm going to head straight to the bathhouse and drink the best sake the world has to offer.
In that case, I'll take care of the cola!
For crying out loud...
You guys have no taste for refinement.
You can't even imagine how to live it up right?
You're missing the best part.
What a stupid fantasy.
What was that, you punk?
Alright, alright.
What are you going to do, Robin?
Let's see...
Perhaps I'll unwind a bit and indulge in some beauty treatment.
Be-Be-Beauty treatment?
You idiot.
There's medicine for stuff like that, you know.
Next time, I'll make some medicine for idiots!
All that sounds great and all, but where are we gonna get the money for it?
You've got a point there.
This is all the money we have to spend right now.
Just that coin from earlier?
Listen up, everyone!
With this one-hundred berry coin...
We're going to win so much at the casino that we can splurge on!
But...
What if we end up losing it?
If that happens...
We'll just have to accept a small donation from the casino bank.
Oi, oi, oi, oi...
Geez... I can't leave anything to you guys.
Lucky for us, I've got a great idea!
I call it...
"The Hero Yokozuna Kintarou Show!"
A show?
Please allow me to assist with the production!
Come one, come all!
To the Hero Yokozuna Kintarou Show!
Once upon a time...
Deep in the mountains...
There was a boy named Kintarou Luffy.
Everyday, Kintarou-san would use the animals of the forest as his own punching ba -
...Err, I mean, played sumo with them.
Stop wasting all our salt!
This isn't a serious fight.
You get that, right?
We're just pretending!
I got it!
Now then, let's begin!
Huh?
Eat this!!
What happened?
Weren't you supposed to dodge that?
You're not suppose to start until the ref says, "It's time, both hands down!"
Hey!
You're going to damage the ship! Tone it down a bit!
That's what you're worried about?!
Hey, you trying to kill me, you bastard?!
We agreed on me winning the first round, didn't we?!
Usopp sure is sturdy.
It's time, both hands down!
Like I said, we're just pretending!
Show some restraint!
Why are you so close?
Move back further! Further!
Put some spirit into it! You're still in it!
Ah, time-out, I'm thirsty.
Hey! There's no calling time-out for that!
Put some spirit into it!
Kintarou-san, your big moment isn't until the second half!
You're still in it!
Why, you!
Stop playing dirty!
Kicking is against the rules!
Stop it!
I'm the referee!
I brought some more glasses of lemonade!
Thank you.
I also brought some suntan lotion!
Sanji, could I get some over here too?
The suntan lotion!
You do it yourself!
I want to get some more sun-tanning done!
Not that I have any skin to be tanned in the first place, though!
Here!
Alright!
Imitation Zoro!
Slice!
I'm not done yet!
Yes, you are!
Weapons are also against the rules!
Well, it's a show after all!
It's flashier this way, don't ya think?
Hold on a second there...
Let's stop with this silly farce already.
Silly farce?
Sumo is a serious sport where two men face-off against
each other using nothing but their own skill and power.
How about you face me?
Okay!
I'm not handing the title of yokozuna over to anybody!
The title of yokozuna is mine to take!
It's time, both hands down!
You're still in it!
It's time for you to take a little dive!
Looks like I win!
Hey ref! No matter how you look at it, he's already outside of the ring!
No! It's not over 'til his feet touch the ground!
This intensity in the air...
Get him, Luffy!!
That's what I'm talking about, Franky!!
Give it your all, you two!!
There's no way I'm giving up the title of yokozuna!
Let's settle this with the next blow.
Bring it on!
Take this!
The title of yokozuna is mine!!
Every single time...
What the hell are you two doing?!
What're you gonna do if the ship breaks?!
The yokozuna is Nami!
Huh?
I present you with the winning prize. The yokozuna rope is yours.
Now then...
If you will, Nami-san.
If you would just lift your leg for me.
Oh, my stars!
I don't want that dirty thing!
Hey Nami, what's that light over there?
Nami?
Everyone, looks like we've arrived.
That's...
Gran Tesoro?!