Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
Twenty years ago,
everything was taken away from me
and many people's lives
were ruined.
It was caused by a single attack--
Buster Call.
That attack is now...
...targeted on the friends I was finally
able to find, whom I can be myself with.
The more I wish to be with you,
the more my fate
will show its fangs to you!
No matter how far I go on the sea,
I have a huge enemy
that I can't shake off...
...because the world and
its darkness are my enemy!
The incident with Blue Pheasant,
as well as this time...
I've already dragged you
into my troubles twice!
If this continues forever, even though
you guys're good-natured...
...you'll eventually feel
that I'm a burden!
I'm sure you'll betray me
one day and abandon me!
That's what I'm most afraid of!
That's why I didn't want
you to come to rescue me!
If I'm going to die someday anyway,
I want to die
right here, right now!
I see!
That indeed is a sound argument!
That's true.
No one is stupid enough
to think that having you isn't a burden.
Look at that symbol,
you damn pirates!
That logo indicates the unity
of over 170 member countries
spanning the four seas
and the Grand Line!
This is the world!
Do you now realize how completely
powerless you guys are to fight against it?!
Do you realize how huge
of an organization
this woman has been pursued by?!
I now understand well the
identity of Robin's enemy.
Sogeking.
Shoot through that flag.
Roger.
This is my new weapon,
a huge slingshot...
named Kabuto!
Have a good look at its power!
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
Oh, no...!
Mission accomplished.
Th-They've gone and done it!
Do they understand what it
means to attack the flag?!
The pirates declared war
against the World Government!
Are you insane?!
Don't think that
you'll be able to survive
after making the entire
world your enemy!
Bring it on!
Robin!
We still haven't heard you say it!
Say you want to live!
Robin...
Robin!
To live...
I thought it was something
I dared not wish for.
No one ever let me wish for it.
The sea is vast,
so someday, definitely...
...you'll come across friends
who'll protect you!
Believe in Luffy.
If...
it's really okay for me
to utter my wish for once...
I...
I want to live!
Take me to the sea with you!
You guys...!
I love you guys, dammit!
Let's go!
"I Wont Hand over the Blueprints!"
Franky's Decision
Okay! We pulled the lever!
All right!
Looks like Mozu and the
others did okay, too.
Go, Straw Hat!
The drawbridge is coming down!
Looks like they pulled through.
Good timing.
I-I'm trembling with anticipation!
Lower that bridge already.
He looks evil.
Robin!
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
Stay there!
They're in high spirits.
To think that they don't fear
the flag of the Government...
How pointless.
There's no way
that they could defeat us.
Stay there!
The drawbridge is coming down!
Go! Straw Hat!
How dare those damn pirates?!
We're not gonna let it happen!
Get the trench mortar ready!
Stop the drawbridge!
Break it if you have to!
Yes, sir!
I'm not gonna let you do that!
Pipe Hitch Knives!
This is the end of you!
Demolition Chop!
Chief Justice Baskerville!
Too bad!
We're actually
the Chief Justice trio!
What?!
I, the Left Baskerville,
am named Bas!
I, the Right Baskerville,
am named Kerville!
And I, the Center Baskerville,
go by the name...
...Princess!
What the heck?!
So those three were just
sticking together? That's all?
What for?!
We're good friends!
Shut up!
Fire the trench mortar!
The drawbridge
stopped coming down?!
How dare they get in our way?!
Damn bastards!
Who's doing this?!
Chief Spandam!
Please evacuate
from the Tower of Law!
All right! Good job!
I'm gonna head to the Gate of Justice
before they come over to this side!
Come, Nico Robin!
Someone! Bring Cutty Flam!
Robin!
Those pirates are just nobodies.
I've got the assassin group
CP9 on my side!
Nico Robin, a survivor
of the island of scholars
who schemed to bring back
the weapon...
Cutty Flam, who inherited
the weapon's blueprints...
I'm definitely not gonna stand back and
miss this opportunity to gain big power!
Cutty Flam...
That's...
Hey... don't tell me...
...those are the ancient
weapon Pluton's blueprints...!
They're the real deal.
Do you believe me?
Lucci... Kaku...
You guys can tell, right?
I thought it was unlikely...
So you were hiding them
inside your body, huh?
T-The real ones?!
Are those the real ones?!
Hand them over...
Hand them over to me!
Those are my long-sought
blueprints!
Nico Robin.
Rumors are such unreliable things,
aren't they?
While we were being
brought to this damn place,
I came to realize
that you aren't the evil
who's trying to misuse the weapon.
How to build the weapon isn't
what the Water Seven's shipwrights
have been inheriting for
generations in the first place.
Tom-san achieved
so many great things,
and he gave up everything in order to
preserve these blueprints for the future.
At least, as long as there's a risk
that a woman named Nico Robin
can restore the weapon,
the world needs
those blueprints to fight back.
Hey, Spanda.
What Tom-san and Iceberg
risked their lives to protect is...
Hand them over to me already!
...the wish of this
weapon's architect--
that is, if the ancient weapon fell
into the hands of an idiot like you
and started being used
to cause trouble,
he would want another weapon
to be built in order to stop it.
It's true that if you use Nico Robin,
you can revive the ancient weapon.
Even if she doesn't
want to help you,
as long as there's a chance
that she could be used,
she's still dangerous.
But she's got friends
who would be willing to risk
their lives to protect her.
So I'll...
...take a chance.
I can think
of only one way that I could
uphold the architect's wish in this situation.
Just shut up and hand them
over to me already!
Those are mine!
Tom-san...!
In this situation,
I'm sure you'd also...
I can think
of only one way that I could
uphold the architect's wish in this situation.
Just shut up and hand them
over to me already!
Those are mine!
Tom-san...!
In this situation,
I'm sure you'd also...
You bastard!
What're you doing?!
It's burned black!
Dammit!
I'm gonna kill you!
Our five-year mission...
The blueprints were kept in order
to create a weapon to fight back...
And you, the Government,
came after them a second time.
Essentially, something like
this should remain a secret,
and so once it's revealed,
it has to be eliminated.
Now, there's no longer power to
fight back against the ancient weapon.
If nothing is done and Nico Robin
falls into your hands,
it'll be hopeless.
But if the Straw Hats win...
...there won't be anything
left to you at all.
I made a bet on their victory.
How dare you mock me...?
Seems like you want
to die here, too, huh?
Bro!
Big Bro Franky!
Hey look!
Bro is at the Tower of Law!
Good! He's fine!
That's Bro!
Bro!
We came to rescue you!
We came with the Straw Hats!
Sodom and Gomorrah
fought hard, too!
Bro!
Let's go back together!
Are you hurt?!
Y... You guys...
You idiots...
Who asked you to come...
To come rescue me?!
You idiots!
Bastards! I'm not crying!
Shut up, you bastards!
What are you, a demon?!
Robin's waiting!
Hurry up
and bring down the bridge!
Oh, yeah, right.
Hurry up, you bastards!
That's right!
Hurry up, you guys!
Or I'm gonna beat you up!
Y-Yeah, you're right.
I like you when you're contradictory
like that, too, Nami-san!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Looks like you helped
my underlings.
But this time,
I, their boss, the great Franky,
will add my super fighting power
to you guys!
Whatever!
I'm still holding what
you did to Usopp against you!
Err... well,
he's right next to you...
Cutty Flam...
How dare you...
...burn my blueprints?!
Ahhh! Bro!
Bro is falling into the falls!
Franky!
Hey, pirates!
What?! Kokoro-san?!
I heard everything!
What're you guys wasting time for?!
Wasting time?
But the
bridge is only halfway down.
Halfway is good enough!
We'll be there in four seconds.
What the hell is that?!
Jump with all your might
towards the falls!
That's... from earlier...!
Is that Granny?
What does she mean?
I don't know.
But she said
jump towards the falls.
A-A sea train?!
Why is it coming into the courthouse?!
Chimney, sound the
whistle with gusto.
Okay!
The sound of the sea train?
What's the meaning of that smile?
Chief Justice!
Please get out of here!
Stop!
Here we go!
I knew it!
Nooo!
Rocketman can still run!
Don't underestimate Tom's Workers,
a legendary ship-building company!
R-Rocketman?!
It's flying again!
What?!
They're coming!
It's a waterfall!
This brings back memories,
doesn't it, Tom-san?
About assisting that Roger guy...
I'm resolutely proud of it!
I'm Luffy.
I'm the man
who'll become Pirate King.
Really?!
Yeah.
Roger
was an idiot like him,
too, wasn't he?
And you helped him out.
Seems like we didn't learn our lesson.
Everyone in Tom's Workers
is helping this pirate kid.
You would've done the same,
wouldn't you, Tom-san?
We're gonna collide!
W-We're gonna crash!
As it stands,
Robin will be in danger.
We have to do something before
they go through the Gate of Justice.
So that means we have to defeat
CP9 and get those five keys, huh?
In any case, we don't
have much time.
Everyone! Take them down
even if it costs you your life!
Just wait, Robin!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Obtain the Five Keys!
The Straw Hat Pirates vs. CP9"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Obtain the Five Keys!
The Straw Hat Pirates vs. CP9