Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Yuba
Nanohana
Katorea
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
and a mighty swell.
After arriving in Alabasta, Luffy and the others
encountered Navy Captain Smoker.
There to save Luffy in the nick of time
was the man who controls fire: Fire Fist Ace.
Ace turned out to be Luffy's older brother.
Ace and Luffy!
Hot Emotions and
Brotherly Bonds
Move.
I'm afraid that's a no-can-do.
Fire Fist Ace...
To think you're Straw Hat's brother...
White...
Spark!
Wh-What is that?!
– Is a house on fire?!
– No, it's no ordinary fire!
What in the world is happening?
It's a fight between flame and smoke?!
He did say he ate the Flame-Flame Fruit.
But Luffy!
Is it true that guy's your brother?!
Yeah! His name's Ace!
You having a brother isn't that surprising,
but what's he doing in the Grand Line?!
Ace is a pirate!
He left the island three years
before me to find the One Piece!
A-Anyways, let's hurry back to the ship!
Let's escape before anyone comes after us!
Yes, Nami-san!
Still, I never thought I'd
see Ace in a place like this!
The path splits into two!
Usopp, left! Hear me, guys?!
Yes, Nami-san!
I'll follow you wherever you go!
Enough, pervy cook!
Cool! The fireball's gone even higher!
It seems there really is no end to
a fight between flame and smoke.
Though it was already obvious enough.
Where did Straw Hat's crew go?
Th-They're gone!
So is Ace! We've lost sight of him!
I caught Straw Hat for the
first time in the Grand Line...
But Portgas D. Ace.
You simply had to get in the way.
Hurry and load the stuff!
We're leaving right away!
Hurry!
Set the sails!
S-Say. Are we leaving again just
after we finally reached the island?
Yes. We only stopped by this town
to get what we're going to need.
Now we're going to head up the
river into the interior of Alabasta.
Our next destination is Erumalu,
the City of Green.
Erumalu?
Hurry!
Pick up the pace!
All set!
Okay! Let's set sail!
Y'know...
Huh?
I get the feeling we're missing someone...
So do I...
Yeah.
We're missing approximately one person.
That moron!
Huh?!
That's weird.
Why am I the only one here?
Where did they go?
Sheesh! I guess my letting you
escape was pretty much pointless.
Yo!
Ace!
Haven't seen you in a while, Luffy!
You too, Ace!
How many years has it been?
Good question.
But, Luffy. It looks like you
still go at your own pace,
just like you did since you were a kid.
You too, Ace!
I was surprised you ate a Devil Fruit,
but besides that, you're the same!
Like when you'd sneak into the fields,
eat 100 watermelons,
and then spit the seeds out like a gun and run!
That wasn't me! That was you!
And then you got big bumps right here!
That was you, too!
I watched and laughed!
I guess we're both the same!
Yeah!
This brings back memories!
Say, weren't your friends looking for you?
Yeah.
But, Ace.
What are you doing in this country?
Huh? You mean you didn't get
the message I sent to Drum?
Drum?
Yeah.
It's no big deal or anything, though.
I'm just in these waters on minor business,
so I thought I might look you up.
Minor business?
I'm a member of the Whitebeard Pirates now.
Whitebeard Pirates?
This is the mark of the Whitebeard Pirates.
It's my pride.
Oh?
Luffy.
Won't you join the Whitebeard Pirates?
Your friends can come too, of course.
No.
I figured not. Just thought I'd ask.
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate I know.
I wanna help him become Pirate King...
And not you, Luffy.
That's fine!
Then we'll just have to fight!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King.
Hey! Don't drink it all, Luffy!
Something must've happened in town.
Smoker and all the marines left the ship...
But...
This is perfect!
I'll use this chance to escape somehow!
Mr. 11.
You must be members of Baroque
Works if you know my codename!
Are you Millions?! Hurry and untie me!
Yeah, we are members of Baroque Works.
But we're Billions.
Meaning we're candidates to be Number Agents.
Mr. 11. You're barely an agent.
You're not much stronger than us.
O-Oh! I see!
Sorry about that, Billions.
But could you hurry and untie me?
Don't be silly!
With you gone, one of us can
be promoted to a Number Agent.
So let's empty one of the Agents' seats!
W-Wait!
Hey!
Fire Fist Ace is in this town!
What?! Fire Fist Ace?!
The Second Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates?
If we can take down Ace,
we're guaranteed to be Number Agents!
Anyways, let's look for your friends.
Getting spotted by the Navy's always a pain.
They might've gone back to the ship.
Which harbor is your ship in?
Actually, I can't remember at all.
Oh, geez.
Pirate ship captains usually remember where they leave their ship.
Don't worry about it!
You are the same as ever.
Say, what kind of crew do you have?
A swordsman who wants to be the
world's greatest sword master.
He's always wearing a haramaki.
A navigator who likes maps
and tangerines and money!
Then there's a cook who
makes really yummy food...
Oh, and there's a liar, too!
And then a reindeer!
That's quite the variety you got there.
We also have a princess and a duck now!
Oh?
They're all so interesting!
I'd say you're probably the
most interesting of all, though.
Still, only a handful of people for a
pirate crew... That's just like you.
I also want a musician!
Stop right there, Fire Fist Ace!
As you can see, there's no place to run now!
Fire Fist Ace! Your head is mine!
Prepare yourself!
I-Is it really okay to set sail without Luffy?
The Navy will be all over the harbors.
We need to hide the ship first.
There should be a cove ahead
that's hidden from view!
So we'll wait for things to cool down,
then look for Luffy.
Yeesh!
He's always, always causing trouble like this!
He's a real reliable captain...
Fire Fist Ace! Your bad luck ends here!
Hey! Isn't that Straw Hat Luffy?!
N-Now that you mention it...!
H-He's worth thirty million berries!
Talk about lucky!
Fire Fist Ace and Straw Hat Luffy!
Once I have your heads, our promotion
is a hop, skip, and jump away!
Anyway, let's find your ship.
Let's go to the shore.
Yeah.
Hey, you!
Hold it right there!
Bastards!
Get them!
Take this!
What the...?! What the...?!
So sorry!
Hold the bastard down!
Wh-What the...?! His arms stretched!
He has Devil Fruit powers?!
Don't scare me like that, you jerks!
Gum-Gum...
Oww! Hot!
...Bazooka!
D-Don't let 'em scare you!
The rank of Number Agent is riding on this!
After them!
Oh! The ocean!
See your ship?
There's no escape!
You guys just never learn.
Oh! There it is!
Hey! Over here! Guys!
Hey, Luffy. Go on...
Never mind.
Oh! There he is! It's Luffy!
I found Luffy!
You did?
Yeah. That stupid face is definitely his.
Huh?!
I'm back!
Sanji-san! Tony-kun!
Oh, come on!
Not again...
Sorry 'bout that, Sanji, Chopper!
Do you not know how to learn your lesson?!
I oughta gut you whole!
Yeah! Do you have any idea how
much trouble you've caused?!
Try to act somewhat like a captain!
Sorry.
Oh, that's right! Ace!
Ace?
Your brother was with you?
Is it okay to just leave him there?
I guess he'll be okay! Ace is strong!
He's strong?
Yeah! He hadn't eaten the
Flame-Flame Fruit a long time ago,
but I still never beat him in a single fight!
He's real strong, Ace is!
There's a flesh-and-blood
person you could never beat?!
I guess the big brother of a monster is an even bigger monster...
That's right! I lost all the time!
But I'd win now if we tried!
I assume that's another groundless claim.
Who...
can win what now?!
Oh! Ace!
This is the crew I was talking about!
Oh! Thank you all for taking
care of my little brother!
Eh? Oh, not at all.
He might be a bit much for
you to handle too, but...
No, not at all.
Take good care of 'im.
You probably have lots of catching up to do.
Why don't you come in?
I'll make some tea.
No, uhh, that's okay.
Don't do it on account of me.
T-Talk about unexpected...
That's for sure.
I would've expected him to
be as reckless as Luffy...
No, this sensible man can't
possibly be Luffy's brother!
He's a nice guy who cares about his brother!
Brothers can be so wonderful!
The sea is just full of surprises...
Come now, everyone!
See! Aren't these guys neat?!
Baroque Works!
Those are the Billions' ships!
Fire Fist Ace and Straw Hat Luffy!
Don't think you can get away!
We'll show you just what Baroque
Works' Billions are made of!
Those guys again?
Luffy. I'll clean them up.
Eh?
What's he going to do?
Especially in that little boat...
Let's see how skilled
this Second Division Commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates really is!
Here he comes! Fire Fist Ace!
Just try to get past five of our ships, if you can!
He jumped!
F-Fire!
Shoot him into the ocean!
Fire Fist!
Whoa!
Captain Smoker!
Straw Hat Luffy and his crew
are nowhere to be found.
What do you think, Tashigi?
Vivi was with them.
Vivi? Princess Nefertari Vivi
was with the Straw Hats?
She must be a hostage.
They abducted the princess
for some sort of scheme...
No.
Vivi was acting like she was part of the crew.
The princess? Part of their crew?
Something really is happening in this country.
Captain Smoker!
I'm sorry, sir!
Mr. 11 was done in by someone
while he was tied up on the ship!
We still haven't located the Straw Hats, either!
No need to fret.
I have a good idea of where they're headed.
He's after Crocodile.
Crocodile?!
One of the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
the pirates given Government approval?!
You know I hate the Seven Warlords.
Especially that detestable man.
B-But standpoint-wise,
he's a Navy and Government ally!
He's always been a clever pirate.
He's never been the type to just
quietly obey the Government!
Tashigi!
All you need to remember is one thing!
A pirate is a pirate, no matter where he goes!
Straw Hat will show up wherever Crocodile is!
Things should become clear if we go there.
And next time, you won't get away, Straw Hat!
Woohoo!
Ace is one of us now!
Cheers!
Who said I was joining you?
Here's to delicious drinks!
Cheers!
Don't worry about it!
They're always looking for an excuse to drink to!
Medicine is horrible!
Ace! Are you sure you won't join us?
I'm chasing a certain man.
His name's Blackbeard.
Blackbeard?!
He's the pirate who attacked Drum Kingdom!
He used to be a member of the 2nd
Division of the Whitebeard Pirates,
one of my men.
But he committed the worst
possible sin on a pirate ship:
he killed a crewmember and jumped ship.
So, as the commander,
I gotta find and get rid of him.
So that's why you're chasing after him?
I came here because I caught word
that Blackbeard was seen in Yuba.
Then your destination is the same as ours!
We've just entered the Sandora River.
First, we'll land at Erumalu,
then head into the interior of Alabasta
to reach Yuba here!
The leader of the rebel army is in Yuba.
I see. So you're headed to Yuba next.
I'll follow Nami-san and
Vivi-chan wherever they go!
Get lost, Love Cook.
Say what, you...?!
A-Anyways! It looks like we can
travel together for a short while!
Yeah, yeah!
His brother is more than welcome here!
Let's have a fun time, Ace!
Yeah!
Kodomo no koro yume mita boukenka mitai de
Like the adventurers I dreamed of when I was a child
Omoi no hate ni tsurenatte yuku yo
I continue on to the ends of emotion
Sukuiageta tenohira kara
I scoop up my hands,
koboreochiru suna to jikan
and the sand and time that spills from them
Kono tame ni umarete kita to oshiete kureru
show me that this is what I was born to do
Korogeochisou na supido de
Let's continue swimming
Bokura oyogitsuzukeyou
at a near-tumbling speed
Soshite dare mo
Until we wash up someday
shiranai shirahama he itsuka
on a white sandy beach
Uchiagerareru made
no one knows about
This is Erumalu?
Huh? There's nothing here.
Erumalu, the City of Green...
The City of Green?!
There's no green anywhere!
It was a thriving city until just recently...
This was?
Karoo.
I have an important favor to ask of you.
I want you to go to Alubarna!
Next time, on One Piece:
Erumalu, the City of Green,
and the Kung Fu Dugongs!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Erumalu, the City of Green,
And the Kung Fu Dugongs!