Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue his brother, Ace, who will be executed!
He and the Whitebeards finally got over the
barricades to make it to the scaffold!
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught,
Luffy runs toward Ace with the Whitebeards' assistance!
You guys!
Pops?!
From now on, back Straw Hat Luffy up...
...with all your strength!
They made a path!
I'm here, Ace!
Grandpa! Move out of my way!
I'm not going to move!
Because I'm a vice admiral of the Navy!
I've been fighting against pirates since long before you were born!
Old man!
If you wanna pass through here,
you have to kill me first!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Because of the path you two...
...have chosen to live!!
Each on Different Paths
Luffy vs. Garp!
Please, grandpa! Just let me through!
Luffy!
C-Coby! S-Stay with me, Coby!
Damn Straw Hat!
How could he do this to Coby without mercy?!
I'll make him pay!
I-I have to become...
...much much stronger...
Y-Y-You are alive! I'm so relieved!
Where's Luffy-san?
That damn Straw Hat is...
...being blocked by Vice Admiral Garp!
Are they really gonna fight?!
Luffy-san!
Straw Hat is heading to the scaffold! Dammit!
It's easy to get him from this distance!
Aim at Straw Hat Luffy!
You impertinent fools!
Stand back!
Slave Arrow!
We...
Love...
You...
Pirate Empress! Whose side are you really on?!
Of course, Luffy's...
...but what if you hit
Vice Admiral Garp with a stray bullet?!
What?!
N-No!
Vice Admiral Garp! He is none other than...
...my grandfather!
Your grandfather?!
Vice Admiral Garp?!
If I get married to Luffy,
then of course, he becomes my grandfather!
It's just...
...In your head!
You gotta find a way, Straw Hat! Hurry up before the bridge collapses!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-kun!
Luffy! Straw Hat Luffy!
Like I said, if you wanna pass through here,
you have to kill me first!
Ouch!
You bastard!
Grandpa!
Why do you want me to fight with these guys?!
That's your training!
My training?!
It just makes me hungry
and I don't wanna get hit anymore!
Don't be such a baby!
You've got to become the strongest Navy soldier!
I'm gonna become a pirate, not a Navy soldier!
Huh?
You fool!
Ouch!
Nothing's more painful than grandpa's fist!
Gum-Gum...
What a fool...
I gotta tell you something!
What is it?
I'm not gonna become a pirate!
You finally got it!
I'm not gonna become just a pirate,
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
You can't be influenced by Red-Haired like that!
You're dismissed!
I've got to beat some character into him!
Grandpa!
I'm not gonna let you become a pirate at any cost!
Although you're worn out and sleeping, your stomach is active as always.
I guess you must hate me
for being such a strict grandpa.
But Luffy,
the reason that I'm training you so harshly
to become a Navy soldier is...
...that I don't want you to stray from the right path at any price.
That is my wish.
Luffy, we'll have a great dinner tonight
because I swiped plenty from the Navy.
You can eat as much meat as you want!
Grandpa...
I can't do it, grandpa! Move out of my way!
If you can't, Ace will die!
No way!
Things don't always go as you want! I'm not gonna have mercy on you!
Luffy, I consider you...
...my enemy!
Luffy!
Garp!
Dammit! My mind is so warped! It's not the right time for this!
Pops and brother and friends are...
...going down one by one bleeding, but...
I'm so happy that I can't hold back my tears!
At this last moment,
I'm starting to think that I wanna live!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Old man!
You're their parent after all, Garp.
He is about to get to the scaffold!
You called him a reckless piece of crap!
He is reckless!
I wonder how he can set Fire Fist Ace free.
Get lost! You fool!
You're not careful.
Pops!
Finally... finally...
I made it!
Luffy!
You're so...!
Ace!
Hold on!
Take this.
It's your brother's handcuff key.
I have the key!
Luffy, how did you...?!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Look! Fleet Admiral Sengoku is using his power!
I've never seen it before!
You can't get away from me!
Sengoku!
A giant Buddha!
I can't believe that you even have such a thing, Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh no, the key!
Get ready!
Aim at them and be ready to fire at a moment's notice!
No way, the key...!
Straw Hat Luffy!
You're a serious criminal
who should be punished by death, too!
I'm gonna execute both of you brothers
with my own bare hands!
What was that? I passed out all of a sudden...
Straw Hat... Oh!
Three! Why are you here?!
What is that?!
Hey, Three! Protect Ace with a wall!
Gum-Gum...
...Gigant Balloon!
Candle Wall!
Is he expanding?!
The scaffold is collapsing!
What happened?!
Ace is still alive!
We're falling!
I'll make the key! Uncuff him right away!
Alright!
Captain Buggy! There's brother 3!
What?! What is he doing in that ridiculous costume?!
I thought he ran away from here already!
The execution of Fire Fist Ace
has to do with the prestige of Navy HQ!
We have to finish it!
That was...
...the executioners!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank!
Oh, that's good! Admiral Borsalino stopped Straw Hat in the plaza!
Straw Hat?!
You gotta save your brother at any cost!
Mr. 2...!
Okay, what should we do now?
We're gonna rescue Straw-chan!
Because I'm his friend!
I don't need any other reasons!
Friends?
Bon-chan, the gate's closing.
We... have to go.
Thank you!
Straw-chan!
Bon-chan!
You gotta save your brother at any cost!
He never ran away.
He honored his friendship with Straw Hat!
Okay guys, hurry up and get ready!
Yes, sir!
Where's the other guy?! What's taking him so long?!
Since it was such short notice,
he's having trouble getting ready...
Hey, hurry up!
Alright, let's go!
If I tell you that I'm here
out of respect for my late comrade,
are you going to laugh at me?!
No, I won't!
Fire! Blow them away!
Save your brother, Straw Hat!
Okay!
Oh no!
Straw-boy!
No way!
Ace!
Brother 3!
They all got hit!
Fire Fist can't use his power
because of the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
He's dead!
And we got Straw Hat, too!
There's a tunnel of fire in the smoke!
You never change!
Luffy!
You never do as I tell you...
...and always get yourself in big trouble!
Good!
Oh my!
Ace!
I-I can't believe it!
Straw Hat and brother 3 are alive, too!
Ace!!
Ace is free at last!
Seeing Ace and Luffy taking on the Navy in such a well-synchronized combination
raises the morale of the Whitebeard Pirates.
But Whitebeard,
looking to a future still farther ahead,
comes to a decision of his own.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Ace Rescued!
Whitebeard's Final Order!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Ace Rescued!
Whitebeard's Final Order!