Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
He slipped away from my Hair Bind!
Rumble...
I'm sorry, Doctorine.
Just like Doctor put his life on the
line in order to save the country...
...I want to put my life on the
line in order to save my friend.
If I'm gonna die anyway, I'll do it!
Just please, nobody come into this room.
Bubble Master Kalifa!
The Soap Trap Closes in on Nami
Yo...
Yoyoi...
I don't know what's going on,
but the way you firmly stand like a devil...
I like it, my friend!
Whether you're a devil or a demon-god,
a real man wouldn't withdraw even a step!
On my honor as Kumadori the lion,
I'll bring you down!
Shave!
Finger Pistol! Q! Q! Q! Q! Q!
Moon Walk!
Shishi Kabob!
Y-Y-Yoyoi!
N-Now that it's come to this,
I'll use my specialty attack!
Take this! Life Return!
Hair Bind!
H-Hair Bind!
My God! My consciousness,
all the way to the tip of my hair,
is screaming that the best thing
to do here is to run away.
Even so, please don't stop me, Mother!
A man... A man...
A man has battles that he must face head-on!
Shave!
Tempest Kick! Lotus!
Take this! Song of Willow!
Dammit!
I'm super this week, and yet I still
had a harder time than I thought.
But, well...
...I got his key.
#4...
The key the swordsman and
the nose wanted was #2, right?
This guy had #4.
That guy had #3.
And there's only one left.
The one who has the #2 key
is that secretary woman!
I'd better hurry up.
I'll go help them out!
You guys don't have much time, right?
I thought you weren't going to go easy on me.
Did I hear you wrong?
How dare you mock me?!
I won't let you get away with it!
Then, bring it on.
You don't have to wait. The battle
has already started, you know.
I'm surprised that a power holder
could take a bath in front of her enemy.
If your body is halfway submerged,
you shouldn't have full use of your powers.
Are you saying that I'm
leaving myself wide open?
You don't have to worry about it,
because just like me, you can't
exert your strength, either.
Pardon me for a bit.
What'd you do to me?!
Isn't solving a mystery like that one of
the true joys of fighting a power holder?
It was definitely this woman
who put Sanji-kun in that state.
I have to be careful. Or there's no
point in me taking his place to fight.
The strength that ebbed away
is coming back little by little.
I'll show you the power
of the Perfect Clima Takt!
You're mistaken if you think
I'm just a cute beauty!
I can move my legs, too!
Here I come!
Thunder Charge:
Swing Arm!
That's an amazing weapon.
These are...
...clouds?
There's no way I'd just lay on
the floor doing nothing, is there?
Thunderbolt... Tempo!
It's your own fault for acting so confident.
That was a surprise.
I never thought I'd be hit by lightning indoors.
What was that thing that
guarded you from the lightning?
It turned into bubbles and disappeared.
You have no chance against me
unless you solve that mystery.
I wonder if you can do it.
It was as if soap turned into bubbles.
A soap woman with
Bubble-Bubble Fruit powers...
I wonder if it's something like that.
B-But even if, for example, you figured
out what kind of powers they are,
it's not like you have a
chance to win! How insolent!
So that was right on the mark.
Now I kinda feel guilty.
You're right. My selling point is cleanliness.
I ate the Bubble-Bubble Fruit
and became a soap woman
whose entire body lathers.
Isn't it wonderful?
Whoa! How sexy! To be honest,
I'd be happy to have a secretary like her.
Hey! What am I, a middle-aged guy?!
But isn't that poorly suited for fighting?
That doesn't look very strong.
But I can freely manipulate the
bubbles that come out of my body.
What? What's going on?
I'll show you.
The bubbles from the bathtub are...!
Bubble Master!
Soap Sheep!
This is...
How's this? Isn't it wonderful?
You're an idiot, aren't you?
You shouldn't be deceived by my appearance.
What?
Sheep Cloud! Relaxing Bubbles!
You did lose your strength at the
entrance of the room. Why was that?
That's right...!
That must've been her powers, too.
Bubbles!
Come to think of it, when I
stepped into this room...
...there were bubbles all over the floor!
Shoot!
You noticed it too late.
My strength is ebbing away.
This happened earlier, too, because I
stepped on the bubbles on the floor.
You'll learn the horror of
this power little by little.
The bubbles that come out of my
body scrape away all sorts of things...
Obviously filth and spots, but also
your strength, among other things.
And I don't want you to forget that I'm
an assassin from a secret organization.
I can move my body! Her kicking
me made the bubbles go away!
I'm not gonna take this anymore!
Thunder Ball!
That weapon's power alone...
...is still an unknown quantity to me.
My strength is ebbing away.
This happened earlier, too, because I
stepped on the bubbles on the floor.
You'll learn the horror of
this power little by little.
The bubbles that come out of my
body scrape away all sorts of things...
Obviously filth and spots, but also
your strength, among other things.
And I don't want you to forget that I'm
an assassin from a secret organization.
I can move my body! Her kicking
me made the bubbles go away!
I'm not gonna take this anymore!
Thunder Ball!
That weapon's power alone...
...is still an unknown quantity to me.
Golden Bubbles!
What're you doing?!
I can't stand!
What?! What's wrong with my legs?!
They look pretty, don't they?
Everything I touch gains a beautiful gloss.
I'll make your skin shiny...
Every inch of your body.
Iron Body!
I don't know what's coming next,
so I'm gonna go ahead
and replenish my cola first.
Come to think of it, I wonder
how that deer's doing.
What the heck's going on?!
Wh-What the hell...
...is this?!
That's the CP9 guy who was in the fridge!
What?! Did this monster bring him down?!
What the hell is this?
I feel like that deer was
wearing the same kind of hat...
Hey! You're not that deer-gorilla, are you?!
Hey... This can't be happening...!
There's no mistake.
Kumadori-san!
He flew from the Tower of Law?!
Can't be...! Who on earth could...?
Seriously... what the hell is he?!
A voice...?
Hm?
Hey, hurry up!
Why are you stopping, Nico Robin?!
Hey, are you listening, you woman
whose very life is a crime?!
Hey, Lucci! Drag her along!
Grab her by her hair!
It's an order.
Get moving, Nico Robin.
Don't tell me... you still think that the
Straw Hats are coming to your rescue?
How stupid!
Are you seriously still laying your
hopes on such weak-looking pirates?
That explosion earlier was
surely just our imagination.
There's no way that they can come here!
While you're enjoying your little dream,
we'll pass the Gates of Justice.
"Underground passage
(current location)"
The Bridge of Hesitation lies
in front of the Gates of Justice.
"Bridge of Hesitation
(halfway)"
First we'll cross half of the bridge.
When the gates are opened,
the other half will rise from the sea,
"Gates of Justice
(cross-section)"
and we'll finally go through
the Gates of Justice.
Once the gates are closed again,
you'll never have the feeling of hope...
...ever again.
The only feeling you'll have is a sense of guilt.
You'll endlessly atone for your
sin of having lived until today.
Right, Nico Robin?
Now, let's hurry.
Come on already!
Robin!
Wh-Wh-What was that?! I just heard a voice!
Hey! What was that voice?!
Chief, please take Nico Robin
and hurry on ahead.
Hm? Doors?
They don't look like iron this time.
Hm? The space has opened up. Where am I?
There you are! Pigeon guy!
I'm glad you came.
Hey! Come in, CP9!
A pirate strayed in!
Geez... Hey, are you listening?!
Wait! What you're holding is...
Hm?!
Ahhh! I pressed the button on
the golden transponder snail!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Resounding Bad News!
Buster Call Invoked!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Resounding Bad News!
Buster Call Invoked!