Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats reach the New World at long last,
the harshest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard—an island divided into the Burning and Frozen Lands.
There they were captured
by Caesar Clown, the island's ruler,
and forced to face his weapon
of mass destruction, Netherworld.
But thanks to a clever ploy of their newfound ally,
the Warlord Trafalgar Law, they managed to break free.
Now they are headed
for Gate 66 of Building R.
However, Caesar made Netherworld
flow into the institute itself.
You've got to be kidding!
Run! Run!
What're you doing?!
Hurry up!
Get me down!
Tashigi-chan!
That's enough!
You have to survive!
Goodbye!
Smoker-san told me...
...to help them!
--No, Captain-chan, it's too late!
--There's... There's no time!
Don't be ridiculous!
Your colleagues are still outside of the gate!
Outta my way!
No means no!
Captain Tashigi!
Well done, guys!
We certainly got our beloved Captain-chan in our hands!
The Treasonous Vice Admiral!
"Demon Bamboo" Vergo
Passageway Between Building A and B
I can't believe he broke the wall of the institute
and let the gas in.
That Caesar guy does such bizarre things.
We got away for now
but it's not safe yet.
You're right.
We have to find the children quickly and head for the R-66 gate!
Then we gotta escape from this disgusting place.
Hey, go faster!
You people!
When did all of you get on?!
Now it's too heavy even for me.
I'm so sorry.
But you have to hang on.
We have no choice.
What?
Is there a compelling reason?
Yeah, we are...
...too tired and we don't want to run!
That's the worst reason!
Get off of me!
Your name...
is Brownbeard, isn't it?
I'm sorry...
but I want to rescue my son Momonosuke as soon as possible!
R-Rescue your son?!
However,
since I ran a lot already...
I just don't want to run anymore!
Get off, you fools!
I'm pretty hot with my coat on.
You can hang it here.
Great.
I'm gonna take mine off, too.
Don't get comfortable on my back!
If you're not hurt, why don't you run yourselves?!
I'm hungry.
I'm a samurai - I don't get hungry.
Brownbeard-san,
do you have anything I can eat?
Shut up!
When we get to a soldiers' post,
I will buck you all off!
Passageway Between Building A and B
Captain-chan!
Captain-chan, are you listening?
Let's go ahead!
So he was making such a deadly weapon on Punk Hazard
while the island was believed to be closed.
If nothing is done, the damage will spread around the world!
Let's get out of here
and make a report to Navy HQ!
What's the matter, Captain-chan?!
If we can't escape from here alive,
what did those guys who saved your life died for?!
I'm sorry.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Wait a minute!
What's that noise?
There is something on the ceiling!
What is that creature?!
I think that thing came here along with the Straw Hats!
Is it a lizard or something?
I heard that there was a dragon on Punk Hazard!
It's a mythical animal
that Dr. Vegapunk created for the security of the island.
It didn't look so scary before.
It's coming!
He dodged them!
H-He's chewing on steel!
If you get bitten by such strong jaws...
Everybody!
Run to Building B!
He flies, breathes fire, and chews up steel!
What a creature!
What happened?
He's flying away.
Is he trying to escape?
He looked upset.
Did he get intimidated by Captain Tashigi?
He was very scared.
Captain Tashigi, you're gonna love this!
Reinforcements have arrived!
The Vice Admiral came to help!
Vergo!
Vice Admiral Smo-yan
and Vice Admiral Vergo!
We have both key figures of G-5 here!
We're invincible now!
No...
Yeah! Now we're safe!
Run, everybody...
Run!
V-Vice Admiral Vergo,
did they do something wrong?!
Even if they needed to be punished,
your Finger Pistol could kill them...
Welcome.
I've heard about you,
Commodore Smoker.
Nice to meet you.
The soldiers of G-5 are rough and not very smart
but once you get to know them,
they're not as bad as people say.
Soon, you'll see that they're very loyal.
Where is Vice Admiral Vergo?
He's not here.
Where did he go?
Don't worry.
Vice Admiral Vergo has to go home suddenly sometimes.
His younger sister's sick.
Vice Admiral!
Stop it!
That's not what Navy soldiers would say!
I don't think your house collapsed because of our bombardment...
What do you mean by that?!
I'm sorry.
I'm responsible for their actions.
Oh yeah?
Then I want you to take full responsibility!
You...
Don't get carried away!
I understand.
We will do anything
to make you satisfied.
Vice Admiral Vergo.
About the report on the kidnapped child from the other day...
Oh...
I told some soldiers to look into it
but it was an accident at sea, as I suspected.
So it was a false report.
A false report?
It's hard for any parent to accept his or her child's death.
So they try to keep thinking
that their child was kidnapped to keep their hope alive.
You will see...
when you become a mother someday.
Is that how it is?
Yes, that's how it is.
Everybody, back away!
He is not the man that you used to know!
For a long time, he has been...
Captain-tan!
Captain-chan!
He's an impostor!
Vergo-san wouldn't do such a thing to Captain-chan!
He's right!
Are you in disguise or a Devil Fruit user?
Stop mocking Vice Admiral Vergo!
Vice Admiral Vergo...
...always defends us misfit Navy soldiers!
He's a man of humanity and justice!
Stop mocking him!
I'll kick your ass, you impostor!
Go to hell!
You're unforgivable, you impostor!
I've lost my voice!
Please stop!
Help us, Smoker-san!
A lady is...
Who is it?!
...in need!
Is that...
O-One of the Straw Hats?
Why is a pirate helping us?
I heard the sound of...
...a woman's tears falling.
Building B
Sanji has taken off somewhere making a serious face!
I felt a mysterious presence back there.
Forget about him.
Something is coming!
Is that...
That's the dragon-san from earlier!
He looks a little different.
Different? How?
The look in his eyes.
The sedatives have worn off as I thought.
Sedatives?
Yeah, he's violent by nature.
It's hard to handle him without sedatives.
Plus, he's one of the smaller ones that are newer and more advanced.
They're faster and much more resilient!
Let's just run for now!
Run faster!
Building B, Central Staircase
Damn!
I don't wanna fall behind!
Straw Hat,
where are you heading?
I'm gonna catch Caesar!
What about you?!
I'm gonna sort things out with Vergo.
Is he with Caesar?
I think so.
Don't get in my way!
Wait, you bastard!
Building B, Gas Balloon Landing Pad
Help!
I'm scared!
Get me out of here!
Help me!
Hey, stay away from the door.
Let's go back with everybody!
You can have a sweet candy with your friends.
So let's go back to the Biscuits Room!
Brothers!
Sisters!
Help me!
In any case, I have to get out of here first
to go rescue the children!
Let me out!
Oh?
What is a child doing here?
Let me out!
Be quiet!
If you don't stop, I'll shoot you!
Heavy Point!
Stop it!
Who is it?!
I'll shoot you!
Don't move!
Are you okay?!
A monster!
Help!
It must be withdrawal symptoms.
Calm down!
No!
Oh yeah!
The sedatives!
This will ease your pain.
I'm gonna help you now.
Help!
Good girl!
It's done!
It's gonna work soon.
What was I doing?
You were pounding on the door.
Oh yeah,
I was trying to get out of here.
Hey, we took you out of here earlier -
why are you back here?
We came back here in the Flying Gas Balloon
that Master picked us up with.
But...
…big brother and sister told us not to go back.
Of course!
What about the other kids?
Everybody's going to the Biscuits Room
because they have the candies there.
What?!
No!
You shouldn't eat the candy!
What?
This is bad!
Hey, could you take me to the Biscuits Room?!
Okay! I know a shortcut to the Biscuits Room!
Follow me!
Caesar's Laboratory
What the hell is Vergo doing?!
The G-5 soldiers are my test subjects!
It'll be a total waste if I don't kill them with Netherworld!
That fool!
I have no choice.
Block off the passage ahead of them
and let the gas flow in from the gate behind them!
But Vergo is still there.
I don't care if that idiot lives or dies!
Just do it!
Near the Biscuits Room
Building B, 3rd Floor
The Biscuits Room is down this way!
Let's go!
The Biscuits Room is this way!
Can I have the candy?!
Oh no! Those are the children?!
We can't let them go beyond this door!
Mocha!
If you wanna save your friends,
you have to help me!
Okay!
Mocha, hold the door!
What are you doing, Mocha?!
Open up!
I wanna go to the Biscuits Room!
Listen!
Don't let them get to the Biscuits Room!
Uh-huh!
Open it!
Hey!
Why shouldn't we...
...eat the candy?
Because...
Ready?
No!
Wait a second!
You...
I've been running so fast that the friction has burned the floor!
But that was...
...not fair!
You were gliding on smoke!
Okay, ready?
Wait!
I told you to wait!
I'll say "Okay" when I'm ready!
I'm catching my breath now.
Hey, I didn't say "Okay"!
Listen,
Vergo is my enemy!
I know!
My enemy is Caesar!
Keep your hands off of him!
Oh, it's my enemy!
I won't let you get away this time!
Caesar!
The showdown with Caesar begins!
As Caesar uses his Gas Gas Fruit abilities that previously defeated the Straw Hats...
...Luffy launches a mighty offensive of his own!
The battle...
...grows more intense than ever!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A White-Hot Battle
Luffy vs. Caesar"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
A White-Hot Battle
Luffy vs. Caesar