Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
Indeed, tomorrow is a day to commemorate.
I refuse to let them enter the village!
Straight north! Straight north!
They're in big trouble if they touch my treasure!
Dammit! What do I do?!
I can't climb up!
Outta the damn way!
I can't let you get past this slope...
Because I only lied, like I always do...
So the village is going to have
just another ordinary day!
So I absolutely won't let you go!
They're late...
They all know full well what happens...
...to those who upset my plans...
I'll slaughter them all!
The Terrifying Duo!
Meowban Brothers vs. Zoro
About time...
Y-You guys are that strong?!
Yeah!
What took you guys so long?!
You're the one who got me stuck back there!
That was an accident!
It couldn't be helped!
It's better for one person to be saved
than for two to stay down there...
Then you should've stayed!
Seriously! How am I supposed to
know which way north is and isn't?!
What?! You're the one who ran off first, all full of confidence!
That was just because.
Night is long gone now...
He– Captain Kuro– has a short temper...
Hey, men!
Don't tell me those two brats did you all in?!
Listen!
We don't have time to be dilly-dallying here!
If our enemy is strong,
we just need to be stronger!
Now watch this ring closely!
On "one, two, Jango,"
you guys'll grow strong.
Your wounds will be completely healed,
and you will grow stronger and stronger!
What're they doing?
It's hypnosis!
He's trying to convince them to be stronger!
How ridiculous!
Stronger... Stronger!
One! Two!
Jango!
No way!
H-He gouged out the cliff!
What power!
They really did get hypnotized!
With that many people that strong...
Go! Crush anyone who gets in the way!
You guys get back!
We'll handle this!
Hey, Luffy!
Luffy?!
You got hypnotized too?!
W-What a simple-minded person!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Damn you, Captain Kuro...
You were completely wrong
to think he'd have no effect!
These guys are no ordinary brats!
Where is he going?!
Wha–?
What's he planning to do?!
Go! Luffy!
He's gonna destroy the ship!
No, he's not!
He's gonna crush us with that!
Please do something, Captain!
Crap! Crap!
This was no time to be gawking!
On "one, two, Jango", you'll get sleepy!
One!
Two!
Jango!
Eh?!
Klahadore the butler went to the shore?!
Yeah!
And he had a scary look on his face!
Is Kaya-san okay?!
Alright! Let's move out, Usopp Pirates!
Hey! Quit sleeping!
But I should still be in bed...
This is no time to be sleeping!
We could be in trouble!
Eh?
I think pirates really are going to attack us.
Our captain said he was lying,
but I think that was a lie!
I think so, too!
Me, too! Something just wasn't
right about our captain yesterday!
You don't think...
But our captain used to go through here!
No good! It's closed up!
Let's look for another one!
You! How dare you make a fool of me,
insulting me for having the blood of a pirate?!
Stop, Usopp-san!
Klahadore...
Are you there, Klahadore?
Klahadore?
M-Merry!
Merry!
What's wrong?! What happened?!
Open your eyes, Merry!
Please don't die!
M-Miss...
Thank goodness, you're all right...
Merry!
Merry? W-Who did this?!
Klahadore! He... attacked me!
He... he was a pirate all along!
W-What are you talking about?
He got close to you so he
could get your fortune...
No... That's absurd!
It's the truth!
Then, what Usopp-san said yesterday was...
Yes. Now that I think about it,
he tried his hardest to help us
when he learned the truth!
Yet, not a single one of us
even tried to hear him out!
You gotta run, Kaya!
They're gonna kill you!
You gotta escape for now!
We protected a real villain
and drove off that brave lad,
who ran about with desperate resolve,
all for the villagers' sake!
S-Someone help! Merry is–!
It's no use, Miss!
The staff has been on leave since yesterday.
What?! Then I'll...
You mustn't get flustered!
The incident hasn't happened yet!
You must think calmly about
what you need to do now!
If Klahadore's goal is your fortune and mansion,
then just let him have it all!
They're not worth protecting with your life!
You're right.
Cruel as it may be,
you are the only one who
can stop Klahadore now.
Can you do it?
This isn't your responsibility, but...
Even I know this isn't a
situation I can run from...
I understand that fully!
I'll talk things over with Klahadore!
What're you doing?!
Hold on tight!
But these bars are slippery!
Climb over anyways!
Aren't you worried about Kaya-san?!
Oh, no! Someone's coming out!
Hide!
It's Kaya-san!
She's alright!
It looks like something has her worried!
Kaya-san, walking outside all by herself...
Something's up!
Something's gotta be up!
Looks like they're just about wiped out!
I guess so.
Hey! Never mind that,
Luffy's trapped under there!
He won't die.
Worry about your own injuries or somethin'.
Damn that brat!
Now the plan's really screwed up!
If Captain Kuro caught sight of this,
he'd slaughter all of us, too!
Hey, Butchie! Come look!
This is bad stuff!
What the hell?!
We still have a trump card!
Come forth, Meowban Brothers!
You called, Captain Jango?
You called?
Siam...
...and Butchie!
Together, we are the Meowban Brothers!
Butchie! Siam!
We absolutely must get past this hill,
but as you can see,
an obstacle is in the way!
Get rid of it.
W-We can't possibly do that!
Right, Butchie?!
Yeah, he looks strong!
Huh?
And besides, we're just
supposed to guard the ship!
Yeah!
This isn't really our place to fight...
W-What?
They're not their trump card?!
Siam! Get going already!
Eh?! M-Me?!
Hurry!
O-Okay, okay! I'll go!
He's in tears! What's he trying to do?!
Why's he making him fight?
Hey, you! Get ready!
I'm gonna scratch you good with these claws!
What am I supposed to do?!
Hey, you! Stop or I'll kill you!
If you can!
What?!
What the hell?!
You!
You just underestimated me, didn't you?!
I'm impressed you could block that,
after my innocent cat act!
You seem to have a little skill,
but I wouldn't underestimate
Siam of the Meowban Brothers!
Missing something?
Don't look at me, though...
There it is...
"Cat Burglar"...
Give those swords back!
Give them back?
But you already have a sword.
These are just in the way.
Alright! Now I'm much lighter!
You're supposed to take good
care of other people's things!
Bastard!
What?!
What did you cut?!
I can bend like a cat!
You're up, Butchie! Get 'im!
Right, Siam!
Cat...
...astrophe!
Damn! He got away!
Hey! Hold him down, Siam!
My bad!
The bastard's way stronger than I thought!
What the hell?!
One hit from that'd turn every
bone in my body to powder!
He's not getting away this time!
'As right!
I'm not that great at the
One-Sword Style, but...
Let's go, Butchie!
Okay! Let's do it, Siam!
– Pussy Willow March!
Oh, no!
They got Zoro on the defensive!
What're you doing?!
He's not gonna get anywhere just
blocking those two guys' attacks!
I'm gonna help him out!
Take this!
Lead Star!
Gotcha!
Why're you attacking a guy on our side?!
No, it's not like that!
It seemed like he let it hit him on purpose...
Eh?! On purpose?!
Usopp, you dumbass!
Do you want to die?!
You don't suppose...
...we're the ones who just got saved?
Had you hit them with that slingshot,
those two probably would've
come after us instead!
He...
But this is no time for that!
Damn it! If I just had another sword!
I'm gonna get his swords!
If I give 'em back to Zoro,
he'll win for sure!
In that case, I'll do it!
Don't push yourself!
You can barely even stand!
Nami!
What do you need swords for?
No! Uhh! I-I can explain!
Night is long gone now,
so it seemed odd that the plan
wasn't making any progress...
C-Captain Kuro!
W-We're dead!
This can't get any worse!
What is all this?!
What the–?!
Did they have a falling out?!
He's handling those two like they're nothing!
I can't sense where damn Kuro is!
Kaya-san! Look out!
What's she doing here?!
Hey, where's Luffy?!
Still asleep! Urgh!
– Get up already!
I'll protect the meat shop...
Next time, on One Piece:
Luffy, Back in Action!
Miss Kaya's Desperate Resistance
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Luffy, Back in Action!
Miss Kaya's
Desperate Resistance