Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy lost his brother Ace in the
Paramount War against the Navy
and has come face-to-face
with Dark King Rayleigh.
What are you gonna do, Luffy-kun?
Meanwhile, the rest of the Straw Hats...
...have all gotten underway
in order to keep their promise
to each other and Luffy.
Okay.
I made up my mind.
I'm gonna go back.
To Marineford!
Sanji's Ordeal
The Queen Returns to her Queendom!
Th-This is a Navy ship #204.
We demand permission to enter.
You're right on time.
Okay, may I have your code number?
The code number is 5963.
Code number, confirmed.
Open the Gate of Justice.
Yes, sir!
Crank.
Alright, well done.
Luffy-kun, how are you feeling?
I feel fine now. Not bad at all.
The former Warlord - "First
Son of the Sea" Jinbe!
The former first mate of
the Pirate King -
Dark King Silvers Rayleigh!
And Straw Hat Luffy! What do they want?!
Meanwhile, in Birdie Kingdom...
Birdie Kingdom
...where the birds and humans have stopped fighting.
Are you really leaving now, Mr. Raccoon Dog?
We just became friends.
Uh-huh, I read in the newspaper
about my friend's ordeal
so I wanna get back as soon as possible.
I can't believe what happened to...
...Luffy's brother, who I met in Alabasta!
I wanna see Luffy soon and
give him medical attention.
He must've pushed himself as always.
Mr. Raccoon Dog!
I'm glad that you and the
birds cleared the air!
That's because you risked
your life and talked to them.
Well...
You guys, live in peace with these humans!
All they want are the various
plants that grow on that tree!
That's right! We don't want your
eggs and we won't hurt you!
We're different from those who chased
you away from your home island!
Now that you mention it,
the medicine that you make out of the
plants on that tree really works!
My wound healed already.
Of course it did! This medicine
is passed on from father to son.
To be honest, I wanna stay on
this island and study the plants!
I'm sure there are ingredients unfamiliar
to me. But I don't have time.
Come see us again!
That's right! You're always welcome, Mr. Raccoon Dog!
Yeah? I'm happy to hear that!
When I see my friends, I'll
tell them about this country!
And I'll come to see you all again!
Take this. It's a long journey
and you'll get hungry.
Thanks.
Come see us, Mr. Raccoon Dog!
Oh, cotton candy!
Alright, guys, be nice to each other!
Goodbye, Mr. Raccoon Dog!
Okay, I got a box lunch
and some cotton candy!
I'm gonna head for the meeting spot now!
I don't have a pirate ship!
Even if I had one, I don't have a navigator!
So I don't know how to get to Sabaody!
Well, I'll just get on any ship...
No, then I'm gonna get lost!
Oh, what am I gonna do?!
M-Mr. Raccoon Dog...
Damn! I gotta fulfill my role as
the doctor of the pirates! Luffy!
Huh? What did you say?
Your father will give me a ride?
Yeah, see you!
It's really high and fast!
I'll make it there in a matter of seconds!
Huh? You can do better?
Cool!
It's like a roller-coaster!
I feel sick... I got carried away...
Hey, News Coo! Give me the newspaper!
I'll read it as I eat my lunch.
The information about the war
should be updated by now.
Yum!
You've got to be kidding me!
Why?! What's going on?!
What made Luffy do this...?!
Meanwhile, in the East Blue,
East Blue, on the giant bridge
Robin has been freed by the Revolutionary Army and...
--You saved me!
--Revolutionary Army, thanks for coming!
I'm glad!
Robin!
Soran!
It's great. Can everybody
be free from now on?
Yes.
At least, you're not gonna be
forced to build the bridge.
Hey...
Will you accept this?
Thank you, Soran.
You're leaving, aren't you, Robin?
Yes.
Robin!
Can I see you again?
Robin-san.
Are you gonna head for Sabaody?
Yes.
"The light of revolution."
We've called you that and searched
for you for more than 10 years.
You're the only survivor from Ohara,
the country that fought against the world.
When we find you,
we have to protect you from
the Government at any cost!
That's what the boss told us.
Boss?
The leader of the Revolutionary
Army - Dragon.
Luffy's father...
What a curious turn of fate!
I beg you again.
Please meet our boss! I'll take you to him.
I can't. I have to return somewhere.
Besides that, you don't need to protect me.
Because I have friends.
You mean the members of
the Straw Hat Pirates.
Yes.
Then, let us give you a lift
part of the way at least.
You can't see the end of this bridge
even if you walk for several days.
Let us take you wherever you're going.
We'll be able to unlock the
3rd and 4th prisons soon!
Roger that.
Tell the others to get ready for
the release of the prisoners.
Yes, sir!
Can I ask you something?
Anything.
Why does the Revolutionary Army need me?
Th-That's because...
You'll see several ghost towns before
we get to the end of the bridge.
That's because the whole country
moved as the construction progressed.
For your information, the site
you see is from 300 years ago.
Why are they building this bridge?
It's an order from the World
Nobles - Celestial Dragons.
Celestial Dragons?
I don't care if there is a reason or not!
It wouldn't bring down the death
toll of those they call slaves!
Did you see Straw Hat Luffy -
Dragon-san's son in today's newspaper?
Yes. He went missing after the war,
but he showed up again and did such a thing.
We have to show this
article to Nico Robin now.
She's worrying about him.
I don't think they got to the end yet.
Oh, thank you!
For you, Robin-san.
Luffy! I'm glad he's okay!
What is it? Is there something funny?
Yes.
Meanwhile, on Peachy Island---
Kamabakka Queendom, the island for New Kamas...
Grand Line
Peachy Island, Kamabakka Queendom
I said "Give me a ship!" I
have a promise to fulfill!
I've wasted so much time fooling
around with you people!
With that excuse, candy-chan,
you're just trying to
escape from this island!
We won't let you do that!
Yeah, that's absolutely right!
Of course, I wanna get out of this country
that's completely devoid of women!
What is that ship there?
I-It's Iva-sama! Iva-sama is on it!
Huh? Who is it?
Hey, what's wrong? Is that person that great?
She's the queen of Kamabakka Queendom...
...Emporio Ivankov-sama!
What?! That name was in...
She's the queer queen in
the newspaper?
How timely!
She was with Luffy so I bet she knows a lot.
It's been awhile.
Can't believe it!
Sh-She's my type!
No, wait, wait!
She's here because she's a queer, too.
I almost fell for it!
Who are you?
I-I am...
Her breasts are sticking out!
Her ass looks so tight!
No, I won't be fooled!
Do you want something from me, candy-boy?
Yeah, I have a lot of
questions for you! First...
...what's your favorite type of man?
No, I mean, about Luffy!
Luffy? You mean Straw-boy?
Bingo!
So you were at the Navy
Headquarters with him!
Luffy, you're so lucky!
I mean, you guys must've been through a lot.
Tell me everything.
My lady...
And who are you?
Dammit! I knew it was coming! Screw you!
And how do you know Straw-boy?!
I'm one of his crew.
His crew?!
--So this is a wanted poster of Straw-boy.
--Yes, it is.
And this is "Pirate Hunter" Zoro.
Don't know him!
This is "Cat Burglar" Nami.
This is "Sniper King" Sogeking.
Uh-huh.
And this is you.
No!
See?! You're not in these posters!
Then there's no proof that
you're one of Straw-boy's!
I told you that I am!
Tell me how is Luffy doing
now, you queer king!
I know that you were with
him from the newspaper!
Then, is this you?
I said that it's not...
It's not but it is...
The name is mine.
Why are you struggling so much?!
That's... me! That is me!
That weird guy on that poster
is definitely me so...
No, it looks nothing like you!
Then, don't make me say it!
I threw up blood, you fool!
It's no use.
Even if it's only 0.1 %,
as long as there's a chance
that you're a puppet from
the Navy or Government
Vi won't tell you any of the
information concerning Straw-boy!
I understand. Then let me borrow a ship.
I'm gonna go to the meeting spot.
Vi won't give you a ship.
Then, I'll swim!
What did you just say?!
So you're not just saying
that you're his crew!
Vi have no choice.
You've touched my heart.
For the sake of your passion,
Vi'll tell you what happened to Straw-boy...
Or not! Heehaw!
--So you won't tell him?
--You fooled us there!
Iva-sama!
Shut up, you fools!
Damn...
Looks like his defenses are down!
Now is the chance! Dress him
up with the sweets dress!
I'll never wear it again! Back off!
I'm a true manly man who loves ladies!
Stay away from me, fools!
Boo! Boo!
Hey, so your name is Iva, right?
I decided to steal a ship
because I'm a pirate!
You gotta fight me one-on-one!
Alright!
Now, Iva-sama,
the grand master of the Kamabakka style, New Kama Kenpo...
...vs. "Black Leg" Sanji!
A 3 minute one-game match!
Even her stand-in was very
strong. She must be formidable!
I'll go all out from the start!
Fight!
Diable Jambe:
Première Haché!
Wh-What a powerful kick!
V-Vi should be strong but I'm gonna fall...
gonna fall...
fall...
Or not!
Heehaw!
You're not gonna fall?! You got me there!
Seems like you're a staunch boy.
But Vi think you need to be disciplined.
What?
New Kama Kenpo, 44 Aesthetic Arts:
Hair Removal Fist!
Death Wink!
Hell Wink!
Galaxy Wink!
Vi'll tell you how Straw-boy is doing, Spiral-boy!
Why did you change your mind?
Because the whole world knows about it by now.
Vi wonder what he's thinking.
It's in today's newspaper?
Luffy!
Iva-san, there is a call
for you from Baltigo.
Oh yeah?
Go to the transmission facility.
Grand Line
Land of White Soil, Baltigo
Because of the recent war,
people know so much about you now, Dragon!
Didn't it make your men upset?
Looks like they're relieved to
know that their enigmatic boss
was a human after all.
It doesn't matter now.
Luffy is not a kid anymore.
But I can't believe that you were with him.
It must be a trick of fortune, huh?
Anyway, it was an unexpected
prison break for me and Inazuma.
Vi have a lot of things Vi want to discuss
with you and even more questions.
Yeah, I bet.
We need to quickly summon our
commanders from all over the world.
The death of Whitebeard
will change the world situation
and the Government regime.
On top of that, I have to tell
you what happened to Kuma.
Yes, Vi want the details.
What made him obey the Government?
The Kuma that Vi knew is gone now.
He tried to kill me!
Oh, by the way, Dragon,
have you read the newspaper today?
Straw-boy has surprised me once again!
He's as wild as his father.
Vi can't believe he did such a thing on Marineford!
Navy HQ was heavily damaged in the Paramount War.
Luffy returns to the place where he lost Ace,
this time with Rayleigh
and Jinbe at his side.
The miraculous news would bring great shock
to his friends, as well
as to the whole world!
Next time, on One Piece:
"An Unexpected Return!
Luffy, to Marineford!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
An Unexpected Return!
Luffy, to Marineford!