That woman is living in a fairy tale.  She believes she can save her homeland by sacrificing herself.
And now you've come along too.
What's this, a foolhardy suicide squad?!
Nami didn't come here to sacrifice herself.
She was just the advance guard, coming to fight!
Get ready, Gold Lion Shiki!
We're the main battalion!
There's nothing left of your factory, your royal palace, or your island!
Your plan has failed completely!
I will never let you touch...
my crew...
or the sea...
FOR AS LONG AS I LIVE!
Gigant Thor...
Axe!
Is a man from East Blue really standing in my way again?!
ROGER!
The "Gold Lion", Shiki.
This story begins three years before the curtain rose upon the Great Pirate Era.
Fleet Admiral Kong!
Roger and the Gold Lion have made contact in Edd War, over in the New World!
Yeah, I heard.
Wait, Garp!  We're not done talking.
You might not be done, but I am.
Garp!  Get back here!
Garp-san, did you turn down your promotion again?
That's so cool of you!
I can already do as I like, so I don't need a higher rank!
Tsuru-chan, let me come along if you're sailing out there.
Nobody invited you to go, did they?
You'll just break the ship as soon as you board, so I don't want you with me.
Oh, don't say that.
I'll be the one to take down that damn Roger.
Garp!  I was entrusted with the Shiki case!
Stay out of this!
Oh, don't mind me.
I'll let you take all the credit.
That's not what I meant!
Wow, Admiral Sengoku and Vice Admiral Garp are both going!
Well, it is Roger after all.
Garp-san just can't leave him alone.
Captain Roger!
Your life comes first, right?!
Just this once, we should just listen to what the Gold Lion says!
Hey, your body won't let you die no matter how many times they cut you, so why do you care?
I still have weaknesses, you dumbass!
Oh yeah, Crocus-san!  How is the captain's condition?
He'd be better off not fighting, right?
Please, medically relieve him!
Unfortunately for you, he's in perfect shape!
Rayleigh-san!
Just give it up.
We've been together a long time,
and we've never been able to stop Roger.
No way!
Have faith in Tom's ship, the Oro Jackson!
Roger doesn't have much time left.
How many times have we had this discussion, Roger?
A lot of things have happened between us, but let's put the past behind us!
We'll use that apocalyptic weapon you've found and my military might!
And then, with the perfect plan I've spent so many years developing,
we can conquer the entire world at once!
Become my right hand man, Roger!
I have no interest in conquering anything, Shiki!
If you can't do as you please, there's
no point in being a pirate, is there?!
No matter how you try to pressure me,
Gold Lion!  I refuse your offer!
Don't, Captain!
Don't you realize how many ships we're up against?!
Move.
In other words, your answer is...
"Please kill me right here and now!"  Isn't it?!
No, it's "I'm gonna crush every last one of you!"
The man known as the Chief of the Great Pirate Armada, Gold Lion Shiki...
and the future Pirate King, Gold Roger, clashed.
This fight came to be called the Great Battle of Edd War.
Roger's ship, which many assumed would be completely obliterated,
was spared by a sudden change of weather.
In the end, half of Shiki's fleet sunk into the sea.
Furthermore, an unfortunate accident befell Shiki...
forcing him to flee the battlefield and tend to his injuries.
So what about the steering wheel?
Ah, Doctor Indigo.
I can't remove it.
It's stuck so deep in his skull that forcing it out could kill him.
I see.
It's fine.
It happens all the time.
No, accidentally getting a steering wheel stuck in your head in the middle of a battle is quite unheard of.
Still, your vitality is as impressive as ever.
Well, I am mighty enough to be called "Lion", after all.
What the?!  Who's that chicken?!
That's YOU!
Yeah!
Uh, no...
Two years later, the Roger Pirates finally did the impossible...
and successfully conquered the Grand Line.
Gold Roger came to be known as the Pirate King.
Shortly after, the Roger Pirates mysteriously vanished.
Then, after another year had passed by...
Extra!  Extra!
News of the Pirate King's capture spread, surprising the entire world.
Roger was captured?!
Our sources are reliable.
Liar!  You think I'd believe that?!
You all know how strong he is, don't you?!
Chief!  Please, calm down!
Don't go spouting off random crap like that!
Chief, where are you going?!
Intruder alert!
The intruders are by the plaza in Marineford Bay!
How many are there?!
No way! It's...!
Just one!
The enemy is the Gold Lion Shiki, and he's alone!
There's no way Roger could've been caught by trash like you!
I respected that man's strength!
Admiral Sengoku!
Roger is the Pirate King.
In his battle with you, he left victorious.
The Pirate King?!  So what?!
If he'd have just lent me a hand, we could have ruled the world together!
We might have been enemies, but we were part of the same era!
If he's here, then let me see him!
If he's gonna die, then I will be the one who kills him!
The execution will take place in one week, in his hometown,
the "Town of Beginnings" in East Blue, Loguetown.
Roger's death should break the spirit of even the most formidable pirates.
Vice Admiral Garp!
The legend of the Pirate King, Gold Roger,
will end in East Blue, the weakest sea?!
Don't make me laugh!
That'll be your last insult to that shithead, won't it?!
Its weakness makes it the perfect place...
East Blue is a symbol of peace!
We will not let you interfere with the execution!
Garp.  Sengoku.  The Gold Lion.
Before reaching it's conclusion, their battle destroyed half of Marineford.
What is this?!
Hey!  Get the Vice Admiral away from here!
Thus, the pirate, Gold Lion,
was imprisoned at Impel Down.
One week later...
My wealth and treasure?
If you want it, I'll let you have it!  Look for it!
I left it all at that place!
The death of the Pirate King, Gold Roger,
raised the curtain on the Great Pirate Era!
The news spread quickly around the world.
The people understood that the seas would get a lot rougher from that point on.
A frightening era is at hand.
They say that more pirates will show up, Oimo.
They won't attack us, though.
Tonjit, did you hear?!  Huge news!
Someday, I will set the world record for the largest stilts!
Captain Cricket!
They say that Roger died and left behind a huge treasure!
This is amazing!
So there's still some romance left in the world!
Justice will grow stronger!  It must grow stronger!
How can this be?!  A cursed child has been born!
It's the curse of the Pirate Era!
The Great Pirate Era?
Can we all become pirates?
It means that we've got to become stronger, or we can't join the pirate crew.
Did you hear the news?
They say the Pirate King died, leaving behind a huge treasure!
The time of pirates has begun!
Let us out!  Right now!
A new era has begun!
The seas of the new age belong to the pirates!
Roger... How could you die?
Ridiculous.
Those treasure-hunting, empty-headed pirates will be a nuisance on the seas.
What "new era"?
Pirates are the rulers of the sea.
Someday, I will make them understand that.
And then, after another two years...
The legend of the Great Prison crumbled.
Warden!  Reporting in!
Gold Lion Shiki has escaped!
He's still somewhere inside the prison!
What happened to his Sea Stone shackles?  Did they come loose?
No, they're still locked.
He severed off both of his feet!
Find him, no matter what it takes!
We cannot let someone like him escape!
You don't know of my two swords?
They're both renowned blades: Oto and Kogarashi.
I-I-I want a promotion!
Ah, I meant to say...!  Shiki!
It's too bad for you, but I'm leaving now.
I don't need my legs.  You can keep 'em.
Thanks for taking such good care of me these past two years!
Assistant Warden Magellan!  I found Shiki!  Please help me!
Headline: Impel Down's first ever breakout, Chief of the Pirate Armada, "Gold Lion" Shiki
And then, the pirate known as Gold Lion, whose fangs had been dulled once before,
broke free from his cage, and was once again free to roam the seas.
Shiki escaped!
Alright, now I've got legs again.
This is Sengoku.
Sorry to interrupt you during your vacation Garp, but it's about the Gold Lion.
Yeah, I heard.  We'd better be careful.
He's not the kind of man who'd want to make peace.
Still, I doubt he'll attack us right away.
He's a pretty careful guy, after all.
Makino!  Where'd Garp go?
He said he was going to the mountain.
You little brat, don't just wander off on your own!
Wait, Ace!
Ace-chan!  It's me, Grampa Garp!
Garp?!
Uh, I mean, Garp-san... So you're back?
Hey.
I wanted our child to inherit the dojo...
But if it's a girl...
Oh, it'll be alright.
You'll become strong, won't you Kuina?
What's that?  A traveler's ship?  That's a rare sight.
I heard rumors of a man named Yasopp.
I'm Shanks.
A pirate.
Going Merry...
Someday, I'd like to build a ship like this...
They say that Shiki escaped from prison!
If he comes to East Blue, I'll take him down!
We'll be counting on you, Bellemere.
The Gold Lion, huh?
Captain Zeff!  I hear they call him the Flying Pirate.
My kid's blowing bubbles!
Damn it!  Another failure!
That Hiluluk... He did it again?
Your majesty!  Don't you think you're spoiling Wapol-sama a bit too much?
Maybe you're right... I'm worried too.
Nico Robin is in this country...
She's just a kid, but apparently her bounty is 79 million Beli!
What the...?!  I'm stuck!  I can't get out!
How can this be?!  It's a miraculous fit!
How's the sea train coming along?
It's coming steady!
I helped him, so it'll be alright!
This guy can't make anything but weapons!
It's useless, Laboon.
I got on Roger's ship and made sure...
The Rumbar Pirates are...
Time to ship out Binks’ Brew...
42 degrees!
It's so difficult!  42 degrees is really hard!
Oh, I farted.
I'm here, Shakki!
Oh, Hacchan!  Welcome.
Is Rayleigh here?
He's inside.  Want some juice?
Sure.
Rayleigh!
Rayleigh?
So you made it out, eh, Shiki?
Still, what do you plan to do now, after all this time?
How's the sea without Roger?
The wall that's blocked our way is now gone.
Seems like this is your era, Whitebeard.
If you've come here just to spout a load of crap, then I'm gonna send you to the bottom of the sea, Gold Lion.
Good to see that you're still the same, old, annoying geezer.
I'm planning to go into hiding for a while, and then I'll show this lukewarm era the true terror of pirates.
You've got some new scheme going on?
In the Grand Line, on the island that reaches into the clouds, Merveille...
Doctor Indigo, is your research complete?
I've made a discovery...
It seems this island's balance is maintained by several types of flora.
And these plants don't grow down on the surface...
Just cut to the chase, Indigo.
How many years will it take to fulfill my plan?
Well, let's see...
Ten... Fifteen...
No, we can't do it any sooner than... Twenty years.
Alright.  I see.
The plan will commence in twenty years.
I will show the world a living Hell!
Then, twenty years pass...