Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
However, there they find the New Fishman Pirates
have been plotting to destroy Ryugu Kingdom,
arm in arm with Vander Decken, who has been
stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
and involved in an all-out war!
The Noah is turning away. It's not gonna crash into the island!
Princess-sama saved us by drawing the ship away!
--Princess Shirahoshi! --Please escape!
I have to go out to the sea in order to keep the Noah away from the bubble!
I'll give you one last chance, Shirahoshi!
If you say "Yes," I'll spare your life!
Have mercy, Decken-sama!
Marry me!
You're not my type!
Then go to hell!
We're not gonna let her marry a guy like you!
She's our only baby sister! We're not gonna let you hurt her, Decken!
Brother Mamboshi-sama! Brother Ryuboshi-sama! Hoe-sama!
I'm sorry that we suspected you...
Don't mention it. Take me to the deck!
Oh, Hody Jones!
What happened to Neptune? Did you kill him?
I'm tormenting Shirahoshi with the Noah now.
Don't you think it's a good idea?
Huh, Bro?!
I have a good idea too!
What is it? Let me hear it.
If you die now...
What'll happen to this ship?
Decken!
The Start of an Intense Battle!
Luffy vs. Hody!
Hody! You... squirt!
My left hand...
...touched you.
What are you doing, you bastard?!
You betrayed me first, Decken.
Honestly, I panicked a little when this ship covered up the sky over the island.
But it was a good idea to break the bubble.
Fishman Island would be washed away
but we'd still have the Fishman District.
If you die here and now, your Mark-Mark power will become ineffective
and this ship will fall onto Fishman Island again...
Then it will destroy everything.
Now, more than anything, I want all of those annoying Straw Hats to be gone.
Thousands of my men will die too
but I can just get more human slaves, as many as I like, later.
Thousands will die, huh?
That's good. But first,
you...
...drop dead!
You fool! Don't do it!
Become a martyr for the New Fishman Island.
You'll die soon.
Then the ship will start falling again and it will fall onto Fishman Island.
Since I'm a kind man, I'll make your dream come true,
the very least I can do, before you die.
I'll kill Shirahoshi for you!
He stabbed Decken! What kind of relationship do they have?!
This is no time to think about that. Hody's gonna come this way!
We're gonna stop him!
Out of my way, you fools!
You stupid interlopers!
Brothers-sama!
Shirahoshi! Get away at full speed!
Now you're out of Hard Shell Tower - it's so easy to kill you.
It's no use!
The Merfolk may be the
fastest swimmers in the world but I'm way faster than you right now!
Brother-sama!
Shirahoshi!
Hody!
Gum-Gum...
...Snake Shot!
Luffy-sama! Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
--Straw Hat! --B-Brother!
Sorry to be late. I was caught up in strategizing.
You bastard!
Conchcorde Plaza
Meanwhile, at Conchcorde Plaza on Fishman Island...
Captain Vander Decken-sama abandoned me!
I need you to become a
sacrifice upon Shirahoshi's death, along with the island!
Why don't you fight, sea spirit!
Please! Do something about the Kraken!
--Beat him up, Kraken! --You're strong!
They're both huge but he doesn't seem like he wants to fight.
The Kraken will defeat him!
Hey, Great Monk! You must have misheard him!
What Decken said to you was "I'll leave the plaza up to you!"
What?
That means he wasn't gonna destroy the island!
But he said "Become a sacrifice."
He wanted you to fight hard as though you were going to sacrifice yourself.
Do you think so?
Yes. Isn't that right, guys?
Huh? Y-Yeah... he's right!
How lucky to be trusted by your captain that much.
--You're amazing! --It's time for you to man up!
Oh, that's what it was!
No, it wasn't.
Now, take this
and beat the Straw Hats up with us!
The Energy Steroid!
No way. It's not gonna work on that giant body!
It's working tremendously well!
What?!
Surume!
Captain Decken! I'm sorry that I didn't trust you!
Yeah! He beat the hell out of the Kraken!
--What happened? Are you all right?! --It's no good! He passed out!
Are you guys my enemies too?!
He's like a different person!
Leave it all up to me!
Where is my enemy?
Th-That guy right there, Wadatsumi!
Is that him?
All right!
Watch out, Jinbe-chan!
Fishman Karate:
7,000 Brick...
...Roundhouse Kick!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
How could he do such a giant creature that much damage?!
Nami-san!
Oh no! The wind blast brought Nami-san down!
Get up, you bastard!
Ouch! Who is it this time?!
You big shit!
What would happen if you so much as make a scratch
or two on our beautiful navigator?
Unbelievable! His kick worked too!
How strong is his leg that it can hurt a giant like him?!
Oh no!
I got messy.
That wasn't my fault!
I will fight you, Great Monk!
Pay with your life, you Jumbo Steamed Bun!
How strong can they get?!
Mil Fleurs!
Help us, Hyouzou-san!
Old man, can I get a wasabi octopus?!
No, you're not in a bar! Plus, you shouldn't eat octopus!
Don't be mean!
It's no use! He's completely drunk!
How pathetic!
If you can prove yourself now,
it's your chance to become an officer in one move.
I knew a little surprise attack like this wouldn't do.
Who are you?
I'm the soon-to-be No.1 Fishman swordsman - Nuru-sama!
What?
--What's wrong? --Is it a hangover?
Hyouzou-san!
You're not too bad!
You're weak.
Can you say the same thing after this?!
So bright!
If you can't see, you can't defend yourself from my sword!
Take this!
What?
You only use your eyes to see. That's why you're weak.
Go train some more and come back!
That was just dumb luck!
I'm gonna be the No.1 Fishman swordsman, I won't lose...
Who is No.1?
Stop!
Hyouzou-san, we're on your side!
--He looks strange. --That's not how he gets drunk usually!
He's much stronger!
Tottering Hash!
Sh-Shields don't work!
He was writhing in agony without any injury until a while ago!
Are you kidding? This is like what happened when Hody-san changed.
Hyouzou-san has become a monster, too?!
It feels great! I feel a surge of energy!
Oh, I wanna cut more people!
Let me cut you!
Run! Somebody, stop him! There's no way to defend ourselves!
It could be anybody!
I found one!
H-Hyouzou-san got stopped!
You look tougher than the anglerfish I just beat.
Zoro!
Sorry. I'm gonna take this guy.
This will be a nice warm-up before we go to the New World.
It gets less powerful in water as I thought.
"Less powerful"?
Stupid lowly creature!
Don't you know where you are?! You're in the deep sea!
A human like you has no chance to win a fight!
On top of that,
everything will come to an end soon.
Whether it's Shirahoshi or Fishman Island or your friends!
A fool like you can't protect anything!
No.
I'll protect them all!
That's what I worked for...
...those 2 years!
The Straw Hats are battling the
officers of the New Fishman Pirates.
The new, stronger attacks the crew has learned in their two years of training
continue to be revealed.
Far above them,
the Noah is getting closer by the second,
as it descends to destroy Fishman Island.
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Massive Brawl!
Straw Hats vs. New Fishman Pirates!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Massive Brawl!
Straw Hats vs. New Fishman Pirates!