Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
Wait!
What you're holding is...
Whaaat?!
"Navy"
The silver transponder snail
has received a signal!
A Buster Call has been requested!
A Buster Call has been
requested by Admiral Blue Pheasant!
Where?
Enies Lobby!
Have five of the vice admirals
near the destination respond!
Considering the distance,
I think it's quicker to head
there from headquarters.
How quick?
It's possible to get there within 30 minutes.
Immediately have ten battleships
get ready to set sail,
and summon five vice admirals!
Be swift!
Yes, sir!
A Buster Call has been requested!
The destination is Enies Lobby!
Have ten battleships get
ready to set sail immediately!
Hey! Hey!
Yes, Chief.
Dammit! Oh, crap! This one is
the portable transponder snail.
What have I done? I wasn't careful.
Of all things, I pressed the button
on the golden transponder snail!
Of all things...
...I requested a Buster Call!
Everyone! Leave the island!
A Buster Call has been
requested on Enies Lobby!
If you stay on the island, you won't survive!
This isn't your concern!
A Buster Call has been requested!
Battleships are coming!
Get off of Enies Lobby!
What was that?!
Where was Robin speaking from?!
The other side of these doors.
I can't let you pass. At least
give me time to say that.
Coo coo.
Get out of my way.
Robin's behind those doors, right?!
So she's there. So what?
You won't be able to see her...
...ever again.
No... I'll go there to see her!
I'll be right there, Robin!
Five Namis?
Nami Strikes Back with Mirages!
Stand up, Nico Robin!
Stand up already, you bitch!
What's that look in your eyes?!
Cancel the Buster Call right away!
There may still be time!
Shut up! You're still saying that?!
I'm the Chief of CP9! There's no way I can say,
"I made a careless mistake and
requested a Buster Call" now, you idiot!
What do I care how many casualties it'll cause?!
Once I hand you over to the World Government,
my future is all set!
That's all that matters, right?
That won't happen. Never!
What?
Everyone is... Luffy is...
...right behind us.
Don't get the wrong idea.
There isn't even a shred of hope for you.
The one who's fighting Straw Hat
right now is CP9's strongest member,
Rob Lucci, whose Power Level is 4,000!
Don't tell me you seriously
think that brat can defeat him...
Even if a Buster Call is invoked
or Straw Hat is right behind us,
that doesn't change the situation at all!
Do you get that, you bitch?!
Luffy... Everyone...
Robin!
It's a Buster Call!
Battleships are coming!
Hurry up, or we'll be burned to a crisp!
Get out of here!
That looks funny!
But no one's come here, when I
thought I'd show them the way.
It looks fun over there.
Chimney. Gonbe. What're you two doing?
Oh, Grandma!
Well, I found a weird hole.
Then, I took the pirate guy there.
And then, and then,
the pirate guy became small!
Small?
But, but, he did wham!
Wham?!
Right?!
Oh? That pirate kid did?
I don't quite understand,
but it sounds like it's getting
more and more interesting.
Things have suddenly started happening, huh?
Sounds like if I stay in this tower
too long, I may lose my life.
If you're gonna run, then leave the key here.
Shave!
I'm sorry.
I wanted to spend more time playing with you.
Shoot!
But we have to evacuate quickly, too, so...
Golden Bubbles!
This is the same attack that got Sanji-kun.
Even though I was being careful...
I can't hold the Klimatakt.
My entire body is slippery! I can't stand up!
How dare you make my body like this?!
Although it has the downside
of reducing your curves,
it does give you the most beautiful skin.
I envy you.
But in return, your fighting
power is reduced by half.
You should just give up on the key I have.
I... I can't do that!
Cool Charge!
That's no use. Playtime is over.
Tempest Kick!
What?
Mirage Tempo. I'm right here.
When did you...?! What's going on?
Finger Pistol!
Another fake! Where are you this time?!
This way! Right here!
What's that?!
Sh-She grew huge?!
What?
So you were a power holder, too!
She's a ditz.
A Buster Call has been requested.
Hurry up!
Go! Renowned sword, Nose Storm!
Tempest Kick!
Finger Pistol!
Okay! Good job!
Tempest Kick!
Finger Pistol!
Again?! Ahhh! No!
Zoro-kun! This plan really is reckless!
I suggest you stop this immediately.
No, wait.
What?
Our enemies are totally seized by fear
after seeing the power of the
renowned sword, Nose Storm.
What?! I-Is that right?
I'm back!
To think that he turned his friend into a sword...
He sure attacks recklessly.
Ha! He's just desperate.
It's just pointless resistance.
Zoro-kun! I've made up my mind! I'll do it!
This is the turning point of this fight!
Let's keep the plan going!
Go ahead and fight with no restraint!
That's what I wanted to hear!
Renowned sword, Nose Storm!
Killer Attack, "A Lure"!
"A Lure"
"Allure"?!
"Allure"
Oh! That's a beautiful,
splendid killer attack name,
suited for the renowned sword Nose Storm.
I like it, Zoro-kun!
Huh?
What? Um...
Hm?
What's that? It looks as if
he's asking us to kill them.
O-Oh...? Hmmm?
Z-Zoro-kun, what on earth are you doing?
I'll get them first!
I'll be the first!
Shave!
Dammit! To think that you used
that masked idiot as a decoy...
That was close.
So you meant "A Lure" instead of "Allure"?!
"Allure"
"A Lure"
I'm not tasty.
Am I bait? A decoy?
What a horrible man you are!
One more time. Killer Attack, Makie!
I don't even have a say in this?!
Besides, you're using those
words "killer attack" wrong!
Aren't I the one who'll get killed here?
Zoan type... So is that your trump card?!
Seriously, that's not me!
At any rate, this form...
It looks like a reindeer, and I know that
hat and the mark on it without a doubt.
But I can't believe...
...this is Chopper!
What savage beast's power does she hold?!
Moon Walk!
Tempest Kick!
Hey! Stop it!
What?!
Chopper! Hey, you're Chopper, right?
How did you become like that?!
I wonder if he can't recognize me,
since I look like this.
Aren't you Chopper?!
Let me tell you something!
I didn't think that was you!
Chopper!
Sh-She ignored me! How insolent!
Chopper! What's wrong?!
Take a good look at me! It's me! I'm Nami!
Chopper!
Chopper! Stop it!
Sanji-kun is downstairs!
Where did such a monster stray in here from?
Don't hurt him! He's my friend!
What happened to Chopper?
This is terrible. I have to stop him right away.
That's your friend? You pirates
sure own a creepy pet, huh?
Chopper!
She ignored me again! How insolent!
You're free to go stop that monster,
but I have a duty to stop you, too.
I'm gonna hurry up and finish it here.
Tempest Kick!
This is bad! Even the soles
are slippery. I can't dodge it!
Huh?! I could dodge it!
Ah... My right leg went back to normal.
Why? What caused it?
It's wet...
It got wet in the earlier
commotion. Oh, that's right!
Water! I can wash off
the soap power with water!
Aren't you being too optimistic?
Even if you figured out how
to undo Golden Bubbles,
there's no way I'd let you do that.
Sheep Cloud! Relaxing Bubbles!
I'll blow away those bubbles with wind!
Cyclone...
Shoot!
O... Oh, no... My strength is...
Supple Finger Pistol!
Takt...
Whip!
That was helpful.
Helpful?
If you blow me away like that,
the annoying bubbles on my
body get blown away, too.
That's a bluff. If you so wish,
I'll keep blowing you away until you die.
The weather forecast is cloudy!
Cloudy Tempo!
This is different from the
magic show stuff I used to do!
Clouds? More lightning?
Thunder doesn't get generated
from such thin clouds.
Instead, they'll condense!
Don't tell me...! No, she might do that!
The weather forecast is rain!
--Cool Ball!
--Shave!
Pour down! Rain Tempo!
You're not sweet at all. After I was nice
enough to make your skin silky smooth.
If being sweet means not
putting up a fight, then I'll pass.
Cool Charge:
What?
Mirage Tempo!
She disappeared?!
Now I understand... your powers...
...as well as the strength of CP9.
What's this?!
Mirage Tempo...
Fata Morgana!
Hey, is that really Chopper?
How come he doesn't recognize us?!
Who else has those antlers and wears that hat?!
Hm? Hey, wait a sec, Franky-kun!
That attack pose...
What're you trying to fire?! He's one of our...
D-Don't be reckless!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Nami's Decision!
Fire at the Out-of-Control Chopper!"
Nami's Decision!
Fire at the Out-of-Control Chopper!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!