Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
These are just in the way.
There it is...
"Cat Burglar"...
I'm not that great at the One-Sword Style, but...
Let's go, Butchie!
Okay! Let's do it, Siam!
Damn it! If I just had another sword!
If I can just get Zoro his swords...
What do you need swords for?
Luffy, Back in Action!
Miss Kaya's
Desperate Resistance
To think that these brats have held you back...
How the Black Cat Pirates have fallen...
Right... Jango?!
B-B-But... you said letting that kid
go wouldn't cause any problems!
Yes, I did say that.
But so what?
We knew he was going to try to stand up to us.
The only thing I didn't count on...
...was you guys' feebleness!
U-Us, feeble?
Who're you calling feeble?!
Watch what you say, Captain Kuro!
Yeah, you were strong before!
But that was three years ago!
It's not like we partied while you
lived the easy life in this village!
'As right! We've attacked lotsa
towns and sunk lotsa pirates!
Your point being...
You've done nothing for three years!
There's no way you can beat
the Meowban Brothers of today!
S-Stop! Butchie! Siam!
You're not our captain anymore!
Sorry, but we're gonna kill ya!
W-When did he get behind them?!
And those weapons...
Who...
Who are you going to kill?!
He snuck...
...behind us!
Eh?!
He's gone!
There it is! The Pussy Foot Maneuver...
Pussy Foot Maneuver?
You're right.
I do feel a bit of sluggishness.
He's handling them like kids,
after they had the upper hand
against Zoro and his one sword!
That man's "Pussy Foot Maneuver"
is a silent movement technique.
Even a group of 50 assassins would
be killed before sensing him!
There's no way we can escape his plan!
And I got chills after seeing that
habit of his again three years after!
His odd way of lifting his glasses
to avoid cutting his own face
with those Cat Claws...
Clear proof that he hasn't
forgotten how to fight!
It seems I've grown a bit good-natured myself,
during my last three years on dry land...
I'll give you five minutes.
If you can't take care of
things here in five minutes...
...then I'll kill every last one of you...
...with my own two hands!
Five minutes...
Five minutes should be enough!
H-Him! If we just beat him,
we can get past this hill!
We had the upper hand against him just now!
We'll cut him up in five minutes!
We're counting on you, Meowban Brothers!
Zoro!
What?!
H-Hey, you!
Now you're kicking my swords, too?!
Where's my "thanks"?
Yeah...
Thanks!
It's no use!
Three swords won't help any!
Your skill's still the same!
Tiger...
You don't get it, do you?
...Trap!
Four minutes.
Just having three swords is different
from knowing the Three-Sword Style!
He's strong...
One hit...
H-He beat the Meowban Brothers in one hit!
Don't worry!
I'll crush every last one of you
before your five minutes are up!
Three minutes.
I-I'll... slaughter him...
C-Captain...
H-Hypnotize me...
P-Please, Captain!
He's alive. You do sloppy work.
His tough fat saved him, huh?
Get 'im, Butchie!
More hypnosis?!
This guy means trouble!
He could already crack the ground apart!
What happens when he's powered up?!
This is my chance!
I gotta wake him up while I still can!
What is that crafty girl up to now?
Everyone's seriously hurt,
and he's just sleeping!
Die!
Get up!
Nami! Look out!
Two minutes.
Get up!
Nami! Look out!
Split in two!
Dodge it!
W-What the...?!
A chakram!
It wasn't just a hypnosis tool?!
Nami! How dare you stomp on my face?!
H-He's alive?!
Can't tell if he has bad or good timing...
L-Luffy...
Luffy!
Oww...
Ouch!
H-He's alive again!
This is bad!
Five minutes is impossible now!
Nami! That hurts, you jerk!
Th-That wasn't me!
It wasn't me-
N-Nami! Did you hurt your shoulder?
I-It's nothing. I'm fine...
I've done everything I can for now,
so I leave the rest to you...
We absolutely can't afford to lose this fight...
Yeah!
For the treasure!
It'll all work out in the end!
Try hard! For my treasure!
Okay! That sounds like you, alright!
One minute.
You can't be serious!
Not even Captain Jango and Butchie-san...
...can finish them in one minute!
Butchie! There's no time to think!
Kill that haramaki bastard!
And I'll handle that weird kid...
I'll kill Straw Hat!
It's about time for everyone to die now.
Huh? That bad butler is here too!
Isn't he...
Didn't he fall off that cliff and die?
No matter.
Don't approach me...
...from behind!
Kaya!
U-Usopp-san! Are you okay?!
K-Kaya... What are you doing here?!
I'm so sorry, Usopp-san...
I know you may not accept my apology,
but I just couldn't believe it...
K-Klahadore, a pirate...
N-Never mind that!
Why are you here?!
I-I told you to run away!
Your life is in danger!
But you're fighting!
Even after I treated you so horribly
and you've been hurt so much,
you're still fighting for me! So I...
Miss Kaya...
Why are you here?
S-Stop this...
Stop this, Klahadore!
Merry told me everything.
Isn't that the girl from the mansion?
Meaning she's the plan's final target?!
Then there's no need to go to the village now?
We just need to kill her, right?!
Klahadore, please!
If you want my fortune, you can have it all!
Just please leave this village! Right now!
I will gladly accept it... but...
...there's one other thing I want, you see...
What I want...
...is peace of mind.
Peace?
Yes. I want simple peace.
I find the villagers' trust that I've
fostered these past three years
to be nice and comfortable now.
So I want to have that peace of mind forever...
And I...
And I will have that peace!
And your fortune...
In short, pirates will come to the village!
And...
...you will leave your will and die!
These two things are absolute.
N-No...
Y-You're not...
Run! Run away, Kaya!
There's no use talking to him! Run away!
Y-You're not Klahadore.
You're not Klahadore...
Kaya...
Leave this village!
Oh... You'd point a gun at me...
Leave this minute!
I see. You've certainly grown
a lot these past three years...
...Miss Kaya.
Do you remember?
So much has happened in three years...
We spent so much time together,
even before your parents passed
away and you became bedridden...
So much time...
So many memories...
Together we suffered...
Together we rejoiced...
K-Klahadore...
I would visit the city with you,
and whenever you had a fever,
I constantly looked after you...
You listened to my stories so happily...
I devoted myself to you...
For so long...
Yes, for so long, I endured it...
Yes, it was all so that I could kill you today...
I, a man once known as Captain Kuro,
had to smile humbly for some snot-nosed girl...
I went against my nature
and sucked up to you...
Damn you...
Do you understand these daily insults?!
Do you understand this man
once known as Captain Kuro?!
Kuro!
Come to think of it...
...I still owe you for hitting me...
Usopp-san!
You hit me with all your might, as I recall...
If you hate getting hit that much,
I got a hundred more punches for you!
Usopp! You go save Miss Kaya!
Leave the bad butler to me!
What a helplessly evil guy!
I don't plan to help him, though!
I'm goin' after that hypno-freak!
Kuro! You're not cut out to be a pirate!
My ambition is much greater than yours!
Next time, on One Piece:
Beat Kuro!
Usopp the Man's Tearful Resolve!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Beat Kuro!
Usopp the Man's Tearful Resolve!