Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil.
This country will soon be destroyed.
And it will be rebuilt under a new king.
Namely, me!
Citizens of Fishman Island!
It's time to say goodbye...
...to the old Ryugu Kingdom!
Three hours from now, at Conchcorde Plaza,
I'm going to cut this incompetent King's head off!
Straw Hat Pirates!
I'll show you something good.
I know you are somewhere on the island watching this.
You people shattered Arlong's dream - he was a symbol of Fishmen's anger.
Zoro! Usopp! Brook!
--What fools... --I can't believe they got caught!
--It's water! --It's water!
That room will be filled with water by the time we finish executing the King.
You lowly creatures can't survive that, can you?
Shark! Take me to the Ryugu Palace!
I said "Wait," Luffy-kun!
Huh?
You people shouldn't fight Hody!
Jinbe! They have my crew!
And I got to do something about Hody before my friends get into real trouble!
You're impossible!
Just shut up!
Stop me if you can!
I shouldn't let my guard down just because we fought together.
I almost forgot that you're that man's brother.
You ready to do this?
Kid?
"A Rift Opens Up! Luffy vs. Jinbe!"
People called me The Submarine of the East Blue when I was a kid.
I can easily swim across even a twenty-five meter pool!
I can run that far!
I can't swim but I can run!
Hey, Brook! Let's see which one of us is faster sometime soon!
You can't beat me! I'm going to run beyond the horizon!
Anyway, it doesn't look good, does it?!
No, it doesn't! The surface of the water is getting closer!
--Look, look! The water is... --It's coming! It's coming!
Shut up!
What's your problem?! How can you be so calm?!
Yeah! Do you have any ideas?!
Nope.
--Don't be so honest! --That's so clear, I like it. Yeah...
If only I had my sword.
Sword? But...
I have no choice.
I have to do it in front of you two...
What is "it"?
Dorororororo...
Bone, bone, bone, bone...
Hey Brook, what are you doing?
Hey! Brook!
Bang!
Boom!
I'm out!
What?!
Okay, see you!
Hey, w-wait, wait, wait!
You got some explaining to do!
You can do something like that now?
Yes, I can make my soul leave my body.
That's just like a real dead person.
Yes, you're right.
It happened when I was on my world tour as Soul King...
I was in quite a slump at that time for a while.
TDS SALES PLUMMET---- CONCERT TICKETS REMAIN UNSOLD
Sales of TDs and concert tickets were dropping.
And I didn't know what to do.
Today's concert was not so great.
He's not making great music lately.
I couldn't feel his soul!
What happened to you, Brook? Write a new song that will sell!
It's not that easy to make a hit song...
Music is something much more sublime.
Maybe... Maybe, the God of Music doesn't love me anymore.
One more time... Just one more song is fine!
God! God of Music!
Bless me with a melody that will shake everybody to their soul! God!
Boom!
What?! What is going on?!
Since I got this ability, I noticed what's missing in my songs.
I found a way out of my slump!
--What was it? --Well...
If you had the ability to pass undetected through walls...
Any able-bodied male understands the potential, right?
I'm jealous, Zoro! I wish I were him!
Shut up!
Oh, the water got that high!
Do something already!
Luffy-chin! Boss Jinbe!
Luffy! Jinbe! Hold on a second! What are you guys doing?!
I'm gonna go to the Ryugu Palace to save my crew and kick that Hody guy's ass!
I said "Don't do it"!
Hey hey, why do you have to fight now?
Cut it out, guys!
Luffy-sama! Boss Jinbe-sama!
Shark! Take me! To the Ryugu Place!
I said "Wait"!
Outta my way!
Fishman Karate--Shark Brick Fist!
--What?! --Luffy-chin!
Huh?!
Luffy-sama!
Ow... Ouch!
It worked?! He's supposed to be immune to blows like that as a rubber man!
The Fishman Karate is all about manipulating the water around you!
The shock wave can travel through water vapor in the air
and through to the water within your target's body!
Every living thing is made up of water. So even a rubber man can't escape the impact!
Damn you!
I won't let you go, Luffy!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
Is this all you learned from your training?
Don't bet on it!
Enough.
Robin!
Robin-chan!
Hey, move aside, Robin!
Who are you?! Move!
Robin-chan's in danger!
Don't fight.
I don't know the reason but you two are friends, right?
Huh?! Why did Robin come out of the forest?!
WATERWHEEL TOWN
Take this!
J-Just give up! You guys can't win!
No way. Didn't you see Boss Hody's broadcast?
This country will be destroyed. And Neptune is gonna die!
What did you say?!
No!
Don't kill them.
If you do so, you'll be no better than them!
B-But...
Ryuboshi, Manboshi, take them into custody.
--I got it-so-la-ti-do! --Count on it!
You're as indulgent as before-dosun.
Does indulgence run in the Neptune family's blood?
You are not just getting back at humans but hurting your fellow beings.
Doesn't it pain your heart?!
Any Fishman who sides with humans deserves death-dosun!
Lead the way for your father--towards death! Fukaboshi!
Screw you!
Shit!
Dammit!
They did it!
They got the New Fishman Pirates!
Only the 3 great royal brothers could do it!
Prince Fukaboshi-sama!
Leave the rest up to us.
Thank you.
Let's get to Conchcorde Plaza to save our father!
All right. Let's go!
Okay, let's go to the execution ground.
Do you want some of us to stay here at the palace,
Boss Hody?
No, I don't think so.
This Ryugu Palace is impregnable.
Leave some men to open the gate when we come back.
We don't want the new king getting locked out!
We sure don't!
That'd be nonsense-jamon!
You can't win citizens' hearts with violence!
You have only a little life left. Say what you want.
This hurts.
That stupid swordsman cut me there.
The drug is wearing off. Hey, give me the Energy Steroid.
Y-Yes.
The pain is gone!
Is it okay to take that much at once?
I-I don't know.
Boss, what should we do about those 3 Straw Hats?
They're just humans. They'll drown if we leave them like that.
No matter who is coming to save them, no one can break into the palace.
That aside, how are the new residents from the Fishman District doing?
They're doing fine.
They're already moving.
That's good. There'll be empty houses for them.
Some will leave the country and the others will die.
They can just move into those houses.
We'll make a great country in which all citizens can look down on humans.
I found it! The ray of hope!
Those Fishmen that we saw earlier are all gone and nobody is here in the palace
but they left Pappagu-san behind.
All right then, Brook, ask Pappagu to find the key to unchain us.
--And the keys to this cage and this room... --Wait a minute, fool!
Huh?
One of my swords is enough. Just bring my sword.
I'll cut them all!
Wow, you're so reliable!
All right, I'll go ask Pappagu-san!
I-I'm scared!
What the hell? I thought we were just invited to a banquet.
I wonder if those Straw Hats are doing okay.
Pappagu-san...
Huh? Huh?
--Pappagu-san... --What? What?
I found you!
Boom!
I'm here!
A ghost!
Wait!
It's a ghost--I'm scared!
Pappagu-san! It's me!
I don't have much time! I need the key... I mean, the sword! Hey, wait!
No, stay away!
--No!! --What do you mean "No"? Listen to me! Wait!
Are you okay, you two? And Sanji?
Think about it, Luffy!
What will happen if you guys resort to violence now on Fishman Island?
Everytime Fishmen tried to open their hearts to humans, humans disappointed them.
"Humans are very violent." "Humans hate and look down on Fishmen."
What happened in the past planted those twisted ideas in Fishmen's minds.
In the case of Arlong,
many Fishmen believe that humans hunted him because he was a Fishman.
If you, the people who beat Arlong, fight Hody now,
what do you think will happen?
Even if it helps the island overcome this crisis,
witnessing you people knocking down Hody who is standing against humans...
...would make the islanders to think that things will never change.
But, Jinbe,
we have to rescue our crew.
And if nothing is done, Hody will rule Fishman Island.
We have so many friends on the island.
Hey, Hachi.
You've been trying so hard to hide who did that to you
but you said a while ago...
...that Hody attacks those Fishmen who are sympathetic to humans.
Did you get beaten by them because you spoke up for us?
Hachi!
Hatchin, is that true? Hody and his crew did that to you?
I can't...
Jinbe!
I think part of the reason Luffy wants to fight is because this is your home.
I heard that you helped our captain when he had his back against the wall.
We can't thank you enough for that.
And if Luffy wants to fight, we will go along with him!
We can't just leave the island like this.
We have reason to fight!
The reason is...
Camie-chan's here!
And Shirahoshi-chan's here!
Yes! This country is the Mermaid paradise of my dreams!
Get out of my way, Jinbe! You gotta let me go!
No, I won't! Leave it up to me!
You bastard!
Then I'll just beat my way past you!
I'll fight you as many times as I have to till you understand!
What did you say?!
Cut it out, guys!
Neptune's execution draws ever closer.
Hody's powerful allies are mobilizing.
The New Fishman Pirates are overrunning every part of Fishman Island.
But then, just as his ambition is coming to fruition,
an terrifying change befalls Hody!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Something Has Happened to Hody! The True Power of the Evil Drug!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!