Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they faced the New Fishman Pirates who were looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
and instigated an all-out war.
The Sea Kings stopped the Noah from falling onto Fishman Island.
Please help me!
I cannot stop Luffy-sama's bleeding!
Take my blood.
It's F.
You can have as much as you need.
Hey, Jinbe.
Join...
...my crew!
The Secret Uncovered
The Truth of the Ancient Weapon
The royal family came to a decision!
Yeah! We are free!
Damn Hody! Look at yourself!
I thought I was gonna be a slave forever!
Straw Hats! I owe you one!
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Huh?! That's a bit...
What? I-I'm gonna become king...
Finally I can set sail for the New World!
Are you sure about releasing Hody's human slaves?
Their anger against Hody could turn towards all Fishmen.
That is a different story.
This island has always been a place for pirates to travel and rest.
And since they meant no harm to us,
there is no reason to hold them here-jamon.
Now, for the rest of the New Fishman Pirates...
--Don't cut my head off! --P-Please!
We didn't even know that Hody killed the Queen!
They're all nuts, really!
--He's right! --It's Hody's fault!
We're not responsible!
I order you all to live on this main island!
What?!
What?! Are you telling us to live law-abiding lives?
It sounds better than working under Hody.
No way, King-sama! We don't want them among us!
We can't let our kids walk the streets!
Of course, I meant they need to do their time and work
under the supervision of my army-jamon.
I will give you all jobs to use up your overflowing energy.
From today on, the Fishman District
will be sealed off since it is out of our control-jamon!
The dark side of the Fishmen was exposed
along with the real killer of Queen Otohime.
A pirate - Hody Jones attempted to take over Fishman Island...
...but his plans
were foiled by human pirates who were just stopping by the island.
Hey, where is Straw Hat Luffy-jamon?
Well... He escaped.
Escaped?!
Why did you have to leave the plaza as though you were running away?
Can't you see? We had to fight with a lot of spectators watching.
If we stayed, they'd treat us like heroes or something.
Just the thought of it makes me shudder.
Becoming a hero is not a good thing?
Let me tell you something.
A hero is someone who will share his own sake with other people.
But I wanna drink it all by myself!
Again, that's not how you define a hero!
Why can't you join us, Jinbe?!
Come on an adventure with us! To the sea! It's gonna be fun!
Yeah, join us, Boss!
It's nice to have a former Warlord with us!
And Luffy, you need a complete rest!
As I said, I can't join you right now!
I'm grateful that you asked me.
I know it'd be fun to sail the sea with you all.
But I still have things that need to be done.
I have my current responsibilities which
I'm just taking a break from right now.
When I fulfill my duties and am free from them,
I promise I will come to see you all again.
And if you haven't changed your mind,
can I take you up on your offer then?
You swear?!
Whoa whoa, when a man talks about his "duty," you can't press him.
He likes Jinbe so much!
Luffy thinks so highly of you! So we're all gonna wait for you, Jinbe!
All right. Thank you!
Now what are we gonna do? Head for the New World?
What? Are you going to leave the island?!
I couldn't thank you properly and didn't get to talk to you!
All right! Let's stay at the Mermaid Cafe for a week or two!
That'd be just up your alley, wouldn't it?
But I wanna go, too!
Hey, wait!
Who is it?
A soldier of the Neptune Army?
Please wait, Straw Hats!
King Neptune! I caught up with them!
Good.
Luffy-kun, why did you leave? I wanted to thank you...
I don't wanna be a hero!
I know. Let's just have a banquet!
The banquet we could not have before-jamon.
A banquet?! Then I'll be right there! Banquet!
--Meat, meat! I wanna eat! --Boy! Then why did we leave?
We can't say no to a banquet.
All right! Let's go pick up Hachi and Camie!
The Fishman District was sealed off right away by Neptune's order.
Hody, the officers of the New Fishman Pirates, and Vander Decken...
...were placed in the Prison Tower.
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF FISHMAN ISLAND
Go, Kraken! Take him somewhere far!
Wadatsumi, you don't fit into any of the cells in the prison!
We forbid you from entering this country again!
CORAL HILL
Did you catch it?
Yeah!
Let's prepare these and take them to the palace!
They'll have a big banquet with the Straw Hats!
Count on us!
I heard they like sea monster meat.
Let's take snacks and cakes, too!
CANDY FACTORY TOWN
I heard they eat a lot. Take all we have!
Do they have enough sake?
I want them to have our highest quality sake!
Welcome to the palace-jamon, Luffy-kun, everybody.
Let's talk later during the banquet.
RYUGU PALACE
The long flounders will take you to the banquet hall!
--Whew! These rays are huge! --They're flukes.
He just said "flounders."
It's a dark room filled with water.
Are we really allowed in? I'm nervous!
I've never entered the palace before.
What's this place? What happened to the meat and banquet?
Oh, here comes the heroes!
Oh, it's filled with soldiers down there!
Thank you for saving Fishman Island!
We'll never forget what you did for us!
Heroes! Heroes! Heroes! Heroes!
Shut up! Stop calling us "heroes"! I wanna eat meat!
He's right! I wanna drink sake!
You idiots...
Luffy-sama! There is a stage right in front of you!
A stage?
Ladies and gentlemen! Let's start the banquet with the Straw Hats!
First,
we present you the greatest diva of the deep sea!
Maria Napole!
And the Swing Jazz Orchestra!
Wow! What a sweet voice!
Wow! Maria-sama!
She is rocking my soul! Oh yeah!
And the special guests!
D-Don't tell me...
Their beauty takes your breath away!
The Mermaid Cafe Dancers!
Shut up!
You're gonna die, Sanji!
Their beauty can't be captured in a picture! No. 1!
--I'm losing my strength... --Oh no!
--Awesome! --Fascinating!
Camie!
Ishilly! I'm glad that you're okay!
Here it comes! There's no having a banquet without it!
--Super I've been waiting for this! --That's how the Ryugu Palace should be!
Thank you.
Thanks.
Thank you!
Mermaid-chan!
Thank you very much!
Now, King, will you give a toast?
Before I give a toast, I really want to express my gratitude briefly-jamon.
All of you Straw Hats!
Thanks to you...
It's banquet time!
Cheers!
All right! Let's drink!
I know, I know. Nobody wants to hear me-jamon.
Bring the food!
Meat!
Eat! Sing! Drink! Dance!
Yummy!
We have plenty more.
Oh yeah? Thanks!
I need more obviously!
You eat a lot!
Come on, sisters, dance with me! Here we go!
Let's dance.
--I'll dance. --I won't.
--Maybe I'll dance. --I'll dance, so what?
Yum! You have great snacks on this island!
This island's sake is so good!
I already had it once!
I heard you got caught for that!
Forget about those little things!
Bone...
Are you okay, Hero-san?
That bastard, I didn't think of that!
I'm dying-bone!
Sanji!
You can't push yourself like that, young man!
I think you're gonna die soon.
Nobody cares about me-jamon...
The hairy old man doesn't look happy.
Hey, Straw Hat-san! Don't be rude to the King!
Luffy-chin! Luffy-chin!
Luffy, raise your glass!
You too, hairy old man!
Uh-huh.
But I want to express my gratitude briefly...
Father-sama!
Shirahoshi.
Cheers!
Cheers-jamon! Oh, whatever-jamon!
Cheers to you guys, too!
Cheers!
It's very good. I wonder if it's because of the water.
Oh, you can tell the difference, young lady?
I want more!
Why do you look so pale?! It's empty!
I-I can't believe it.
Moonfish! Shake, shake!
Dance more, everybody!
Eat, drink and make some noise-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do!
What do you want to talk to me about, pirate girl?
I'm sorry. I thought this was my only chance to talk to you in private.
What?!
I-I will tell you now!
I have a wife named Otohime who I swore to love forever!
Although she is dead, I am not going to cheat on her...
Who is Joyboy?
I read the Poneglyph in the Sea Forest.
Who is he apologizing to?
You can read it?
I'm a survivor of Ohara.
You don't have to tell me everything if you don't want to.
No.
I will tell you everything I know.
I trust you people.
Joyboy was a person from above ground who lived
during the Void Century-jamon.
That means more than 800 years ago.
That message was written to a Mermaid Princess
who was on this island at that time-jamon.
It's a letter of apology for not keeping his promise to the island.
Promise?
I do not know the details of his promise
but they say somebody will come and fulfill it on behalf of Joyboy someday.
That is the story handed down in our royal family.
So we believe the day will come
and have continued
looking after the Noah for generations just as we promised him.
When the day comes, the Noah will be put
to its true use for the first time-jamon!
I heard when all the battles came to an end today,
the half-destroyed Noah was taken to the Sea Forest...
...by the Sea Kings!
I wonder if Joyboy had power to
control Sea Kings since he was going to use the Noah.
No,
the former Mermaid Princess was the one who had such power-jamon.
That's what I thought.
Then, Princess Shirahoshi has that same power?
Yes.
I think it awoke completely today.
I am not happy about it.
I know how you feel.
2 years ago at a Sky Island,
I read a Poneglyph indicating where one of the ancient weapons is.
It was pointing at this island.
The Mermaid Princess who lived around the same time as Joyboy...
...was known by a specific name, wasn't she?
Since Princess Shirahoshi has the same power, she will inherit that name.
Another name for her will be...
...the ancient weapon...
...Poseidon!
Jinbe reveals speaks about two important matters.
After Whitebeard's death, distribution of
power among pirates in the New World was decided...
...by none other than one of the Four Emperors.
And a fierce and epic battle occurred within the Navy.
Its shocking conclusion...
...becomes a big obstacle for Luffy as he enters the New World.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Straw Hats in Shock!
The Navy's New Fleet Admiral!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Straw Hats in Shock!
The Navy's New Fleet Admiral!