Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can become Pirate King!
Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
BON VOYAGE!  hito kakera no yuuki hirogete
BON VOYAGE!      Let that shred of courage grow
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
saisho wa minna BARABARA ni egaite ita chiheisen
The horizons everyone dreamed of were separate at first
ima nara hitotsu no bouenkyou de nozokeru
but now they can be seen through a single telescope
kimi no KOKORO madowasu unmei no shoppai KONPASU
A bitter compass of destiny is leading your heart astray
saka te ni kajitoru yo
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
BON VOYAGE!
SHIGARAMI mo kako mo sutete
Toss aside your bonds and your past
bokura nara sore demo waraeteru hazu
We can surely smile despite that
yume o kanaeru tame no namida naraba oshikuwanai
Tears shed trying to achieve your dreams aren't for naught
PRECIOUS IN MY LIFE
precious in my life
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
My guess was that there'd be five survivors.
Now, who will die?
You die!
How insolent!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
Showdown in the
Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!
There!
Ah!
Hey, this house...
You remember that pretty lady who
often played the harp at the beach, right?
Yes, I know her very well.
Pagaya-san and his daughter,
Conis-san, live here.
Both of them are very nice people.
They treated me to lunch once.
Well, that woman was actually a bad person.
And her father, too!
What?!
I heard it, too.
If I'm not mistaken, they helped
bad people from the Blue Sea.
Can't be...!
That's true!
They're really bad people who went against God.
My father said so, too!
Y-Your father did? I see...
Oh, come to think of it, your father is...
Yes, my father is a member of the
Divine Squad, so he's been serving God.
My mother always tells me
that he'll come home soon,
but I've never even seen his face.
Oh, but he works for God.
You have a wonderful father.
Really?!
Of course you do!
I hope you'll be able to see your father soon.
Yeah!
Skypiea will be dropped into the Blue Sea!
This nation will disappear!!
I can't let that man's feelings be wasted!
I must... I must tell them at any cost!
You're telling me to die?
Listen to yourselves.
Dangerous... That guy's dangerous!
That's just what you'd expect
from the game's survivors.
However, it seems you don't
realize who you're talking to.
It seems that you still don't
understand the existence of God.
An old fool who wishes happiness for Skypiea...
A warrior who single-mindedly
desires his "homeland"...
And thieves from the Blue Sea,
who are after the gold...
There are many hardships in this world,
so I don't care what my lambs wish for...
...but this nation has a fundamental problem.
If you have time to spout such nonsense,
tell me where the Divine Squad is!
Just what is your goal?!
The return of His Majesty, Gan Fall.
The return of His Majesty?
That's right.
After his visit, God returns to his rightful place.
Return?!
Are you saying that you're leaving Skypiea?
That's right. I've got a place to return to.
It is a place regarded as God's home
by the people on the sky island where I was born.
What's he...?
People call that place "Endless Vearth."
There, the ground extends
as far as the eye can see!
That is precisely the dream world that I seek!
This Endless Vearth is a land befitting me!!
Fighting over Upper Yard...
such small Vearth... is a petty triviality.
Listen.
The root of your conflicts lies in a deeper place.
Think about it carefully!
It was born in the sky, though it's not a cloud.
It lives in the sky, though it's not a bird.
A nation rooted in the sky... This nation
itself is an utterly unnatural existence!
Soil has a place to return to.
So do people and God.
D-Don't tell me you...
It's nothing you should be surprised about.
As God, I'm only adhering to...
yes, the province of nature.
That's right.
I will drag down every human from this sky!
Are you planning to wipe out this nation?
That's just natural.
Don't be conceited, Eneru!
The term "God" is just a title used
to refer to the leader of this nation!
Yes, up until now, anyway.
The real "God" does not live in the human world!
Former God, Gan Fall...
You were worried about the
Divine Squad, weren't you?
Six years ago, you lost against my forces,
and I took your 650
subordinates under my charge.
Just this morning, they finished the
work I asked them to do on this island.
I told you, didn't I?
The only ones who are standing on this
island right now are the six of us here.
Such a shame...
Y-You...
It's not that I wanted to harm them.
When I told them my goal...
...they challenged me with
angry looks on their faces!
They all have family on Angel Island!
Yes, I know.
I have to bury their families soon, too.
Are you...
...a devil?!
Five million... ten million... twenty million...!
Weren't we...
Weren't we the evil ones?
The Shandian warriors...
They attack God's Island, Upper Yard,
only because they want to get back
the homeland of their ancestors.
Are you thinking about that again, my Lord?
Please look at the blessed
lives of people in Skypiea.
It all started when our ancestors
took away Upper Yard 400 years ago.
Isn't it our duty to carry on this battle
and protect that blessing for this nation?
I'm sure we've tried to
negotiate as much as possible.
Those who cannot understand it do not
deserve your compassion any longer.
400 years...
The time for us, or for them,
to accept defeat may have long passed.
Enemy Attack! Enemy Attack!
Is this an attack by the Shandians?!
I-It's not the Shandians!
What do you mean?!
A man who calls himself God Eneru...
God Eneru?
Who could he be to call himself
God in front of His Lordship?
Th-This is...
Divine Squad, huh?
They weren't as strong as I expected.
So you are...
Well, you should at least acknowledge
that they were loyal to God.
Eneru!
So you're God? No, former God, I guess.
How dare you...?!
Eneru-sama, what are we going
to do with this old former God?
Just throw him in the sea or something.
He probably couldn't even
be used for manual labor.
At any rate, this is quite a nice shrine.
But what we need is the Divine Squad.
I'll have them work very
hard as my subordinates.
They are my subordinates.
Quiet! You are not "God" any longer!
20 million volt...
...Vaari!
Weird knight!!
Old man!
God exists in this world.
How mortifying...!
That God... is me!
A Devil Fruit's Power?!
It's probably the Rumble-Rumble Fruit.
If I'm not mistaken, among the many kinds of powers,
it's one of those said to be "invincible."
The power of lightning!
Lightning...
There's no way that humans can defeat him!
Well, it's exactly the time that I prophesied.
Now...
...there are five! I'm glad you've survived!
Now, I shall bring you along with me!
To the dream world that I'm setting off to!
To the Endless Vearth!
I shall bring you along with me!!
What?!
There, I will build an indisputable "Nation of God"!
The only ones who can live there
are the chosen ones here.
What's that guy talking about?
Those subordinates of mine,
who couldn't even handle
a short survival game,
will only lower the nation's stature.
And... What if we refuse?
Robin!
Refuse?
Why? It was decided by God.
If you stay here, you'll fall into
a bottomless pit with this nation!
It's probably true that with
your power, you can do that.
But if you thoughtlessly destroy this nation,
isn't the thing you want going to fall as well?
You mean the golden bell?!
That's right.
Golden bell?
The golden bell...
You needn't worry. I already have some idea.
If I recall the actions you took,
there is only one possible place.
I'm pretty sure that I'm thinking
of the same place that you are.
You seem surprised.
Did you think you'd be able
to outwit me by saying that?
How foolish...
Robin!!
I hate calculating women.
No...
She's a woman!
I can see that.
You've got good skills.
Are you... a nutjob?!
Burn Bazooka!!
Kari!
C-Can't be!
He erased the bazooka's powerful fire!
You still don't get it, do you?
The energy that you can handle is nothing to me.
The thunder reverberated...
That means the air expanded
at the speed of sound!
It's that powerful!!
The scale of his energy is so different from ours!
H-He's really... lightning itself!
Oh, boy... We are about to set off
to the Endless Vearth together.
You don't have to get so
blood-thirsty, you know.
Who said we're coming with you?
I don't care about your so-called "dream world"!!
Zoro! Don't, Zoro! He's too strong!!
Until I teach your body a lesson,
you probably won't understand...
...the definition of "God."
God has an overwhelming power
that could never be matched,
no matter how hard you struggle!
And then you feel it...
The despair!
Having all your hopes dashed
is the same as death itself.
Zoro!
People fear death above all things!
That's why people prostrate themselves
before God and beg for mercy.
That just can't be helped.
Living beings are meant to
bow before that which they fear.
What a pity... That's how instinct is.
What's with this guy? He's incredibly strong...!
What's the meaning of this?
Did you come to be killed?
What the...?!
Are you familiar with a thing called
the "Sea Prism Stone," Eneru?!
Sea Prism Stone?
If I'm not mistaken, it's a stone that
can take away Devil Fruit powers!
I see... I feel weakened.
Sea Prism Stone... It's said that it
gives off the same energy as the sea.
It's a sea in solid form, so to speak.
That's why it can weaken
the power of Devil Fruits!
Die!
Y-You shouldn't... I know. It's Reject, right?
Your body will pay a heavy price as well!
What are you dissatisfied about?
You want Vearth, too, don't you?
Shut up! I'm happy to die...
...if I can take you with me!
D-Don't!
Reject!
Did you hear something?
No way...
Did he defeat him?
Itsumo no you ni zenryoku shissou
Racing full speed ahead as always
A to Z hashirinuketeku
A to Z, we run through it
Nayandari suru sa shichiten battou
We all have worries and fall many times
Itsuka joushou sureba ii zetchou
But we just need to rise to the top someday
Asahi noboru ano umi no
What could be beyond the sea
mukou-gawa ni nani ga arun darou
in which the morning sun rises?
Koukou to hikaru taiyou no aru houkou sukoshi zutsu ikou
Let's go little by little toward the brilliantly shining sun
I never treat you "bad"
Nankai koronda?
How many times did we fall?
Daijoubu bokutachi wa tashika ni ima ashita ni sa yubisashiten da
It's all right, we're definitely pointing at tomorrow now
Smile! Come back to you, friends
Come back to you, friends
It's not that people fear God. Fear itself is God.
In that case, I'm fear itself. Hence, I am God.
I will put an end to this nation
in the sky with God's power!
Huh?
I don't have a clue what you're talking about!
Next time, on One Piece:
Ambition Toward the Endless Vearth!
The Ark Maxim!!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Ambition Toward
the Endless Vearth!
The Ark Maxim!!