Until I can reach that great sky,
I believe, to that one tomorrow, hey
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one dream
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the good times
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Stumbling into the darkness, fumbling about to find the answer
Freezing up when there's no goal in sight
Umm you and me, yes, in this world where we share our feelings
I feel the beat guiding me, and begin to walk, oh yeah
Share the music, anytime
Share the one dream and believe in each other
Share the good times holding hands
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style
Beginning, expanding, this flavor is beyond imagining
I feel so good throughout my body, I know I can be free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far
Share the one dream, by telling each other
Share the good times and laugh
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall
I'll be there soon, I believe, to that one world, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
To rescue his brother Ace who
has been captured by the Navy,
Luffy stowed away on a Navy ship with
the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock's help
and headed to the Great
Prison - Impel Down!
Meanwhile, the rest
of the Straw Hats
who had been sent to separate
islands by Bartholomew Kuma are...
This is a country of laborers.
Pull! Pull!
The people who work here are
criminals from various countries
or citizens of countries that refused to
be allied with the World Government.
In other word, slaves.
--How long until the bridge is complete?
--I have no clue.
You'll become one of laborers so all you
have to worry about is making the bridge!
Is this good to eat? I've
never seen a fruit like this!
Usopp'n!
Boy! What was it?! Did
that plant try to eat me?!
Of course, they're
man-eating plants'n!
Where the hell am I?!
This is the Swindling
Forest - Glinston!
H-H-Help me!
The Crew's Whereabouts
Negativity Princess and the Demon King
I didn't know Navy sailors
got to eat grub this good!
But the meals that Sanji
cooks are way better!
"Hancock & Luffy"
Love-Love Beam!
I can't stop thinking about
those two girls on Luffy's crew.
So you choose those
two girls over me?!
I told you to forget about me.
I didn't know you
were so stubborn.
Tell me what you don't
like about me, Luffy!
I'll change myself for you!
Don't leave me, Luffy!
I won't back off!
Because...
The love those two have for
Luffy can't compare to mine!
Whew! Couldn't eat another
bite! That was so good!
Luffy!
Don't forget that
you are a stowaway.
Is that how that beautiful,
elegant Empress laughs?
Well, I kinda find
that attractive, too.
But something is not right.
"More investigation
is needed."
Meanwhile, the other crew who had been sent
Grand Line, Gloom Island
to separate islands by Bartholomew Kuma are...
Ruins of Muggy Kingdom
I'm holding a grudge...
I know I said that
if I were to travel, I would go to a dark,
damp old castle shrouded in mystery
and spend my time
singing dark songs.
Damn that Kuma!
But I didn't know there
would be no servants!
And I didn't know there wouldn't be bagel sandwiches
and hot chocolate in a comfy bed in the morning!
I didn't know there wouldn't
be any stuffed animals here!
Where am I? Moria-sama!
I miss you, Kumacy!
I wanna go back
to Thriller Bark...
What is that?
That's what I thought! Somebody
has been sent here like me!
I hope that
somebody is cute.
I can't expect too much!
Anyway, I'm not on
my own anymore!
H-He is...
one of Straw Hats!
He must have been
beaten by Kuma.
He's dead, isn't he?
He's still alive with all
those scars and bruises!
Looks like it's just a matter
of time before he's dead.
That serves you right!
I'm alive...
Where am I?
You are...
Run!
Negative Hollow!
I don't deserve to walk on the
same earth with everyone.
I'm sorry.
Why are you here?
What about you?! Don't start
screaming all of sudden!
Where is my sword?
I'm not gonna
return your weapon!
You bitch!
Take this!
Negative Hollow!
I'm such a piece of garbage.
I'm sorry to be alive.
Yes! I can do anything
if I put my mind to it!
How dare you!
Stop talking with your
low voice! It's not cute!
You serve me from
now on! Understand?
Be cute!
What the hell
are you doing?!
Get off of me!
I'm not alone anymore!
Shit! I can't move!
What the hell?
Kumacy!
What did you do to me!
Get off of me!
I'm sorry that I yelled...
It's okay as long as
you learned a lesson.
You little bitch!
I'm sorry about my attitude.
Screw you!
I'll call you "mistress"...
I won't!
I'm really sorry that
I'm being so rude.
That's enough, you idiot!
I don't have any
time to waste.
I got to go back.
The exit is that way.
Yeah?
Why did I tell you that?
Where're you going?! How
can you miss the door?!
Hey!
What? You wanna tell
me where my sword is?
Y-y-y...
...you gonna leave?!
It's none of your business!
I'm not gonna let
you go so easily!
You've got to deal with
me a little bit longer!
Grand Line, Lazy Bones Island
"Land of Poverty" Hungeria
We call on you to answer us!
We pray that all those hateful
people will be terrorized and killed!
Grant our wish!
We call on you to answer us!
Come, Satan!
Come, Satan! Come, Satan!
Grant our wish!
Satan-sama! Satan-sama!
Is-Is this the Devil?
The black magic
really worked!
What a dreadful figure!
He's definitely unearthly!
Our prayer will be answered!
We must have our revenge!
--There is nothing left for us!
--The Long-arm Tribe took everything from us!
Demon King Satan-sama! If our wish comes true,
we are all prepared to
sell our souls to you!
Leave them all bloodied!
Demon King Satan-sama!
How far have I
been carried away?
What happen to Luffy
and the others?!
I must go back to meet them!
W-Wait a minute! Don't go
back to Hell, Satan-sama!
--Try to stop him!
--Maybe we haven't offered him enough!
What does
Satan-sama want?!
A sacrifice? Some blood?
What should we do?
What should we offer to
make him grant our wish?!
What do I want?
Excuse me.
Could I look at your panties?
U-Underwear! Hurry and
show him your underwear!
Um...
I don't need to see the
guys' underwear. Wow!
Returning to the present, to rescue his
brother Ace from prison,
Luffy speeds steadily over the waves
to the Great Prison - Impel Down!
Something stinks! It reeks!
Whew! Couldn't eat another
bite! That was so good!
Luffy!
Don't forget that
you are a stowaway.
Hancock! Is anybody
else in your room?
Oh, damn!
Lieutenant Stalker, did you
really hear someone else?
Yes! I'm sure that I heard "Whew!
Couldn't eat another bite!"
I don't think the
Empress would say that.
It can't be!
If that was her, I'll give
myself a Mohawk!
I'll do that, too!
W-Whew! Couldn't
eat another bite!
She said it!
I'm done. Take these plates.
Don't forget the amount.
I need it five times a day.
Isn't that a bit much?!
What about our food?!
I don't care if you
starve to death!
She's terrible!
But, beautiful!
6 days left for the public
execution of Portgas D. Ace!
After having all their guard
ships destroyed by Whitebeard,
tensions at Navy
Headquarters are rising.
Renowned marines started assembling at the
harbor of Marinford from various regions.
In the name of justice, the machines of war were
steadily being built up at Navy Headquarters.
Meanwhile, in the
Holy Land of Mary Geoise...
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
who had already been summoned
were told the locations of their battle positions.
But they are all ruffians who
can be tamed by no one.
One thing is certain:
It is impossible for them to
cooperate and fight together.
O-Old man!
How can you still live with
all those terrible wounds?
Ace!
Because of you, the
Navy Headquarters -
No! All of the World
Government! - is a mess.
K-Kill me!
You should kill me!
Kill you?
You idiot! Nothing
can stop it now!
Even if you die now, that won't
prevent Whitebeard from fighting!
Nobody can stop it now.
We made the
king of the sea...
...angry!
Father!
Setting aside his concern for his crew,
Luffy heads to Impel Down to save Ace.
An inescapable prison for
the most terrible criminals.
Will Luffy be able to reach his brother, Ace?
Next time, on One Piece:
"Deadly Break-in!
The Underwater Prison Impel Down"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Deadly Break-in!
The Underwater Prison Impel Down