Until I can reach that great sky,
I believe, to that one tomorrow, hey
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one dream
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the good times
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Stumbling into the darkness, fumbling about to find the answer
Freezing up when there's no goal in sight
Umm you and me, yes, in this world where we share our feelings
I feel the beat guiding me, and begin to walk, oh yeah
Share the music, anytime
Share the one dream and believe in each other
Share the good times holding hands
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style
Beginning, expanding, this flavor is beyond imagining
I feel so good throughout my body, I know I can be free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far
Share the one dream, by telling each other
Share the good times and laugh
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall
I'll be there soon, I believe, to that one world, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After being ejected from Sabaody Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma,
Luffy was separated from
his friends and arrived alone
at the female-only empire of Amazon Lily.
Big Sis!
Big Sis! What happened?!
What in the world happened?!
Oh, I, uhh...
He saw my back.
After seeing the secret hidden on the
back of Pirate Empress Boa Hancock,
Luffy was caught by the Kuja Pirates
and taken to a fighting arena.
Love-Love Beam!
Hey...!
Hey, you! What did you do to them?!
They saved my life, you know!
This is the warrior nation of Amazon Lily.
The strong are beautiful.
Fight your hardest and perish.
We will watch and see you off.
You guys are screwed up.
That woman...
She turned your comrades into stone,
so how can you all sit
there and laugh like that?!
Th-The savage is yelling at us!
Unbelievable! What a vicious creature!
I feel bad about those three,
but the Snake Princess was
right to do what she did!
They're the ones to blame! They
broke the rules of our land!
Whatever I do,
I will be forgiven.
The reason for that is,
yes...
...because I'm beautiful!
You piss me off!
These guys have powers?
A Difficult Fight for Luffy!
The Snake Sisters' Haki Power!!
Execution! Execution!
Execution! Execution!...
The younger sisters'
Snake Pit Dance is about to start!
I can't wait to see Marigold-sama's "Salamander"
Youngest Sister
Marigold
Snake-Snake Fruit
Model: King Cobra
with my own eyes!
And Sandersonia-sama's "Eight-Headed Serpent"!
Middle Sister
Sandersonia
Snake-Snake Fruit
Model: Anaconda
How magnificent she looks!
She was a strong warrior
to beat the Gorgon monster,
and this is proof of it!
The cursed younger sisters are lovely too!
Cursed? What're they talking about?
They look like they've
eaten Devil Fruits to me.
He's finished for sure now!
I can't wait anymore! Hurry and start!
Execution! Execution!
Execution!...
Perhaps I should swallow him whole...
Or squeeze him to death...
Don't tell me he's scared stiff!
Just stand there and die!
Hold on! Time out!
What? Going to beg for your life?
Apologizing now won't
make your crimes go away!
No, it's not that.
What's going on?
Look!
There!
You're not cracked, are you?
Wait here, you guys!
Sorry you got turned
into stone because of me!
If Chopper were here,
he could've examined you right away,
but maybe you'll go back to normal again
like when Blue Pheasant turned
me and Robin into ice!
Are you sure you shouldn't be
more concerned about yourself?
Shut up! I can do whatever I want!
That man...
Is he trying to save Margaret and the others?
That can't be!
He's already been sentenced to death!
Alright, then...
So I just gotta kick your asses now, right?!
What a joke!
What did he just say?!
He intends to beat the younger sisters!
Hilarious! Making people laugh
after being sentenced to death!
Men really are hilarious!
Is that okay, beating you up?
Yes, that's fine!
If you haven't given up on your life yet,
then I'll warn you in advance:
I wouldn't fall into the pit between
the seats and the ring if I were you!
You can fall if you'd like,
but the bottom is filled with blades, so...
Are you ready to go now?
Yeah! All set!
Good.
Then let's begin!
Kill him, Sandersonia! Marigold!
Through combat,
give him the ultimate punishment
for the great crime of sneaking onto
our maiden island and offending me!
I've been waiting for this!
I guess he has some skill...
Get him, Marigold-sama!
What the...?!
Poison?! That was close!
Wrong! It's powerful poison!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
It bounced off!
That hurts!
How...?! I'm made of rubber!
See! He really is all bark and no bite!
But it's true that men stretch! How neat!
Huh?! Am I not rubber anymore?!
No, that's not it!
Then why do impact blows hurt?!
That's not fair, Mari!
You're hogging him all to yourself!
I want to have some fun with him too!
Why does that hurt?! I'm made of rubber!
Come to think of it, that axe guy also...!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Hoisa!
Wh-What the...?!
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
It's exactly the same!
But he didn't have powers!
Does that mean it's not a Devil Fruit power?
I take it you have powers, too.
A Paramecia type, from the looks of it?
I knew it!
Why are you lying and saying you're cursed?!
That's a secret we can't tell anyone,
not even an opponent about to die.
Damn!
But I take it you can't use Haki?
Most outsiders can't.
That's why you're weak.
Left kick...
Over here!
She read what I was going to do!
Snake Slam!
Yes!
That one didn't hurt.
Same as usual.
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Snake Dance.
What amazing moves!
With Sonia-sama's Haki,
there's no attack she can't dodge!
You're very straightforward.
I can read you like a book.
What's going on?!
She's guessing my every move!
Focusing entirely on offense
is nice and all, but...
Snake Stick!
Ouch!
Don't forget that there are two of us!
Not good!
He's falling into the pit!
Something seemed unnatural
about that just now...
That man...!
Th-That was close!
So close!
He should've just kept falling!
However tenacious he is,
he still doesn't stand a chance
against the younger sisters!
They're at the very top of the Kuja Pirates!
The Snake Princess put
her hair behind her ear!
Her loveliness knows no bounds!
This man is the very definition
of "nothing but talk."
I can't help but laugh.
Shut up, you dumbass!
Oh, my!
He spoke abusively to
the Snake Princess again!
Unforgivable! Hurry and kill him!
Sonia! Mari!
End that man's life at once!
To ensure there are no further outbursts...
...from his filthy mouth!
I was hoping to have
a little more fun with you,
but you heard our big sister!
It looks like playtime is over now.
Let's give the criminal despair and death!
Margaret!
Hey! What're you doing?! Don't touch them!
What if she breaks?!
She saved my life, you know!
We are going to break her.
You said she saved your life.
Then that's all the more reason to.
I feel bad for her,
but this is your punishment.
Don't be stupid!
This duel is between me and you!
Stop it!
Above.
Hey, you!
Damn! Let go!
You're the only one who
thinks this is a duel.
This is a public execution!
Just sit there and watch!
The emotional trauma you gave our
sister goes much further than this!
Everyone here looks up to the Snake Princess!
She's strong, noble, and the most
beautiful woman in the world!
The Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock!
Hey! Stop it!
She looked up to you guys, you know!
Everyone in this land does.
So I think this is what she would want!
The hell it is!
What are you, stupid?!
Oh, my. What crude language.
After her, we'll break the other two as well.
Nice and slowly, too.
That'd make it more painful
for you too, right?
Here goes!
Three...
Hey! Stop!
Two...
Stop it! Do you hear me?!
It's no use.
One...
Margaret!
I said stop!
The warriors are fainting!
Could this be...?!
What a relief!
She isn't hurt anywhere!
Oh, I guess you guys are sensible after all!
That was "Conqueror's Haki" just now...!
This can't be real!
Only one out of a million
people can master that Haki!
Only a chosen few can use it!
I've never seen any person who
can use it other than our big sister!
This boy has the "qualities of a conqueror"
to stand above others!
He's just like me.
The Color of the Conqueror?
How can this be?
Is he no mere boy after all?
Just who is that guy?!
What's everyone blabbing about?
What's the big deal?
He doesn't realize he used Haki?!
I guess he hasn't figured
out how to control it.
Alright!
You showed me you're strong!
Now let's get on with the duel!
Luffy activates Gear 2,
and the sisters respond by unleashing
their true Snake-Snake powers.
Sandersonia's hair turns into giant serpents
while Marigold cloaks her body in flames,
and the sisters continue their attack.
Next time, on One Piece:
"All-Out Special Power Battle!!
Gum-Gum vs. Snake-Snake"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
All-Out Special Power Battle!!
Gum-Gum vs. Snake-Snake