Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
This smell is...
It's him!
Huh?
Doctorine! There's a problem!
He's... Wapol is back!
Is that so...
Ahh! That bastard!
That annoying mouth!
Look! Everything is as it used to be!
This is my castle.
We're restoring the Drum Kingdom!
Just a moment, Wapol-sama!
On top of the castle...
Hmm?
What's that strange flag?
What happened to the Drum Kingdom's flag?!
I burned that thing.
So you show yourself, Dr. Kureha!
The last survivor of the doctor hunt!
This castle is no longer yours!
This isn't a place for rotten brats like you!
Leave this country!
The Drum Kingdom has already died out!
What'd you say?!
Wait!
I'm gonna beat the crap outta him!
Vs. Wapol's Corps!
The Power of the
Munch-Munch Fruit!
Gum-Gum...
W-Wapol-sama! It's Straw Hat!
Ah!
...Pistol!
– Wapol-sama!
That was close...
How dare you bastards...
Over and over again...
How many times do you have to be in our way?!
Hmm? Why are they here?
Ah!
Since I had someone injured with me then,
I ran, as there was no other choice.
But this time...
I don't have to hold back any more!
Hmm, you bastard!
How dare you suddenly attack Wapol-sama,
the king of the Drum Kingdom!
That's right! He's the king!
How dare you do such a thing to his Excellency,
the most excellent ruler of all
the citizens on this island!
Who cares! You guys tick me off!
Hey young man. You know them?
Yeah, I do! He's that annoying mouth!
The annoying mouth pirate!
That annoying mouth?
He keeps getting in my way!
He ate part of our ship and attacked my friends!
I won't let him get away with it any more!
Before that, aren't you cold in that getup?
Huh?
See?
Didn't they say he was the king?
He isn't a pirate?!
That's what you just realized?!
Humph! What an idiot!
It seems he finally realized his rudeness.
Wapol-sama is the king of the Drum Kingdom.
When he met you before, he was temporarily
a pirate for his own reasons. That's all.
He's done being a pirate
and is going back to being the king
of this castle and country.
Hey, this place is cold!
That's what I've been saying!
It's 50 degrees below, you know!
They're making light of us!
Wapol-sama!
I'm really mad now... Straw Hat!
I'll bite you off!
Um, could you hold on a minute?
Luffy went to get some clothes.
He's gone?!
Let me ask you a question.
He... stretched earlier... His arm...
Yeah, he stretches...
it's because he's a rubber man.
Wh... What's that?
It's a monster!
To sum up, the rebel old hag and some
of the Straw Hats are in this castle.
Once we eliminate all of them, there won't
be anyone else impudent enough to defy me.
Precisely.
This will become the bright day
of the Drum Kingdom's restoration.
I'll start with you, Dr. Kureha!
You've got quite the nerve settling
in the castle during our absence...
and even flying a strange flag!
I made this castle Hiriluk's grave.
I wasn't really interested
in such a run-down castle,
but this reindeer insisted on
flying Hiriluk's flag up there.
I raised this skull towards all the diseases!
Skull...
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
I will save this country as a doctor!
By raising this, I'll fight just like pirates do!
Doctor fought to save this country...
by raising that flag...
Take me to the patients!
I came to save the Twenty MDs!
You still don't get it?!
It was a trap!
As you can see, the Twenty MDs are just fine!
So that was all...
Good... So none of them are sick?
I was convinced...
that this was a national crisis...
So it was just a trick...
Hey... when do you think a person dies?
Doctor!!
When a bullet from a pistol pierces his heart?
No... When he's attacked
by an incurable disease?
No... When he eats a deadly
poisonous mushroom soup?
No!
A man dies when people forget him...
Even if I disappear, my dream will come true.
The citizens' sickness of the
heart will be cured as well...
Why're you crying... Dalton-kun?
I wonder... if it's the same for a country...
Yeah, if there's someone to pass it on to...
Don't worry, Chopper.
Your mushroom can't kill me.
I had... such a good life!
Good-bye, quack...
Thank you, Chopper!
This castle is where Doctor died...
He died trying... to save this country...
So this place is... this place is Doctor's grave!
Grave?! That stupid doctor's?!
How dare you violate my sacred castle
with that scum doctor's flag!
Burn down that flag already!
I won't let you make it inside this castle...
Hmm?!
Never!
Wapol-sama... he is...
That's right! From that time...
The monster... that followed the stupid doctor!
That flag... is Doctor's faith!
So I won't let you take it down!
Never!
Show them no mercy!
We're going into the castle!
Take down every single one of them!
Are you gonna fight, too, old lady?
Old lady?
Ugh!
If they're more than you guys
can handle, I'll give you a hand.
Appreciate that...
Wapol-sama! Please leave them to us!
We'll clean up the small fries right away!
Doctorine!
Hey hey hey, you with the afro.
What kind of brother are you,
throwing an afro at a lady?
Hey, you're getting it now.
You fell for it...
Huh?
Ah! What?! I can't shake it off!
What's this afro?! Static electricity?!
Exactly!
Ahh! Dammit! Come off! Dammit!
Ohhhhh... it's cold! It's cold!
Clothes! Clothes!
Clothes! Clothes! Clothes!
Where're the clothes?!
What's going on outside?
It seems noisy...
It's cold outside! Where're my clothes?
I didn't ask that.
I asked what was happening outside.
Ahh, it's a fight.
I see... You guys're okay, right?
Yeah, so stay in bed.
You can use my clothes.
What? Your clothes're ugly.
They're cooler than yours.
Really?
Well, I guess it's all right if they're warm.
Alrighty!
Oh... I wondered what the fuss was about...
That bastard!
I'll beat up that annoying mouth!
Dammit!
What's with this afro?
It doesn't come off! It doesn't come off!
There're lots more coming!
Marimo's Static Cling!
What the hell are these things?!
They're damn gross!
Hey, reindeer! Don't just watch! Help me!
Okay!
Take these off quick!
They're really gross!
On top of that, they're plain! Too plain!
Ahh! They're now stuck on me!
I'm giving them back to you!
Ah! Don't give them back to me!
Keep at least one!
No! They're gross!
They're gross to me, too!
Stop it!
Don't give them to me!
– What the heck are you guys doing?
– Ahh! Stop it!
Humph! They know nothing about teamwork.
I'll tell you one thing.
Despite their plain look,
those Static Marimos burn flashily.
Hmm?! Oh no!
He's going to burn these afros!
Here you go!
Okay... Hey! Where're you going?!
Decoy plan!
D-Decoy plan? Am I the decoy?!
Check mate!
Ah! Ow! Ow! Snow! Snow! Snow!
Move!
Wapol-sama!
Darn it!
Chopper!
Whoa... This is really warm!
Luffy!
Huh?
Grab my leg from there!
Your leg? Sure!
Like this?
Okay then! Don't let your hands go!
Hmm? Got it!
Armée de l'Air Assault... Gum Shoot!
That was okay I guess...
Th... Thank you. You guys're amazing...
Ah! Hey Luffy! You jerk!
Isn't that Nami-san's jacket?!
Yeah... Look!
He's still alive, though the hippo flew away.
Take it off! You jerk!
Wapol-sama, are you all right?
They're stronger than we thought.
We underestimated them!
I can no longer let them live!
Those bastards!
What?!
I'll show them... the true power
of the Munch-Munch Fruit!
Wapol-sama!
I'll show them... Munch Munch Factory!
Oh, he stood up!
Would a normal person stand
up after taking that attack?
His body's made tough!
Chess! Call out what I ate today!
Yes sir!
Well... you ate one butter-sautéed
cannon and one raw cannon on the ship.
Also cannonball and gunpowder salad as
well as a toasted house in the village.
What kind of stuff do you eat?!
When it comes to omnivores,
this guy takes the cake.
Wait and see...
Food soon becomes my blood and flesh...
He's gonna do something!
Huh?
What's that?
Munch Munch Shock!
Wapol House!
A house?!
Sweet!
It's too soon to be surprised.
Now this is the king's technique!
– Ahh!
Munch Munch Factory!
Ahh!
– Ahhhh!
What the...
H... He's eating his own men!
He's eating his own people!
He stopped moving...
Feast your eyes on this!
Come out, miraculous union!
– Huh?!
– What?! Union?!
I am the strongest warrior
of the Drum Kingdom...
Chessmarimo!
Well... isn't that just one
riding on the other's shoulders?
Sweet!
What's sweet about it?!
Don't let your guard down.
Hmm?
If they were really weak,
a stupid act like exiling doctors...
would've been stopped by the citizens.
The Drum Kingdom's Constitution, Article 1!
"Those who don't do as the
king wishes should die."
That sums up this country!
It's because this country is my country...
and this castle is my castle.
Of all the flags, don't fly that quack's flag!
It will ruin the castle!
A pirate flag...
Hey, reindeer. That flag...
Nothing is impossible for the man
who raised a flag with a skull!
That's what I told you, right, Chopper?!
You bastard... you attacked Doctor's flag!
Doctor... tried to save even you!
Chopper...
Don't hold a grudge against humans.
This country is sick right now.
The king also suffers from
a sickness of the heart.
Hmm?
Why?
Doctor, a guy like him isn't worth saving!
Hmm?
I... I won't hit you... so leave this country!
What're you saying, Chopper?!
You think he'll just listen to you?!
But... after all...
Humph!
Ah!
Chopper!
Hey, annoying mouth!
Huh?!
Straw Hat!
You were a fake pirate, right?
You don't know what this pirate flag means
because you were fake pirates
who didn't even risk your lives!
That guy...
What that flag means, Straw Hat?
Stupid pirate flags have no meaning!
That's why you're hopeless!
What'd you say?!
A pirate flag isn't something
that you can raise as a joke!
What an idiot! If it weren't for a joke,
there's no way I, the king, would raise it!
Don't put that stupid flag
back up when I take it down!
Dodge it! Watch out!
You can't break this flag!
Luffy!
It's a direct hit!
He must've been blown away!
Such an idiot!
See? It didn't break...
C... Can't be! He's stupid!
I don't know who the heck
this pirate flag belongs to...
but since this flag is a person's
pledge to risk his life...
it's not raised as a joke!
This flag isn't something you can
just break while laughing foolishly!
Incredible...
So this is... a pirate!
It won't break... Never...
The skull is a mark of faith!
Nemuranai kono machi mo Ima dake wa madoromu
Even this sleepless town has dozed off for now
Kyou kara to kinou made
From today forth,
nani ka ga kawatte yuku
something's going to change
Kitto yarinaoseru hazu
I'm sure I can start fresh,
Datte hitori janai kara
since I'm not alone
Soba ni ite kureru dake de
Just by having you by my side,
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru
I feel I can become strong
Doko made ikeru kana
I wonder how far I can go,
mirai e tsuzuku basho
towards the place that leads to the future
Tooku de kagayaite sekai o tsutsumikomu
Off in the distance it shines, encompassing the world
Yoake mae
Before dawn
That reindeer is amazing.
He transforms one form after another!
He can really jump.
A beam's next!
He's gonna shoot a beam!
He won't, you idiot!
H-Hey, hold on a sec!
Where did that tin bastard go?
What? He's not here!
When on earth did he...
While you were fascinated by
the transformations, of course!
Where're you, annoying mouth?!
Next time, on One Piece:
Zoan-Type Devil Fruit!
Chopper's Seven-Form Transformation
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Zoan-Type Devil Fruit!
Chopper's Seven-Form Transformation