Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
Just watch carefully!
This is the first step of a hero
that will be engraved in histo...
Tower of Law?! What can
he do from that far away?!
--Snap!
--Who the hell is that?!
He's aiming at us from that distance
without the slightest error, in this wind?!
I was born...
Who the hell is that?!
...on the island of snipers
Long-nose!
Nico Robin is getting away!
Don't let her get away!
Idiots! You can shoot her!
--Yes, sir!
--Shoot her dead enough to keep her alive!
Huh?!
Fire!
What?!
What the hell is he?!
You are...
My body is strong because it's iron.
That landmine wasn't nice, Spanda!
Eek!
They came off!
This is Franky! Hey, Long-nose!
I got the handcuffs off of Nico Robin.
All right!
Thank you, Long-nose!
You can thank those who fought hard
to gather the keys when this is all over.
You are, without a doubt,
one of Luffy-kun's gang!
You can now do as you wish!
Yes.
Everything went according to my plan.
Hm? What's that?
Did I hear something just now?
Robin Freed!
Luffy vs. Lucci, Showdown Between Leaders
What...?
What the heck?
Can't be...!
Was that cannon fire from a battleship?!
The stockade was...
"Justice"
Vice Admiral! The cannon
fire earlier hit the stockade
in front of the main island at 4 o'clock!
--So, what about it?
--Huh?
I'm asking, what about it?
Yes, sir. Well, nothing really, sir!
This is an indiscriminate attack.
I could care less where we hit.
Yes, sir...
Our mission is to burn everything down.
Start with the Tower of Law.
Once Enies Lobby comes within firing range,
we'll launch a concerted attack.
Yes, sir.
If that's clear, instead of
wasting time on reports like this,
why don't you start preparing
the next attack already?!
Y-Yes, sir!
They busted the fence
that surrounds the island.
That was a huge explosion.
If a bunch of battleships come and
rain down cannon fire like that...
Also, look.
The whirlpools that were surging so violently
that they prevented ships from
coming here are now completely gone.
It's because the Gate of Justice was
opened all the way to allow attacks.
"Sea Currents"
"Tower of Law"
Those whirlpools were generated
by the sea currents blocked by the huge gate.
Now that the gate is open and nothing is blocking them,
the sea currents went back to normal and the whirlpools disappeared, huh?
Which means, the battleships...
...will have no trouble coming this way.
--Sogeking!
--There's no time to lose!
Jump down from there!
Don't say a reckless thing like that!
To start with, it's not like I have
superhuman strength like you guys,
or the courage not to fear death!
I'm just an ordinary superhero!
Hm?
Usopp!
The Tower of Law is...
Long-nose!
Long-nose...!
Look! This time, they fired at the Tower of Law!
The Tower of Law is...!
Are they okay?!
As I suspected, the explosion
earlier was no ordinary explosion!
That was cannon fire!
Hurry up and leave the island!
Hey... He couldn't have... right?
Hey! Usopp!
Ahhh!!
You called?!
Hey, you're alive!
Hey! Don't you guys have
the kindness to catch a hero
making a desperate jump
off of the rooftop?! Morons!
Franky! Robin-chan! We're okay here.
We're heading over there right away!
Good.
Well then, let's do something
about things here.
Hey, can I count on you to help fight?
Of course.
Hurry up, soldiers! Take care of them
before the attack goes into full gear!
Yes, sir!
There's an escort ship on the
other side of the bridge, huh?
Don't you think that is the key to our escape?
Looks like stealing that ship
is our only chance of surviving.
Get them!
Dieciseis Fleurs!
Fire!
What the hell?!
Strong...
...Face-Slap!
Second group! Go!
Yeah!
Treinta Fleurs!
Master Nails!
Th-Third group! Go!
Fourth group! And fifth group, too!
All together, get them!
Geez... One after another...
They're such a pain in the ass.
Hey, stand back a little.
Weapons Left!
Fresh Fire!
Franky Boxing!
Yow!
What offensive power...!
We can't possibly fight back.
Not enough for you? Then... Franky...
...Convert!
Franky Centaur!
He's a horse!
No, wait. He's not a horse.
His upper body is attached in the back!
Then he's a monster!
Hold it, you bastards!
I said hold it, bastards!
Hey, you idiots! Don't run away! Fight him!
Ow, ow, ow...!
H-Help!
Hey, escort ship! Send some
reinforcements in! Now!
Yes, sir! How many do you need?
How many do I need?! You idiot!
Listen! Two vicious criminals
have removed their handcuffs
and escaped, and are
now going on a rampage!
The ship's captain, navigator,
signalmen, corpsmen...
All of you! Come out and...
Understood, sir! We'll all work
together and capture the...
...protect me!
So this is about you?!
Chimney! Gonbe! Let's hurry!
Grandma! You're fast!
The power of alcohol is amazing, huh?!
The truth is, it's not really
because of the alcohol.
--What?
--I'm having fun, so...
This is the first time I've felt this
way since Tom-san was still alive.
What's funny, you horned raccoon dog?!
Who're you taking it out on, Moron-ky?!
You are not gonna get away with it!
How about you guys?
Yeah! It's kinda exciting!
This is fun! This is fun! The pirate guy is fun!
Kokoro-san! Chimney! Gonbe!
Thanks for the guide marks!
Pirate lady!
I felt quite a shock just a moment ago.
Looks like it's finally gonna start, huh?!
Cannon fire! Cannon fire!
Shave!
You jerk!
Jet Pistol!
Jet Whip!
Shave!
Finger Pistol!
Yellow Lotus!
Jet Stamp!
His physical ability is as good
as that of a Six Powers Master.
He surely seems like a different person
from the time I met him at Galley-La.
That rising steam...
That strange red tint his body has...
What's going on in his body?
Oh, I get it!
Razor!
Jet Pistol!
I see...
So, it's basically like doping.
You accelerate your blood circulation
by using your legs as a pump.
The blood pressure gets so high that
a normal person's heart would explode,
but since your internal organs and veins
are all rubber-made, you can bear it.
That's a technique only a rubber man can use.
Although your physical ability
indeed spikes, exceeding its limits,
your physical strength itself just
can't keep up with that intensification.
That's not really smart.
You're shortening your life, you know that?
It's better than losing all sorts
of things right before my eyes!
I'll do whatever I can do!
You're too ambitious!
Did you feel the explosion earlier?
That was probably a Navy Headquarters
battleship doing some trial fire.
Before too long, they'll all start firing at once.
Your friends who are in the
Tower of Law will die there.
Even if there are some lucky ones
who are running this way in the
underground passage right now...
Tempest Kick!
What?!
This seawater will gush into the passage,
ensuring that anyone in there will drown.
You...
Nothing is going well for you, Straw Hat.
That naive idea of yours that you
can save everyone and escape...
Let's see how far it gets you.
What're you doing, you jerk?!
Dammit! They're persistent.
Based solely on the head count,
they're like a first-class military force.
Hurry up!
All you have to do is capture Nico Robin
and put her on the escort ship!
Move it! The battleships are coming!
Looks like it's too late.
What'd you say?!
Ah!
Ahh!
Behind the fog...
...we can see the outline of the ships!
H-Hey, don't run away! Wait!
Oh, no...
This serves you right!
They're here! They're finally here!
Th-They're here! The cannon fire has started!
Watch out!
Run!
Get us out of here!
I know!
A Buster Call has been invoked!
Our targets are Straw Hat Luffy
and his gang of about sixty pirates!
However, due to a private agreement with
Admiral Blue Pheasant, the criminal Nico Robin,
last sighted on the Bridge of Hesitation,
is a sole exception to this
and is not one of our targets.
There's no need to assess the current situation!
Completely destroy the
judicial island, Enies Lobby!
All battleships, take your positions!
A fleet of battleships!
The Buster Call has begun!
Boss! There's trouble! There's trouble!
Oh, what's the matter?
Did you get hay fever or something?
Yeah. My nose tickles and my eyes are itchy.
I really don't know what to do!
Hey, that's not it!
The famous millennium cherry tree is gone!
What'd you say?! That really is trouble!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Boss Luffy Is the Culprit?
Track Down the Missing Great Cherry Tree"
I'm gonna be a policeman!!
Boss Luffy Is the Culprit?
Track Down the Missing Great Cherry Tree