Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and in order to move on
to the next stage—the New World—
they return to Sabaody Archipelago!
Huh, what's going on?
It got tense all of the sudden.
But, Rayleigh! Luffy isn't here yet!
Don't worry about that!
Captain!
Huh?
Isn't this the guy you were looking for?
Oh!
Luffy's already on the island!
I gave Sanji a Baby Transponder Snail
when he came here.
He's with Zoro right now.
That's it! I'll gut you like a fish!
I spent two years in hell training my legs for this!
Bring it on!
I'll cut you in half!
Really? That's good.
But he'd better hurry.
The Navy is getting close.
So it's only Monkey-chan
that we can't get in touch with, huh?
But let me give you this Vivre Card.
It'll lead him to you.
Grove #42 should be a good place—it's on the coast.
Anchor your ship there and gather your crew.
This might get a little rough,
but it's time to put the past behind you...
and embark on a new journey!
The Battle is on!
Show Them What You Got From Training!
Read this carefully before you set out.
It has all the details
on how to control a coated ship.
Got it! Thank you!
I wonder how Luffy's changed in these past two years?
I can't wait to see him!
Same here.
Alright, let's head to Grove #42!
Hold on, I have to call Zoro and Sanji first.
Still, about Luffy...
I hope he doesn't get himself into trouble.
Oh, that's right. It is Luffy after all.
Because of him it's never been smooth sailing.
Leave that to me!
I'll go pick him up!
I have a great idea.
Listen up, you lot!
Anyone getting in our way will be arrested!
What are you doing, Navy?!
Leave Soul King alone!
Hey, what happened?!
What's going on over there?!
It's total chaos!
When the Navy tried to arrest Soul King
his fans started rioting!
It seems the star in question has fled the scene!
Damn! That traitor!
It's true! I have some big news!
The musician, Brook,
is one of Straw Hat Luffy's allies
and a pirate himself!
Thanks a lot!
You showed up just in time!
Sister Shakky sent me!
Your friends are waiting for you at Grove #42!
How I've missed them!
Warm feelings of anticipation fill my heart!
Oh, but I don't even have one!
What's with these guys?!
They're both extremely strong!
You've improved a bit,
third-rate swordsman.
And you've learned some more
stupid kicking techniques!
You haven't been neglecting your cooking,
have you, garbage cook?!
What'd you say?!
Ring, ring, ring...
Huh?
Ow! That's right!
The Navy's on the move
and Luffy's somewhere on this island!
We're moving the Sunny to Grove #42
so both of you hurry over!
Roger that.
Clank.
What is it?
Huh, were you not listening?!
Let's see...
Navy. Come. We. Ship. Run.
Got it?
Do I get it?
Why're you talking in pieces?!
Just talk to me normally!
I thought that might be easier
for a meathead like you to understand.
Okay. You. Later. Kill!
Yeah, yeah.
By the way, isn't it getting kinda rowdy over there?
You're right. There. Rowdy.
Huh? What's going on here?
Quiet down, you lot!
We've already found one of the people
who have disrespected me!
It's this guy!
We'll start by teaching him a lesson...
about how terrifying I can be!
And the rest of you take heed!
This is what happens to anybody who defies me!
If you mess with me,
this is how you'll end up!
Is that clear?!
A guy worth 400 million sure is intimidating!
What's the matter with this guy?
Zoro, Sanji, you guys know him?
Huh?
You see, earlier—
Hold it right there, pirates!
Straw Hat Luffy and his underlings!
Surrender now!
Huh, the Navy?!
Grove #46 is completely blockaded!
You have nowhere to run!
What?! How did the Navy find me?
Huh, what are you talking about?
Captain! The Navy's got us surrounded!
Dumbass! Stay calm!
Why do you think we recruited this many people?!
Some of these men have bounties over 100 million!
But there's so many...
Just watch, you idiot!
Hey, Caribou!
Get that soldier from before!
Use him as a shield and clear a path!
Navy soldier?
One of our scouts must've been captured!
Damn, this is bad!
Huh?
What'd you say, Big Boss?!
I said "use the Navy soldier as a shield," you dumbass!
Oh, I get it.
Use this guy as a shield, huh?
What are you doing, Caribou?!
We have to use him
to get out of here!
Big Boss, I'm afraid that's impossible!
What?
That soldier?
He lied to us about summoning the Navy!
Stop, you idiot!
That crazy fool!
He disobeyed the captain's orders!
Uh-oh, now he's done it...
I don't appreciate your unspoken rule
about how you can lie to villains!
We should put a stop to that!
They have no intention of surrendering!
Destroy the pirates!
Stupid Navy! Our boss is Straw Hat Luffy, the man with a bounty of 400 million!
Slaughter them!
This is bad, Captain, let's run!
You fools! Don't charge them blindly!
Huh? Why are they calling me their boss?
Again, what are you talking about?!
Don't be afraid! Get them!
You're...
the pirate wanted for 88 million—
Lip "Service" Doughty!
That was quite the fine "swordsmanship."
Don't be afraid! Take aim!
He's the 92 million bounty...
"Gashed" Albion!
Don't back down! We fight for justice!
Yeah!
It stinks! Hypocrites' blood!
210 million bounty—"Wet-Haired" Caribou...
Huh?
just surrender!
What?! You're a Devil Fruit user?!
Don't struggle!
Straining yourself is bad for your health, you know?
My sword...
This might just work, Captain! Those pirates are pretty strong!
Yeah, you got that right.
Hey, men!
The one who kills the most Navy soldiers
will become my right-hand man!
Wipe them out!
Yeah!
Your right-hand man?!
What about us?!
You two shouldn't just stand around either.
With all these troops at my command,
I can rule the world!
Whoa! What is it now?!
Pacifistas!
What?!
What are the Navy's human weapons doing here?!
They're those bear-like men!
But Hancock told me not to cause trouble...
Again, what the hell are you talking about?!
Pirate—Straw Hat Luffy. Confirmed.
Pacifistas?! Is this for real?!
Did he just lock onto me?!
Pacifistas, huh? How exciting!
88 million berries bounty.
Lip "Service" Doughty. Subdued.
Captain Doughty!
Follow the Pacifistas!
Capture the pirates!
Yeah!
With a single blow?!
Not even a man worth 80 million berries
stands a chance against them!
This is bad news—
Oh, Captain, where are you going?!
Wait for me!
Hey, hey!
You idiot!
I don't wanna fight him—he beat Doughty!
We better run!
Big Boss Straw Hat,
please do something!
At this rate, those human weapons
are gonna wipe us out!
Big Boss!
Huh?
Big Boss is gone!
"Big Boss"?
Is that what they call Straw Hat?
W-Wait! My side hurts!
Fool! Run! They're gonna kill us!
Dumbass! You're in my way!
Huh? Who're you?
That's...
Big Boss!
This'll be interesting!
Look at that, Coribou!
Yes, brother!
Not that way, fool!
I'm sorry! So sorry!
Big Boss Luffy, go get 'em!
Show them the power of the Straw Hats!
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
Hey, you! Don't you know who I am?!
Stand aside, unless you want me to kill you and rip out your guts!
This may surprise you!
I am the son of Dragon—the Revolutionary!
And grandson of the Hero—Garp!
I wreaked havoc during the Paramount War!
I'm a big-time pirate
with a 400 million bounty...
Straw—
You're not Straw Hat,
you piece of trash!
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
Hey, you! Don't you know who I am?!
Stand aside, unless you want me to kill you and rip out your guts!
This may surprise you!
I am the son of Dragon—the Revolutionary!
And grandson of the Hero—Garp!
I wreaked havoc during the Paramount War!
I'm a big-time pirate
with a 400 million bounty...
Straw—
You're not Straw Hat,
you piece of trash!
Huh?
Hah?
What?!
Big Boss Straw Hat!
Now I get it.
These fake Straw Hats had them fooled.
PX-5, who is this guy?
"Triple-Tongued" Demalo Black.
Bounty: 26 million berries.
What?!
26 million? That means he's...
...An imposter?!
We've been busted! Let's scram!
What's up with this shit?!
That guy was just pretending
to be Straw Hat Luffy! He tricked us!
He took advantage
of the real one being dead!
Damn! I got bamboozled
by a 26 million bounty punk!
What?
That guy was pretending to be me?
And that Zoro and Sanji were fake too?
But they looked just like the real ones!
Guess I'd better leave while I still have the chance.
The impostors were fools,
but so are you for allowing yourself to be misled.
You're all under arrest!
And I don't know why,
but the real Straw Hat is here too.
What?
PX-5 identified him
the moment we entered this area.
Target him, PX-5!
That was close!
What was that for?!
This backpack has my previous lunchboxes in it!
I-It's the same face...
It's the same face on the wanted poster!
So that guy is the real Straw Hat!
Don't be taken aback!
We came here expecting
the real one in the first place!
Straw Hat!
Huh?! You gonna get in my way again?!
I'm not supposed to get into trouble
because it'll make it hard to leave.
Don't worry!
You won't be going anywhere!
Unlike two years ago,
I'm officially a member of the Navy now!
And you're under arrest!
PX-5!
Too slow.
What?!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
Jet Pistol!
That Straw Hat...
He used Haki!
He destroyed the Pacifista in a single blow?!
See ya!
I think I'll be seeing you again.
Wait, Straw Hat!
Don't let Straw Hat get away!
Yeah!
Hey, Luffy!
Oh?
Luffy! I knew it!
Why are you constantly
in the middle of some huge fight?!
Oh!
I know it's you this time!
Long time no see, guys!
Roronoa! Black Leg!
I knew they were alive!
PX-7!
Move it!
I cut him!
I snapped his neck!
It's the Straw Hat Pirates!
They're definitely for real this time!
They're nothing like those phonies!
Hey, Luffy, you're No. 9.
Shut it! Stop with the bragging!
Luffy, hurry it up!
Everybody's waiting at the ship!
Okay!
Don't let them get away!
Arrest them, if it's the last thing you do!
Yes, sir!
It's been so long!
I wonder how everyone's doing?
I'm so happy!
Hey, what's wrong?
Oh!
Rayleigh!
What?!
Could it be...
D-Dark King Rayleigh?!
I came to check up on you just in case.
But I see you're fine.
Your powers are even more refined!
Uh-huh!
Now hurry up and get going!
Back to your friends!
Uh-huh!
Rayleigh, thanks for the last two years!
This isn't like you.
Hurry up and go!
Rayleigh!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
After two long years
the Straw Hats finally assemble on the Sunny.
But there is no time to rejoice.
As they are about to depart
for the sea floor paradise, Fishman Island,
the pursuing Marines arrive on the scene.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Everyone Together
Luffy, Setting Out for the New World"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Everyone Together
Luffy, Setting Out for the New World