A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
Give back old diamond-head's gold!
Gold?
You mean old man Cricket's stuff?
So long, Straw Hat!
What's wrong?! Hey, Straw Hat!
Where're you going?!
Where?
The sky!
Take to the Sky!
Ride the Knock-Up Stream
Where the heck is he?! It's already morning!
It's 46 minutes over the agreed time!
We're going to miss the current!
It'll take him longer to come back,
because of all that heavy gold!
I just know he didn't consider that!
No, I don't think he ever
considered the time at all.
Yeah, that's 100% certain.
Do you suppose he was beaten in town?
By that Bellamy guy?!
If he did, he'll have hell to pay
even if he makes it back in time!
I wouldn't put it past you...
Hey!
It's him! Thank goodness! He's back!
I did it!
Luffy! Hurry! We're behind schedule!
Check it out!
A Hercules! It took me forever to find one!
– You were looking...
– ...for a beetle?!
Whoa! Awesome!
It's the Going Merry Flying Model!
It looks like it can fly!
Doesn't it?! They did it for us!
– Look at 'em go.
– Seeing that makes me feel uneasy...
I agree.
Even a pigeon would've been better than a chicken...
That's not the main issue here!
You're an idiot!
Alright! Let's set sail! Ready, men?!
Aye aye, sir!
Get on board already! There's no time!
Or are you plannin' to waste your
chance to go into the sky, you fool?
Right! Thanks for the ship!
It's them you should thank.
Yeah! Thanks, you guys!
You can have my Hercules!
– Seriously?!
– For real?! We can?!
You're a nice guy!
Anyways, let's hurry!
Get on board, before we're too late!
We'll lead the way, so follow us!
– Luffy! Hurry!
– Yeah!
This "city of gold" is just a
product of Noland's imagination!
You need to realize that dreams never come true!
Saruyama Alliance!
Don't screw up, now!
No matter what happens,
give everything you got for them!
Yeah!
Alright! Let's go!
It's time to set sail, guys!
– All right!
– Aye, Nami-san!
Kid! This is where we part ways!
Yeah!
There's one thing that's a definite fact.
No one in history's ever disproved
the city of gold or the sky island.
Right!
People might laugh and call it
foolish logic, but it's enough for me.
That's what romanticism is all about!
Romanticism...
That's right!
Thanks for the gold...
Don't be fallin' from the sky now, y'hear?!
See ya, old guy!
Thanks for everything, Cricket-san!
I'm sure the city of gold is real, old-timer!
Old guy! Don't overdo things!
Mind your own business!
It's morning already!
Well? See anything?
Can't even see the outline
of the opposite shore yet!
Are they really going to a sky island?
Yeah, that's what they said.
It'll be tough to follow 'em,
so let's take care of 'em before that.
Straw Hat Luffy... A 100 million-Berry bounty...
All right! It's currently 7 a.m.!
We should arrive at the destination
area at around 11 a.m.!
Like the old-timer said, the spot
the Knock-Up Stream shoots up from
changes each time, so we need
to arrive beforehand and find it!
Watch! Watch!
We're a little behind schedule, so...
Hey! Are you listening to my explanation?!
See! It faced forward!
There sure are some weird birds out there!
It's true! It can only face south!
This guy's like a compass! So neat!
What'd he say?
He said he's going to face a
different direction to mess us up.
Go ahead and try!
Oh! He faced north!
He doesn't feel right unless he's facing south!
Hey, you guys! Don't get the big boss mad!
It's all right!
Their casualness is getting me worked up!
Huh? What's wrong?
There's no point in being anxious!
Let's have fun!
And who put us behind schedule?
He's right!
There's no point in being tense for hours on end!
I see! Alright, men!
Full speed ahead... while relaxing!
What nice weather!
Are we gonna be okay?!
Huh?! What's that?!
The sky... is dark!
– Bad news, Boss!
– What's wrong?!
Night's coming from the southwest!
Cumuloregalis clouds!
Seriously?! What time is it?!
Ten o'clock! It's way earlier than we expected!
This is bad... Shojo! Can we make it?
Utan Divers!
Into the sea immediately! Look for currents!
Those are cumuloregalis clouds?!
What, now?!
They appeared sooner than expected!
But we don't even know
where the current is located!
Reflected sound detected!
Large current at 12 o'clock!
Large creature detected at 9 o'clock!
Appears to be a Sea King!
Waves going against the
current detected at 10 o'clock!
I believe it's a giant whirlpool!
That's it! Head the ship in the 10 o'clock direction!
It's a sign of the explosion!
Catch the whirlpool! Don't draw back!
What the...?!
– The waves suddenly got higher!
– We're gonna sink!
It's a pre-explosion earthquake! Get ready!
E-Explosion?!
Navigator!
What does the Log Pose say?
It's pointing right at those clouds!
The sky island is up there?!
The wind's direction is perfect, too!
The clouds are heading straight
for the center of the whirlpool!
Hey, what's this "whirlpool"? I don't see one...
Looks like we hit the jackpot this time, brother!
Yeah! And it looks like it'll be
a nice-sized explosion, too!
– We can make it?!
– Yep!
Huh?
We'll take you to the inner edge of the whirlpool!
What do we do after that?!
Get on the flow! If you can get to
the center, things should work out!
The center of this huge whirlpool?!
I've never met any fools like you before.
I wanna go to the sky island, old guy!
The gold... It's been stolen!
I'll be back by morning.
See ya, old guy!
Prattling on about dreams...
W-We're being sucked in!
Nobody said anything about being sucked in!
It's all right! I'll protect you and Robin-chan!
I've never seen such a large whirlpool before...
This is bad! Let's turn back! Let me go back!
Just accept it, Usopp! It's too late!
Someone else is already excited!
Let's go! Sky island!
Alright, you guys! The rest is all up to you now!
Right! Thanks for the lift!
Hold on!
Gimme a break, will you?! I'm scared here!
Let me go back, you jerk!
This thing's gonna kill us instantly!
Nobody said anything about a giant whirlpool!
This is a scam!
It's night!
We're being sucked into the whirlpool!
Let's go back, Luffy! We can still make it!
Isn't it obvious?!
Just this whirlpool is enough to kill us!
The sky island's just a dream within a dream!
A dream within a dream? Yeah, huh?
Yes, Luffy! I don't think we can do this, either!
An island in a dream within a dream!
I'll regret it for life if I pass
up such a big adventure!
H-He's enjoying this...
Hey!
While you guys are pointlessly trying to resist...
Yeah? What?
We're being sucked inside it!
Hurry, Nami-san! Come into my arms!
We're falling!
What?! It disappeared?! How come?!
What happened?!
T-That whirlpool was huge, too!
What's going on?!
No! It's already started!
Eh?
The whirlpool only disappeared from the surface!
Y-You don't mean...
Hold it!
Hey, Zoro!
Look!
I caught up to ya, Straw Hat Luffy!
That's that guy from Mock Town...!
Who?!
I'm here to collect on your 100 million bounty!
Prepare yourself!
Hey, who're they? Friends?
Dunno.
Why's it dark out here?
My bounty?
What do you mean, 100 million?
So you don't know!
There's a 100 million-Berry bounty on your head!
And Pirate Hunter Zoro!
You're worth 60 million!
It's true! He has new wanted posters!
Zoro! You have a bounty now!
What?! Hold on! What about me?!
There's one for me, too, right?!
– Nope.
– Look closer!
Nope.
I see! Your bounties went way up
after the Alabasta incident!
But 100 million...!
100 million! Hear that?! I'm worth 100 million!
60 million, huh? How disappointing!
Don't be happy, you!
Hey, you guys! Don't get distracted!
Here it comes! The Knock-Up Stream!
Get ready!
What the...?
Everyone!
Hold on tight to the ship or get inside!
The ship... it's going up!
Oh, no! We're going to capsize!
Withstand it!
Don't get thrown over!
Go! Sky island!
What the heck's going on?!
The ship's going straight up a pillar of water!
This is neat!
How is this happening?!
Wind?!
Alright! Now we can go into the sky! Go, Merry!
Hold on! I don't think it's gonna be that easy!
W-What's wrong?!
Huh? Did we forget something?
The hull's starting to float!
Eh?!
If this keeps up, we're gonna
get sent flying to our doom!
But what do you want us to do?!
We can barely even hold on!
What's that?!
A Sea King!
It's the one that got sucked in earlier!
See! It's only a matter of time
until that happens to us!
Hey, now!
We're riding up a powerful explosion!
What can we possibly do?!
I guess it is just a natural disaster!
Lots of stuff is falling!
Victims of the Knock-Up Stream!
We're goners, too!
We're gonna fall and slam into the ocean and die!
– Spread the sails! Right away!
– Eh?
This is the sea! Not just a pillar of water!
It's a rising current!
And the wind blowing from
below is a rising air current
produced by the geothermal
heat and steam explosion!
If we're dealing with wind
and sea, I can navigate it!
Who's this ship's navigator?!
You are, Nami-san!
Alright, men! Do what Nami-san says!
We're going to gather up all our dreams
Right!
Catch the starboard wind
and pull the helm to point!
Align the ship with the current!
and set out in search of something to find
Yes, sir!
Oh, no! The ship is about to leave the water!
ONE PIECE!
We're gonna fall! We're gonna fall, Nami!
Do something, Nami!
No, we can make it!
Compasses only cause delays
We're flying!
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
Awesome! The ship is flying!
Is this for real?!
If the dusty treasure map has been verified,
– We did it!
– Wow!
it's not a legend!
Nami-san! You're wonderful!
And I love you!
When it comes to personal storms,
Go! To the ends of our unseen dream!
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
Go!
and pretend it isn't there!
With this wind and current,
we can go as high we want!
We're going to gather up all our dreams
Hey! Nami!
Are we almost at the sky island?!
and set out in search of something to find
If it exists, it's on the other side of those clouds!
Above the clouds, huh?!
A coin in my pocket,
What could be up there?!
and do you wanna be my friend?
Let's plunge through the cumuloregalis clouds!
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Aa hateshinaku tsuzuiteru sora no mukou ni
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
Itsuka mita asu o ima egakihajimete iru
The future that I once saw is now starting to take shape
Jibun ni makesou ni naru hi mo aru
There are days where I almost lose to myself
Sonna toki wa
When that happened,
atataka na basho ga atta
there was someplace warm I could go
Hokoreru mono itsumo kitto
The friends I took pride in always, without fail,
Boku no senaka oshite kureta yo ne?
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Aa hoshi-tachi ga furisosogu kono sora no shita
Ah, the stars are pouring down underneath the sky
Nido to nai ima o hora
This unique moment...
Hey, guys! Look outside the ship!
– What is this place?!
– It's pure white!
Basically, this is an ocean in the sky?!
Ahhh! Something's here!
This is a weird creature...
– Is it a fish?
– Ahh! Something's here!
Now what?!
It's a person! Someone's coming!
Next time, on One Piece:
Sail the White Sea!
The Sky Knight and the Gate in the Clouds
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Sail the White Sea!
The Sky Knight and
the Gate in the Clouds