I finally... managed to get here... Ace.
Look at this. Luffy started to make his way
to become the Pirate King again.
That's our younger brother!
"The Straw Hats Are Back"
It's so ironic.
Since you've been gone, the old
memories keep recurring to me vividly.
You're too slow, Luffy!
We'll leave you behind!
Wait, Ace!
Come on, Luffy!
Oh, Ace! There's a ship!
Hey! Hey!
You idiot!
They can't hear you from this far.
Hey!
"Goa Kingdom, Twelve Years Ago"
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Let's get out of this country and live freely!
I'm gonna become a pirate, defeat all the others,
and become the most notorious pirate in the world!
I'm gonna become...!
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
So from now on, we're brothers!
Yeah!!
Ace! What should we do today?!
Fight a bear!
Let's beat the big bear of Mt. Corvo!
Hey! Wait! Sabo! Ace!
I said wait! Ace!
Ace!
Ace!!
Luffy!!
Wait for me, Ace!
I'll be there soon!
"Marineford, Two Years Ago"
Don't get in my way!
Don't let him through!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Stay away, Luffy!
I know that you know it! We're both pirates!
We both sailed on the sea as we liked!
A wimp like you wants to save me?!
It's so humiliating!
Go back, Luffy!
Why did you come here?!
I'm your brother!
Gigant Rifle!
Ace!!
You can say whatever you want!
I'm gonna save you even if it means death!
Ace!
I'm a vice admiral of Navy HQ!
If you wanna pass through here,
you have to kill me first! Straw Hat Luffy!
Grandpa!
Old man!
Luffy! Both you and Ace have to become
the strongest Navy soldiers!
Ugh, spit! Gross!
Who are you?!
Oh! Ace!
Are you back, Ace?
This is Ace. He's three years older than you.
Be nice!
Because of the path you
two have chosen to live!!
I can't do it, grandpa!
Move out of my way!
Luffy, I consider you my enemy!
Ace!
You're so...!
Wait! You can't get away from me!
Gum-Gum...
...Gigant Balloon!
The scaffold is collapsing!
Blow them away along with the scaffold!
There's a tunnel of fire in the smoke!
You've always been like this! Luffy!
You've never even listened to me
and always done such crazy things!
Ace!!
--You did it, Straw Hat!
--That guy is really something else!
--Can you fight, Luffy?
--Of course!
He's my brother! Leave him alone!
Fire Fist!
Let's hurry, Luffy!
We gotta get out of this place!
Alright!
Don't be afraid!
Gum-Gum...
Firefly!
...Jet Gatling!
Fiery Doll!
You got stronger, Luffy!
I'll become stronger than you someday!
Pheasant Beak!
Flame Mirror!
Blue Pheasant-san's ice...
Listen carefully, Whitebeard Pirates!
I'm gonna give you an order
from the Captain one last time!
Everyone, survive at any cost
and go back to the New World safely!
--Good old man!
--Pops!
I'm the only one that
you ought to worry about!
Straw boy!
Why are you standing around?!
Let's go!
The old man has made up his mind...
I know! And it won't be in vain!
As soon as you rescue
Fire Fist Ace, you run!
The Whitebeards must be a group of cowards!
Well you can't help it, can you?
Because after all, Whitebeard is just
a loser from the old times!
A loser?
Take back what you just said!
Whitebeard is a great pirate
who shaped this era!
The name of this era should be "Whitebeard"!
Ace has been burned!
Ace...
Ace's Vivre Card...
Hey! Wait!
Luffy!
What...
Ace...
Ace-san!
Ace...!
He's been beaten!
I'm sorry, Luffy...
Huh?
I couldn't make it all the way.
I'm sorry.
Wh-What are you saying?
Don't be ridiculous!
Somebody, treat him! Please help Ace!
It's no use.
I can tell that my life is ending.
I can't hold out any longer.
So... l-listen to me, Luffy...
Wh-What did you say?
You promised me that you'd never die...
no matter what!
Ace!
Yeah...
If it weren't for the late Sabo...
...and a high-maintenance brother like you,
I wouldn't even have a will to live.
Oh yeah. If you see Dadan someday,
say hello for me.
When I face my own death,
I even miss a woman like her.
What? L-Like I said,
don't say that you're gonna die...
There is one thing that makes me wanna stay.
That is my desire to see
you fulfill your dream.
B-But I'm sure that you can do it!
Because you're my brother!
Luffy.
Could you tell them
what I'm about to say now?
Pops!
Everybody!
And you, Luffy.
Thank you... for loving someone like me
who is good for nothing...
...and who has such bad blood in his veins...
...up to today.
Thank you!
I promise.
I'll never die!
I now belong to the Revolutionary Army.
My colleague, Ivankov, told me
what happened in Marineford in detail.
I guess both you and Luffy are mad at me.
I couldn't go save you...
I'm sorry!
I wish... I wish I could've seen you again
while you were alive!
I'm gonna inherit... your will!
Luffy is our young brother!
This is the story of
the three brothers, Ace, Luffy, and Sabo.
Their reunion and bond.
"Episode of Sabo"
"The Three Brothers' Bond
The Miraculous Reunion and the Inherited Will"
The beautiful flowers are
brightly decorating...
...this kingdom of love and passion
where animated toys are
living side-by-side with humans quite naturally.
It's Dressrosa.
"Dressrosa, An Urban Area"
Here's your order! Dress Shrimp Paella!
Oh, oops. Excuse me.
That usually doesn't happen to me.
Whoa! Looks yummy!
In order to track down the
source of smuggled weapons
spreading all over the world
from this country and stop it,
Sabo is meeting up with his colleague of
the Revolutionary Army,
who has infiltrated here before him.
Hey, are you listening?
Yeah, Koala. So what's the situation?
First of all, you're paying
for your meal yourself.
You know the king of Dressrosa
changed to Doflamingo
from King Riku a decade ago, don't you?
The official story is King Riku
suddenly became a tyrant one day
and Doflamingo took him down and
saved the country.
But during King Riku's era,
there were no rumors about smuggling weapons.
That means there's a great chance that
Doflamingo is doing something secretly.
Here is your Rose Squid Ink Pasta!
Excuse me again.
You're doing it on purpose, aren't you?!
All three of the Doflamingo Family's
top executives are Devil Fruit users.
Diamante ate the Ripple-Ripple Fruit.
Pica ate the Stone-Stone Fruit.
Trebol ate the Stick-Stick Fruit.
And they have a bunch
of other tough fighters.
The most troublesome one among them
is a girl called Sugar.
We don't have any visual confirmation on her
but we know that she can
turn humans into toys -
she's a Hobby-Hobby Fruit user.
Turn them into toys?!
That means the toys here are...
H-Humanitis!
Please try to remember!
It's me! Your dad!
No! He's hurting me!
Get away from my child! Somebody! Help!
Antonio! Maria! It's me! Try to remember!
I'm a human!!
People who have turned into toys
are slipping out of other
people's memories, it seems.
Behind this joyful sight,
there is an abysmal darkness, it seems.
Doflamingo must be behind this, too.
Here is your Fairy Pumpkin Gazpacho!
Oh yeah. King Riku's second daughter is
a member of the Family, too.
King Riku's daughter? Why?
I don't know why but her name is Violet.
She can see through anything
with her ability, Clairvoyance.
Clairvoyance?
That sounds troubling, too.
Luckily, it hasn't bothered
our undercover operation so far.
King Riku also has a
granddaughter named Rebecca
who is a gladiator at the Colosseum.
The king's granddaughter is a gladiator, huh?
And do you have any idea where
they produce the weapons?
Well... I haven't pinpointed where it is yet.
I saw some ships believed
to be trading ships arrive
in the harbor several times
in the middle of the night
but they were gone in the morning.
I assume there is a port
somewhere inside of the island.
An underground port, huh?
I think so.
Some locations I haven't checked through
because of tight security,
are the palace and...
...the Colosseum.
The Colosseum?
This is fishy.
Let's check there right away, like tonight.
I knew you were gonna say that.
Hack has already gone undercover there.
He said he'll enter a fighting competition
sponsored by Doflamingo.
I bet he's warming up right now.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Speak of the devil, it's Hack.
Hey, this is major!
I found out the prize for
the fighting competition!
The prize?
Considering that you took the trouble to call,
is it like a billion berries?
Is that Sabo?
--When did you get here?
--Early this morning.
You're just in time!
It's so much better than a billion!
Listen carefully. The prize is...
Incidentally, several hours later...
Wow! It's a rocky island!
We made it! It's Dressrosa!
Luffy and the Straw Hats
along with Kin'emon from the Wano Kingdom,
their pirate ally, Trafalgar Law, and the others,
arrived in Dressrosa.
"Greenbit"                  "Dressrosa"
"Guarding the Ship"
As they arrived the island,
they split into three teams.
To hand over Doflamingo's associate, Caesar,
they called Doflamingo to Greenbit,
the small island in the north,
and in the meantime, they were going to
destroy the factory of SMILEs,
Doflamingo's precious man-made Devil Fruits,
to weaken his influence, but...
What you will see today
is one hell of an event!
The king entrusted us
with an extraordinary prize for today's event!
Now, let's call in! The king of our country!
Doflamingo-sama!
Everyone! As you know,
a Devil Fruit will be
reproduced somewhere in the
world when its user dies.
For two years since that man lost his life
in the Paramount War at Marineford,
we were looking for this Fruit and
we finally got hold of it!
He was a 2nd division commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates
and a son of the Pirate King,
"Fire-Fist" Ace!
The ability that everybody
wants was reproduced in the
form of a Devil Fruit in this world.
The winner will get this forbidden fruit!
It's a Logia, the most powerful type of Devil Fruit!
The Flare-Flare Fruit!
"The Colosseum, A Dressing Room for the Competitors"
The Flare-Flare Fruit is mine!
Idiot! It's mine!
I'll become a great pirate with
the Flare-Flare Fruit!
But I can't just give it to you easily.
Mr. Diamante, the hero of the Colosseum,
will fight in the final!
I am the hero of the Colosseum
and I will fight!
Diamante! Diamante!
Diamante-sama!
What a bunch of idiots...
I'm pretty sure that Straw Hat will show up.
I'll be counting on you.
Humph! A weakling like Straw
Hat is not a problem for me!
Their opponent, Doflamingo
was working out a scheme
to catch Luffy and the others
in one fell swoop.
Damn Doflamingo...
How dare he make a toy of Ace's Fruit!
--I thought you'd come.
--I'm here for the search.
Don't fool yourself.
I'll do my job. Otherwise, Koala'll get mad.
Now I remember. Ace was your...
I want it! The Flare-Flare Fruit!
I don't want some stranger
to possess Ace's power.
I won't let anybody have it!
Hmm... It's like a memento
of him to you, isn't it?
It's possible that it's a trap considering
the way Doflamingo dangled
it in front of you.
But one thing is for sure!
You shouldn't let the chance slip by!
You don't wanna regret it afterward.
Let's just go there!
Uh-huh!
Therefore, Luffy left the factory
destroying to Franky and the others
and decided to enter the event.
It's a huge Colosseum!
Listen, Luffy. You can do as you like
but don't let them know who you are.
Got it!
Oh!
Elderly people!
Do you want me to carry
your bag or something?
What a funny toy soldier!
Oh? Am I funny?
What about this? Or this?
Hey buddy, get out of our way.
Oh, I was in your way. I'm sorry!
This is the dressing room
for the competitors.
It's filled with excitement!
A variety of people are here!
He's in the wrong place.
Probably just looking for fun.
All right!
A statue of an old warrior man!
Are you interested in that guy?
Who are you?
I'm Rebecca. A gladiator.
This man was a legend.
He was the strongest gladiator, Kyros.
He won 3000 out of 3000 matches.
An undefeated man.
Wow! He was that strong?!
But no one in this country knows about him.
Huh?
It's so mysterious
but I like this statue! It's so manly!
--What block are you in?
--C.
Great. I'm in D.
I hope we both survive, Lucy.
Happy Store!
"First Round, Block A"
The first round in which over 550 contenders
in total were divided into four blocks,
went on and...
Wow! Oh my, oh my...
The winner of Block A is...
...the captain of the first ship of
the fearful Emperor Blackbeard's group -
Jesus Burgess!
Oh, that guy's in this thing, too...
All competitors of Block
B, please go to the ring!
Leave the Flare-Flare Fruit in my hands.
You do the research of the Colosseum.
Good luck.
Alright, we're moving onto Block B!
A battle of 138 contenders!
Only one person can proceed to the final!
Now, the battle...
...begins!
Four Thousand Brick Fist!
Who the hell are you?!
--You can't come in any farther!
--Where's the bathroom?!
It's not this way! It's on the other side!
I-I can't hold it!
A dead end again.
Where's the entrance to the basement?
It feels so good!
Some of us are taking this
thing seriously, brat!
You'll have to excuse me
for attacking you from behind!
Hey, wait! I'm not even ready to fight back!
Four Thousand Brick Fist!
Just kidding!
Sabo! I'm sorry...
Oh! A champion hopeful,
the Fishman Hack collapsed!
I'm all set now.
King...
Wh-What the...
...Punch!
H-How powerful was that?!
B-Block B - the winner is...
Hey, look! Somebody's there!
Barrier!
I'm a barrier man
who ate the Barrier-Barrier Fruit!
Barrier Crush!
What the...! The winner of Block B is...
it's hard to believe but, Bartolomeo!
The winner of Block A is Jesus Burgess,
and the winner of Block B is Bartolomeo.
Hey, hustle up!
The next battle will start soon!
Hurry up and fix the ring!
What are you doing?!
Do you wanna get scrapped?!
Please wait!
If you oil my joints, I still can work!
Idiot!
Don't be such a baby!
Bear with it a little bit more!
I'll expose the darkness behind
this country at any cost!
Alright! Who is going to inherit
Ace's Fire Fist, the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
I'll do it, Ace!
Finally, the battle of Block C that Luffy is in,
was about to start.
Now, the competitors enter!
Oh! Today's likely winners
are coming in already!
The Hasshoken users are entering first!
He's the 13th leader of
the Happosui Army of Kano!
Sai!
Followed by the vice leader, Boo!
And he was once ill-famed around
the world along with Roger,
Whitebeard, and the others!
The former leader with a 500 million bounty!
Don Chin Jao!
Well, well, this guy is pretty tough, too!
You're finished once you got targeted by him!
A bounty hunter - Jean the Bandit!
There are still more!
Even the pirates with over a 100
million bounty are nothing to them!
They're brutal assassin brothers!
The older brother is Kelly Funk and...
...the younger brother, Bobby Funk!
You must see his killer punch!
A XXX rank boxer - "Destruction Cannon" Ideo!
Here he comes!
A warrior from Elbaph and the most
formidable "Pirate Mercenary"!
A Giant - Hajrudin!!
Don't forget about the
Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
It shows no mercy! Brutal Bull!
Now, all 139 competitors
of Block C are out there!
Will one of these contenders
win the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
Finally!
Now, the battle...
...begins!
Let's do it!
Whoa!
I heard you're trying to kill Lucy.
It's none of your business.
No, that man is not yours to kill!
I guess you recognize who he really is, too.
But I'm the one who will kill him.
My connection with him is much deeper.
Because, ever since I saw him in Loguetown...
I'm the man who'll become Pirate King!!
That man is my icon!
Meanwhile, the Caesar Handover Team led by Law was...
"Greenbit"
...at Greenbit next to Dressrosa and...
That is the beach on the
southeast side of the island.
We'll leave you there at
three in the afternoon.
Look at the beach on the other side!
--Isn't that a Navy ship?!
--What?
It's not fair to hand me over here!
Abort this mission!
The Navy is my enemy, too,
since I'm allied with the Straw Hats.
We still have 15 minutes before they come.
Everyone, cover me with
sniping and surveillance.
Okay, I got it.
Is this...
Who are you people?
What do you want?!
You are...
We are convict gladiators.
We were sent here because we protested
against the Doflamingo Family.
We'll keep fighting and get killed someday
in the ring, as part of the show.
Before Doflamingo became king a decade ago,
gladiatorial matches were not to the death.
There is nowhere to run for us.
They're all tough fighters
but there is a giant warrior
who is literally sticking out!
His name is Hajrudin!!
With the Flare-Flare Fruit,
I'm gonna become the king of all Giants!
Who can stop him?!
On the other hand,
there is a killer bull who
slayed 21 death row prisoners
during a fight in this very Colosseum!
People call him Brutal Bull!
And somehow, someone knows how to tame
and ride this Grim Reaper!
What is he doing?!
Bursting into prominence,
with his cool strength,
he instantly became a crowd favorite!
Lucy!
I like that guy, too!
What a funny guy.
Clank.
Hack lost, huh...
Hey, Robin!
Can you walk a little more slowly?
Who is it?! The Straw Hats?!
No! They found us!
Navy soldiers... What?!
We got stripped of all we have!
Mil Fleurs: Campo de Flores!
--I caught one!
--Huh?! What did you catch?! Robin!
I think it's a little person!
Help me!
Robin, what do you mean a little person?!
Did you rob those Navy soldiers?
Tranquilily!
What?!
Hajrudin!
Is he the most likely to
win this competition?!
I don't think so.
The one who will move onto the final is...
The Hasshoken user,
Don Chin Jao of the Happosui Army.
I can't believe a big fish like him is here.
Can't wait to fight him in the final.
I won't let him have the
Flare-Flare Fruit though.
Go Moocy!
Take them all down!
Oh?
What do you want?
Do you wanna fight me?
Oh, crap! Run, Moocy!
Bull!
What a disappointment!
It was obviously a mismatch!
The Colosseum's Grim Reaper
and the unknown gladiator -
Lucy couldn't do anything...
The Giant's been knocked down!
Hajrudin, undoubtedly one of
the champion hopefuls, lost his chance!
It's an unbelievably major upset!
Thank you for fighting together with me.
Let me carry you to the
side of the ring, Moocy.
That was awesome, Lucy!
He came in and stirred things up in Block C!
Lucy did it again!
I believe this guy still
has a lot more to show!
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!...
That's...
The Navy admiral... Purple Tiger!
--Doflamingo!
--Joker!
They're both targeting us.
I have to buy some time.
Boo of the Happosui Army got defeated
by the Funk Brothers!
Meanwhile, Jean the Bandit
took away Lucy's helmet!
Hey, give it back!
I heard this strange story, Lucy.
I heard a pirate who's worth 400 million
named Straw Hat Luffy is...
...secretly fighting in this competition
to win the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I see...
As I suspected, you are here, Luffy.
Straw Hat Luffy!
Garp's blood runs in your veins!
Oh! Chin Jao starts charging!
Garp!
Block C! There are approximately
40 contenders remaining!
It's narrowing down to the strongest!
As Doffy plotted, you walked into a trap,
Straw Hat Luffy!
No way...
You've got to be kidding!
Room!
I-I can't believe it.
Only those three spots that
they're standing have no damage!
I just wanted to test your skills.
My brother lost because
he trained himself poorly.
Don't be so hard on him.
Rah-Rah-Rah-Rampage!
But, as the leader of the Happosui Army,
I will avenge my subordinate!
So strong! Hasshoken!
Pay for it, Straw Hat Luffy!
Your obnoxious grandpa took
all of my fortune away!
Like I said before,
I don't know what you're talking about!
Talk to my grandpa!
It's too easy for Garp
if I punish him by death!
I will make him feel how painful
it is to live with loss!
Your grandpa is Garp? So you're really him!
Anyway, you jerk! Give me back my helmet!
Try to get it back! If you can get here!
Take this! Charitable Donation!
I made so much money in the
last two years thanks to you!
I captured dozens of
prisoners who you set free
from the great prison - Impel Down!
Damn! Why can't I get him?!
Oh?
Give it back.
You've been hurting me! You bastard!
Out of the ring!
Jean the Bandit has been eliminated!
The legendary pirate Don
Chin Jao head-butted him!
He's still got it after all these years!
Where did he go?
Bullet String!
I'm not gonna let you have it your way.
Are you there, Straw Hat?!
Just give up!
All right! Let's do it!
I can't win the Flare-Flare Fruit
without beating him anyway!
Now, Ideo and Sai,
the two equally matched contenders,
are in a breathtaking fight!
It's a life-and-death struggle!
Is Ideo gonna win?! Or Sai?!
Outta my way!
Move!
What?!
Conqueror's Haki...
B-Block C!
There are only two men left!
Chin Jao has remained as I expected.
Be careful, Luffy!
I didn't know you could use Conqueror's Haki!
What kind of king are
you dreaming to become?!
The Pirate King!
Shut up!
You have to know that there are so many
in the New World
who have the qualities of a king!
Who taught you how to use the Haki?
Rayleigh!
Is he still alive?!
How annoying!
What?
What?! Whaaat?!!
Tell me, Straw Hat.
I want to forget but it's always
right there in front of me!
But it's out of my reach! My treasure!
Can you imagine anything harder than that?!
What's going on?!
The legendary pirate is crying!
"Chin Jao the Drill."
That's what they used to
call me but not anymore.
Answer me! Do you know
what Garp has done to me?!
I can't tell if you wanna cry or be mad!
Watch out, Luffy!
What a fight!
It's too fast and I can't even
see what's going on anymore!
I'm sure what we're seeing now is
one of the greatest fights
ever in this Colosseum!
You're quite a fighter.
I can't get beaten by you here!
But forget it!
I'm like a wolf without its
fangs now and if you're only
good enough to compete against
me in my present condition,
you have no chance!
Just give up being a pirate!
If a guy like Rayleigh chose a brat
of this level as the flag-bearer
for the new generation,
he's not as smart as he used to be!
The Navy showed some good insight when they
squelched the most evil of the lot,
I mean Ace, of course,
in the war two years ago.
That fool had the demon's blood in his veins!
What?
You think you can beat the Navy admirals and
the Four Emperors and surpass Roger?!
That's hilarious!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Rifle!
It's not over yet!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Lucy is flying?!
Come on! I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
With 30 years' worth of my anger toward Garp,
I'm gonna give you an all-out blow!
Damn Garp! I won't forgive you!
I'll carry this anger even towards
your children and grandchildren!
What's that?!
Am I just hallucinating or...
Lucy's arm looks very big!
Watch what I'm gonna do, Garp!
I'm going to kill your precious grandson!
I'm going to smash him
to the marrow of his bones!
Hasshoken Technique!
Gum-Gum...
...Thor...
Non-Drill Dragon...
...Elephant Gun!
...Non-Nail!
Whaaat?!
Oh, he went out of the ring!
Chin Jao is eliminated by
being thrown out of the ring!
Yeah!
What a man!
He beat the legend and
won the fierce battle for Block C!
Lucy the Gladiator!
--Lucy!
How much farther can he carry the momentum?!
And who is going to win the championship
and the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
The fighting competition
in the Corrida Colosseum!
Now, these three contenders
have gotten the chance
to challenge the Donquixote Family!
However, due to the extensive
damage to the ring,
the start of the battle for Block D
will be delayed by 15 minutes.
Lucy the Gladiator, huh...
Wait, Straw Hat!
Oh, boy! They're so persistent!
Fight me!
Listen! Our old man wants
to say something to you!
Boy... There's no place that
I can feel comfortable.
Now you're a man of 400 million
so you have so many enemies.
But I still can't believe that
crybaby became so strong...
Can you, Ace?
Hey, Sabo!
Oh, Ace!
Sorry I'm late!
Whoa! You got a lot!
Way more than I did!
That's a lot of money!
How'd you get that?
I robbed some thugs.
Damn! You won again!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
This is our "pirate savings"
that we'll use together someday.
It's been five years since we started it.
We worked hard.
I wonder how much we need
to get a pirate ship.
"A pirate ship"?!
You guys!
Are you gonna become pirates?!
I'm gonna become one, too!
He found our secret.
He's gonna tell somebody if nothing is done.
--We gotta kill him.
--Alright, let's do it.
What?!
Help me!! I don't wanna die!!
Shut up, you fool!
I didn't expect that you'd kill me!
Somebody's coming!
Are you sure that it was a kid named Ace
who took the money from you guys?
He's...
I didn't know that those thugs
were working for Bluejam!
I shouldn't have taken that money...
That's Porchemy who works under Bluejam.
Do you know that he strips off your scalp
alive after you lose a fight with him!
Let's just let them pass for now...
Oh?
Where is he?
Let go of me! You bastard!
How could he get caught?!
Help me! Ace!!
That fool! He's calling my name!
Do you know Ace?
I'm his friend!
Oh, but he just tried to kill me.
He's such a big mouth!
Lay low, Ace!
I don't know if you know about this
but I heard that Ace stole some
money from us and ran today.
You don't know where is it now, do you?
I... I...
I don't know...
A terrible liar!
Alright, alright! It can't be
helped that you don't know.
Hey! What are you doing?! Hey!
Let go of me!
Where are you taking me?! Dammit!
This is good.
Ace!
Sabo! I moved all the treasure!
How was it?
Have they shown up around the
other tree to look for the money?
No, they haven't. That kid...
He hasn't told them anything!
What?
Spit it out already!
Answer me!
I won't say it.
I won't say it!
Tsk! You little shit!
I won't say it...
I won't say it!
Fine. Enough.
Then you die.
Don't!
It's him! He stole the money from us!
Ace!
Sabo!
You made it easier for us
by coming here voluntarily!
Porchemy-san!
Oh?
Let's go, Ace!
--Go ahead!
--You fool! Hurry up!
When I come to face someone,
I won't run!
That's our money!
We have better plans for that money!
Stop talking crap!
If I'm beaten by kids,
I may as well quit being a pirate!
Ace!
I'm gonna kill all of you!
That was scary!
I thought I was gonna die!
Shut up! Stop crying already!
I don't like cowards or people who cry a lot!
Um... Thank you!
For... For helping me!
--You...!
--Whoa-whoa, he's just being thankful.
Why didn't you cough it up
in the first place?
I thought if I said anything,
you wouldn't be my friend.
It's better than dying, isn't it?
Why do you wanna become my friend that much?
Because I have nobody else to trust!
Being lonely is more
painful than getting hurt!
Is it easy for you when I'm around?
Uh-huh.
It's hard without me?
Uh-huh!
Do you want me to... live?
Of course I do!
I see.
But I don't like spoiled kids like you.
Have you ever gotten hit by a spiky thing?
I'm only 7!
When I become your age - 10,
I'll stop crying and become stronger!
I wouldn't cry even if I were 7, stupid!
I'm gonna become stronger than anyone!
I promised Shanks that I'd
become a great pirate!
--You? Become a pirate?
--Yes!
--No way!
--Yes way!
Hey, by the way,
I have a little problem.
The pirates will try to kill the three of us
after this for sure, right?
The Trash Mountain that I've been
living at is close to their den.
So...
Ace! Luffy! Who is that?!
How come there is one more kid?!
Hey, you must be Dadan! I'm Sabo!
Sabo?!
I know your name!
I've heard that you're a worthless brat, too!
Oh yeah?
I've heard that
you're a worthless old bag, too!
That's unnecessary information!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol...
Gum-Gu...
What are you trying to do?!
One point!
One more time!
No! The rule is only 100 matches
per person a day.
Luffy lost 50 times to me and Ace.
Me vs. Ace is 24 - 26.
I lost by two.
Dammit!
You guys!
When I become 10 years old,
I'll beat you two up!
We'll be 13 then.
You'll never catch up to us!
Damn! It's not fair!
Looks like it's not my place
to do anything about it.
I'll leave the rest up to you, Luffy.
While all of that was going on,
we have all the competitors in the ring!
With one abstention,
there are 137 contenders for Block D!
Okay, let's go for crocodiles!
I love crocodile meat!
You wait here.
You can't swim so you'd slow us dow...
Crocodile meat!
--I said "wait"!!
--He said "wait"!!
"Goa Kingdom, Midtown"
I'm glad that they took the
skin for such a high price!
We got more for the pirate savings!
I'm hungry!
--Let's eat something.
--Uh-huh.
Three ramen noodles.
This is ramen?!
Yum-yum!
Here are your...
You kids!
Those three naughty boys!
It's those three again!
Why were they let in?!
Don't let them run away!
Somebody, catch those three kids!
Sabo?
You're Sabo, aren't you?! You're alive!
--Who is that?
--He confused me with someone else.
H-Hey!
Wait! Sabo!
He's calling you!
We can't have secrets among us!
What?!
The son of a noble?!
The man who called to me today was my father.
Why were you living here
if you are from a noble family?
They love those who can maintain their
status and defend their property.
Not me!
I'm sorry for both of you but I was
all by myself even if I had parents!
Stay away from Gray Terminal.
People who live there are scum!
Nobles have a low opinion of Gray Terminal
but it's better than the stifling Highland
where your life has been arranged for years to come!
Ace! Luffy!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Let's get out of this country
and live freely!
You don't have to tell me to!
I'm gonna become a pirate and
defeat all the others and
become the most notorious
pirate in the world!
It'll be the only proof of my life!
It doesn't matter if all the people in the world
reject me or despise me,
I'll become a great pirate
and show them what I can do!
I got it! Alright then...!
I'm gonna become...!
You fool...
I was wondering what you'd have to say...
You're funny, Luffy!
I can't wait to see how you turn out
in the future!
Did you guys know?!
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
Brothers? Really?!
When we become pirates,
we might not be on the same ship
but our brotherhood will always be with us!
Wherever you are, whatever you do,
we'll always be bonded together!
So from now on,
we're brothers!
Yeah!!
Ace...
Ace!
F-F-F... First Mate!
Huh?! What are you talking about?
Y-Y-You're Zoro-senpai, aren't you?
Luffy-senpai's right-hand man?
How do you know about Luffy and my name?!
I'be albayz bween your ban!
Stop crying!
If I bring Luffy-senpai here,
can I have your autograph?
You can do that for me?
I'll be counting on you!
Wait for me there!
I'm gonna bring him at the risk of my life!
"Pirate Hunter" Zoro!
Pentachromatic Strings!
Although I told him that,
where did Luffy-senpai go?
I can't find him anywhere.
I can't face Zoro-senpai like this...
L-L-L... Luffy-senpai!
Scalpel!
Bullet String!
What are you gonna do now?
Dressrosa is right there.
Zoro! Kin'emon!
Luffy! Don't shout, idiot!
I'm glad to see you!
Crest Head showed me the way!
Where is he?
He collapsed on our way here.
And what do you want?
You fool! Why didn't you tell me
there was this kinda competition?!
You're right. Sorry!
Ring, ring, ring...
--Is this how you use it?
--What are you doing?
Sanji-dono told me to
call once we see Luffy-dono.
Yeah?
Oh yeah, Luffy.
The Colosseum has been besieged by the Navy.
You don't care?!
That was what we came here for!
"Off the Coast of Dressrosa"
Ring, ring, ring...
Must be Kin'emon.
Call Usopp with the other one, Chopper.
--Okay!
--Clank.
Sanji? It's me!
Luffy!
This is Usopp!
Alright. Tell me your situation.
This is Franky!
I'm with Usopp and Robin!
We are currently with the King Riku Army,
an anti-Doflamingo coalition in this country.
--An army?
--Of Little People.
Luffy, do you remember
we met the strange toy soldier
outside of the Colosseum?
Uh-huh.
He was actually the commander of this army.
And all the people here are looking to
take down Doflamingo this very day.
It seems like everybody's happy at first
but this country has a very dark side.
If we can knock out Sugar,
the Hobby-Hobby Fruit user,
all the toys will change
back into their human forms!
The toys have had their families,
loved ones, and friends taken away by Sugar!
I'm sure they're angry at Doflamingo!
If we can change them back
into their human forms,
Doflamingo's establishment
will be shaken up big time!
We'll let Sugar eat this
clump of Tatababasco Sauce,
the hottest spice in the
world, and knock her out!
Right! We'll bring down the Doflamingo Family
by carrying through this operation
and take Dressrosa back for King Riku!
Yeah!
This brave, little army is going to
challenge their filthy, monstrous enemy!
I can't let them down!
Luffy! No matter what you say,
I'm gonna fight with them!
Franky...
You're free to go all out!
We'll be there as soon as possible!
Thanks!
--What's going on?! The town is...
--It's coming this way!
What the...
Tra-guy! Doflamingo!
Hey, Tra-guy!
Why are you with Doflamingo...
Stupid brat! You've pushed it too far!
Tra-guy!!
Mingo!!
How dare you shoot Tra-guy!
Straw Hat.
It's none of your damn business.
Law was originally my subordinate.
Responsibility for dealing with him falls to me!
--Kin, retrieve Tra-guy!
--Okay!
What's this heaviness?!
Zoro-dono!
Zoro! Kin'emon! I'm coming!
Oh yeah... It's Sea Prism Stone...
Admiral-dono!
I can't believe he was a Navy admiral!
An admiral?!
Hello. Life is full of ironies.
You need to come to the Palace with me, Law.
Law-dono...
Wait!
Catch Roronoa Zoro!
What?!
How are they flying?!
Let's run for now!
Tra-guy!
Hey, Luffy! Look for the exit now!
We're gonna wait for you
by running around here!
Okay!
I'll take Tra-guy back at any cost!
And beat the hell out of Doflamingo!
Wait for me, Tra-guy! I'll be there!
Damn! It's a dead end again!
Where's the exit?!
Oh! Crest Head! Glad to see you here!
L-L-L-Luffy-senpai!
L-Luffy-senpai, d-did you
get to see Z-Zoro-senpai?!
Yes, I did! Thank you for that!
My pleasure!
Now I gotta go somewhere
so I need to get out!
But Luffy-senpai,
what about the Flare-Flare Fruit?
I wanna keep it out of
the hands of a few people
but I don't have a choice!
My friend's gonna die!
In that case, you can count on me!
I was gonna bring the precious
keepsake from Ace-sama
to you once I won it, from the beginning!
What?! I can have it?!
Of course!
So you can go out without worry!
Thanks! I appreciate it!
Luffy... Ace...
I couldn't do anything at that time...
The Flare-Flare Fruit...
I won't let you have it.
"Straw Hat Luffy"!
Who the hell are you?!
You can't talk to Luffy-senpai so casually!
He is the legendary pirate
Fire Fist Ace-sama's brother
and he'll become the Pirate King one day,
you idiot!
I've known that from way back.
You've known that from way back?
Who are you?!
Don't you recognize?
I don't know you!
Come on! I'll kick your ass right here!
Straw Hat Luffy.
Fire Fist Ace.
The Flare-Flare Fruit belongs to Ace!
I won't let you have it!
I think you had another brother...
What?
He's...
He's... already...
Y-You are...!
It's been a while! Luffy!
You've finally made it out
so why are you crying?!
Stop crying already!
Don't you wanna save Tra-guy?!
I'll save Tra-guy!
And I'll kick Mingo's ass!
Plus, the Flare-Flare Fruit is in good hands!
I-I never imagined he'd be alive!
Who are you talking about?!
Th-That day... Dogura...
Dogura told us that... So...
I-I thought he died at that moment!
I heard Robin-san's here
in this country, too.
I hope I can see her after such a long time.
I'm glad that you got to see him.
Yeah... I thought he was gonna punch me.
Are you crying?
I don't cry!
If you were there, do you think
you could've changed something?
Nobody knows.
Yeah.
Let me know when you find
out about the underground.
Okay.
In any case,
I will win Ace's Flare-Flare Fruit!
We will inherit his will!
Th-The fighting competition
in the Corrida Colosseum!
The last winner moving to the final is...
...unbelievably, a convict gladiator
and a granddaughter of King Riku,
the blot in the history of Dressrosa!
Rebecca!
Screw you!
--I know she cheated!
--You little tramp!
"The Lift to the Entrance of the Royal Palace"
How do we get into the palace?!
--By kicking their asses!
--You're Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
I've been waiting for you.
I'll help you enter to the palace!
Who are you?
"Violet, Clairvoyant"
I'm Violet. Now let's hurry!
The King Riku Army has started to move, too!
We'll sneak into enemy territory
through the underground passage!
Yeah!
The fighting competition
in the Corrida Colosseum!
The final round starts soon!
The special ring is set!
We can't help getting excited!
I made it!
Oh! Lucy! I'm moving on to...
Huh? Lucy?
You're Rebecca, aren't you?
I know your background.
It's gonna get a little messy, maybe,
but I won't do you wrong.
They're just putting up a good front.
This country is like...
...the country we grew up in, in some ways.
Stop it!
--Sabo...
--Give Sabo back!
What, you little shit? Do you want more?!
Stop it!
Ace!
I'm okay...
Give him back, Bluejam!
What do you mean "give him back"?
Sabo is my son.
How dare you two tempt Sabo to run away!
Nobody tempted me!
I ran away of my own will!
You stay out of this!
I'll leave the rest up to you, pirates.
Of course, mister.
We will take care of these two
so they won't bother your boy again.
Wait a minute, Bluejam!
Dad, that's enough! I understand!
What do you understand?
Don't do it, Sabo!
I'll live as you want
so please don't hurt these two!
I'm begging you.
They're very important to
me, they're my brothers!
Sabo...
Let's go home, Sabo.
Hey! Don't go!
Run! You don't have to worry about us!
You said you wanna live freely with us!
--Are you gonna put an end to your dream, Sabo?!
--Sabo!
Sabo!!
Oh, Sabo! You're back.
You got bigger.
Now Stelly, say "hi" to your older brother.
Nice to meet you, Brother-sama!
My name is Stelly and I'm 8.
Who is he?
We adopted him.
Just in case you failed in life...
Anyway, he's your smart younger brother.
You have the devil's luck
because they're gonna
take care of the burnables tomorrow night.
If you had stayed in the Trash Mountain,
you would've died.
What do you mean?
They'll burn down Gray Terminal.
What?!
They decided it months ago.
A group of observers from
the World Government
will arrive in Goa Kingdom three days later!
And they'll have a World Noble - a
Celestial Dragon with them on the ship.
So to gain his favor, the
members of the royal family
decided to burn up all the
shameful parts of this country.
There are a lot of people living there!
They can't...
I said they'll burn up all
the shame of this country.
You mean, the people, too?
H-Hey!
I-It is not my fault.
--Run!
--The fire is spreading all around!
Help!
--We can't run! The fire is everywhere!
--We have nowhere to go!
Ace... Luffy... Run!
--That brat is still there!
--Make him go away.
Please! My brothers are out there!
Let me through!
No matter how many times you come, we won't!
This country will be cleaner after this.
Ace... Luffy...
What happened to you, boy?
Old man...
The royalty and nobles are...
behind the fire...
Believe me!
This town smells worse than Gray Terminal.
It smells like rotten people!
If I stay here... I'll never be free!
I'm ashamed of being born a noble!
They finally made a kid say this!
Goa Kingdom!
No matter how many times you run,
you can't get away, Sabo!
Ace. Luffy.
You guys are okay, aren't you?
I wish I could see you.
This place is like a birdcage.
I don't think I can stand
living in this country
filled with stale air of rotten people.
What is freedom? Where can I find it?
"The Day of the World Noble's Arrival"
Hey, there is a ship leaving port
on a day like this!
It's a child!
There's a child on the ship!
What a nice day!
It's perfect for setting sail!
Oh no! That's mine!
Somebody stole my fish boat!
Could it be Sabo on that ship?
The Government's ship is here!
The ship is huge!
I might get tossed about by the waves.
Let's get away.
Sabo!
There is a child on the ship!
When someone flies a black flag,
he's a pirate regardless of who he is-eh.
But most importantly,
a commoner shouldn't cross the path of my ship!!
Damn! Why did they shoot me?!
Sabo is...
Stop lying, you fool!
Don't even joke about it!
I'm not lying or joking about it!
It was so sudden...
Where is the guy who killed Sabo now?!
I'm gonna kill him!
Stop it, you little shit!
Sabo was killed by this country!
This world!
What can you do about it?!
Dammit! Let go of me!
Boss! We just got a letter from Sabo!
"To My Brothers
From Sabo"
Ace, Luffy, when you get this letter,
I'll already be out on the sea.
Things led to things and I decided
to set out to sea before you.
My destination will be anywhere but here.
There, I'll become stronger
and become a pirate!
The three of us have to become
the freest pirates ever
then let's meet up again somewhere.
Somewhere on the big and open sea!
Definitely, someday!
By the way, Ace, which one of us
do you think is the bigger brother?
Two big brothers and one little brother.
It's odd but our brotherhood is my treasure."
Luffy is still a weak crybaby but...
...he is our little brother
so take good care of him!
How much longer
are you gonna lie there?
A-Ace... I...
I wanna become stronger!
So I can protect anything or anyone!
I don't have to lose anybody!
I beg you!
Ace, please don't die!
Cut it out!
Listen carefully, Luffy!
I promise that I'll never die!
How can I leave a wimpy brother
like you behind?
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
So listen, Luffy.
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
Uh-huh.
We gotta go out to sea someday
and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
The fighting competition
in the Corrida Colosseum!
The final!
The contenders will enter at any moment!
Who's gonna come in first?!
It's him!
The man who has risen to
prominence in this competition!
Here comes our favorite - Lucy!
Watch over me, Ace!
Now, they're all there!
These four winners from the first round!
And the man who is going to fight them is...
He saved this country along
with Donquixote Doflamingo,
and is one of the top
executives of the Family!
Mr. Diamante!
The winner of this round will get
a Logia Devil Fruit, the most powerful type.
The Flare-Flare Fruit!
The rules of the final are...
Don't start!
Redo the Block D match!
We couldn't have been beaten by
a little tramp like her!
Don't ruin my event!
I ate the Flutter-Flutter Fruit and
became a flag man!
Lock.
Corrida Glaive!
Wh-What the...?!
I-It's flying!
Did you guys see how it attacked?!
The deadliest Fighting Fish
from different schools
will try to kill the contenders in the ring!
And one of them has the
Flare-Flare Fruit on its back!
The rules are simple!
The one who gets it and remains standing
in the ring will be the champion!
I see.
Sounds like fun!
You can't have the Flare-Flare Fruit!
All right! It's gonna start soon!
A scramble for the Devil Fruit!
A death match involving the Fighting Fish!
I haven't done this kind of thing for so long.
I'm excited!
You bastard!
Lock!
Wow! That was close!
Barrier!
There it is!
I got it!
This ring is a pain...
It's getting exciting!
Is that the entrance to the palace?
Shh! Don't let the guards find you.
Gum-Gum...
...Gigant Pistol!
What the hell is he doing?!
Let's burst in!
This is the front entrance of the Rampart Tower!
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
Lucy dodges easily!
Only he can move like that!
What is he talking about?
Outta my way!
I-It's no mistake!
He came in and stirred things
up in this event! Lucy!
Then, who is the guy fighting at the Colosseum?!
What the hell is going on?!
It's going for Burgess this time!
Shockwave...
...Elbow!
Th-There you go!
Burgess's Shockwave Elbow!
It blasted a massive hole
in the spectator area!
This man is Jesus Burgess!
He's one of the Ten Titanic
Captains who support
the upstart pirate - Blackbeard!
--That bastard!
--Don't involve the audience!
Oh, there is the Fighting Fish
carrying the Devil Fruit!
It's going for...
...Rebecca!
I've gotta cut the chain at least!
Yes! I've got you!
You can't have it, Straw Hat!
I'm gonna bring you down
along with that fish!
--Run!
--He's gonna do it again!
How smart of you to stand behind me!
Lucy had no time to run!
He's not gonna try to get away? Lucy!
Shockwave...
Dragon Claw!
...Elbow!
Oh my! Burgess's armor has
shattered into pieces!
They're not gonna just give it up, huh?
--Where is Kin'emon?!
--He headed for a place called the Toy House!
Okay!
--What the...!
--Pica!
Be careful!
He's a top executive of the Family!
Luffy, take her and go on!
I'm gonna cut this stone guy!
Rebecca can't do anything against
Diamante's overwhelming power!
Damn!
--Hey, Musclemelon!
--No, I'm Bartolomeo...
--You protect her!
--What?!
That's...
"Gladius, Pop-Pop Fruit User"
I ate the Pop-Pop Fruit and became a rupture man!
I can detonate my own body. And...
...inorganic objects as well.
Get blown to pieces!
Jet Stamp!
Soldier! Where are Franky and the others?
I'm here to take down Doflamingo!
Straw Hat! We gotta go!
Violet! Damn you...
Hurry to the 2nd floor!
How could you...
...betray Young Master-sama!
Helmet Pop!
Oh no!
The 2nd floor, right?!
That must be it!
Where did they go?!
There are some cracks in the
basement of the Colosseum!
This place won't last until it's over!
Shockwave Elbow!
Nice!
Boy! We made it straight to our destination!
Hey, why do we have to hide?! Mingo is there!
What's wrong? You look pale.
The Little People of the Tontatta...
"Trebol, Stick-Stick Fruit User"
...have been beaten up by Trebol,
a top executive of the Family!
What?!
My friend should be with them!
He's there.
The one with a long nose...
But Sugar is about to...
As long as he's there, it's gonna be fine!
I'm sure Usopp will take care of it!
He's not even conscious now.
Don't do it, Sugar!
You were trying so hard to make me eat this but...
"Sugar, Hobby-Hobby Fruit User"
...you can have this poison grape back.
--Oh, the Tatababasco grape!
--Our only hope!
You eat this.
Drop dead.
S-Sugar!
I'm sorry, Doffy!
Trebol!
Sugar has passed out!
What? Hey, is this some kind of joke?!
What is happening here?!
The toys are turning into humans
one after the other!
Hey! Keep working!
Please don't! Please don't!
What?
How dare you push us around all this time...
Dressrosa is in turmoil!
--Come on out, Doflamingo!
--I'm gonna kill you!
--Doflamingo is a devil!
--Take down Doflamingo!
--How dare you call yourself a king?!
--You fooled us!
A decade...
We've worked hard on this for a decade!
Oh? Where did the soldier go?!
It's him!
Brother Kyros!
Who is he?
He's the former commander of
the King Riku Army - Kyros!
The strongest gladiator
in the history of the Colosseum!
That's the old man the statue is of!
And he's also Rebecca's biological father!
I'm here to take back the real Dressrosa!
Let's follow him!
You bastards!
E-Even I don't know how to
explain this situation!
Hey! How much longer are you gonna cry?!
Am I a babysitter?!
It's not that!
I had a father!
I just remember!
I guess that's the plot that's been
undermining the country, Rebecca.
Lucy...
Things always have a core.
And if you can strike it,
you can turn any situation around.
Even the ring has one. A core.
Let's just finish up this fight.
Dragon Claw Fist! Dragon...
...Breath!
The ring has exploded!
Lucy's unbelievable attack!
The ring is sinking!
It's floating!
You bastard! What did you do?!
I gotta go somewhere! I'm gonna win this!
The ring has totally collapsed!
Everybody, please evacuate immediately!
You can't hold on to my neck!
I'm losing my strength...
I found it!
Don't! We weren't gonna
give anyone that prize!
It's Doffy's!
Everybody's out of the ring! I'm the winner!
What?!
You said the one who gets
this will be the winner!
It's all mine, isn't it?
Th-The champion!
Oh my! The one who got the Flare-Flare Fruit
by taking advantage of this mess is...
...the biggest dark horse
of this competition!
Disgusting!
Lucy!
Oh my great senpai! Help me, too!
You're a man.
You have to take care of yourself!
What?!
Who are you really?
My name is Sabo,
a member of the Revolutionary Army!
What about the first Lucy?!
He's a pirate who's worth 400 million
and the man who'll become the
Pirate King someday!
Straw Hat Luffy! He's my brother.
I'm gonna make one more attack so watch out!
Ow, it's hot!
I really can generate a fire!
--He ate the Flare-Flare Fruit!
--Isn't he the guy from the Revolutionary Army?!
No, it's just my imagination! It's not hot!
I am a fire now!
Ace! I take over your ability!
I never wanna go through that again. So...
I will save Luffy's life that
you saved with your life!
Luffy! You just take out your enemies in front of you
and become the Pirate King!
I promise!
I... I will never die!
Ace!
We're gonna advance seeking freedom!
Here I go!
Fire Fist!
The flame of life that I reached out and touched
It will never be extinguished
Along with the bond we bound ourselves to
In this time when lies look glittering
We let the same wound soak in the same rain
Searching for the reason we were born
The boys sang that they will defend freedom
I wasn't by myself, I wasn't afraid anymore
At the extremity of sorrow, you were there
Liberator, let it be heard
By my heart that's tired of crying
The song of liberation, that voice of laughter
The liberator is you
There are no walls in this world
Let the song of liberation be heard
Thank you, Luffy!
I'm glad that you're alive!