Until I can reach that great sky,
I believe, to that one tomorrow, hey
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one dream
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the good times
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Stumbling into the darkness, fumbling about to find the answer
Freezing up when there's no goal in sight
Umm you and me, yes, in this world where we share our feelings
I feel the beat guiding me, and begin to walk, oh yeah
Share the music, anytime
Share the one dream and believe in each other
Share the good times holding hands
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style
Beginning, expanding, this flavor is beyond imagining
I feel so good throughout my body, I know I can be free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far
Share the one dream, by telling each other
Share the good times and laugh
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall
I'll be there soon, I believe, to that one world, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy was ejected from Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma, a Warlord of the Sea.
I have my Vivre Card!
Good thing we all got one!
I'm sure I'll see everyone again!
After being separated from his friends
and sent to an unknown isle alone,
Luffy intended to rely on his
Vivre Card to reunite with the others, but...
Aren't these Laughing Mushrooms?
Hurry! The smoke is rising from over there!
What do you suppose this is?
Luffy, after accidentally
eating a Parasite Mushroom,
was carried to a village by mysterious women.
Huh? Look here!
What's wrong?
There's still one mushroom left!
But doesn't this one seem
different from the others?
It's oddly shaped!
Anyway, I guess we better pull it off!
What's this? What's this?
What's going on?
Oh, Granny Nyon!
There's a mushroom growing
on this girl that won't come off!
Oh, my!
Th-This person...
...is a m-m-man!
Th-This is a m-man?!
I've never seen one before!
Hurry Back to Your Friends!
The Maiden Island Adventure
Maiden Island
Amazon Lily
This is the all-female empire of Amazon Lily.
On occasion, women will leave
the island and return with child,
but oddly enough,
they only give birth to girls.
"Kuja"
Inside a tall mountain surrounded
by thick jungle is a large hole,
and inside it a fortress-like village
was built and a country created.
Come on in!
Oh, that ribbon!
We both have one!
I found it!
Step right up! We have
Sea King meat on hand today!
It looks good!
It'll make your skin nice and smooth, too!
How about some fresh-picked
fruit from the jungle?!
All the wage-earning and manual labor
is done by women too, of course.
I brought it!
Thanks! Just set it right there!
Sure thing!
Raised from birth as warriors,
they truly are burly and large-hearted,
but they also have an air of
elegance about them as well.
There is no place here
for greedy, foolish men at all.
"Fighting"
And, more than anything, the
women of this island are strong.
Here are today's odds!
1,000 Gol on Poppy!
1,500 on Pansy!
In this land, the strong are beautiful.
Should a man ever approach this country,
eradication is all that awaits him.
"Prison"
The man's awake!
Let me see! Let me see!
I want to see, too!
He's moving around!
Look! He has no breasts at all!
What a weird, rugged creature!
He looks so weak with his
shaggy hair and scrawny body!
He slept for quite a long time...
But I heard he ate meals while asleep!
Did you know that?
What do men usually eat anyway? Raw meat?
I get the feeling he'll eat anything...
What's going on?
--What's all the noise?
--Oh! He can talk!
Where am I?
What was I doing again?
Oh, yeah!
Everyone was separated at Sabaody Archipelago!
I can't hear!
Everyone! Shh! He's saying something!
I remember eating mushrooms,
but everything after--
My hat's gone!
There it is!
Give it back, you jerk!
His arm stretched!
What kind of body does he have?!
That's a relief!
M-M-Men can stretch their arms!
How shocking! Notes! Notes!
This is most intriguing!
Say! What's your name?
I'm Luffy.
I'm naked!
You're slow!
I feel breezy!
Do you know where my clothes are?
Men are slow and want to conceal
their heads before their bodies!
Umm, before you get dressed, umm...!
What's inside that bag
sewn between your legs?
Bag?
Wait, you don't know what these are?
What a weirdo! These are balls!
Balls?
--Balls?
I can't see them! Scoot over, Margaret!
Sorry!
Your notebook's in the way!
What are balls?
They're the family jewels, of course!
Wow!
So men have family jewels!
Gorgeous!
Family jewels!
Could you take your jewels out
and let us see them?
Hell no!
Are you trying to kill me?! You idiot!
Here are your clothes then!
Yours were all torn up,
so I made new ones with the same design!
Oh?! That's great!
Thanks! I don't even know who you are!
I'm sure you'll like them!
What did you...?
I added sexy flower frills too!
Outdoor outfits are all about the frills!
Great job, Margaret!
He seems so happy he's shaking!
He's thanking you on his hands and knees!
Don't be stupid!
I'm a man, you know!
Prepare to attack!
What?!
What a vicious temper!
Is that your true nature?!
Wantonly yelling without any care
for the fact that we saved his life...
What a savage temperament!
His words and actions haven't shown
a shred of elegance whatsoever!
His kind really is incompatible
with us after all!
Even so, Kikyo!
He hasn't done much!
I'd feel sorry for killing him!
Wait! Hold on!
You saved my life?!
What happened?! Tell me!
These girls saved you after you ate
a lethal mushroom and collapsed.
Oh, really?! Thanks, you!
Sorry for complaining about the clothes!
Just don't shoot me!
Your apologies and excuses mean nothing!
This is the woman empire of Amazon Lily!
Men are forbidden!
That has been the absolute
rule here for centuries!
Never in history has it been broken!
Woman empire?!
Now that you've regained consciousness,
we have no sympathy for you!
Yeah! Now that I look closer,
it's nothing but women!
What a weird country!
We'll put an end to that
disdainful way of talking as well!
Hey!
Do we really have to put an end to him?
Aphelandra!
When the Snake Princess returns,
she will absolutely disapprove
of this situation!
You'll also be charged with the crime
of bringing a man into the village!
Margaret.
Sweetpea.
Aphelandra.
This is for your sake!
It is best that we cover up this incident!
Wait! Let me go!
I have to get to the place
my friends and I agreed on!
Shoot!
He broke through the roof!
Don't let him escape!
These arrows are really strong!
Yikes!
He's nimbler than he looks!
Aphelandra!
Right!
Sorry for saving you and then doing this!
He fell!
Now he's bouncing!
Hmm, now what do I do?
Take him down!
Don't let him escape! After him!
There he is!
Only one meat chop left
until they're sold out!
First come, first served!
Hold on! You gotta pay for that!
Treasure payment plan!
Enemy on the loose!
The man has escaped!
My food disappeared!
What is that?!
He went that way!
My meal is gone too!
Kill him!
Just give yourself up!
I-Is it just me, or are
there a lot more of ‘em?!
Get back here!
I'll get him! Aphelandra!
Right!
You're not getting away from me!
He dodged it!
I can't stop!
Sweetpea!
That's far enough!
We've cornered you!
You guys just don't give up...
Oh, right! My Vivre Card!
I left the old guy's piece
of paper in my other pants!
There she is! That's her!
I can't talk here!
Sorry! There's something I wanna ask you!
Let go! Help!
Oh no! Margaret's been abducted!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Hey. You alright?
Stay away!
You... turned fat just now, didn't you?!
You must be crazy to jump from way up there!
I was ready to die!
It's a miracle we're still alive!
Really?
Stay away!
I'm not gonna do anything.
I've heard that you men have a virus!
Do all men suddenly grow fat?!
I don't have any kind of virus,
and it'll be a pain to explain,
so let's just say all men suddenly grow fat.
Anyway, was there something
in my torn-up pants pockets?
It's really important!
Is this it?
This is it! This is it! What a relief!
I wouldn't know what to do without this!
Thanks for holding onto it!
L-Let go!
Oh, what a relief!
There was something written
on it, so I figured...
What is it?
Here, look!
How odd! It looks like it's moving!
A bunch of stuff happened
and all my friends went flying
through the sky in different directions.
But thanks to these pieces of paper,
we can all get together again!
They're all tough, you see!
Oh, I've been thanking you non-stop!
Is there anything I can do for you?
Could you take out your family
jewels so I can see them, then?!
I told you, they don't come off!
Men are cheapskates after all!
You're really serious about taking them!
Put the sword away!
Who are these "friends" of yours?!
Oh, I'm a pirate!
Do you know what a pirate is?
You're a pirate?
This land's empress is a pirate, too.
Really?
Then she has a women-only pirate group?
Are they strong?
That's a foolish question!
The most elite warriors of this land
ride aboard her pirate ship!
They're very strong!
Everyone here looks up to the Snake Princess!
She's strong, noble, and the most
beautiful woman in the world!
The Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock!
This land is closely protected
by her and her two sisters!
Oh no! The Snake Princess' ship is nearby!
This is bad!
We need to end the
incident with the man quickly!
Kikyo...
It looks like the man jumped
into the jungle after all!
Warriors! To the jungle!
Kill the man and rescue Margaret!
The Snake Princess has returned!
Vice Admiral Momonga of Navy Headquarters
waits for the Kuja Pirates
to speak with Hancock,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
However, Hancock refuses to
comply to the Navy's summons.
In return, she unleashes her Devil
Fruit abilities on the marines.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Everyone Falls in Love!
Pirate Empress Hancock"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Everyone Falls in Love!
Pirate Empress Hancock