Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue his brother, Ace, who will be executed!
He and the Whitebeards have invaded the plaza to make it to the scaffold!
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught, with the Whitebeards' assistance,
Luffy finally freed Ace! However...
Watch closely.
Wait!
Luffy!
Looking for the Answer
Fire Fist Ace Dies on the Battlefield
Ace...
Ace!
Ace-san!
He's been beaten! Dammit!
Stop, Red Hound!
Can't believe it!
Hurry up! Do something about these handcuffs!
I'm trying but... Damn, I can't break them!
Oh yeah! He can do it!
He?
Yeah, the guy who uncuffed Ace!
I'll make the key! Uncuff him right away!
Yeah, you're right! Bring him here now!
Okay!
Fire!
How's this war going to end?
That's what you get for hurting Ace!
Have you learned your lesson, Red Hound?
No way! Is he a monster?!
Looks like you're still alive!
Fire Fist Ace!
Don't do it...
Don't do it!
Ace!
I can't believe you let
your guard down, Whitebeard!
I won't let you interrupt!
Brat!
Jinbe!
I'm not going to let you touch him!
You're just delaying the inevitable, Jinbe!
Since you were once a Warlord,
I bet you know what I'm capable of!
I'll happily risk my life to buy some time!
I've been ready to die from the start!
Jinbe!
Marco! He's here!
Gee, thank you for helping me! I almost got killed...
Cut the crap and uncuff me now!
V-Vice Admiral Garp!
What are you...?
Garp!
What are you doing?! Are you losing your mind?!
You better keep holding me down
like that, Sengoku!
Because if you don't, I will kill Sakazuki!
You fool!
Looks like I need to execute a traitor, too!
Jinbe, get down!
How annoying!
So you guys are Haki users?
How could we mess up this badly?!
I'll never forgive myself for what happened today!
Can't you see that it's too late to save Fire Fist?!
Take a look!
Ace...
Hey, are you all right? Hey.
Ace, you need to get treated right away!
I'm sorry, Luffy...
Huh?
In order to save me,
you pushed yourself that far but...
...I couldn't make it all the way.
I'm sorry.
Wh-What are you saying?
Don't be ridiculous!
Somebody, treat him!
Please! Please help Ace!
Hey somebody! Help Ace! Please!
Hurry! This way! Give him first aid now!
Okay!
Straw-boy...
Ace! Are you alright?!
Hurry up and treat him!
Okay, let me see the wound!
Please!
This is...!
Huh?
Hey.
What's the matter? Hurry up and help him!
I'm sorry.
What do you mean by that?
What's going on?! Just do something!
Hey, aren't you a doctor?! Hey!
It's no use.
My organs have been burned.
I can't hold out any longer.
I can tell that my life is ending.
That's not true!
Oh yeah, Iva-chan!
Hey, I beg you!
Inject that stuff into Ace! Please!
Like you did to me, why can't you help Ace?!
Hey, I beg you! Please! Help! Help Ace!
Please inject that into Ace...
Straw-boy!
Ace-boy... can't make it!
Huh? No way.
You promised me!
You said...
...that you'd never die...
...no matter what!
Ace!!
Ace...
What did you say?
You can't hold out any longer?
You promised me...
...that you'd never die...
...no matter what, Ace!
Do I even deserve to have been born?
What if Gold Roger had a child?
Of course I know what'd happen to him!
He'd get his head cut off for sure!
No way! I'm not content if we kill him that easily!
How about we prick him with a needle
one time for every grudge
that someone holds against Roger.
No way! Instead, we should burn him alive first
and humiliate him in front of the whole world before he dies!
Good idea!
And then everybody'll say "serves him right!"
His last words should be:
"I'm sorry I was born! I'm just a piece of trash!"
But I don't think that he ever had a child!
No one wanted me to be born.
Ace! You caused trouble in the city again!
They're making a fuss about it!
Don't give us a hard time!
Hey! Are you listening, Ace?!
Shut up, Dadan!
What'd you say?!
If I were stronger, I would have killed all of them!
I wouldn't even have the will to live...
...if it weren't for Sabo
and an unruly little brother like you.
Oh yeah. If you see Dadan someday,
say hello for me.
While facing my own death,
I even miss a woman like her.
Like I said, don't say that you're gonna die!
There is one thing that makes me wanna stay.
That is my desire to see you fulfill your dream.
But I'm sure that you can do it!
Because you're my brother!
That day...
Listen, Luffy.
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
Uh-huh.
We gotta go out to sea someday...
...and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
Like we promised that day, I have no regrets...
...in my life.
That's a lie! Don't lie to me!
I'm not lying.
Something tells me
that what I truly wanted was not fame.
Did I deserve to be born?
What I wanted was the answer for that question.
Become my son!
You better tell me that my beloved son is all right.
I'm your brother!
You can say whatever you want!
I'm gonna save you even if it means death!
Guys! Rescue Ace and...
...destroy the Navy!!
I'm gonna get Ace back!!
Finally...
I made it! Ace!
Just tell me one thing.
Were you happy to have me as your father?
I can't speak loud enough anymore
for everybody to hear me.
Could you tell them...
...what I'm about to say now?
Pops!
Everybody!
And you Luffy.
Thank you...
...for loving such a good-for-nothing like me...
...who carries such despicable blood in his veins...
...up to today.
Thank you!
Old man.
Huh?
Do you think...
...that I deserved to be born?
That's something...
...you'll see as you live.
Ace...
It is a reality difficult to accept.
Ace's death cruelly unfolds before Luffy's eyes.
But the battle does not pause.
As the pursuit intensifies,
Whitebeard's rage shakes all of Marineford!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Navy Headquarters Falls! Whitebeard's Unspeakable Wrath!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Navy Headquarters Falls!
Whitebeard's Unspeakable Wrath!