Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Yuba
Nanohana
Katorea
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
and a mighty swell.
In the Alabasta port town of Nanohana,
Luffy reunited with his older brother, Ace.
Ace demonstrates the power
of the Flame-Flame Fruit.
With Ace by their side,
the party follows the Sandora
River upstream toward Yuba.
Erumalu, the City of Green,
And the Kung Fu Dugongs!
– Halt!
– What business do you have here?!
Please! Let us see the king!
How long is this civil war going to keep up?!
With this civil war and drought,
we have nothing left to eat!
Please help my child!
There's no milk left!
Stop! Quit pushing!
We can't let you through!
– Let us speak with the king!
– You want us to just die, then?!
– Hey! Say somethin', will ya?!
– Are you just gonna abandon us?!
And you call yourself a king?!
Why, you!
Don't you dare insult His Royal Highness!
Cease that at once, guards!
I'm sorry.
My lack of strength has put you
through such unbearable suffering.
Those who wish to speak,
please come inside
and tell me of your qualms.
All I can do now is share your
suffering as if it were my own as well.
I ask that you endure a little more.
I will return calm to this kingdom.
Even at the expense of my life!
Father! Someone set this up!
It's clear that someone is trying
to throw this kingdom into ruin!
I hope you're all right...
Where are you now,
and what are you doing, Vivi?
Tea's ready. Come on up to the kitchen.
Thank you, Sanji-san!
Heya! I'm Captain Rice Ball Usopp!
Oh! And who are you?!
I'm a riceman!
Quit playing with our food!
If you got free time,
go wash dishes or something!
Geez! I need to finish our packed
meals before we cross the river!
Need a hand?
No, no. You are a guest on board.
Just sit back and relax.
All right.
Don't wash the dishes in that mop bucket!
What a nice breeze!
Nami-san.
I'd like to land the ship here for a moment...
Eh? What for?
I have an important task for Karoo.
Karoo?
Karoo.
I want you to go to Alubarna Palace on your own
and deliver this letter to my father.
I've written down everything Igaram and I learned
about Crocodile and Baroque Works' schemes.
And that I've returned to Alabasta
alive with supportive friends.
Can you do it?
You'll have to cross the desert on your own.
Listen. You have to drink your
water with care in the desert.
Karoo! Good luck!
Now let my father know
this kingdom can be saved!
Drink your water with care!
Karoo... Thank you...
I knew Crocodile, one of the Seven Warlords,
was in this country...
But a pirate trying to steal a kingdom?
That sounds like a bad joke.
A pirate dropping anchor in
one spot and settling down?
Don't tell me he's trying to usurp the throne.
Alright! Let's set sail!
Hold on! I'm not on board yet!
There could be another side
to this takeover thing.
Another side?
Some sort of deeper goal...
Alabasta, the kingdom of sand...
Even if you build cities atop the sandy earth
and exist there for thousands of years,
the desert will always be
filled with the stench of death.
From its very inception, this land
has embraced the shadow of death.
I've just received word that the
Billions' ships stationed in Nanohana
have all been wiped out by someone...
I'm having this verified as we speak.
There are more replacements for
the Billions than we even need.
A single drop of water spilled in the
desert is no obstacle for my plan.
But, if anyone who would
dare defy me has appeared...
crush them.
Understood.
I've already sent the Lizard
Runners to contact the others.
Excellent.
We're finally here!
We're finally going into the desert!
I bet it'll be hot...
– It gets over 50 C in the daytime!
– Eh?! It does?!
What happened, Nami-san?!
Where did your dancer outfit go?!
Aah! Not you too, Vivi-chan!
Why are you dressed like that?!
In the desert, any exposed skin
will wind up terribly sunburned!
This is terrible... My dancer girls...
Put this on, Luffy-san.
Okay! Thank you!
– Let's get ready to disembark.
– Yeah.
Okay! Let's land!
What's that?
– Turtles?
– Aren't those seals?
Kung Fu Dugongs!
"If you wanna come on shore,
you'll have to beat me first!"
"Or else go back to the other shore, cowards!"
Is what he says.
I can't sit quietly by when
someone calls me a coward!
– Let's do it!
– Wait! Usopp-san!
Kung Fu Dugongs are strong!
– One is winning over there!
– Winning is bad, too!
Huh?
It's a Kung Fu Dugong rule
that if someone loses,
they become the winner's pupil!
That's very martial arts-ish.
The number of pupils just went up!
Alright, everyone! After me!
Stance!
No! Like this!
Yeah! Now go like this!
That's it! Like this!
Like this! Like this!
Like this!
Alright! Let's set out for Yuba!
Hold on, now!
Are you bringing them with us?!
You can't, Luffy!
The Dugongs can't cross the desert...
So cute...
I don't know why, but I feel like
we're doing something very sad...
Me, too. What should we do?
I know!
Let's see here...
What're you doing?
Here!
You can have this! So stay here, okay?
– Help!
– Chopper!
See ya!
Hey now, Luffy!
Do you understand the current situation?!
They said they were coming with me,
so why couldn't we let them?
We couldn't go to any city with
that big of a group! You're so dumb!
Honestly!
We would've been in big trouble
had Chopper not persuaded them!
Yeah!
They kept saying, "We'll accompany you!"
They really would've come if
we hadn't given them food!
Sheesh! Thanks to you, our food
supply's gotten a lot smaller!
– He knows how to cause trouble.
– That's for sure!
– What's this?
– Is this the town of Yuba?
No...
This is Erumalu.
It used to be known as the City of Green...
City of Green?
The sight of this town explains everything.
What the Baroque Works organization has done to this country...
What the people of Alabasta are going through...
Wow! There's nothing here at all!
Yes. It's a ghost town now,
but up until just recently,
it was a thriving city full of greenery!
This place was?
Rain was always scarce, but even so,
the city was able to manage
by saving every last drop of rainwater it could.
But, for three years now,
not a single drop of rain has
fallen in any part of this country.
– For three years?!
– That long?!
But even without rain,
what about the river we just crossed?
Yeah! Couldn't they just pipe
water in from that big river?
The answer to that is up ahead.
Never in the thousands of
years of Alabasta's history
has the rain stopped completely.
But, there was one place where
the rain fell more than usual...
Alubarna, the capital.
The city with the king's palace...
The people called it the King's Miracle.
Until what happened that day, at least...
Lower the cargo!
It's falling over!
Look out!
Hey! Are you alright?!
Oh, no! This is bad!
We were supposed to deliver
this to King Cobra in Alubarna!
What is this green powder?
What is it?
H-How should we know?!
We're only following your king's orders!
– Right?
– We're just couriers!
Run!
Wait... Could this be?!
Dance Powder?!
You've heard of it?
Yes.
It's also known as "Rain-Summoning Powder."
Rain-summoning?
I'd only heard stories about it,
but a researcher in a country
where it doesn't rain created it.
By creating a misty smoke from it
and letting it rise into the sky,
you can artificially cause it to rain.
That's what Dance Powder is.
Oh! I get it!
You mean that mystery powder!
I ate some a while back!
It tastes really bad!
It isn't food.
It's for making rain.
What?! You think I'm lying, don't you?!
Hey, you!
Hold on! Wouldn't something like
that be perfect for this country?
As the name suggests, the country
that developed Dance Powder
was almost happy enough to dance at first.
But there was a big catch:
the neighboring country had a drought.
Understand?
Dance Powder quickly and
artificially matures clouds
that would normally grow into
rain clouds further downwind
and causes them to rain.
So...
Oh, I get it!
It steals rain that would've normally
gone to a neighboring country!
Eventually, war broke out
between the two countries
and many lives were lost as a result.
Ever since, the World Government
has put a worldwide ban
on the production and
possession of Dance Powder.
Powder that can bring both
happiness and dread when used...
When all that Dance Powder was
brought into the port town,
Alabasta was in the middle of
a strange weather phenomenon
where rain fell nowhere but in
the town where the king lived.
We haven't had a single drop of rain
because the king's been using Dance Powder!
Alubarna's rain wasn't a miracle at all!
It's all because of the king that we're parched and starving!
Hold on, Vivi!
That means your dad is the bad guy here!
You idiot! He was framed!
Vivi-chan's father would never do any such thing!
Never... Never...
Of course, my father had nothing to do with it,
but at around the same time,
a massive amount of Dance Powder
was found inside the palace...
They even had people working inside the palace?
What's this road, Vivi-chan?
This was a canal that used to bring
water in from the Sandora River.
Someone destroyed this canal, too...
With its canal gone, the City of Green
could no longer secure water.
As if praying, the people continued to wait,
but rain never came.
Ever since the Dance Powder incident,
distrust in the king grows daily.
And it's all how Crocodile planned, huh?
And then the fighting finally began.
To escape the fighting,
the exhausted people abandoned the city
and left for other oases in search of water.
And then...
the City of Green withered away.
– Huh? Is that someone's voice?!
– Is it the rebel army?!
Don't tell me Baroque Works
has been following us!
– No. It's just wind.
– It has to be someone's voice!
It's coming from all directions!
What do we do, Big Brother?!
There's no danger.
It's just wind blowing across the
town and echoing off old buildings.
It's as if...
It's as if the city of Erumalu is crying...
Here it comes!
Whoa, what was with that wind?
Someone's collapsed!
There are still people in this city?!
What did my father...
What did the citizens of this country ever do?
These people have worked so hard to live,
being natives of a desert land who
are forced to fight with nature.
Yet he's destroyed their lives!
What gives him the right to do that?!
What?!
All the while, as one of the Seven Warlords,
he pretends to be a hero of the people!
No one realizes he's deceiving the entire country!
Crocodile! Crocodile! Crocodile!
I...
can't let him get away with this!
Geez, you're all such kids.
Vivi!
Let's get moving!
I'm itching to do this now!
Let's go to Yuba!
That's where the rebel army is, right?
Yes. I'm going to persuade their
leader to stop the rebellion.
Persuade?
All of Alabasta's calamities are Crocodile's doing!
I'm going to tell him the truth
and have him stop the
pointless shedding of blood!
Got it.
Kodomo no koro yume mita boukenka mitai de
Like the adventurers I dreamed of when I was a child
Omoi no hate ni tsurenatte yuku yo
I continue on to the ends of emotion
Sukuiageta tenohira kara
I scoop up my hands,
koboreochiru suna to jikan
and the sand and time that spills from them
Kono tame ni umarete kita to oshiete kureru
show me that this is what I was born to do
Korogeochisou na supido de
Let's continue swimming
Bokura oyogitsuzukeyou
at a near-tumbling speed
Soshite dare mo
Until we wash up someday
shiranai shirahama he itsuka
on a white sandy beach
Uchiagerareru made
no one knows about
I can't go on...
I can't take hot weather...
Then take off that animal suit.
You jerk!
Are you making fun of reindeer?!
Hey. What in the world is Luffy doing?
– He's riding a camel!
– Wait! Something's chasing him!
Ugh!
How is he able to summon trouble like this?!
Next time, on One Piece:
Adventure in the Country of Sand!
The Monsters that Live in the Scorching Land
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Adventure in the
Country of Sand!
The Monsters that Live
in the Scorching Land