Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle on Fishman Island,
the Straw Hats reach the New World at long last—
the harshest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
After receiving an emergency signal,
they landed on Punk Hazard,
a strange island divided into two parts—
the Burning Lands and the Frozen Lands.
I can't let them escape!
Room!
What is this?! It's like a thin film...
Shambles!
E-Everybody, calm down!
Let's do a roll call!
--Chopper! --Here!
--Franky! --Yeah!
Sanji-kun?
What?
Nami-san?
You're Nami... aren't you?
Uh-huh!
What is going on here?!
You stupid pirate, don't push your luck!
You ate the Op-Op Fruit and you're the modification man, I believe!
Stay out of his sword's reach!
You guys are in my way! Get out of the circle!
The circle?!
While you're in the circle he created,
you're like a patient on an operating table!
This is his operating room.
He has total control over it and can manipulate anything as he pleases!
He's the Surgeon of Death!
Don't do it, Tashigi!
Your Haki is not strong enough!
Captain-chan!
A Clash!
Law vs. Vice Admiral Smoker
Research Institute, Main Entrance
C-Captain-chan got cut in half!
--Hey, you're alive, aren't you?! --Tashigi-chan!
How...
How dishonorable! I got sliced but I'm still breathing!
Why don't you just kill me, Trafalgar?!
You talk like a master swordsman.
Let me tell you something, Navy soldier girl.
The weak can't even pick their way to die!
You bastard!
You can't reach me with that sword.
I can chop you more if you liked it.
Damn you! Stop insulting our Captain-chan!
Captain-chan, don't worry!
We'll riddle that fool with bullets!
Bullets?!
How did the bullets get here?!
Where did the bullets that we shot go?!
Those are the bullets you shot.
I switched them with the snow falling over you.
Is he invincible?!
Get down! He's gonna cut everything again!
No one can stop his sword attack!
That bastard! Captain-chan, run!
Captain-chan!
Smo-yan!
The Surgeon of Death--Trafalgar Law!
You're just a pirate!
Stop messing with the Navy!
I feel an unpleasant energy.
You have Sea Prism Stone on the tip of your jitte, don't you?
Oh no! The recoil made the sword cut the artwork!
The ship's gonna fall onto us!
Let's run! He doesn't want us to be here anyway!
I don't care if you're a Warlord or not!
Just get out of my way!
Vice Admiral Smoker!
Captain-chan, let's get away!
--But... --He's no match for us!
White Blow!
Run! Get out of the circle!
Th-They were strong... Too strong...
Straw Hat Luffy and his crew...
Damn! They took Boss Brownbeard with them!
W-We got to help the Boss!
They're cold-blooded pirates!
I don't know what they're gonna do to him!
Boss Brownbeard!
We have to let the Master know!
Follow me, those of you who can stand up!
Team Luffy, Frozen Lands
I heard a huge noise. Was it Sanji and the others?
Hey, Alliga-taur!
You really don't know what happened to my crew?
Shut up! I won't tell you anything!
Fine. Then run faster! To the building that Brook saw!
We gotta save Nami and the others!
How humiliating to lose to such a squirt!
You robbed my people so cruelly of all they had, you cheap muggers!
Don't try to give us a bad name!
You guys attacked us first!
You're showing no sign of remorse, alligator guy.
Brook, I know you don't feel cold because you don't have flesh...
So why did you steal the coat?!
Because I felt like it.
I'm so happy to see you all again so I wanted to share in your feeling cold!
I feel bad that Nami and the others were abducted in those clothes.
I hope they don't get frostbite and lose their limbs.
Geez, Robin! Don't share those gruesome concerns!
Master, what should we do?
Mr. Law and Smoker are in a big battle.
What is he thinking?
I thought the plan was just to make them go away.
But those escaped pirates took the kids in the Biscuits Room with them
and ran into Law and the others at the front.
So the Navy saw the children?!
Yes.
That's what I feared the most.
Now they know something is going on on this island!
Even if we kill Smoker,
the Navy will become aware that something is wrong.
I thought so.
You just got back - what are you doing now, Monet?
It was them.
We should have paid better attention.
Oh yeah, I forgot to mention.
Vegapunk's dragon and
Brownbeard's Centaur Patrol Unit have been defeated.
--What?! --Unbelievable!
Which means those pirates you kidnapped along with
their ship had other crew members
and they were in the Burning Lands already.
They made it across the lake and they'll be here in a matter of minutes.
They were so strong. Now look.
"The Straw Hats Are Back"
I'm sure it was them.
The Straw Hats...
I'm sure you have heard about them.
They're an unforgivable archenemy not just for the Navy
but for the World Government too.
The World Government, huh?
If they're so notorious, maybe it's good for us!
Whether it's the Straw Hats or Smoker,
we can get rid of all those troublemakers who are learning what's
going on on this island at once!
But Master, even if they're a group of misfits,
if we kill all the G-5 soldiers,
the Navy would be on the alert, wouldn't they?
Well, we can just suppress things that are going to
happen on the island from now on.
--Call Joker. --Yes, sir!
Team Sanji
A mountain behind the institute
We made it out from the backdoor but what should we do now?!
Even with this strange transformation going on,
we have to keep running for now!
What's going on?! It's super confusing!
--Bros! --W-We're gonna freeze to die!
Deadly cold? I don't give a damn!
The samurai and the brats? I don't give a damn anymore!
What?!
Isn't there a camera somewhere?!
I wanna take a picture before we return to normal!
What're you gonna take a picture of?!
And stop having nosebleeds in my body!
This is more important, Nami! Don't button up my aloha shirt!
Are you all okay?
I know it's cold but hang on a little bit longer!
The Spiral Bro is being kind! It's too creepy!
What happened? Did you get your bodies switched?
Looks like that's what happened.
Hang on, kids!
I'm being treated very differently from before.
I didn't know humans felt this cold!
Bros, stop!
It's cold...
This is it... I-I can't even move...
--Me too! --I'm freezing too!
Damn! We shouldn't have taken them with us when
we didn't know where to go.
I don't feel cold at all with this body.
Pieces of the ship are falling like leaves off a tree!
Are you okay, Smo-yan?!
Captain-chan, how is your body? Did they stick together?
By the way, your right hand is my left foot!
My hands! Whose feet are these?!
Dammit! We're in big trouble!
We lost our means of communication and the ship!
I thought the Warlords were on our side! That bastard!
Hey hey, Captain-chan, don't try to move! Stay here!
Tashigi, keep this in mind.
Pirates will always be pirates!
Pirates will be pirates!
Why are you here?
No one, not even pirates or Government allies,
is allowed to be here on this island, Law!
That means you people are not allowed, either!
Law, why are you here on Punk Hazard?
I never understood why you joined the Warlords in the first place!
What are you up to?
What we need to do now is to achieve higher status.
Pirates all over the world have started to pay respect
to the Straw Hats because of the incident at Enies Lobby.
Yes.
I'll put all my pride on the line and kick their asses in the New World!
Whether it's the Straw Hats...
...or the Warlord who serves for the World Government - Trafalgar Law,
pirates will be pirates!
I've never trusted you Warlords.
Maybe that's the right thing to do.
Law!
What is this place to you?
Who's behind this?
What are you up to on this island?!
Why don't you answer first?!
What are you all up to?!
There are things that you can't see unless you change your standing, Smoker!
Scalpel!
My heart!
I don't have to tell you anything.
Smoker collapses after his heart is stolen.
With Law looking down coldly before them,
the rage of Tashigi and the G-5 reaches its peak and they attempt an attack...
When Luffy suddenly appears!
The meeting between the two, who share a deep bond from the great war,
causes the situation to drastically change!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Reunited After Two Years!
Luffy and Law"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Reunited After Two Years!
Luffy and Law