Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
rashinban nante jyuutai no moto
compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
delirious with fever, i take the helm
hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
if the dusty treasure map has been verified,
tashikameta no nara densetsu janai
it's not a legend!
kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
when it comes to personal storms,
biorizumu nokkatte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
omoi sugoseba ii
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
poketto no koin
a coin in my pocket,
soreto You Wanna Be My Friend
and do you wanna be my friend?
We Are
we are!
If there's anyone we can't
abandon, it's Bellemere!
Damn! Why did this have to happen?!
Don't act hasty, Bellemere!
Delicious! Nothing's quite like
my special tangerine sauce!
Ten more minutes for the duck in the oven.
Got the side of vegetables...
And the stew is boiling.
Now just some fried rice omelets,
and everything's ready!
This'll be a big blow to our family budget.
Oh, are they back?
Survive!
Mother Bellemere
and Nami's Bond!
It's open! Come on in!
Pardon me...
Too bad. I'm a former marine.
What brings Grand Line pirates
all the way out to Cocoyashi Village?
What's so funny?!
Powerless! Powerless!
Powerless! Powerless! Powerless!
How powerless your inferior species is!
Let's escape with her out the back door!
But the pirates might already be there!
We'll be fine!
Hold it!
Doctor!
You mustn't return home!
Wha...?
Move! We have to save Bellemere-san!
Nojiko! Nami!
Listen closely, you two!
This may not be the best situation to-
no, because of the situation,
I must tell you a somewhat cruel story!
Doctor?
Bellemere-san!
It's no good!
These guys are real monsters!
I'm gonna be killed!
Nojiko! Nami!
Bellemere!
Don't waste your life for some
pathetic sense of justice!
Some battles aren't worth fighting!
Some issues can be solved with money!
Gen-san...
That's right, marine girl.
100,000 per adult. 50,000 per kid.
If you can pay for your
whole family, I'll let you live.
You should be thankful I'm telling you.
My whole family?
That's 200,000 total.
How much do you own, all together?
Including what I've squirreled away...
a little over 100,000...
Hey!
There's a meal for three people in here!
Oh? A family of three, huh?
I almost forgot!
She invited me and my friend to dinner tonight!
Come, Bellemere.
Hurry and pay your amount.
Our delicious food's going to get cold!
Gen-san...
I hear you have 100,000.
Thank goodness you have enough!
Now everyone in the village is spared!
It's true-
the village register has no record
of her getting married or giving birth.
She's single.
"Single & No Family"
Do you understand?!
There's no proof that you two
and Bellemere are family!
Leave this island before they take notice of you!
Escape across the sea!
There's no other way for
all three of you to survive!
I feel it's reckless to send you two
out to sea at such a young age!
There's a chance something bad could happen!
But at least you'll have...
No.
I don't want to!
Why do we have to leave?
They're the ones who came here!
I... want to live in this village...
Is it because we're poor
that I can't be Bellemere-san's kid anymore?!
Why? Why?!
Thank goodness. Now they won't kill.
– Alright, we'll leave the village!
– Nojiko!
Let's go! Because that means
Bellemere-san gets to live!
Hold it.
Who said I paid for me?
That 100,000's for my two daughters.
I don't got enough for me.
Bellemere! What are you...
I'm sorry, Gen-san.
I just can't say I don't have a family...
Even... if it costs me my life...
How could she?!
Yeah, maybe we're not related by blood...
...but we're a family.
I want to be their parent,
even if it's only in name.
They're... my kids.
– Bellemere-san!
– Wait, you two!
I wish someone richer had adopted me instead!
It was just a lie! I was lying!
Bellemere-san!
I wanted... to buy you lots
more books and clothes...
I'm sorry!
I was never able to do
anything mother-like for you!
That's not true!
We don't need anything!
Just don't die!
Stay with us forever!
I want you to see the world map I draw!
Yeah... Your map...
Make your dream... come true!
Live!
Bellemere-san!
These're your girls, I take it?
Yeah, that's right!
Promise me you won't lay a hand on them!
Of course!
As long as you die like a good girl!
Help!
Now they're thirsty for blood...
Don't kill 'em.
Just handle 'em as you see fit.
Perfect timing for our first
example to the others!
Die with your pathetic love.
Nojiko! Nami!
I love you!
You just never learn, do you?!
Let go! I'll pay later!
With my body!
You fool!
You made another boy cry?!
He made me mad!
Blehhh!
It's okay. Kids will be kids.
He said your tangerines suck, Bellemere-san!
Say what?!
Bellemere!
Don't give in to anyone...
Even girls need to be strong...
It doesn't matter if people don't praise you!
Don't have hate for this era you were born in...
Never forget the strength to
be able to smile at any time...
Bellemere-san!
Under my rule, anyone without money dies!
Understand, you inferior species?!
What's this?
A sea chart?
No!
I drew that!
It's important to me! Give it back!
You drew it?
– Give it back!
– Nami! No!
Oh? This is quite impressive.
She's an invaluable asset!
Bring her with us!
Right!
No!
Let go! Let go! No!
– Let Nami go! Let go!
– Stop!
You got your money!
You promised not to lay a hand on her!
Yeah. I ain't gonna hurt her.
I'm just gonna borrow her.
Gen-san! Help!
Keep your hands off the children!
Kuroobi.
Gen-san!
Gen-san! Gen-san!
I'll save you, Nami...
I won't let you pass...
No! It's okay!
You don't need to save me!
Please!
This is getting tedious.
I'll... save...
Please, no more dying!
All of the village's ships have been sunk...
Our idea of trying to let
Nojiko and Nami escape to sea...
...was too optimistic...
Just as I feared, the Navy won't listen to us.
This island will be under his control.
Bellemere knew!
She fully knew how they work,
from her experience as a marine!
She knew not a single
person could ever escape...
They took Nami with them...
What... am I supposed to
do now... Bellemere-san?
We've found out where the Arlong Pirates are!
It seems they intend to
settle down on this island!
It's time to decide!
Do we fight now and die defiantly?!
Or do we place our hope in waiting
for help from the Government,
while living under the fear
of being killed at any time?!
It's one or the other!
Only Navy Headquarters
stands a chance against them!
But HQ has its hands full in the Grand Line.
Our hopes of them coming all the
way out here are as good as zero!
But I can't let Nami go!
I'll fight!
Me too! I doubt I can live my life
knowing I abandoned a child!
We're all family here!
Even if it means I die killing them,
I'm gonna save Nacchan!
Bellemere gave her life up to protect them!
Let's fight 'em again!
They'll blame us all anyway
if just one of us fights!
If you survive, lots of fun things will happen!
Nami!
Nacchan!
You're all right?!
Nami! Nami!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Did they do anything to you?
Nami?
I'm... joining...
Eh?
I'm joining... the Arlong Pirates...
I'm going to join the Arlong Pirates...
...to be a surveyor and draw sea charts!
What are you saying, Nami?
Are you in your right mind?
Did they do something
horrible to you? Did they?
No.
They threatened you, didn't they?
No!
Say it!
Let go of me!
Nami...
Nami!
T-That's an Arlong tattoo...
You...
Nami...
Look at this... They gave me all this money...
And they say they'll buy me anything I want...
Nami!
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Joining pirates is absolutely unforgivable!
And them, of all people!
Do you even know what
kind of people they are?!
So what?!
If I'm gonna get killed living
a proper life like Bellemere-san,
then I don't wanna live properly!
I can't believe this...
Bellemere-san...
Bellemere-san was killed because of us!
How can you just...
That's enough, Nojiko.
Leave, Nami!
Never step foot into this village again!
Nami!
How could she be so foolish?
Did she not see Bellemere as her parent?!
No, that's not true...
Nami loved Bellemere-san...
Hey...
Bellemere-san said that if we survive,
fun things will happen, right?
Lots of fun things...
Yeah.
After Arlong dragged me off,
five Navy ships came to capture him,
but they were all sunk easily...
I don't think the Government will
send any more help to this island.
That's what made me realize
I have to do something.
I made an agreement with Arlong
to buy Cocoyashi Village from him.
To buy the village?
For 100 million berries.
If I buy the village, we can be free.
No one else will have to die.
In exchange, I have to join his
group and draw sea charts...
B-But, 100 million berries?
I'm not sure you can earn that
much working your entire life!
I will earn it!
No matter what it takes!
Everyone's working their
hardest to pay the tribute money,
so my only choice is to do it alone.
Because if I ask for help from
anyone, more people will get hurt.
It'll hurt, you know...
Yeah...
Staying with the people who
killed Bellemere-san'll hurt.
I'll be fine. I'll put on a big smile,
even when I see his face!
I've decided not to cry anymore.
I've decided to fight on my own!
Do you know how painful
of a choice it was for Nami
to decide to fight and survive on
her own, at the mere age of 10?
For the only deal that
could save the village, she...
I'll make whoever makes
my beloved Nami-san suffer-
W-Why, Big Sister?
I told you!
I came here to tell you to stop!
If you make a big fuss
about her being your friend,
the pirates'll grow suspicious of Nami
and her eight years of fighting
will be all for nothing!
Don't make her suffer any more than she has.
She has to fight alone,
so the most painful thing for her
is having people who call her their friend!
– Get back here! Damn brat!
– How dare you steal our treasure?!
Stealing from pirates?!
Yeah!
I'm using the huge number of
pirates in this era to my advantage!
It's like, "You get what you deserve!"
You're covered in cuts, though!
Yeah. I sorta screwed up.
But look at this! One million berries!
Forget that!
You need medical treatment, quick!
I'm fine! It's nothing!
No one will ever find it here!
I'll gather money little by little,
and it'll be 100 million when I'm grown up!
I have a long ways to go...
100 million berries...
It's taken a long time,
but just seven million left...
I can earn that much now in one try!
Just one more journey,
and it'll all be over...
Everyone in Cocoyashi Village
and I will be free of Arlong.
And then...
And then, I think I can finally
smile from the bottom of my heart...
Bellemere-san...
What does the Navy want with Nami?
You simply need to lead the way quietly.
Why does that old guy have
a pinwheel on his head?
So cool!
Guess I'll get started on
my final act of plundering!
The Navy?!
And why is Gen-san with them?
Are you the girl thief known as Nami?
Our information has it you've hidden
treasure you stole from pirates
in this tangerine orchard.
They were pirates, though.
I have no intentions of condemning you.
However, stealing is stealing.
Therefore, as of this moment,
all of the property you've stolen
now belongs to the Government!
Now give us all of your stolen goods!
We're confiscating it!
hamidashita kimochi tsunagara nakute
my overflowing feelings don't connect
kimi no te o gyutto ni girikaesu yo
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
hitori demo boku wa arukidasu kara
I'll set off by myself,
tooku made zutto mitsumeteite ne
so keep watching me intently as I go into the distance
kesa kara chotto kangaeteita
I was thinking about it a bit since this morning
doushite konna ni atsui no
why is it so hot?
itsu kara ka sonna koto bakari ga
starting from some point,
hanarenai yo
I haven't been able to get away from that
kakedashita kimochi tsukamaetakute
I want to catch those feelings that rushed off,
jibun sae mou oikoshite yuku yo
and I'm already about to overtake myself, even
tobidashita yume o dakishimetetai
I want to embrace my dreams that have jumped out
issho nara boku wa hashitte yukeru
with you, I can run there
Alright!
Now we know all about this island!
Let's hurry and meet up with Luffy!
Yeah.
What're you doing?
Appreciating happiness.
I can stop Nami-san's suffering
with my own two hands!
Hey, Nami! What's wrong?!
You're still here?!
Just leave the island already!
Next time, on One Piece:
Luffy Rises!
Result of the Broken Promise!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Luffy Rises!
Result of the Broken Promise!