It's showtime!
One, two, three, it's about to start
The delightful show
Five, six, seven, are you all set?
It's waiting for you...
...just beyond the door
There are traps that devils
and angels whisper about
Listen closely and you'll begin to see
That's right, life is roulette!
And it's waiting for you...
Gran Tesoro
Ohhh
"There's nothing money can't buy!"
After someone argues
"Being a goody-two-shoes
will get you played like a fool!"
Then a stab in the back
Oh!
There are traps that devils
and angels whisper about
What the heck is that?!
It's huge!
I can see through it all
Gold and jive
Forget everything and just have fun
Nami! Is this really a ship?!
Yes! It's the world's biggest entertainment city!
The casino town where
anyone can strike it rich...
...Gran Tesoro!
It's pretty much an island if you ask me!
All right, guys! Next stop: casino!
Yeah!
Huh? Something's shining...
- I think it's...
- Gold dust?
It really is gold!
All right, guys! Load up all you can!
Yay!
Yohoho! This rain is giving me golden bones!
Super!
- Oh, even the water is gold!
- Interesting, isn't it?
Gold and jive
Forget everything and just have fun
There's the entrance! Franky!
I'm on it! Coup de Burst!
Gold and jive
Forget everything and just have fun
Go!
Awesome!
Mellorine!
What is all this?!
Incredible!
Who's that?
What the...?!
We're the Long Long Pirates!
Hand over all your valuables!
We lost at the casino! We need money!
Huh? That's crazy talk!
Take this!
They're shooting at us!
What the heck?!
Tesoro-sama!
Pirates are causing trouble!
It's all right.
The crowd's loving it.
Is that...?
Yes. I believe it's the Straw Hats.
The Straw Hats?
Oh-ho. What a surprise.
This'll be fun.
Huh? What the...?
Hand over your valuables!
Talk about rude. I was trying to sleep here.
Dunno who you are,
but you drew your sword first.
You're goin' down.
Bring it on!
Three-Sword Style:
Demon Slash!
"320-million-Berry bounty"
Come on, now.
You're making me spill her drink.
What?!
Damn pest.
"177-million-Berry bounty"
Robin-chan! Sorry for the wait!
"130-million-Berry bounty"
Thank you, Sanji.
Where's your money, girl?!
Here's a news flash for you...
We don't have any money.
"66-million-Berry bounty"
Sacrifice your flesh...
...to break your opponent's bones!
Not that I have flesh, though!
"83-million-Berry bounty"
Shoot 'im! Shoot 'im!
Radical Beam!
Now we're gettin' flashy!
"94-million-Berry bounty"
Shark Arrow Devils!
Bull's-eye!
"200-million-Berry bounty"
Oh!
Usopp!
Are you okay?! Pull yourself together!
"100-Berry bounty"
Now I remember! These guys are—!
Hey! Long-Head!
Quit messing...
...with...
...Sunny!
Wha...?! Long-Head?!
I'll have you know...
...that I'm the heinous, despicable...
...captain of the Long Long Pirates...
...Alexander Alex Kent Paul
Harris Hendricks Award...
...Rudolph Eccentric—
Bullets don't work!
What?!
I'm made of rubber!
Gum-Gum...
- ...Jet...
- Wait, I'm not done—
...Pistol!
"500-million-Berry bounty"
They took out our captain!
Run!
Gold and jive
Forget everything and just have fun
The gold!
Gold and jive
Forget everything and just have fun
Whoa!
Awesome!
Help!
Gold Splash!
I welcome you to the world's
largest entertainment city...
Welcome to Gran Tesoro.
Wow!
This place looks neat!
Oh!
Awesome!
Even its port is super-fancy!
Wow! Amazing!
Might you be the Straw Hat crew?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure's mine, mademoiselle.
I'm Sanji, the ship's cook.
It must be destiny that brought me to you!
Oh, what a nice compliment.
It's an honor to meet you.
My name is Baccarat.
I'm a concierge for VIP guests.
You know us?
Oh, but of course!
All government heads, Navy leaders,
and famous pirates are on our VIP list.
See?
Guess that means we've hit the big time!
Yes! If you need anything, feel free to ask me!
Please, this way!
Turtle! Turtle!
- Whoa! What is this thing?!
- Is it a vehicle?!
Yes, it's known as a Turtlemobile.
It's a chief form of transportation here.
Whoa! It's powered by turtles?
Yes. Eight rare Muscle Turtles, to be exact.
Turtle!
Turtle.
Please, get in.
Whoa! It's so fluffy!
There's a drink bar here!
Drink anything you'd like.
Oh! There's alcohol too!
Any cola?
Okay! Let's go!
Yes. City of Gran Tesoro, here we come!
Turtle! Turtle! Turtle! Turtle! Turtle!...
Yahoo!
Woo-hoo!
This is one smooth ride!
Yes!
Turtle-Royces are equipped with
the company's finest Gentle Turtles.
Huh.
First up is the downtown area.
Wow! I feel like we're in a dreamland!
No, no. This is still a plain area of town.
Huh?!
This ship is approximately 10 kilometers long.
10 kilometers?!
Yes.
It's fully equipped with hotels,
a shopping mall, and a casino...
...as well as pools, an aquarium,
a theater, and a golf course.
This giant ship itself is
its own independent country,
officially recognized by the World Government.
The front of the ship is also
equipped with Giant Turtles,
allowing it to travel to anywhere in the world
regardless of any sea or wind currents.
The luxurious area is coming up next!
Oh!
So cool!
The entire city is filled with gold.
Yes. Gran Tesoro's king,
Tesoro-sama, just loves gold.
He gathered gold from all over the world
to build this dreamlike ship-city.
So he's really rich?
Yes.
Tesoro-sama is known around
the world as the "Casino King."
He's also a top-class entertainer,
and an actual king of a country.
He's so fantastic!
Hey! I bet swiping just one of those
could get us a ton of money!
You read my mind! I've been
itching to steal since we got here!
That's no good. I'd advise against it.
Eep!
Look up there.
Video transponder snails?!
Yes.
They've been installed all over the city.
As per city law, anyone caught
stealing or causing destruction
will be thrown into the underground prison.
So do behave yourselves.
Come on! Let's go to the casino already!
Yes, of course.
But first...
Wow! You all look like
top-class, dignified pirates!
We can really put this on credit?!
Yes, of course. You're famous VIPs.
This is a gambling city. You can
just win the money to pay it off.
Yeah! Good point!
No, you don't understand at all!
What if we lose?!
This building sure is tall!
Pay attention!
So this is a casino!
Yes. Welcome to Gran Tesoro's pride and joy
and the world's only eight-star hotel...
The Reoro!
Awesome! It's so gold and shiny!
It's built entirely out of gold. It's gorgeous!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
- What's with you kids?!
- Buy a flower!
P-Please!
You're VIPs, right?!
- Flowers?
- Come on! Buy one!
Come on, man! Just buy one!
Okay, okay!
How much?
- 5,000 Berries!
- That much?!
We need money for our freedom!
Come on! We said "please"!
Huh? What does he mean?
Come now, children. Quit pestering my guests.
You know you don't belong here.
Now go.
Brother...
W-We're sorry.
Let's go!
Wait for me!
Huh? Wait!
Sorry about that!
Come. The casino awaits!
You sang wonderfully again tonight, Carina.
Good work today!
I was nothing compared to you, Tesoro-sama.
Tesoro-sama.
Baccarat has made contact with the Straw Hats.
Oh, really?
What a nuisance they caused
by taking out Doflamingo.
I wonder how much
entertainment they can provide...
Oh! That name!
I've heard of 'im before!
He's always spouting crap about
bein' the Pirate King...
Right?!
- Whoa! You're too drunk!
- Yeah!
H-Hey!
Tell me.
Who said you could laugh first?
Umm...
Only one person decides
what's funny in this city.
Do you know who?
Y-You, of course—!
Tesoro-sama! Please forgive me!
I promise not to laugh anymore!
Oh, so you do understand?
Then that'll be all.
Help!
Did you see that? The way he wriggled?
Now that's entertainment!
What shall we do with the Straw Hats?
Ah, yes. Our usual "deal" will do.
Understood.
This should be a truly entertaining show.
Whoa!
So this is a casino! It's so big!
Yes. This casino features a wide
variety of games and attractions.
Feel free to ask any questions you have.
I'll be your guide.
Thanks.
For now, we'll lend you
20 million Berries' worth of chips.
20 million?!
We can really borrow this?!
Yes. Go right ahead.
Thanks! I'm gonna go play!
Ack! Luffy!
We're coming too!
Hey, now!
- Let's go!
- Yeah!
Get back here!
Urgh, those selfish jerks!
What game is this?
Oh, this is a hands-on Turtlemobile race!
Huh? A race?
Yes! It costs one million Berries to participate!
What?! One million?!
It's time for the anything-goes
Turtlemobile race, Hot Shell!
If you guys lose,
you're in for some serious trouble!
We got this!
All we gotta do is win, right?
Six cars! Customization allowed!
Obstruction allowed!
Basically, whoever completes a full lap first wins
and earns ten times the participation fee!
- The moment of truth is upon us!
- Ready... Go!
They all start together!
Turtle! Turtle! Turtle!...
Who will break ahead of the pack first?!
Oh, Jimmy Myers jumps into the lead!
"Profit unnoticed" is Jimmy's motto as a CEO.
But he transforms when in the driver's seat!
Outta my way!
He widens his lead!
What?!
Oh, no! Jimmy's out of the race!
In the lead now is...
Go!
Sergeant Straight, hater of all that is twisted!
The pool area is up next!
They're nearing the first curve!
Sergeant!
We can't make this turn!
Don't be stupid!
The word "turn" isn't in my vocabulary!
Aye, aye, sir!
Oh, my! He's fallen off the course!
Four vehicles remain!
Oh! Rushing up from behind is...
...Straw Hat Luffy's team
in a rental Turtlemobile!
They're closing in on
Whitejack the Quack in first place!
You ain't getting past me!
- Killco-chan!
- You got it!
See ya!
Oh, crap!
Oh, they've really slipped up!
They're getting passed left and right!
Hurry, Usopp!
I know!
Halfway through the race, Whitejack is in first
with the three other cars in hot pursuit!
Wha...?!
Oh, my! Whitejack is
knocked out of the race, literally!
Kent Beef Jr., the South Blue's
rancher king, packs a real punch!
What's this?!
The newspaper king, Count Times,
breaks ahead! Impressive!
Damn!
- What?!
- Turtle! Turtle! Turtle! Turtle!...
Go!
Get 'em, Pork!
Moo!
A dirt course lies beyond the tunnel!
Can they make the turn?!
Oh! They've left the course!
Oh! Nice shot!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Go!
- Let's get married!
- Huh?
Urgh, those guys...!
Oh, my! What's this?!
Luffy!
Oh! Team Straw Hat is back on track!
- No way!
- Not bad.
Go!
They're in the home stretch!
They're locked in a dead heat!
Who will the winner be?!
Go!
- Team Straw Hat wins!
- Yes!
All right! Let's keep this
roll going and win, win, win!
- Yeah!
- All right!
Come on, come on! Yeah, yeah!
Awesome! It just keeps pouring out!
- Thank you.
- Wha...?! You won again?!
We won!
Way to go!
Amazing! We just made 30 million Berries!
Oh, man!
Nicely done, everyone!
Perhaps you'd like to visit the VIP room next?
What's that?
It's high-risk, high-return.
Win and you're a billionaire.
Are you game for some special gambling?
Huh? Hey, what do you think?
We accept the challenge head-on, of course!
That's great! Wonderful!
Are we here?
One moment.
Who is he?!
This is Tanaka-san,
head of the casino's security.
Welcome.
He has the power of the Through-Through Fruit.
He can pass through any non-living object.
Take my hand, if you would.
Whoa! We passed through it!
This is the VIP room?
What kind of place is this?!
I bet on even!
I bet on odd!
Huh. So your "special gambling"
is a plain ol' dice game?
Yes.
Whoa, hold on! The Navy's here too?!
Oh, crap, they are!
Never fear.
The World Government recognizes Gran Tesoro
as a special neutral area.
The Navy can't go after pirates.
That's the rule here.
- Wow.
- Makes sense.
Everyone ready? Let's begin!
Who is that?!
That's Dice.
He's the undefeated champion
of the underworld's ultimate death match show.
He's so dominant that
he's run out of opponents.
These days, he's in charge here as a dealer.
Yes!
Whoa, he's strong!
He's going to break it with that axe!
Here we go!
He's in the air!
Now he's spinning!
Yes!
The axe was meaningless!
Feels so good!
2-6, even!
What do you think? Exciting, isn't it?
None of that made any sense.
Okay! We'll start by lending
you 300 million in chips!
300 million?!
This is our chance to
suddenly become billionaires!
- Yeah, but...!
- We really must be cautious!
Okay! All on even!
Wait, you!
Yes!
Feels so good!
Snake eyes! Even!
All right!
Whoa! Awesome!
You doubled our money!
Well done, Luffy-san. You're remarkably lucky!
We can do it! We really
are gonna be billionaires!
Calm down!
- Oh! Tesoro-sama!
- It's Tesoro-sama!
What a pleasant surprise.
Welcome to Gran Tesoro.
Are you having a splendid time?
Who are you?
Oh, allow me to introduce myself.
I own this ship. My name is Gild Tesoro.
Oh! You're the Casino King guy!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
What are you being competitive for?!
A visit from the "future Pirate King"...
I'm truly honored.
I know! What do you say
you and I make a little bet?
A bet?
This is such a rare occasion.
How do these rules sound?
If you win, I'll make a special allowance
and pay you ten times your wager.
T-Ten times?!
Of course, you won't need
to pay tenfold if you lose.
I already have more money
than I know what to do with.
This is the only way to make it exciting for me.
So, what do you say?
You're on! I won't lose!
Uhh, is this really a good idea?
We're on a good winning streak!
I trust Luffy's luck!
All right! I've decided!
All on odd!
A brilliant max bet!
I'd expect no less of Luffy-sama.
Luffy! Wait!
You've been most impressive.
Here we go!
Well?! What is it?!
Yes...
Oh. I lost.
No way! Luffy lost?!
Nice work, nice work.
That was quite the thrilling show, Baccarat.
Show? What does he mean?!
You have powers, don't you?
- Huh?!
- Yeah. I do.
I have the powers of the Luck-Luck Fruit.
I can remove the luck from anyone I touch.
- Their luck?!
- So you took Luffy's?!
Huh? All my luck's gone now?
- That's right.
- But I feel normal.
What's going on?! M-M—
My stomach hurts!
Huh?!
- No way!
- Luffy has a stomachache?!
Wha...?!
A banana peel?!
The Luck-Luck Fruit is powerful, all right!
You guys cheated!
Cheated?
Sounds like you guys need a quick lesson...
...on this city's unbendable rules.
Here, whoever falls for ruses...
...loses.
We've been had?!
Now, then. Please repay the 320 million
Berries you borrowed, if you would.
You know we can't pay you anything!
Then I guess you'll just
have to work your debt off.
Work?
The people who work here are
debt-ridden slaves who lost at the casino.
If you refuse, I'll just have to
collect on your debt by force.
Is that so?
Like to see you try.
Ouch!
I twisted my ankle...
What?! Are you okay, Baccarat-chan?!
Touched you.
Crap!
Oww! Hot! Hot!
Banana!
Sh-She's formidable!
You moron!
Through Illusion!
He vanished!
Ugh! Not again!
Damn! What's his deal?!
Strong Right!
Yes!
Feels so good!
Nice punch!
Give me more!
Tch! What's with this guy?!
I'll handle him.
Taking out the boss is the
quickest way to end a fight.
Oh-ho. What a bold statement.
You think you can beat me?
In this city?
Easily.
What the...?!
Zoro!
Don't fight, you guys!
Very astute of you.
They'd all be golden statues
by now if they had tried anything.
What power is this?!
Gold.
I have the powers of the Gol-Gol Fruit.
I can fully control any gold that I've touched!
Huh?!
What did you do to Zoro?!
When you entered the city,
you were showered in a gold dust.
That was my way of infusing your bodies
with gold that I can manipulate.
Everyone who comes here is under my
control from the moment they arrive.
Everyone!
Now, then. Perhaps there is
a way to pay off your debt...
With his 320 million Berry bounty.
You planned this from the start!
No one can defy me!
We'll see about—
- Stop right there.
- Who are you?!
Just do what he says.
You're...!
All right! We'll get your money!
Give us some time!
Whoa! Nami!
Certainly. I'll wait until tomorrow at midnight.
But if you're late...
...we'll make a big show
out of his public execution.
What?!
All right! Do we have a deal?!
Hey, now!
Yes, of course.
This is the ultimate bet, after all.
Can you gather the money by tomorrow night...
...or will you live the rest
of your lives as slaves?
Make it nice and entertaining.
I expect great things from you.
I'm starving!
Never mind that!
Zoro is more important right now!
Obviously! That's why food comes first!
That makes no sense!
But it is better to think on a full stomach!
Yeah, I guess you have a point...
Oh...
All right! Let's eat!
Meat! I smell meat!
Oh, Luffy-san!
Sheesh. Let's let 'im cool down.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Hold it!
What's going on?
Oh. I see your skill hasn't faded, Cat Burglar.
Wish I could say the same about you, Hellcat.
Huh?!
Urgh!
I knew it was you, Carina.
It's been a while, Nami!
You work for Tesoro!
Shh!
You guys know each other?
Yep.
Nami and I are like...
long-time burglar buddies.
- Right?
- No.
We fought over treasure a lot when
I was a thief in the East Blue. That's all.
'Cause you were so greedy.
You're way greedier than me!
Say what, Cat Burglar?!
Greedy Hellcat!
Let's just eat already!
Sorry about my behavior at the casino.
I had no choice. I'm casing
the place by working for Tesoro.
That's okay. Don't worry about it.
Wait, are you after the Tesoro Stash?!
Tesoro Stash?
It's said 20% of the world's
Berry supply lies hidden in this city.
People call it the "Tesoro Stash."
Stealing it would be the greatest
feat a thief could achieve.
Many famous thieves and burglars
have attempted to steal it,
but not a single one has ever succeeded.
I finally got close enough
to Tesoro to make a spare.
A key?
It opens a giant vault at the top of the tower.
So you really are...?!
Yep. I'm going for the
500 billion Berries in the vault!
- Huh?!
- F-F-Five hundred billion?!
Is that a lot?!
It's more than enough to
purchase a small nation.
A country?!
Tesoro regularly gives a portion
of it to the Celestial Dragons.
Oh, a Heavenly Tribute?
He uses his monetary influence
to control the Celestial Dragons.
So that's why the Navy and World Government
turn a blind eye to Tesoro.
Makes sense.
The Tesoro Stash flows to pirates too.
A golden emperor who rules
the underworld with money...
That's who he really is.
Say, wanna team up?
You could buy your friend back
with the money we steal.
Why bother? We can just take 'im back by force!
You saw it yourself.
Gold imbued with
Tesoro's power is inside us all.
He could solidify us any time he wanted.
Our only option is to win by this
city's rule of "deceive and steal"!
All right, then.
Whoa, Nami! Can we really trust her?!
What other choice do we have?
So we can save Zoro?
If we succeed.
Okay! It's a deal!
Now we're talking!
Whew. Oh, well!
Our target is 500 billion Berries!
We're going to steal the
untouchable Tesoro Stash.
This is a life-or-death gamble!
But only on the condition
that we split it 70-30—
Huh?!
Get real! I'm the one who prepared the key!
So? There's more of us than you!
So what?! You're totally helpless without me!
Come again?!
Don't give me that!
You okay, Tempo?!
Hey, now.
Did you do that on purpose
'cause we work for Tesoro-sama?
W-We're sorry! Please forgive us!
Nope!
Your debt just went up by 20,000!
Oh, no...
It's those kids!
They're being forced to
work off their family's debt...
...as lifelong slaves for Tesoro.
What? You got a problem with me?!
Please stop.
Huh?!
Have these children done something?
L-Listen, ex-soldier!
Do you got a problem teaching
kids respect or something?!
I beg for your forgiveness.
Have you forgotten what happens
if you defy Tesoro-sama?!
You're supposed to smile for your customers!
C'mon! Smile!
That attitude's gonna get your family killed!
Smile more!
- I'm sorry... Please forgive me.
- What's that? I can't hear ya!
Those creeps...!
You know what happens if
you defy us! Don't forget it!
Don't blame us. Blame yourself
for getting tricked like an idiot!
- Mister!
- Boss!
I'm fine, Ricca.
Okay. Back to work.
Hey!
Why didn't you fight?!
There's no point in fighting.
Why not?!
Without money, we can never be free!
Brother!
Welcome, Cipher Pol member
whose name I forget.
Huh?!
You can count on me, Spandam of CP-0,
to protect the Celestial Dragons
and your Heavenly Tribute!
Yeah. Good to hear it.
As appreciation...
Whoa! What the...?!
For you.
This guy...
What's the matter? Don't want it?
W-Well, I suppose I can take it for now!
That reminds me, the Straw Hat
crew is aboard our ship.
What?!
I hear they caused you a
great deal of trouble before.
Should we really let him handle this?
Tell the head of Cipher Pol
to send someone more helpful.
And... to send ten Navy battleships.
Understood.
Just as we thought.
So, any word from Max?
No, he's been completely out of contact.
Knowing him, he's probably
at the casino non-stop.
Oh, that reminds me, I heard they're here!
Huh? Who?
The Straw Hats.
Yeah?
"Complete Justice"
Ten battleships?
That's a laugh.
Tesoro is an ex-pirate.
Why should the Navy lend him a hand?
Tell me. When exactly did
CP-0 become Tesoro's lapdog?
This is for our mission. Not Tesoro.
I'll take command.
You will send ten ships, without argument.
You mongrel. Do you know
who you're talking to?!
You sure think highly of yourself...
...Rob Lucci.
Man. They're already
handing out loads of fliers...
Hey, Luffy! Get some shut-eye!
We got disguises to prep in the morning.
Carina.
We're all set.
Great.
Where were you?
Oh, I had an errand to take care of.
I thought you had ditched me again.
Huh?! When did I ever ditch you?!
Don't pretend you don't remember.
It was when we locked horns trying
to steal the Treasure Pirates' plunder.
Oh, yeah.
Instead, we both got captured and tortured.
So, who wants to die first?
Well?!
I'll give it back!
I'll even give you all the money I've saved up!
Just, please, spare these two lives!
Carina?!
Oh-ho. All right, then.
Be back by sunset, or she dies.
Trust me.
I will come back.
But... you never did.
Time's up. Some friend she was.
She wasn't my friend, or anything else.
- Huh?
- Say, let's make a deal.
My treasure's hidden at the west cove.
It's all yours, if you let me live.
"A girl's gotta survive on her wits, you know?
Heehee ♥ Carina"
No...!
What a pity.
She not only ditched you,
she stole your treasure too.
That was a long time ago.
I could've been killed, you know!
We both would've been killed
if I'd given the treasure back.
I had no other choice at the time.
You're unbelievable!
Backstab me this time
and you'll regret it, Hellcat.
I know, Cat Burglar.
All right! Just as we planned!
Okay!
What was the plan again?
What?! I just explained it!
The giant vault is here, in the Hyper-Suite area.
The 500 billion Berries is there,
inside the golden sky dome!
It's impossible to break in.
The floor, walls, and ceiling
are all made of thick gold.
Can't we bust through it?
No. Tesoro has "awakened" abilities.
He's connected to all of the gold in this city.
He'll immediately notice if we
hit the gold with strong impacts.
Hold on! Then how do we get inside the dome?!
Here. A spiral staircase that leads inside.
This is our only way in.
But the place is filled
with video transponder snails.
They'd normally spot us immediately.
But there's a flaw.
That's why I asked for your help.
Team A will scale the hotel's exterior
to reach the upper area...
...sneak inside through the clock...
...and head for the control room.
The team will then operate
the host transponder snail above...
...and temporarily cut the
video feeds from the staircase.
Meanwhile, a second team, Team B...
...will take the elevator from
the casino floor to the VIP casino.
The team will slip past
Tanaka-san's checkpoint...
...and head for the Hyper-Suite area.
The entrance to the
spiral staircase is at the rear.
Past the security guards,
it's a straight shot to the staircase.
While the transponder snail video feeds are off,
the team will race up the stairs
and use this key to open the vault at the top!
We'll stuff the wads of cash
into the hotel's laundry carts
and leave right through the front door.
Then, it's "mission complete"!
Okay...
Upsy-daisy.
Still only halfway.
This is way too slippery to climb!
Not a problem!
This calls for the spy tool Usopp and I made!
Spy tool?!
Just watch!
Franky...
...Snapping Turtle...
...Rocket!
Oh!
Awesome! It's so spy-like!
Right?!
Oh!
I just remembered. Can't you fly, Sanji-san?
Not with anyone that heavy.
Besides, I have the important task
of protecting these ladies!
Shh! They're coming!
Oh! What handsome hunks!
Carina-san?!
Say, where are you taking that?
Umm, to the VIP area...
Dice-sama demolishes them,
so we always bring him replacements.
Wow! Let me see it!
Oh! Wow!
It's... so big!
Yes! Very big!
It's so impressive!
Yes! Very impressive!
Thank you! Keep up the good work!
We will!
Perfect.
Three of Dice's men...
May I help you?
Carina-sama. Please, come right in.
Woo-hoo! What a great view!
Careful! Don't let any customers see you!
Yeah!
All right.
The security area is up there,
where the clock is.
Got it!
Luffy!
You okay?!
I'm in trouble too!
Grab on!
Coup de Boo!
Go!
Huh?!
We made it...
We're in!
Let's go!
The security area is in the back!
The entrance to the staircase is up ahead!
We need to get through there.
I'll handle this.
Nice work, Big Sis!
Let's go.
This is as far as I've been.
There's no telling what to expect now.
These are...!
Red-eyed owls...
- What are they?!
- They're natural traps.
They hoot loudly if their eyes
shine on anything alive!
They're...
I thought so!
- What is it?!
- They're saying the directions their heads move!
These ones say, "Up. Down. Up."
Wow! You can understand animals?!
Oh, you don't hafta praise me!
It doesn't make me happy—
Just focus!
Now!
Stop!
- Now's our chance!
- Let's go!
Uh-oh!
Run!
Brook! Hurry!
I know!
Ack! It's hard to run in this!
Oh, no!
Brook!
H-Huh?
It seems you're okay 'cause you're not alive.
I feel so left out!
We've managed to reach the spiral staircase.
Franky! How are things on your end?
Almost there!
All right!
There it is! A humongous transponder snail!
It's the host snail. It's in charge
of all the surveillance feeds.
Cable #3 is the one tied to the staircase feeds.
There it is!
You can cut the video feeds
by putting this white snail there!
Okay! Got it!
Whatever you do, don't get spotted!
Okay! Now!
That was close!
- Be more careful!
- All right!
Okay! Now you just gotta attach the snail!
Oh...
Huh?!
Huh?
What the...?!
Intruder!
Brother!
That's...!
Uh-oh! Did they screw up?!
This is bad!
Fire!
There they are!
- Let's retreat for now, Luffy!
- Yeah!
Franky!
I never thought you'd try
to break your way in here.
Unbelievable. Do you not care
what happens to your pal?
Zoro!
Wonderful, wouldn't you agree?
I can't think of a more perfect
stage for a public execution.
This is entertainment!
Go on, Straw Hat.
Laugh.
No!
I'm going to kick your butt!
Gon Bomba!
It's no use.
In this city, I'm unbeatable!
Can't move...!
This is a lesson for you.
In this world, those without
money are powerless!
They'll always be ruled by money instead.
Shut up!
I won't let that crap rule me!
"That crap"?
All right, then...
Let's see you overcome it!
Assuming you'll ever get a chance.
Bottomless Hell!
I hope you relished that taste
of true entertainment!
Please, continue to enjoy
your time here at Gran Tesoro!
Man...
See? It really is pointless to fight!
Shall I go down and finish them off?
Don't bother. Go check
the spiral staircase instead.
Understood.
Oh, no! He's coming this way!
We'll be trapped like rats!
We need to get out of here!
There they are!
- Sanji-kun!
- Leave it to me!
Concasser!
Diable Jambe:
Poêle à Frire Spectre!
Overkill much?!
- Get 'em!
- That way!
Huh? What is this place?
These are the Hyper-Suites,
where the Celestial Dragons stay.
Celestial Dragons?!
Oh!
That's...!
Oh, man. Now what do we do?!
Running won't get us anywhere.
We have to take a gamble!
Brook?!
Don't be stupid! That's someone else!
Oh! Franky!
Huh? Where are we?
Everything is gold!
Looks like everything here is made out of gold.
Awesome!
We need water...
Water...
We need food...
What's going on?
Please... We'll give you all the money you want!
We don't got any food or water.
- You can't be serious...
- Damn!
Man, you guys are super-rich!
It's pointless.
Gold ain't worth nothin'...
At least not here, in the vile Gold Prison.
Gold Prison?
Yeah.
Tesoro gathered gold from all over the world
to build a golden city...
and a golden prison beneath it.
Ironic, isn't it?
A bunch of fortune hunters,
surrounded by gold as they die...
There's plenty of gold here, but no food.
Tesoro enjoys watching us suffer down here.
Who are you?!
Me?
I'm just a no-good loser.
Whoa, I can't believe it!
Are you Raise Max?!
- Who's that?
- You never heard of him?!
Raise Max, the legendary gambler
who's never lost a single bet!
He was my hero when I was a kid!
He's a huge star!
Rumor had it he joined the
Revolutionary Army, I believe...
Yes, I am Raise Max, the undefeated gambler.
Except for two times.
You lost the game of life?
I gave up that name long ago.
And not 'cause of the Revolutionary Army!
I took a big gamble in this casino...
and lost terribly.
The moment I lost that bet...
...is the moment Raise Max died.
Damn! We need to hurry and save Zoro!
Hey! How do we get out?!
- There is no way out!
- Death is all we got now!
Damn... All right! I'll break a wall! Gum-Gum—
Wait! Stop! Tesoro will notice
if you demolish any gold!
Besides, your arms can't break anything!
Then I'll use my head! Gum-Gum—
Stop!
Listen, straw hat kid!
Just give it up!
No matter what you do,
you can never beat Tesoro
while his gold is infused in your body!
Then I'll get rid of it!
There's gotta be some way, right?!
Uhh, well...
Sounds like it's not impossible.
Tesoro can't control gold
that's soaked in seawater.
Washing the gold off your body
with seawater should fix things.
Okay! Then let's go get seawater!
It's no use! There is no seawater on this ship!
Tesoro would never allow that, obviously!
There's only one possible place
to find it. The pump room.
This place is encased in gold,
but there is one air duct leading out.
It connects to a giant pump room
on the bottom of the ship,
where seawater is converted into fresh water.
But the duct is filled with vicious Golden Bats.
Many people have ventured in,
but not a single one has survived.
Bats?!
This is a gamble you'll never win.
Just give it up.
No! I refuse to!
- I'm going!
- Hey!
Franky! Hurry up!
Yeah!
I have no doubt he'll get out
of here and thrash Tesoro!
When the going gets tough,
he always gets tougher!
You're a gambler, right?
This is worth staking our lives on.
You're that sure, huh?
I like this bet!
I really must thank you, Roronoa Zoro.
Tickets to your public execution
have smashed all sales records.
How does that make you feel?
On top of the world.
I welcome your bravado.
It'll make for an exciting execution!
They can't possibly get the money in time.
Yet you still believe in them?
What else should I believe in?
The moment your hope turns to despair
is going to be a true delight.
I heard what happened!
S-Saint Camael!
What is this meaning of this?!
Is it true that thieves
have come for my money?!
Why aren't you stopping them?!
This is why I despise commoners!
O-Our apologies!
Have no fear! We've increased
the security around the vault!
Unacceptable!
Huh?!
I can't trust any of you!
Everyone is to leave the vault right this minute!
- Huh?!
- You can't be serious!
You dare talk back?!
You must be working with the thieves too, then!
Or do you dare suggest that we're wrong?
- N-Not at all!
- Nothing of the sort!
I wouldn't defy the
Celestial Dragons if I were you!
You know what'll happen if you do...
Don't you?!
Y-Yes! Right away!
We're in some serious trouble
if they ever find out about this!
For sure. But we had no choice!
Zoro's execution is going to start soon!
Tch. There's a whole flock of 'em!
Oh, no!
Help!
- You okay?!
- Yeah!
Let's go!
Zoro!
Straw hat kid...
That sound!
What the...?!
That's one huge ventilation fan...
The pump room is below it.
But there's no getting through here.
That's one of Tesoro's traps.
It's made of Sea Prism Stone,
which blocks Haki,
weapons, and special powers!
Just give it up.
No! I'm gonna stop it!
Stop!
You idiot!
- Luffy!
- It's impossible! Stop!
It's not impossible!
I... won't give up!
Darn it!
Again!
Damn...
Damn!
Straw hat boy...
Enough already!
Let's fall back for now!
No! I'm not done yet!
I refuse to give up!
I refuse!
Yeah, I know.
I'll stop this fan.
I've been reduced to a pathetic loser.
But I feel like betting one last time...
...on you.
Old guy!
What are you planning?
This is just another type of gamble.
And I'm gonna take it.
Now!
Max!
Old guy!
No! I won't give up!
I won't give up!
- He did it!
- Max!
Stop, damn you!
It's no use. He's just not strong enough!
Guys!
Our families are toiling 'cause of our debts!
We've had enough of this cruelty!
We... wanna be free!
Whoa...
They actually stopped it!
Straw hat kid!
Go... and pulverize Tesoro!
Yeah!
I will!
We did it!
It's the pump room!
We made it!
This is the vault door!
Once we open it with this key...
...we win.
It's showtime!
Yeah!
What the heck?!
What is this?
Surprised, I bet! This is the Sky Theater!
Sky Theater?
Indeed!
It's the perfect stage for
Roronoa Zoro's execution, is it not?
Behold!
Zoro!
A superb view, isn't it?
There is neither an enormous vault
nor 500 billion Berries here!
The Heavenly Tribute is already
on the Celestial Dragon's ship.
You've been had!
By my loyal servant...
...Carina.
Carina! You mean...?!
It's like we told you at the start.
Here in Gran Tesoro,
falling for a ruse means you lose.
Seriously?!
Damn it!
- Nice!
- This is great!
We've been watching you this whole time.
This is a popular gambling event.
"How close can they get to the vault?"
We always play this game
when infamous pirates show up.
Thanks for the fun.
Fools risking their lives for money,
only to be duped in the end...
There's no greater show than this!
Wonderful...
The excitement you've
brought is simply wonderful.
As a reward...
...here's a nice little show for you.
This one's at its climax too.
Luffy?!
Okay, Luffy!
Now let's bust this and get us some seawater!
Got it!
Gum-Gum...
...Bell!
Uh-oh! I forgot I can't handle seawater...
Oh!
The gold in us is washing away!
Yes! We did it!
We're free now! Free!
What's going on?!
Not good!
We've been tricked?!
Luffy!
Franky!
Damn!
The moment that hope
transforms into despair...
Now this is the ultimate entertainment!
Money is power! Money is everything!
Those without money... have nothing!
No love...
No dreams...
No strength...
No freedom...
Not even hope.
We've come so far, too!
Luffy!
You're gonna pay for this...
- ...you bastard!
- Sanji-kun!
Now! On to the finale!
Looking nice!
Tesoro!
Now you can watch from your VIP seats...
...as Roronoa Zoro's head comes off!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Let's give a big round of applause
for these people about to die!
Gold Splash!
Farewell, Straw Hats.
I win!
Now this is entertainment!
What the...?!
What's going on?!
What's happened?!
What's so funny?!
Who tricked whom, I wonder...
Huh?!
Th-This is... seawater...
What?!
Tesoro-sama!
This way!
Whoa!
Seawater!
It's raining seawater!
Tesoro can't solidify us anymore!
We're free!
We're finally free!
Super...
...Comeback!
Franky!
Looks like we're just in time.
What did you do?!
We knew you'd make it rain
gold dust at the end of the show.
We had some inside knowledge...
...thanks to Carina.
So sorry.
I was actually working
with the Straw Hats all along.
Carina...
Everything you guys "saw"
was an act we put on.
We never gave a crap
about the vault or your money!
All we needed was this seawater.
One shower and we're immune to your power.
Falling to the bottom was part of the plan too.
It's how I managed to route the
seawater into the fountain pipe.
Luffy knew nothing about the plan, of course.
We're not on your terms anymore.
Now we can fight!
It's your turn to play by our rules.
We're pirates, you know!
We take what we want by force!
We'll be taking our crewmate back now!
Tesoro!
Luffy!
Nice work, Luffy! The plan worked!
Plan?
Yeah. All that's left now...
is to beat him senseless!
Insolent cretins...!
Oh, did we make you angry?
But this is Gran Tesoro.
It's your fault if you get tricked here.
This is the perfect show for the
world's #1 casino, wouldn't you agree?
Now this is...
...the ultimate entertainment!
And now I'm gonna...
...kick your butt!
So, how does it feel?
The moment hope turns to despair...
You call this hope?
You call this despair?
I'm... gonna be a star!
Stop that stupid singing!
Stupid! Shut up, Tesoro!
If only I had money...
How much? This makes us buddies.
You scum! You can't pay up?!
That's a nice song.
Someone's going to buy me someday...
Stella!
But they'll never buy my heart...
I can make it happen! I'm gonna buy you myself!
Money can buy anything!
Stella!
Thank you...
- I was just happy that you cared so much...
- Stella! Stella!
- I felt joy... from the bottom of my heart!
- Stella!
Who gave you permission to laugh?
Don't you dare...
Don't you dare...!
Tesoro-sama?!
Don't you dare laugh in my face!
So what if you've broken free of my spell?
I can just cast it again!
Crap! Hold on!
Coup de Boo!
Everything in this city obeys my will!
And I'm the one who decides what's funny!
You gotta be kidding me!
- I can't keep going...
- Huh?!
This guy is insane...
What's that?!
Now! Let's restart the show!
Now do you get it, Straw Hat?!
I reign supreme over everything in the world.
And you're nothing but trash,
destined to be ruled over.
You are seeing a god!
You're annoying!
I already told you! Nobody is gonna rule me!
Gear 3:
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Don't get cocky!
Is he...?!
Brother!
Luffy!
Nice.
You!
Very nice!
Two Gorilla Slash!
Feels so good!
Give me some more!
That armor...!
It's no ordinary armor, actually.
This Gold Armor was created
using Tesoro-sama's abilities!
Gold Armor?!
In other words...
...we've powered up a whole lot more!
So, you guys want money, right?
I'll give a large sum to anyone who
takes the head of one of my enemies!
Really get this show going!
As... my pawns!
Oww!
Huh? I'm feeling weak...
You let your guard down!
That's a custom-order spike chain
made of Sea Prism Stone!
Straw Hat!
It's finally payback time for
what happened at Enies Lobby!
You're...
- ...who, again?!
- Wha...?!
If you've forgotten who I am...
...then I'll just have to remind you!
Tch! Who's this brat?!
You're...!
I've made up my mind!
I... won't give up anymore!
I've decided to fight...
I've decided...
...freedom is great!
Huh?!
It sure is!
Yeah!
What nonsense is that?! Just look!
There's no way you can beat this many people!
Listen up!
This world is rigged for
the people in power to win!
I wouldn't be so sure.
What?!
Old guy!
Hey, kid!
Deal me in!
This bet is a sure thing! Trust me!
I'm the legendary gambler, Raise Max!
Yeah!
All right! Let's win us some freedom!
These lowlifes...!
You!
Out of the way!
Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Ultra Tiger Hunt!
So good!
1,080-Pound Phoenix!
Can't get enough!
More! More! Hurt me more!
Tch...
Damn him!
Do you know the surefire trick to gambling?
You bet with coins stolen from your opponent!
Interesting!
All right! Here goes!
Go on! Catch me if you can!
Tch! You're missing on purpose,
you slippery creep!
Well, this is a show, after all.
Of course I'm going to play with you...
- ...before I slaughter you!
- Shut up!
Gotcha!
Bastard!
- Huh?!
- What is she doing?!
She's turning her allies unlucky!
Well, this is our chance!
Green Star: Explosive Skull Grass!
What?!
Oh, lucky me!
The Luck-Luck Fruit can do more
than remove luck from others.
It can also convert others' luck into your own.
In other words...
...I'm unstoppable now!
In fact...
...this single coin is all I need
to beat the lot of you!
Yeah, right! That'd never stop us!
Oh? Are you sure about that?
This'll be a blast!
No way!
Oh, lucky me!
What can we do against that?!
We keep attacking.
Her luck has to run out sometime...
Will you last that long, though?
It's our only option!
Wash tubs?!
Birds?!
Bananas!
Oh, done already?
I still have plenty of luck, you know.
Darn it! What do we do?!
I have an idea!
Special Attack...
...Usopp Dash!
Wha...?!
Oh, my. Running away?
What a pathetic crewmate you have.
Tesoro!
Luffy!
Done already?!
Just getting started!
Grizzly...
...Magnum!
That's rousing!
It's no wonder you're worth 500 million!
Fire!
What?!
Please wait!
Even if you are in charge of this
Heavenly Tribute defense plan,
we can't just unleash salvos at them!
There'll be civilian casualties!
So?
Hurry! Tesoro is running amok!
My life is in danger!
Give me that!
What are you doing?!
Use any means necessary! Rescue us at once!
Click.
Huh?! Hello?!
Inform all ships.
Your orders for this mission...
...are to destroy Tesoro.
All ships, prepare for bombardment!
Target Gild Tesoro!
Fire!
Fire Fist!
What are you doing here, Revolutionary?
What, you expect me to ignore this?
No more needless casualties, CP-0.
Besides, this is my little brother's fight.
I'd appreciate you staying out of it.
Tch. Feeble Navy.
I'll show you what happens
when you defy a god!
Gon Fuoco di Dio!
This is what you call justice?
No. I call it freedom.
Ridiculous.
Fear me!
This is the power of a god!
Tesoro!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
Crumble before my might!
Gon Inferno!
Straw hat kid!
No...
That's a nice look on your face, Carina.
I'm disappointed in you!
Carina!
Nami?!
Why did you risk yourself for me?
Because I owe you.
Huh?!
That day... You really did save me.
I fooled you all!
You!
Your treasure...
...belongs to me, the great Carina!
"Carina strikes again!!"
So screw you!
That's when I realized it.
After her!
You risked your life and acted as a decoy
so that we could both survive.
Nami...
Carina.
You worked with us earlier. So believe in us!
They absolutely won't lose!
We're a team, aren't we?
Yes!
Nami!
Believing in your "team" will get you nowhere.
Despair, and bow down to me!
Then I'll end this show!
I don't care...
I still believe in them!
Huh?!
Tesoro!
Let her go!
Laugh, Straw Hat...
This girl still believes in you.
You people are nothing but
scum that lost a bet to me!
I've bought your lives!
All of the losers on this ship...
...are my property!
You're just like some other guys I hate!
Let her go!
I told you to laugh, so laugh.
She's my property!
I'm free to do whatever I want!
Nami!
Isn't that right, Carina?!
Robin!
Spider Net!
Tch!
My friends aren't things!
Gear 4!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Gun!
Whoa!
You're...?!
I didn't want to reveal my trump card so soon,
but I had to answer my captain's call.
You can only pass through
non-living objects, yes?
Robin-chan. Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
That's good. Sorry for the trouble.
He's on fire!
Diable Jambe: Première Haché!
Damn this cook for putting
a lady in harm's way!
This is... the end!
Sorry for the wait, guys!
Oh? And why did you come back?
Usopp!
Why...
...to save my friends, of course!
You know you can't hit me.
He hit her!
How? I should have had plenty of luck left...
It couldn't be...!
Way to go, lucky girl!
You hit the miraculous jackpot!
Jackpot?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes!
You'll hafta do better than that to cut me down.
No-Sword Style... Kalasutra: Grand Dragon Twister!
Don't underestimate me!
Black Sword:
Death Lion Song!
What's the matter? Did that feel so good...
...that you're speechless?!
No way!
They took out our bosses!
R-Run!
Gran Tesoro is done for!
To hell with money!
Hey...
Where do you think you're going?
You're my property!
- What?!
- What's happening?!
Nami!
Franky!
Behold the beauty of gold.
I'm going to drown everything in it...
and swallow it up!
I'm sinking!
I give people happiness.
Because of me, they rejoice...
...become obsessed...
...suffer...
...get ripped apart...
...and despair!
Tesoro!
Yes! Feel anger, Straw Hat!
Everyone you held dear and tried to protect
is about to be swallowed by my power!
That's the way of this world!
Gold rules over all!
Then...
...rule over this!
Gon L'ira di Dio!
Gum-Gum...
...Leo Rex Bazooka!
How do you like that?! I've become a god!
Gold Splash!
You're no god! You're nothing but a monster!
Get him!
I'm the man who's gonna be Pirate King!
I felt joy... from the bottom of my heart!
Stella?
Wow!
Straw hat kid!
He did it!
He beat Tesoro!
What the...?
Tesoro?!
He went out beautifully.
I almost thought a god had descended.
Actually, his nickname is...
..."Monster."
Take Tesoro into custody!
Luffy!
What's that sound?!
What is that?!
Guys! Run for your lives!
Tesoro intends to sink the ship!
Get to the ship, guys! We gotta leave!
The road is blocked!
Come on!
A robot!
Hurry! You too, Carina!
- Go without me.
- Huh?!
I'm going to move this ship away.
Even if you leave now,
you'll get caught in the explosion.
But I can reduce the casualties
if I move the ship away.
Don't be crazy—
Huh?!
You have a good crew.
I'm glad my final job was with you guys.
Carina...
Franky!
Get her to safety.
Got it!
Carina!
Hey!
Where is she?! It's gonna explode!
What the heck?!
Why are there fireworks?
There she is!
Huh?
"Phantom Thief Carina strikes again!!"
"Phantom Thief Carina strikes again"?!
She pulled one over on us!
She stole the whole dang ship!
She was after all of the gold all along.
She used us like fools.
Oh, she tricked us?
I forgot the Navy was here!
Okay, guys! Let's run for it!
What is this?
That hellcat...
I'll act like a dumbass for you, so come on, engage
Say something crappy to fire up my rage
"A girl's gotta survive on her wits, you know?
Heehee ♥"
It's only when I feel pushed to the limit
That instinct kicks in and a new me awakens
I know you get what I mean
When I say this fight you picked ain't worth it yet
Give me more rage! I wanna get serious
This ain't cutting it! Come on, piss me off!
We idiots can only chase idiotic dreams
No matter how many times we triumph, let's never let it be enough
Hey, you "not my business" wimps who never wanna rock the boat
Where do you get off jeering from the sidelines?
You're the ones who are gonna get laughed at
A moping heart's the worst kind of unburnable trash
Give me more rage! Rationality only gets in my way
'Cause what I want, I can only get by going past my limit
Let the sparks fly till we're both blind
Let's go at each other body and soul, so we can shine
This world is full of problems, and there ain't any answers
So those of us who have enough fun are the winners
Give me more rage! I wanna get serious
This ain't cutting it! Come on, piss me off!
We idiots can only chase idiotic dreams
No matter how many times we triumph, let's never let it be enough