Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be Pirate King!
Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
BON
VO
Let that shred of courage grow
YAGE!
YAGE!
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
YAGE!
BON
VO
YAGE!
shi
ga
ra
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve your dreams aren't for naught
cious
in
my
life
i
pre
cious
in
my
life
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
In order to prevent Luffy and Nami from reaching the ark,
Eneru released Mamaragan. However...
It's useless, Eneru.
The land won't be beaten!
Luffy was approaching the ark.
Hand over... the golden bell!!
Disappear with the land!
Raigo!
Gum-Gum...
...Fi... re... works!!
Gold Peony!!
Clear up!!
Straw Hat! Ring the "fire of Shandora"!!
Luffy finally reached the ark, and at the
end of the fierce fight with Eneru...
Well then, I'll ring you as well!!
Gum-Gum...
...Gold Rifle!!
Reach!!
The Battle Ends!
Proud Fantasia Echoes Far
Can you hear it?! Old diamond-head! Monkeys!!
The city of gold... was right here!!
That bonehead did it!!
How beautiful...
What a pretty sound! What is this?! What?!
I believed that this moment would come one day.
So this was the ring that Noland heard.
Suu... I wonder if Vearth is singing...
So God really... exists?
What a miracle!
I had half given up on the bell ringing again after its 400-year silence.
Great Warrior Calgara... Can you hear...
...the echo of the fire of Shandora...?
What happened to this land?
What is this tone? Could it be...?
Is this the legendary...?
Are you hearing this... Montblanc Noland?
Sorry to have kept you waiting so long.
I hope...
...this reaches your descendants!
You like this bell's sound, too?
Old-timer! Th-This is...
Yeah! There's no doubt about it.
There's only one bell in this
world that echoes this far!
This is romanticism.
From the sky...
I'm getting worked up.
About the monsters that appear with the cumuloregalis clouds,
there used to be a story like this.
When there is a human far up in the
sky and strong sunlight shines on him,
his figure is reflected in the
deep mist of the far sky.
The shadow looks as if it's a huge monster.
So the true form of those monsters are
the shadows of the humans in the sky?!
Then does that mean that we've already confirmed that people live in the sky?
Yeah.
I thought the story was a meaningless
fantasy and I'd forgotten about it,
but it seems that it was true.
I can hear the loud ring of the golden bell.
The city of gold really exists in the sky!
Noland
the Liar
Noland wasn't... My ancestor wasn't a liar!
Noland
the Liar
You rang it to tell me that from the sky...
...right, kid? I appreciate it!
Monkey
Old-timer?!
What's the matter?! Are you sick?!
Those kids... I'm glad they were safe!
I was... so worried...
Look!! That's...
God's ship...
It's God!!
They're sinking...
God Eneru and his ship are...
...sinking...
The bell's ring is the fire of Shandora,
a long-gone city that took pride in its prosperity.
The island's singing voice that
proclaims the end of the battle...
The promised ring was
delivered after 400 years...
Although the journey of the
restless island was long,
it's hard to forget the distant memory.
Long ago, people entrusted their
words in the sound of the bell.
They placed proud words in the
song sent to the distant sea.
Comrades...!
It rang...
Yeah.
I wonder... if the old guy and the others heard it.
Yeah, I'm sure.
We're... right here!!
Tie the ropes to strong-looking trees!
Aisa... Were you worried?
Here... your treasure!
I don't care about that!
Laki...
How's everyone else?
They're fine! Don't speak right now...
Someone's there!
Am I still alive?
No! You have to get treated right away!
My treatment can wait.
Before treating me, do something about that guy, or he'll die.
You're right! His body's falling apart,
right down to the bones. This is terrible!
Hey, that's one of the guerrillas.
We don't owe him anything.
Yeah. I don't really know why, but it
seemed like he was going all out, so...
Huh? What the heck?
Are you feeling sorry for him?
Who knows...?
Um...
Is he gonna be okay, Raccoon-Doggy?
I'm a reindeer! Look, I have antlers!
Don't worry. He'll survive.
Thank you!
Pierre, go and rest with those Blue Sea people.
Pierre, hurry up and go bring the families!
So, in the end, both the golden bell and Eneru's golden ship...
I think they fell.
So now it's a city of gold in name only, huh?
Which means our journey in poverty continues.
I'd want those dials rather than gold,
since we won't be able to get them
once we get back to the Blue Sea.
In any case, I wonder if Nami-san's all right.
I wonder where Conis-chan is...
Is it okay to leave Wyper
with the Blue Sea people?
Don't worry.
It seems that Aisa made friends with them.
At any rate, we have to hurry.
It's pointless if our enemy wakes up.
Gather those who can move.
We'll banish the priests to the clouds.
Yeah!
Are you done with him?
Yeah. All he needs now is rest.
Yoo-hoo!!
Luffy!
Nami-san!! Conis-chan!!
Luffy!!
Everyone! I'm glad you are okay!!
I was so worried, but I couldn't do anything.
Conis-chan, so you were
worried about me that much!
I don't think so.
Is that food, you guys? Where'd you get it?
We found the priests' food storage on
our way back through the forest.
There were more.
But how did you get down from that height?
We used my Gum-Gum Balloon.
By the way, Conis, where's your old man?
Hm?
Well... um... he protected me...
...and then Eneru...
Don't tell me...
Conis-chan...
Conis-san...
Conis...
Hey, we're talking about you!!
I'm sorry I'm still alive!
Father!!
In the White Sea on the lower level?
Yes.
I found myself thereafter being knocked off.
Those who came down to the lower
level heading towards Cloud End
are also coming back to the White-White
Sea via restored Milky Roads right now.
However, since there's no Angel Island anymore,
they're heading towards Upper Yard.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, God!
I'm no longer known by that name.
You were all forced to work in a place
like this for six long years. I'm sorry.
We lost Angel Island, the home we
were supposed to return to.
The Shandians, too, lost their home,
Village Hidden in the Clouds.
Is the battle really over?
God's army is gone, but...
Chief, is the 400-year rift something
that can be filled so easily?
Boy, I stuffed myself!
It's totally night now.
Shall we go back to the ship now?
Nami, what're you saying?!
Huh?! If we go back to the ship,
we can have a long relaxed
sleep in a warm bed, right?!
Hey Usopp, you heard what she said?
Yeah, it's terrible.
Not thinking anything after seeing that,
you're unqualified to be a pirate...
no, to be a human!
"That"? What're you talking about?!
What the heck are you talking about?!
I'm returning... to where God should be...
Things that obstruct my field of
vision cannot exist in the sky.
You all were in my way.
I won't let anyone have it.
It's fit just for me.
It's a boundless land, just like a dream.
Now, let's set off, Maxim...
To God's world that floats brightly in the night...
To the land without end, the Endless Vearth!!
Where am I?
Inside the ruins of Shandora.
Gan Fall!
Oh, you shouldn't move yet.
You... are a Skypiean!
Rest.
Chief! Were we captured by the Skypieans?
There's no distinction among those injured in battle.
The golden belfry...
We still have the duty to protect it to the end!
This is...
...the sound of drums announcing a battle!
There's fire on the ruins, too?!
Don't rush, Wyper.
Wait a little and see how things turn out.
No matter what kind of heroic reason for
the fight there was in the distant past,
to us who live in the present time,
this sky is our home.
The land, at least, is not refusing anyone.
But at this very moment, there's actually...
Right... Go ahead and check
it with your own eyes.
Right now, no one wants to fight.
It's party time!!
Samishii nara koe o kikasete
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
Samayoinagara sora o mitsumeteru
You gaze at the heavens as you wander about
Tsuki no you ni matataku koto mo wasure
Just like the moon, you keep your gaze constant
Shizuka ni kie fukaku utsurikomi kaketeku
And your deep reflection wanes as you slowly disappear
Kono mama kawarazu sono kotonoha ni nosete
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Yume o mite ikusen no yoru ni
Dream, you travelers
Tada nagareru tabibito-tachi yo
who spend countless nights drifting
Tatoe modorenakute...
Even if you may not be able to go back
sore demo mata ayumu deshou
you will surely start moving forward again
Hold our true motive in your hearts and speak not of it.
Where did you learn those words?!
So these are the words engraved on the belfry...
The ancient weapon Poseidon?
Why was Gold Roger...?
Could the Rio Poneglyph be...?!
We're pirates, you know.
Now, let's snatch the gold and run!!
Next time, on One Piece:
I Made It Here!
The Yarn the Poneglyphs Spin
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
I Made It Here!
The Yarn the Poneglyphs Spin