Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Have a safe trip...
my stupid son...
Goodbye Drum Island!
I'm Going Out to Sea!
Whoa!
It's beautiful...
Yeah...
Cherry blossoms, huh?
Hey... is Chopper okay?
Let's leave him alone for now.
He's experiencing what it's like
to set out on a journey as a man.
Yeah, he is about to leave the
island he's spent his entire life in.
Yeah...
I'm leaving, Doctor... Doctorine...
My adventure... is finally starting.
This is a joyous day!
The moon is out and the
cherry blossoms have bloomed.
Chopper! Hey, Chopper!
You son of a gun!
How long are you gonna be in a daze like that?
Drink!
What?
Come here and sing!
Here, stick these chopsticks up your nose!
What?
Really, what a grand nighttime
view of cherry blossoms...
How could we not have a
party at a time like this?!
Are you surprised?
You made friends with
some really crazy guys, huh?
Friends...
That's right. They're over the top,
but since you're one of us now,
you'll have to get used to it.
Karoo!
What were you doing frozen in the river?
He probably slipped or something.
He's a clumsy one!
Quiet, Mr. Bushido!
Yeah... yeah...
He says that the guy named Zoro was
swimming in the river and disappeared.
He thought Zoro was in trouble so he
jumped into the river and got frozen.
So it was your fault!
Ow...
Tony-kun, you can understand
what Karoo is saying?
Yes. I'm an animal by nature,
so I can talk with animals.
You can talk with animals?
That's incredible, Chopper!
To be able to do that along
with your medical skills!
Dummy! Praising me like that wouldn't
make me feel happy! You jerk!
He sure looks happy.
By the way, Nami, what do
you mean by "medical skills"?
Chopper is a doctor... a first-class one
with all the medical skills
hammered into him by Dr. Kureha.
What?!
Chopper! You're a doctor?!
Incredible!
No way!
Good Lord! What did you think Chopper
was when you asked him to join us?!
A seven-form transforming interesting reindeer.
Emergency food.
What?!
Ah...! Darn it! I forgot to bring my
medical tools since I left in a hurry!
Can't be... Then what is this?
What?
My bag!
It was in the sleigh.
How come...?
How come?
Didn't you prepare for the trip by yourself?
Ah...
After all... she knew
everything you were thinking...
What a wonderful person she is...
– Ah! I got snot on the chopsticks!
– Yeah...
Hey, Chopper, you try it too!
Geez... When you're reminiscing...
Right, Chopper?
Chopper?
Don't!
Okay... guys!
Attention!
– You bastard!
– Well, I'd like to introduce
our new friend to you!
– Sanji! Go!
– Tony Tony Chopper!
– He'll be our ship's doctor.
– I...
To celebrate his coming on board...
Hey! Listen to me, you jerks!
I...
I've never had this much fun before.
Yeah!
Let's toast to our new friend!
Cheers!
I wonder if they've left the island by now.
A reindeer with a first-rate heart
and first-rate skills as a doctor...
If the cherry blossoms that Hiriluk put
his life into really did lead to a miracle,
it'd have to be just that clumsy
reindeer going out to sea.
That kid... acting like he's all grown up...
He'll be a fine ship's doctor.
So, what're you gonna do from here on?
I was... working as the Captain
of the Security Guard under Wapol.
I will have to atone for that sin.
I was thinking about leaving this land
and entrusting this new country to the citizens...
Are you... going to do that then?
No... I've come to realize that
leaving isn't the only way of atoning.
This country is breaking the shackles of monarchy,
and a new country made by the
citizens' hands is about to be born.
There may be something I can do for
the birth of this country by staying.
I feel that that is indeed a way for me to atone.
Humph, you youngster...
You do have a heart to care for the country.
A heart to care for the country, huh...?
I once learned it from a girl who was only ten.
The Holy Land of Mary Geoise
Ahh... the World Summit?
Such a tiresome, worthless event.
It is, indeed.
I wonder if Drum Kingdom
will be okay like this...
The rift between the king
and citizens keeps growing...
Ah...
It's the king of Alabasta Kingdom...
It's Nefertari Cobra-sama!
So that's the king of Alabasta,
famed for his benevolence and wisdom.
Revolutionist Dragon...
This man's ideologies are dangerous.
It's very clear that he'll become a
big enemy to us, the World Government,
in 5-6 years and stand in our way.
Ahh... How ridiculous.
That has nothing to do with my country.
I govern my country so that my people
won't be led astray by a revolutionist.
If you guys wanna capture him,
go ahead and do it on your own.
Wapol!
You're too selfish!
Have you no respect for this summit, Reverie?!
Act more responsibly!
Damn Nefertari Cobra!
Humph!
What an unpleasant conference that was.
Hm? That's...
That's the daughter of that detestable Cobra!
Oops! My hand slipped.
Wapol-sama!
Vivi-sama!
Oh, excuse me. If I'm not mistaken,
you're the princess of Lord Alabasta.
What a poor child, to be the
daughter of that hopeless king.
You bastard! What're you doing?!
Stop, Igaram! I'm fine!
I'm sorry, too, for bumping into you.
What a child!
In the Reverie, where kings gather,
even a minor argument can trigger a war.
She tolerates this situation knowing that?
Already at this young age...
Humph! What an annoying brat.
Let's go, Dalton.
Sorry.
It hurts!
You were magnificent, Vivi-sama.
The princess' heart to care for the country...
Her nobility hasn't changed one bit.
How magnificent she turned out to be...
Dalton-kun...
The heart to care for the
country still remains in us.
Let us do something...
to help this new country...
Hiriluk...
This country will surely be reborn...
just like your son, Chopper...
Dalton-san! This is serious!
I just remembered something serious!
What is it?
Look at this.
It's him!
The Straw Hat pirate who beat Wapol!
There's no doubt about it!
A thirty-million-berry bounty is
on his head... They are...?
Oh? They're quite the rogues, aren't they...
Where did you find this?
Well... I completely forgot
to report it to you, but...
about a week ago, a man who
appeared to be a traveler
suddenly appeared in Robelle Town.
It was an unusual day where no snow fell.
We don't know where he landed.
Anyway, this guy said that
he was after Blackbeard,
the pirate that attacked this country.
But once he realized that
Blackbeard was long gone, he said,
Then let me ask you one more question.
Has a pirate wearing a straw hat come here?
When we said we didn't know,
he showed the wanted poster and said,
If this guy comes here...
If he does...?
tell him that I'll wait for him
in Alabasta for just 10 days.
Okay?
Hey! Wait! What's your name?
Oh yeah... I forgot...
My name is Ace.
If you tell him that when he comes,
he'll know who I am.
Hey, please catch him!
He just ate and skipped on the bill!
Ahh! Well then, tell him, okay?
Thanks!
He'll wait for 10 days in Alabasta... huh...?
Hm? Dr. Kureha, what's the matter?
You look out of it.
Do you know Gol D. Roger?
D? Are you talking about Gold Roger?
Is that what he's called these days?
It looks like...
my reindeer went with an extraordinary guy...
So... the will of D... was still alive...
Amazing!
The sea is huge!
Of course! And the ones who go on
adventures on that huge sea are pirates.
I see! Pirates are incredible after all. Hm?
Huh?
Whoa! What's that?!
It's a seagull.
There isn't a seagull that big.
Hey! Seagull!
Ahhh! It's coming!
See? I was right. It is a seagull.
Now's not the time to discuss that!
It's coming because you called it!
Amazing! It's a great adventure!
Hey, where's Luffy?
Hm?
Yoo-hoo!
Hey! Don't become bird food!
Ahh! It's terrible! A bird ate Luffy!
This is no time for playing around!
Luffy's in trouble!
Did he say he wanted our help?
No, he didn't.
Then there's no problem.
Don't worry about it.
But...
Gum-Gum...!
Propeller!
Amazing...
Ahhh!
Hey, Sanji! I've got some meat! Huh?
What? Are you guys sleeping?
It's your fault!
How are you gonna fix this situation?
I had a good hand!
Really? Sorry.
Whoa! That's huge!
Now we can have some decent meals.
Is this edible?
Hm? What's the matter, Chopper?
Yeah...
Well... Pirates are...
Pirates are incredible after all!
Yeah? Incredible, huh?
Hey, you guys!
This ship is arriving at Alabasta soon.
We don't have time to play around!
Move it!
All right...
So, what's Alabasta?
It's the country that Vivi's father governs.
A rogue named Crocodile is trying
to take over Alabasta right now.
I hear that Crocodile is one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Seven Warlords of the Sea?
They're the pirates authorized
by the World Government.
Pirates are authorized by the Government?
Yeah. They're overwhelmingly strong.
And, they crush other pirates one by one.
So the Government authorizes
them to crush pirates.
Crocodile, huh...? I can't wait to see him.
Crocodile is a hero in Alabasta because
he crushes the pirates that attack towns.
But that's only his public face.
Behind the scenes, he is pulling strings
to cause a civil war in Alabasta...
in order to take over Alabasta...
No one has noticed it.
The citizens... My father... No one...
All right then! In any case, all we have
to do is beat up that Crocodile, right?
Yes. If we can first stop the
civil war and expel Baroque Works...
Baroque Works...?
Ahh... Yeah, you don't know
about them either, do you?
To be honest, I can't quite understand, either.
Baroque Works has a complicated system.
The system itself is simple.
First, at the top, there's a boss, Crocodile...
in other words, Mr. 0.
There're 12 agents and one animal who
receive orders from the boss directly.
Each of the 12 agents operates
separately as a pair with a female agent.
Mr. 1 and Miss Double Finger.
Mr. 2 doesn't have a partner, though.
Mr. 3 is the candle man we
met in Little Garden, right?
Yes.
He was paired up with Miss Golden Week.
Oh, that girl...
Mr. 4 is paired up with Miss Merry Christmas.
I don't know much about these two, either.
And that snot guy!
Mr. 5, right?
Snot?
Yeah. His snot is a bomb.
Mr. 5's entire body is a weapon.
Miss Valentine has the powers
of the Kilo-Kilo Fruit.
It's that woman who can
change her weight freely, right?
From Mr. 1 through Mr. 5,
they're called officer agents.
They all have the powers of a devil fruit.
And they work only on really important missions.
For Mr. 6 through Mr. 13, their job
is fund raising for the company
by leading the employees at
the entrance of the Grand Line.
Come to think of it, there was
a strange monkey and chicken.
They're Mr. 13 and Miss Friday.
They're a punishment squad.
Their main job is to punish those who fail missions.
Other than these people,
there're 200 subordinates called
"Billions" under the officer agents,
and 1800 subordinates called
"Millions" under the frontier agents.
This is the secret crime syndicate, Baroque Works.
That means... 1800 plus 200, so...
There're 2000 subordinates?!
2000!
All right! I understand it very well now!
In any case, all we have to do
is beat up that Crocodile, right?
I'm sure you don't get it at all!
If Baroque Works' last big job
is to take over Alabasta...
the rest of those "officer agents" will all
gather in Alabasta.
Yes...
I see... Then, in any case,
we'll beat that Crocodile guy...
That's enough.
You keep your mouth shut!
Oh, yeah?
Un, deux, ora! Un, deux, krah!
I-I'm sorry, Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
Gimme a break!
Who do you think I am?
I'm Bon Clay-sama,
a Baroque Works' officer agent,
who's so fearful that even a
crying child will become quiet.
Hey, you! You navigator, over there!
Y-Yes sir!
Just tell me! What's 0-chan's order?!
Kill Mr. 3 on the direct route
between Alabasta and Little Garden.
So you do know what it is.
Direct route means going in a straight line, right?
That's why we traveled straight from
Alabasta to this Little Garden, right?
But then, what's going on?!
We got to Little Garden without meeting Mr. 3!
Doesn't it mean that you
guys missed Mr. 3's ship?!
No... that can't be right...
Then are you saying that
it was because I'm stupid?
No... Mr. 2...
Shut up!
Anyway, we can't be failing in the
"beating puny Mr. 3 mission"
at an important time like this!
We can't afford to fail.
If we did, Mr. 1 and his
partner will come to kill me.
Do you get that?!
If you don't wanna be my prey,
then look for Mr. 3!
Super full speed!
We're heading to Alabasta on the Swanda!
Now listen!
Don't overlook even a single small ship!
Yes sir!
Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
What? Pirates are attacking towns in the Kingdom?
Don't they know this country has Crocodile?
Who knows... Sir Crocodile...
Maybe a country where riots are going
on is an easy target for pirates...
Are you going?
Sure. I have to do a good job
for my public position, too.
How kind of you...
Of course.
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
are pirates who crush other pirates.
We're heroes to people.
Nemuranai kono machi mo Ima dake wa madoromu
Even this sleepless town has dozed off for now
Kyou kara to kinou made
From today forth,
nani ka ga kawatte yuku
something's going to change
Kitto yarinaoseru hazu
I'm sure I can start fresh,
Datte hitori janai kara
since I'm not alone
Soba ni ite kureru dake de
Just by having you by my side,
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru
I feel I can become strong
Doko made ikeru kana
I wonder how far I can go,
mirai e tsuzuku basho
towards the place that leads to the future
Tooku de kagayaite sekai o tsutsumikomu
Off in the distance it shines, encompassing the world
Yoake mae
Before dawn
Hey, make something, you damn cook!
I can't because a certain idiot ate all the food.
What a useless cook...
Huh?! Looking for trouble, you bastard?!
Shut up, you two!
It's your fault!
Look! We can now see the island!
All right! We'll land then!
And eat! Oh, and Alabasta!
It's a side note?!
Next time, on One Piece:
Alabasta's Hero and
a Ballerina on the Ship
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Alabasta's Hero and
A Ballerina on the Ship