A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
Who are they?
Kicking Claw Force!
Those bruises...!
They drank the water that shortens their lives... the fatal fuel...
They only have a few minutes left to live...
If you're gonna die anyway, I don't
even have to kill you myself, right?
You wicked fiend...!
This is the very definition of stupidity.
Howling Fangs!
So you're the type...
who'd die for your country, too?
H-Hold it!
Koza-san!
The battle is over!
Everyone!
Subdue your anger and drop your weapon!
The Royal Army no longer has the will to fight!
Is that true...? Koza-san...?!
Yeah... the battle is now...
Koza!
Where Vivi's
Voice Gets Heard!
The Hero Descends!
Koza!
We're gonna make an awesome city
and make this kingdom even lusher!
For sure!
D... Don't fight... Rebel... Army...
Koza-san!
How dare you shoot Koza-san?!
Get them!
Baroque Works!
You...! Why'd you shoot Koza?!
Rebel Army... L-Listen to me...
Ahhh! What's going on?!
A sandstorm suddenly...!
Rebel Army...!
They started shooting at us!
Those bastards...!
What's with this dust devil?!
We can't see ahead!
Dammit! Those bastards...!
Don't shoot carelessly!
What's going on?!
Humph! There's nothing to wonder about,
since Baroque Works members infiltrated both armies.
No!
Hey! Hang in there!
Surrender, my ass...!
Launching a surprise attack
by raising the white flag...!
Is this how the Royal Army works?!
How dare they play dirty?!
Please! Stop, everyone! Don't fight!
Look! I'm here!
S... Stop... Rebel Army... This battle is...
Are you okay?!
Counterattack! Royal Army!
Stop...! Stop already...
Please... Stop... Stop...
You fought well, young lady...
But... your voice will no longer reach them...
So this is it...
Run, Vivi!
Get away from that man!
No.
This dust devil... is your doing, isn't it?
Not yet...
If I stop the attack that's
scheduled to happen in 15 minutes,
I can still reduce the number of casualties!
If we do this, the rebellion will stop.
If we do that, the rebellion will stop.
Wake up, Princess.
I can't stand how annoying
your idealistic theory is.
If you wanna talk about ideals,
you have to be able to make them real.
You're not qualified to do that!
I don't care if it's annoying.
I won't give up on my ideals, either!
You could never understand!
I'm the princess of this country.
I won't give in to someone like you!
You really have no charm...
I won't give up... I will...
I will... save this country...!
Vivi!
15 minutes until the Square is blown up.
More and more of the auxiliary
rebel forces will gather here...
One after another, all without realizing their own fate...
Had you let the Royal Army know earlier
about the explosion on the Square...
...even if there had been a panic,
you could've saved thousands
or tens of thousands of lives...
Stop! Please stop it, Crocodile!
In the end, your optimistic
ideas about saving everything
have resulted in the deaths of
all the citizens you love so much.
From start to finish, everyone
in this country... amused me.
You did a fine job of spying on our
company for the past two years...
It's me! Don't you recognize me?
I suppose I can't blame you.
I did lose some weight...
But when all is said and done,
you guys couldn't stop anything.
Stopping the rebellion...
Saving the kingdom...
Your worthless ideals...
only created more unnecessary victims...
Let me tell you something...
You can't save this country.
Goodbye, Princess...
It can't be...
Crocodile!!
Luffy-san!
Straw Hat...!
Just in time.
Luffy-san...! Pell...!
There isn't much time left
before the Square is blown up.
Everyone... is already down...
My voice... no longer reaches anyone...
At this rate, the country will...
Don't worry.
Your voice is heard by us.
Yes...!
Again, I'm saying that my injuries
are obviously worse than yours.
You're a man, so stop whining!
My leg is injured! I can't stand!
Ahh, I'm fainting. This is bad.
You're lying!
Be careful... Luffy-kun.
I ate lots of meat, so I got tons of blood!
I won't...
...lose again!
How did he get out of that
quicksand with those injuries...?
Luffy's alive!
Tony-kun!
Wh-Wh-What?! Luffy!
Vivi's here, too!
See?! See?! I told you! I knew it!
Really?
You don't look like someone who knew!
Usopp-san! Sanji-san!
Ahhh! What the hell, Vivi-chan?!
You're hurt so bad!
Usopp!
Nami-san... Mr. Bushido...
Everyone's alive...
Who asked you to create a prop for parties?!
Hey, you're standing!
Nami-san!
It... It did have a powerful attack, didn't it?
I'll deal with you later!
Vivi... So what's going on?
What's with this dust devil?
Yeah...
Hey, you jerk! Why is Nami-san injured?!
I'm gonna gut you!
She's just fine, isn't she...?
Ahh... Chopper, I have a favor to ask.
Will you bury my body in a wasteland?
He's already got fatal wounds!
Sorry, guys. I lost against him once...
So...
...I won't lose again!
I'll leave the rest to you!
Go already.
If you can't win...
...who can?!
I'm gonna put an end...
...to all this!
Yeah!
Everyone...
I still have... this many friends...
You bastard!
No matter how many times you try,
you can't even hit me.
Looks like you wanna be skewered again.
Gum-Gum...!
Who is that?!
Could he... possibly...?!
...Buzzsaw!
He hit Crocodile...!
Well, well...
Get up.
That time, the water that dropped on
your hand... the water I got in Yuba...
...taught me that you can't turn
into sand once you touch water.
You take rain away because
you're afraid of water, right?
Now I can beat you up.
Our fight starts now.
Doko ni mukatte hashireba
Which direction should I run towards
Motto suteki na ashita ni aeru?
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
Kaji o totte mune ni shimatta
I took the helm and opened the
Kiseki no chizu o hirogeta
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
Sora o mezashite yume o sagashite
I aimed for the sky and sought out my dreams,
Michi ni mayotta toki mo aru
though at times I got lost
Yume ja nakute kimi to deatte
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
Suteki na jibun o mitsuketa
I discovered the wonderful person in me
Chiisana yuuki kara
With just a bit of courage,
ookina mono te ni shita
I gained something grand
"Negai" o ima koso "chikai" ni kaete
Now's the time for my "wish" to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Mirai no monogatari o egakou
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
Atarashii kaze ni subete no omoi nosete ima...
I'll put all my feelings in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
Doko made mo oikakete Shining ray
I'll chase after you wherever you go, Shining ray
Crocodile! I'll beat you up this time!
Luffy! Don't lose against a guy like him!
Geez... You sure took your time getting here.
Okay, then! I'll leave the rest to you!
Hey! Don't run away!
We're gonna look for the cannoneer!
Is he nearby?!
There's no time left! This is the last chance!
Next time, on One Piece:
Sand Gator and Water Luffy!
The Second Round of the Duel
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Sand Gator and Water Luffy!
The Second Round of the Duel