Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
They've come all this way
after crossing Aqua Laguna.
When you think about it, it's incredible.
Seems like they've at least got good luck.
This time, we have permission to kill them.
It's easy when we don't have to
worry about going easy on them.
Drawbridge?
Yeah. The Franky Family is
currently fighting to bring it down.
Once it comes down, we can go
over to the other side at once.
Geez... When it's right in front of us...
CP9...
I thought I gave up everything...
I didn't want you to come to rescue me.
Why do you come after me?
"Everything Is for Her Friends!
Robin in the Darkness!"
I wanna talk about Nico Robin.
Do you know something?!
Did that woman change after
you guys came to this town?
Yes, suddenly.
After she went out to town,
she suddenly disappeared,
and by this morning, she was the
suspect of your attempted assassination.
When my friends finally found her,
she said she would no longer come back to us.
We didn't know what was going on.
So we came here tonight
in order to ask her directly again
why she's leaving the ship.
To make my wish come true...
A wish that can never come true if I'm with you!
What is this wish that can never
come true if she's with us...?
Let me tell you what I know.
It was probably when you lost sight
of Nico Robin the first time.
CP9...
The Government's operation
was already in progress.
There is, of course, a reason
for that woman's actions.
But before I tell you about that,
I want you to know that Nico
Robin and I both have a means
to bring back the ancient weapon
that could destroy the world.
Destroy the world?
That's right.
A problem occurred in our plan.
Everyone, come to the bedroom right away.
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
Now, you get it, Nico Robin?
The blueprints you guys were after are fakes.
Even if I am to be killed, I won't give
those blueprints to the Government!
But if you're sniffing around
the Poneglyphs on another front
and helping the Government as well,
then I have to stop you right here, right now.
I'm not seeking the Poneglyphs
in order to bring the weapon back.
I just want to know the history, that's all.
Such a claim doesn't mean anything!
I told you, didn't I?
Over... and over again...
Even if you don't intend to do so...
Weapons hurt people despite your intentions!
They can even hurt those
who mean a lot to you!
That which hurts people doesn't
necessarily have malicious intent.
If that simple curiosity of
wanting to know the history
leads to the destruction of the world,
you should die right here,
right now, Nico Robin!
Even after you saw the Ohara devils' fate,
you still want to chase
after the world's history?!
Don't talk like you know
everything about Ohara!
You don't even know how much the
World Government messed up my life!
If you hate the Government that much,
then why are you helping them?!
Because I have a wish I want to come true
even if I have to give up everything.
There're two conditions that
CP9 forced on me in this town.
One is to pin the assassination
on the Straw Hats.
The other is to turn myself in
to the Government and obey them.
If you do that, you'll die, too.
Why do you accept such conditions
after evading them for 20 years?
In this lone instance,
CP9 has been given permission
to exercise Buster Call against the Straw Hats.
Buster Call?
It's an emergency order to
summon five of the vice admirals
from Navy Headquarters and
ten battleships to one place.
Once you've been targeted by the
national war-class military power,
nothing will remain of you.
Normally, in the Navy, this authority
only belongs to the three admirals
and the head of the Navy, the fleet admiral.
But this time,
through the admiral Blue Pheasant,
CP9 was given the authority
to exercise it just this once.
If I didn't accept the conditions,
Buster Call was going to be exercised on us.
When I heard the name Blue Pheasant, I gave up.
I was always able to make good
my escape for the past 20 years
because I had nothing to protect...
Because I could betray people
and use them as a shield.
But I really can't do that any longer.
The life I once gave up on...
The heart that I lost...
The dream I could no longer have...
They picked them all up for me.
I was able to make friends who
would believe in someone like me.
Then, your wish is...
That the six Straw Hats, excluding me,
can leave this island safely!
Are you saying, for that, you don't
care if the weapon is brought back?!
You don't care what happens to the world?!
That's right, I don't!
Luffy!
What the hell are you doing there?!
N... Nami! Are you there behind me?!
Well, hey, listen!
At any rate, that pigeon guy sent me flying
and I flew right into this gap.
Don't fool around at a critical time like this!
While you've been taking your
sweet time, Robin was taken away!
Robin intends to die for us!
She sacrificed herself in order to protect
us from an attack by the Government!
When she knew that she was going
to be killed if she was taken in!
Then...
...after all, Robin was...
...lying?
Yes!
Good...
Whoooa! There it is!
This looks cool!
Amazing!
I'm warning you, this is a crazy train.
Its name is Rocketman.
We can't even allow passengers to be on board.
Okay! Well then, let's go, shall we?!
Now departing Water Seven for Enies Lobby...
Here comes the sea train Rocketman!
All right! Depart!
We're gonna go...! To get everything back!
Whoa! Cool!
A power strong enough to give me control
over any large country I might desire
is in my hands now!
Why did Blue Pheasant give you the
authority to exercise Buster Call?
Huh?
You're in no position to ask me
questions, you insolent woman!
If I hadn't recognized
the value of your existence,
it would've been practically worthless!
So you should appreciate me!
You, the repugnant kin of Ohara,
the land of devils...
Nico Robin...
Hurry!
Run to the evacuation ship!
--Put out the fire!
--Protect the books!
Revealing the history isn't
what Ohara was trying to do.
We just wanted to accept the voices
of the past and protect them.
No! I'll stay here, too! Mom!
Mom!
Live, Robin!
Listen carefully, Robin!
You're alone now, but you'll
meet friends someday for sure!
Friends?
Right. The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
--Monster!
Her mom abandoned her!
No one is born into this world to be alone!
You will understand someday.
They said that she's a survivor
of those Ohara devils
who planned the world's annihilation.
Don't let her get away!
Now, give me the money!
I reported her to you, right?!
Your sin is being alive!
Go meet the friends who're
surely waiting for you
somewhere at sea, Robin!
Sogeking.
Hm?
Shoot through that flag.
Roger.
Huh?
This is my new weapon,
a huge slingshot... named Kabuto!
Have a good look at its power!
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
Oh, no...!
Mission accomplished.
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
after making the entire world your enemy!
Bring it on!
Robin!
We still haven't heard you say it!
Say you want to live!
To live...
You shouldn't be allowed
to live in this world, Robin!
Your existence itself is a huge crime, Robin!
I thought it was something I dared not wish for.
No one ever let me wish for it.
The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
If... it's really okay for me
to utter my wish for once...
I...
I want to live!
Take me to the sea with you!
Let's go!
Come, Nico Robin!
I've got the assassin group CP9 on my side!
Cutty Flam...
Here we go!
I knew it!
"Straw Hat Theater"
"Part 5"
Rodusa is wearing sunglasses because
she's a monster known as the Gorgon
who turns people to stone
when they look her in the eyes.
But she didn't have eye contact with
anyone today for a different reason.
There you go again, monster!
Now, Dragon. Give me those mystical horns.
You're always shooting at me.
It hurts, you know!
You're a monster, too!
"Centaur
Usoppaka"
"Dragon
Lugyao"
If you've got time, why don't you fish?
Mystical fish live in this sea.
--I want the mystical horns, not mystical fish.
--This is a village called
Monston in a monster forest,
--Like I said, catch some fish.
--I'm gonna make bugle horns out of them.
--where monsters live free from care.
Hey, you have a bite.
Oh?
Ahh! I got tricked by the sweet bait!
"Kraken (Giant Octopus)
Choperken"
You again, Choperken?!
What're you doing on the sea floor?!
I'm looking for a mystical treasure
that's on the sea floor right now!
More importantly, give me
more of those sweet baits!
Hey, Choperken!
"Mermaid
Stronamie"
If you lay your hands on that
mystical treasure, you'll pay for it!
Huh? It's laying on the sea floor,
so first come, first served.
Oh? You've got some nerve.
You wanna compete with me?
--Scary!
--Hiya!
What idiot is troubling my love, Stronamie-san?!
"Water Imp
Sanzaler"
I'm gonna beat him up!
Hey, what're you doing?
Are you trying to catch me?
A mystical fish.
I'm not a fish! I'm a water imp.
More like a naughty monster who lives
in the sea despite being a water imp.
Give yourself up!
"Minotaur
Zoromilk"
What about you?! You're a minotaur,
and yet you're a Holstein!
Shut up. I'm gonna get that mystical
bowl on your head today for sure!
I'm not gonna let you have it.
It'll endanger my life.
More importantly, I heard that that
iron rod you have is a mystical thing.
Why don't you try and get it?
Shut up, you guys!
Mystical this, mystical that...
You guys are all mystical beasts!
Gasp!
But, you know, Rodusa.
You were crying the other day
saying that you lost your mystical earrings,
so we decided to give
something even rarer to you.
Hey, hey! Don't spill the beans!
What?!
The reason why she doesn't
look in everyone's eyes
is in order to hide her happiness,
embarrassment, and tears.
Everyone...
...thank you!
Stone...!
--This is Monston,
a village of carefree monsters.
--Why...?
Robin! Sorry to have kept you waiting!
I'm coming for you now!
Th-The pirates are coming here!
We have to go to the Gates of Justice now!
Franky?
Cutty Flam...
Don't tell me... What you have in your hand is...
H-Hand those blueprints over to me!
Next time, on One Piece:
"'I Wont Hand over the Blueprints!'
Franky's Decision"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!