Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace, who will be executed!
He and the Whitebeards have invaded the plaza to make it to the scaffold!
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught, with the Whitebeards' assistance,
Luffy ran on the path that Inazuma created
and finally made it to Ace!
I'm a remnant from the old times!
There is no ship that can carry me in this new era!
Let's get this over with!
The Power That Can Burn Even Fire
Red Hound's Ruthless Pursuit
Marineford is in danger!
Stop Whitebeard!
"Absolute Justice"
He's willing to destroy the whole island!
Pops!
I don't wanna leave you! You gotta come with us!
Do you disobey your Captain's order?!
Why don't you just go, fools?!
Pops!
Now is our chance!
Kill Whitebeard! He's dying already!
Pops!
Hurry up! Let's do as Pops said!
You don't mind leaving Pops behind?!
Yeah, how dare you!
Stupid! No one wants to leave him alone!
Then...
Grumbling about it at a time
like this is the same as trampling on Pops' determination!
Can't you understand?!
Pops!
Hurry and get ready to sail out!
Ace!
We're gonna leave soon! Come on now!
Commander Marco, let's go!
Pops...
You messed with us!
Die!
W-Wait! All I want is to get away!
I have no intention to fight...
W-What?!
My wax is as strong as steel!
There's no way that a normal sword can cut it!
He's also a Devil Fruit user!
No wonder!
He's strong enough to try to protect
Fire Fist even at Fleet Admiral Sengoku's elbow!
No no, don't overestimate me like that! I'm not a big deal...
Oh no!
Damn Whitebeard!
I can't believe he still has that much power
after getting wounded so badly!
Since he isn't concerned
about Fire Fist Ace anymore...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
It's clear his intention is to sink Marineford into the ocean.
Along with himself!
Vice Admiral Garp! You're alive!
He wants to end this era? Yeah, the time is right.
What happened to Whitebeard?!
Were his allies defeated after he sold them out?!
Is the connection still out?!
How long should we wait?!
Damn! We couldn't see the whole picture
because Buggy the Clown stood in our way!
The guy over there must be...!
The great pirate—Captain Buggy the Clown?!
Yes, that's who I am indeed!
What did he want to say?!
If nothing is done, I can't report anything to the head office!
What's going on at Marineford now?!
What?!
The Transponder Snail hasn't come out yet?!
Damn! Captain Buggy is about to
beat Whitebeard—it's no time for this!
Don't say it as if it's so easy!
He's dying but he still has
boundless power—didn't they see it?!
Why did I even say that I'm gonna beat that man?! I really screwed this up!
I can't do it! It's impossible!
What?! We gotta broadcast Captain Buggy's
big moment all over the world!
Get it out at any cost!
Come out now!
Or we're gonna burn you out of it!
No, we gotta soak it into water!
Let's do that!
Come on!
Stop it, fools!
Huh?
It's not like he volunteered to be a slave for the Navy.
But he got beaten up in the battlefield like this.
Don't you feel sorry for him?
Just let him go, okay?
Then we gotta cancel
"Captain Buggy's beating Whitebeard
and broadcast it live to the world" plan?!
No way! Even you want to pull out from Marineford?!
I'm disappointed in you, Captain Buggy!
Oh no!
When it comes down to it,
they're all strong guys
who've been locked up in Impel Down!
I better not make enemies of them!
The Transponder Snail came out voluntarily!
Oh, he's...
...crying!
Oh yeah! He came out because he was touched
by Captain Buggy's kindness!
Captain Buggy can even win the hearts of the Snails!
He's amazing as we thought!
That is the man who will conquer the world—he's our Captain Buggy!
D-Damn bastard! Why didn't he just stay inside?!
Now there's no way that I can back out!
Alright, let's begin!
Captain Buggy, make a declaration to conquer the world now!
It's your moment!
Smoke: good, lighting: good!
Stand by!
Oh no, I mean... Dammit! This leaves me one choice!
Alright, shoot my bravery!
Capture the moment that I kill Whitebeard!
Hey, look!
The picture's back!
But I can't see what's going on
because of the smoke!
Is the Navy losing?!
What happened to Whitebeard and Ace?!
Um, well...
Transponder Snail, go lower!
Hi, everyone! I'm Buggy and I'm a legend!
You again?!
Get to the sea now!
Those remaining have to get back
to the New World safely!
Don't let them get away! Kill as many as you can!
I'm the only one that you ought to worry about!
Commander Jozu!
Looks like he's badly injured but he'll make it!
Captain gave us an order! Come with us!
Brenheim! You gotta carry Jozu!
Straw-boy! Why are you standing around?!
Ace, let's go! The old man has made up his mind...
I know! And it won't be in vain!
Back off, you bastards!
We don't need words now.
Just tell me one thing.
Were you happy to have me as your father?
Still some fight left in you?
You are too valuable to let die now, boy.
If you still wanna run wild, run as wild as you want on the sea under my name.
Become my son!
Of course!
Wh-What was that?!
The scaffold was destroyed!
So was Navy HQ!
Did Ace get executed?! What's going on?!
Move the camera to Whitebeard!
I'm Buggy and I'm a legend!
The great pirate—Captain Buggy the Clown!
Is it true that you're gonna beat Whitebeard?!
And with his head in your hand,
you're willing to become one of the Four Emperors?!
I'm Buggy and I'm a legend!
You're just repeating that!
Say something forward-looking! Let's do it again!
Enough with Buggy already!
Show us what's going on in Marineford!
Oh yeah!
You're not what we're interested in!
No, I mean... I just wanna do something flashy...
What are you doing?!
Run! Run to the ship!
Ace-san, Luffy-kun, get in front of me!
Jinbe!
They want to get you two!
But what the old chap wants
is as many survivors as possible!
Old man!
We've stolen a Navy ship! Get on board quick!
Do they really think that they can get away?!
How simple they are!
Admiral Sakazuki!
You guys, move aside a little bit!
You two, just keep going until you get to the ship!
As soon as you rescue Fire Fist Ace,
you start running!
The Whitebeards must be a group of cowards!
What?!
He's obviously trying to provoke you!
If you stop, you're playing right into his hands!
Well your captain is that kind of guy
so you can't help it, can you?
Because after all, Whitebeard is just...
... a loser from a bygone era!
Ace!
A loser?
Take back what you just said!
Hey, don't, Ace! Don't stop!
Just let him say whatever he wants!
He mocked Pops!
Ace!
Did you say "take it back?"
Not in a million years! I'll tell you why.
Your father Gold Roger conquered the Grand Line
and opened the door to the new era called
the Great Pirate Era by sacrificing himself.
As a Navy admiral, it's not my place to say so,
but he was true to his name: the Pirate King!
In contrast, what has Whitebeard done?
I wonder if he really had the intention to fight.
I assume that he established a large family someplace
and was satisfied being a big fish in a little barrel.
There are some fools in this world
who'd say that his name
is keeping peace on various islands
but if you ask me,
he's just intimidating small-fry
and thinks that makes him a hero. Ridiculous!
When Roger was alive, Whitebeard had second billing
and even after Roger's death, he couldn't become King.
That means he'll never surpass Roger.
He'll be a loser forever!
That's who Whitebeard is and that's the truth.
He's a poor man when you think about it.
He gathered some punks who call him Pops
and roamed the sea with his fake family.
Stop it.
Although he reigned over the sea for decades,
he couldn't become the King and attained nothing.
In the end, he was stabbed by a fool—
one of his own sons—who fell for my lie
and he will die to protect that foolish son.
Don't you think that's an empty existence?
Stop it!
Don't do it, Ace, come back!
Ace!
Pops gave us a place to live!
You can't understand his greatness!
People don't deserve to live if they can't live justly!
Punks like you guys don't deserve a place to live!
Stop it!
Whitebeard will die as a loser!
It's fitting for a big fish in a little barrel!
Whitebeard is a great pirate who shaped this era!
Don't make fun of the man who saved me!
Don't do it, Ace!
The name of this era should be "Whitebeard!"
Both Whitebeard and you guys who call him Pops
are the same after all—losers!
Ace has been burned!
Are you careless because you ate a Logia type fruit which
is the most powerful of all?
You're just fire but my magma can even burn fire!
My power is far stronger than yours.
Ace!
Hey, Luffy-kun, you shouldn't fight anymore!
Ace's Vivre Card!
Gold Roger the Pirate King. Dragon the Revolutionary.
I was surprised to hear that
the sons of those two are stepbrothers.
You two have filthy blood running through your veins.
I don't care if the others get away
as long as I can get the two of you!
Watch closely.
Wait!
Luffy!
This is certainly a Vivre Card.
But I haven't told you that this card
also tells you how much vital energy the owner has.
This card belongs to someone who you care for, right?
Yeah, it's my brother's!
Hold onto it, always.
That paper will lead us to one another.
Ace is pierced by Red Hound's fist
while protecting Luffy.
Jinbe and the Whitebeard Pirates try to save him,
but Ace, realizing he is about to die,
finds the voice to convey his feelings
to his friends one last time.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Looking for the Answer
Fire Fist Ace Dies on the Battlefield"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Looking for the Answer
Fire Fist Ace Dies on the Battlefield