Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hody's merciless plot puts Fishman Island in unprecedented danger!
Everything will come to an end soon.
Whether it's Shirahoshi or Fishman Island or your friends!
A fool like you can't protect anything!
No.
I'll protect them all!
That's what I worked for those 2 years!
"A Massive Confused Fight! The Straw Hats vs. The New Fishman Pirates!"
Protect them all? Don't make me laugh!
You've got such a big mouth, haven't you, Straw Hat?
I can't believe he'd even harm Decken!
Shirahoshi! Get away!
Draw the Noah away from the island!
It's too late.
What did he mean by "too late"?
Wait a minute!
He just beat Decken, right?
What would happen to the Noah if Decken dies or loses consciousness?
Decken's power would become ineffective!
And the Noah would fall...
...onto the island!
Why did you kick me?! It hurts!
Shut up or I'll kick your fat ass again!
Even Captain Decken wouldn't kick me for no reason at all!
You damn Steamed Bun bastard! How dare you...
...bring Nami-san down with the wind blast!
This is my payback to you!
--This is for... --Huh?
...the wind blast that Nami-san took!
Ouch!
Oh no!
Watch out for the wind blast, Nami-san!
A wind blast, again?! Please!
Keep your guard up! Look out!
Something came out from that stick earlier!
Black Ball!
--What is it this time?! --Is she a magician?
No, don't call me a magician!
Call me a charmer!
Although it's not really a charm. It's based on science!
Clouds?
Storm Cloud Rod!
Ouch!
Help me!
Stay away! I don't wanna become a dried squid-ch!
--Damn that woman! --Hey, Ikaros.
That guy in the black suit was overreacting because that woman got hurt.
I think that woman may be the Straw Hat's weak link.
Really?
I'll hold her legs and you kill her with your spear!
I got it-much!
Well, if you don't wanna get burned, leave me alone!
What?
I can't move my feet!
You're gonna become a dried squid-ch!
W-W-Wait a minute!
Why can't I move my feet?! Somebody!
Nami-san! Oh yeah!
Take this! The Squid Spear!
Could I look at your panties...
No!
Is he on their side?
Why don't you dry up? Become a dried squid-ch!
Huh?
Hm? What's wrong-ch?
Suck all the fluid out of his body and dry him up-ch!
Hey, Squid! What's up?
What's wrong? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Why?!
Excuse me.
I'm pretty dried up already.
What?!
I don't believe you-ch!
It's a long story. How I became a dried-up skeleton.
--No, believe me. It was over 50 years ago... --Help me!
Hey hey, isn't there anybody who is strong enough to fight?!
Huh?
Are you all right?
Who are you-ch?!
It's me!
--I don't know you-ch! --What?! You don't know this super robot?!
Hm? You must be one of their officers, huh?
Then I bet you have backbone.
Though I'm a squid, I'm still a Fishman! I have backbone!
Oh, he has a backbone even though he's a squid!
Sympathy!
That's not what he meant.
Hey, Skeleton, get out of there already.
Huh? Why?
Your foot! Your foot!
What about my foot?
You're stepping on him!
Huh? What is he?! I couldn't move because of him?!
Um... Who are you?
How did you like it?!
What?
Getting a head-butt to the bottom of your foot!
--What? --Huh?
It may take some time for you to feel the pain!
What?!
He doesn't wanna admit that he got stepped on!
Sorry that I stepped on your face!
Don't say that!
This technique allows me to give you a head-butt to the bottom of your foot!
It's called Super Sole Head-Butt!
He named it!
Where did you go, Coral Head?! I'll bite you good!
No one can beat me in the ground. I can move freely!
Daruma-san!
Don't make too many tunnels in the ground!
We're all gonna fall into them!
Yes!
Chopper! Did you finish it?
Come out this way!
What a fool! That guy is off his guard-dogon!
I'm gonna beat him up!
Hey, Chopper? Can't he hear me?
Get squashed and go to hell-zugan!
Usopp! Get down!
Horn Cannon Elf!
Nice, Chopper! Did you connect all the tunnels?
Yes, it's nice and ready!
All right! Here we go!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Explosive Skull Grass!
How did you like that?!
We fought a ground digger once in Alabasta already!
Our experience gave us the upper hand!
Yeah!
Damn you coral monster!
Is this all your doing?
I'll show you my extraordinary power!
Speaking of power, I have one up my sleeve, too.
I'm gonna bite your nose off!
Try it if you like!
Back me up, Chopper!
Hey, back me up!
Oh?
Chopper?
Now, it's my turn!
Damn you! You made me angry!
I won't forgive you even if you say sorry!
I'm gonna beat you up!
Great! That's how a swordsman should be!
You're strong!
--Help me... --Are you okay? I'll treat you right away!
--Honey, stay with me! --Daddy!
Treat him now!
Damn Hody! He can't do this to unarmed citizens!
Is the Princess okay?
I don't know...
But I'm sure she's still fighting for us!
Madame Sharley!
What's gonna happen to the island?! Is it really gonna fall?!
That Straw Hat pirate guy will save the island, won't he?
Won't he, Madame Sharley?!
--Let's pray. --What?
All we can do now is pray for the safety of the Princess and the others.
Pray that they will save Fishman Island!
Go further! More!
She's desperate!
Stay away from the island!
Noah!
Shirahoshi!
If the Noah falls, everything will be destroyed!
--Oh no! She couldn't hear us! --Don't go up!
Turn to the side! You have to change your course!
They noticed!
Shirahoshi!
Shark Slicer!
Brother!
Ryuboshi!
Don't mess with my plan!
Brother! Stay with me!
Decken's power must have become ineffective by now.
That's why I stabbed him.
I see!
If she just keeps going up, the ship could fall onto the island!
Then, Wimpyhoshi's effort to draw the ship away means nothing!
Brother-hoshi, let's catch up with Wimpyhoshi!
Alright!
Shirahoshi!
Wimpyhoshi!
You can't go any further!
Fishman Island will be destroyed along with all the islanders!
And Straw Hat,
I'll make sure that all of your friends are dead!
Are you all right?
Shirahoshi!
Turn to the side!
Wimpyhoshi!
Stupid Mermaid!
That little shit!
--She heard you! --She turned to the side!
How annoying!
You can't do that!
Wait!
Let go of me!
I won't let you go after her!
Damn you!
Noah! Come this way!
I can't hold on...
Noah! Come after me!
--Let's go! --Yeah!
Damn you, Decken! Drop dead already!
Dammit.
Hody that bastard, I won't forgive him!
Noah! I'm right here!
The ship's starting to go sideways!
Good! Keep going, Wimpyhoshi!
Shirahoshi!
Keep going!
I touched Hody with my left hand.
You're my target! Don't forget it!
I'll drive you into the ground physically and mentally, until you die!
Noah!
Shirahoshi! Keep going - a little bit more!
There is no point if it doesn't fall onto the island!
I'll hunt you down... to the ends of hell!
I won't let you go!
Hody!
A little more to go, Wimpyhoshi!
Decken!
I will... kill you!
I'll pass through by force!
You can't!
My axe! Hit Hody!
Shark Slicer!
I will protect!
The Noah is falling!
Just in time!
Fishman Island...
...is in danger!
No!
I win!
The Noah begins to fall again,
and Luffy tries to stop it to save Fishman Island,
but underwater, he's at a disadvantage as he battles Hody,
and can't get the upper hand.
Furthermore, the last air on the Noah's deck is lost,
making Luffy's demise eminent!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Luffy Loses the Fight?! Hody's Long-Awaited Revenge!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!