Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace, who was to be executed!
Luffy finally freed Ace!
However, Admiral Red Hound landed a fatal blow against Ace
and Ace died in Luffy's arms!
The man Roger is waiting for...
...is definitely not you, Teach!
Forgive me, my sons.
I raised such a ridiculous fool.
You guys gave me everything.
I owe you everything.
Farewell, my sons!
The Show Begins
Blackbeard's Plot is Revealed
Head Office! Head Office!
There's big news out of Marineford!
Is that true?!
Is Whitebeard really...?! Are you sure?!
I can't believe that Whitebeard is...!
The news spread around the world like wildfire!
"The Whitebeards failed to rescue Roger's son Ace!"
"And their legendary captain, Whitebeard, is dead."
Extra! Get ready to issue an extra!
Breaking news!
Following Fire Fist Ace, we have confirmed the death of Whitebeard! I repeat:
At Marineford, Whitebeard...
Whitebeard is...
...Dead!
Then this is it for the Whitebeard Pirates!
The war will be over soon!
We can finally live in peace!
People who, with their own eyes,
witnessed this historic event being reported...
...stand transfixed, words frozen on their lips.
So Whitebeard's gone now...
He was 72 years old.
The man who once rivaled the Pirate King.
Captain of the Whitebeard Pirates.
The great pirate—Edward Newgate...
...also known as Whitebeard.
He fell in the decisive war
at Marineford bay...
...between the Whitebeard Pirates and Navy HQ,
backed by the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
This is great!
Things are really gonna change now.
No doubt about it.
But first,
I don't think things will settle down that easily!
With the most heinous criminals and the jail manager of Impel Down,
I wonder what Blackbeard is up to.
What's gonna happen?
Is this really the end of the war?
Also, the thing Whitebeard said
before he died...
The One Piece...
...is real!!
It's only a matter of time before the world finds out!
I wonder how the pirates will react!
But even before that,
can we say this war is really over?
Why did Blackbeard come to Marineford?
That bastard!
Marco! Everyone feels the same!
But you better hold your tongue for now!
I know, Vista!
Hurry up and get on the ship!
Don't you remember our captain's last order?
Ace!
Pops!
Jinbe! Bring Ace's brother, hurry!
Okay!
Ace-san! Old chap!
I couldn't do anything to help you two!
I want to help Luffy-kun at least!
Don't let the pirates get away!
Kill them all!
Captain Buggy, where're you going?!
Are you stupid?! I'm getting out of here!
I can't kill Whitebear—he's already dead!
Captain Buggy!
I couldn't do it!
Black Hole!
Captain Buggy, now is your chance!
Hurry and kill Whitebeard!
I know that you can make it over the crack!
Stop telling me what to do!
It wouldn't be smart to just jump him!
I'm waiting for the right time!
They're talking like it's easy!
Vortex!
You can't create earthquakes anymore!
I see! Captain Buggy knew this would happen
and waited for this moment!
Let us help you!
Oh no, wait...
Here you go, Captain Buggy!
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait a minute, guys!
Ouch! Damn!
I-Is that what a dying old man is capable of?!
N-No! That's what makes him
the legendary Whitebeard!
I was too scared and couldn't even approach him!
Whitebeard was scary!
That old monster is scary, even when he's dead!
I don't care if you think I'm hopeless!
I say goodbye to you fools!
Captain Buggy!
He's crying... Captain Buggy...
I know why!
"Yesterday's enemy could be today's friend!"
Somewhere along the way he felt pity
for his rival, Whitebeard, as a fellow man!
He could've killed him!
And yet he's leaving
without trying to make excuses!
Son of a gun! He showed us something
more important than killing Whitebeard!
I can't believe that he chose to have pity on him instead of all the fame it would've brought him!
Just as we thought, he truly is a man among men!
You're way too cool, Captain Buggy!
Wait, Captain Buggy!
Let us come with you!
Captain!
He was so tenacious!
It's good to see him finally drop dead!
It's going as we planned so far.
Now's the time, Captain.
Alright, let's begin!
They're up to something again!
Teach, that bastard!
What is he gonna do to Pops now?!
I'm gonna put on a show!
It's a show that will shake the whole world!
What is that black cloth?!
Blackbeard got under it
with the body of Whitebeard!
Now, please don't trespass for a while!
What do you think you're doing?!
He deceived us by joining
the Warlords only to end up betraying us!
Stay alert!
I can't wait!
Are we gonna disband if we fail?
Hurry up! To the sea!
Luffy-kun!
Stay with me!
You have to carry on in this world where Ace-san no longer lives...
...tomorrow and the day after!
Fire!
You have to live strong!
Jinbe, if I don't escape death...
I'm sorry but could you look after my brother?
I might have to refuse that request, Ace-san.
You mustn't overestimate me.
I'm not as good-natured as you think.
Even if he's your brother, we're in a pirates' world.
I only assist or protect
the ones that I hold in high regard!
Even now, my feelings
haven't changed at all, Ace-san!
I'm not helping him because he's your brother!
I think highly of Luffy-kun! That is all...!
Hurry up, Jinbe! Luffy needs treatment posthaste!
Pacifista! Kill Straw Hat!
Even though he's a Warlord, Jinbe is our enemy now!
We're allowed to kill him!
Perfume Femur!
Boa Hancock! Are you gonna stand in our way again?!
Fire Fist Ace and Whitebeard are dead already!
I don't like persistent men!
Jinbe! Please take good care of Luffy!
Jinbe! Get on this ship!
Okay!
What's this?!
Damn! He froze the sea!
We can't leave!
Hurry up and do something!
It's Admiral Blue Pheasant!
Stop Blue Pheasant!
I have no choice! I'll look for another way!
When I say that I won't let you get away,
you should give up on your life, you fool!
Hand Dragon's son over to me!
Red Hound! He didn't die?!
I thought he was beaten by Pops?!
He traveled underground...
...By making a path with lava!
Jinbe!
I cannot do that!
Because I've already made up my mind...
...to save his life even if it means my death!
Alright then, I won't ask you again!
Coby! Red Hound-san wants to kill Straw Hat at any cost!
Once he has you in his sights, you can't escape him!
Luffy-san...
We're gonna protect Ace's brother!
That's what Pops wanted!
Yeah! Ace's family is our family, too!
"Family"? Don't be ridiculous!
You guys just left Fire Fist Ace
and your "father" Whitebeard to their fate and ran!
What did you say?!
Take this!
I-It doesn't work at all!
Outta my way, you cowards!
Move aside, Jinbe!
Emporio Face Growth Synthesis!
Iva-san, let me assist you!
Great Scissors!
Keep your hands off of Straw-boy!
I'll kill Dragon's son for sure!
Hell...
...Wink!
Ever since Impel Down,
Straw-boy has been pushing himself...
...physically and mentally.
He's long surpassed his limit!
If I were to let something happen to him,
I would never be able to face...
...my comrade, Dragon, for the rest of my life!
I agree!
I have no time to play with you guys right now!
So back off, you two!
Bring it on!
I'm burning way hotter than you right now!
Looks like he's all set now!
Let me see it already, Captain!
Alright, everybody, thank you for waiting!
It's the greatest show in the world
presented by Captain Teach of the Blackbeard Pirates!
Please enjoy it!
B-Blackbeard!
What was he doing in there?!
Nothing's changed on Whitebeard's body!
And neither has Blackbeard's!
Navy!
I'll show you what I'm capable of.
Now that we face each other as enemies once again!
Black Hole!
What's going on?!
That's my Dark-Dark Fruit power!
And now...
...this is...!
That pose is...!
That's...
...the power of the Tremor-Tremor Fruit!
It's the power of the dead Whitebeard!
But how is he able to use it?!
You did it, Captain!
We're not gonna disband then?
It looks like I made the right choice
teaming up with these guys!
Pops' tremor power?!
What did he do, that bastard Teach!
The gravity of darkness
that returns everything to nothingness!
And the power of tremor that destroys everything!
I've obtained them both at last!
Nobody's a match for me now!
I'm the strongest man in the world!
I don't know how he did it but...
he acquired Whitebeard's power!
How is that possible?!
That means we still have to fear
the power of the Tremor-Tremor Fruit?!
I thought it was impossible
to have two Devil Fruit powers at the same time?!
It's impossible for the average person,
that's for sure.
But Teach is a little different, as you guys know.
His body is fundamentally different compared to ordinary people.
That's why he was able to do it!
Hey, did you guys see that?!
Tell all the people in the world! The boring people who love peace,
Navy soldiers, the World Government, and pirates!
This has to be a nightmare!
The future of this world has been determined!
Yes, as of today...
my era begins!
I thought the Navy had won now that Whitebeard is dead!
I can't believe that he has two Devil Fruit powers!
Who the hell is Blackbeard?!
I thought the war would be over soon!
Then why is this happening?! Hey, Coby!
Even though Luffy-san's brother
and Whitebeard died, this war is still not over?!
Blackbeard freely uses the power
he stole from Whitebeard to wreak havoc.
Meanwhile, Red Hound and the rest of the Navy
chase down the pirates in the name of justice.
The battle shows no sign of dying down,
but only increases in intensity!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Insatiable Red Hound! Lava Fists Pummel Luffy"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Insatiable Red Hound!
Lava Fists Pummel Luffy