We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for... ONE PIECE
Compasses and stuff'll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Blast through the stingy night!
We've no interest in treasure chests
Pockets bulging with dreams, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
Hey, Zoro!
Robin!
Sanji!
Their bodies are vanishing!
Why?! Didn't we win?
Dang it! Were we too late?
Phew! I'm very much alive.
For a second, I thought I
was about to go to Heaven.
Sounds good to me! If we can go together,
I'd love to go to Heaven!
This isn't funny, you jerks!
We seriously thought you were dead.
You nearly vanished!
Oh, yeah! I forgot about something important!
What is it?
I had totally forgotten about him...
What's the matter?
We've got a problem!
There he is...
You understand what I'm saying, don't you?
The World Government is
assigning you a special mission:
Annihilate everyone on the island,
including the Straw Hat Crew.
That will be easy.
His hands... are dangerous!
Guys, get him!
Yeah, you heard them!
Let's get him!
Stop, men! You don't stand a chance!
Pirate Hunter Zoro...
I will start with you.
It Repels Everything
Kuma's Paw-Paw Power
Hey! Stay with me!
Are you gonna make it?
What did that scumbag do?!
He didn't even touch the guys
to pierce them with something!
Is that his ability?
This is beyond cruel!
After many long years under
Moria's reign in the dark forest,
we only get a moment of happiness
before another Warlord appears
and declares that we must die!
That's low, dagnabbit!
You know good and well that the
Straw Hats just finished a fierce battle!
You might be too much for us,
but we have the energy to take you on!
I don't care if you're a Warlord!
Compared to Oars and Moria,
you don't look so big!
Shut up and get back.
He asked for me. Didn't you hear him?
I'll accept the challenge.
I don't need backup.
Don't make me look bad!
You and your crewmates have
earned quite the reputation.
It's said that Straw Hat Luffy has
several skilled subordinates on his ship.
Well, well, well! But it's true, it's true!
This is no time for all
of you to act flattered!
You have stirred up trouble
in various places.
Your captain was not the only one
to make a name for himself over time.
Hey, Zoro! Wait! This is totally nuts!
You're battered and bruised
clear to the bone!
The world is designed so that
when it rains trouble, it pours.
If I start making excuses,
will someone come rescue us?
If I die, then that shows
the limit of my ability!
Two-Sword Style...
...Draw...
...Castle Gate!
What was that?!
Look! He hasn't even done anything
and Zoro's breathing heavy!
What is that guy's ability?!
What's with the mark he
keeps leaving in the debris?
Look at the palm of his hand!
A-A paw?!
What is that doing on a human's hand?!
36-Pound Phoenix!
Look out!
He repelled Zoro's attack with his bare hand!
Is that even possible?
Is that your ability?
I have the power to repel various things.
I am a paw man,
having eaten the Paw-Paw Fruit.
A-A p-paw man?
--Huh?
--Why does that sound so peaceful?!
Are there soothing Devil Fruits?!
It's hard to say whether you're
a Warlord or a Purr-lord...
Maybe he's not such a big deal after all.
Franky...!
Franky!
Cyborg Franky, is that
the extent of your strength?
Franky, breathe!
Breathe, Franky!
Franky... got blasted away from the front!
That attack is incredible.
He might be repelling air.
A normal cannon wouldn't hurt Franky.
It's called "Pad Cannon."
When air is repelled at the speed of light,
it creates a shock wave that
can shoot through people.
Your time is up.
Thrust Pad Cannon!
Streaming Wolf-Swords!
--Zoro!
--He got repelled with his attack!
Curse you...
He's in trouble! He can't keep this up!
It's a miracle he's fought
for as long as he has!
As it is, that behemoth Oars
nearly beat the life out of him!
Zoro, behind you! Run!
Zoro!
That's as far as you go!
Concasser!
Sanji!
He didn't repel that with his paws!
I bet Sanji cracked your skull, you bastard!
Jerk! Stay out of this!
Black Leg Sanji...
So that would be you.
Sanji's kick didn't even faze him.
What's going on here?!
Why is he so hard?!
Is his face made out of iron?
F-Firebird Star!
Sniper King...
What a presumptuous title.
Huh?
This is too much for them!
They don't stand a chance.
They're gonna get killed!
Zoro! Sanji!
As I feared, I will not derive
pleasure from killing you
while you are in this weakened state.
The government ordered me
to annihilate everyone, but...
What is that supposed to be?
Air? Is he condensing the air with his paws?
The bubble is getting smaller!
He's applying pressure to a large body
of air by repelling it with his paws!
That's making it shrink!
When all of that air depressurizes,
it will generate power!
The giant sonic blast it
creates will be like a bomb.
Wh-What?!
A bomb?
In other words, he's making a bomb?!
A... bomb?!
I will spare your lives.
In exchange, all you need to do is
hand over Straw Hat Luffy's head.
As long as I get his head,
the government will not complain.
You want us to sell out our friend?
Now then, give Straw Hat to me.
Forget it!!
What a pity.
Ursus Shock!
Stay out of this, Mosshead!
I'm taking Kuma down!
No, you're staying out of this!
You jerk... Why did you...?
You're the cook.
It's the warrior's job to
risk his life in combat.
Next time, on One Piece:
"My Crewmates' Pain Is My Pain
Zoro's Desperate Fight"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
My Crewmates' Pain Is My Pain
Zoro's Desperate Fight