Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy broke into Navy HQ to save his brother,
Ace, from imminent execution.
However, both Ace and Whitebeard tragically lost their lives.
Whitebeard, Ace...
We'll see to the burial of those two.
Only because it's you, I allow it, Red-Haired!
But...!
I will take the blame myself!
Thanks.
Treat the injured now!
This war is...
...over!
Mighty Leaders Face Each Other Down!
Heralding the "New Era"!
What's wrong with it? I can't make out a thing.
Are they having trouble with the transmission?
So, what happened to the war?
Did the Navy win?
They did, didn't they?
It's clearing up.
Were the Whitebeards defeated?
Did the Navy really win?
Regarding the war occurring at Marineford
being waged by the Whitebeards and we, Navy HQ,
the process took longer than anticipated due to the enemy's persistence
but the Navy soldiers all fought fiercly
with a great sense of justice
and defeated all of the Whitebeards and their allies.
We are happy to tell you
that Navy HQ has attained complete victory!
They did it!
The Navy is invincible! Praise to our heroes!
I want to serve at Navy HQ someday!
The war is over!
Yes!
I'm glad!
The legendary pirate—Whitebeard—lost!
The war is over, right?
Yes! You're safe now!
Alright!
They did it!
We're safe!
Hurrah for the Navy!
Hurray for the World Government!
And for victory and justice and peace! Hurrah!
At the scene of the Paramount War.
Seven ships float in the sea off Marineford.
The burden of a new pirate era
falls on their shoulders.
They have witnessed
this historic event with keen interest.
They stand and watch the dust settle upon Marineford—
evidence of the workings
of justice in this Great Pirate Era—
and they all feel the coming of a new era of bloodthirst on the surface of their skin.
Captain Drake.
Finally... it's over.
The Navy will never be the same again.
It won't take long,
before Whitebeard's territory will become a sea of blood.
Blackbeard is the key.
He's gained new followers and Whitebeard's power.
I'm sure they're gonna be
the eye of the storm for a while!
It's all... his fault!
I'll track him down soon enough!
Let's go! To the New World!
What the hell is going on?
What are you talking about, Apoo-san?
They'll be enemies someday.
Do you really think he'll save him?
Huh?
I'm talking about Trafalgar Law.
He's known to be ruthless.
He wouldn't save Straw Hat Luffy
if there wasn't some sorta catch.
It's odd.
What's wrong, Captain Hawkins?
I've been trying to see the odds
of Straw Hat Luffy's survival
but it never reaches zero.
To be honest, I was scared when the war started,
but now the great pirate, Whitebeard, is dead.
So it's really over, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
What's over?!
That new force which emerged during this war—
that Blackbeard—is a force to be reckoned with!
The New World is ruled by the Four Emperors.
Whitebeard, Red-Haired, Kaido, Big Mom.
But since one of them is dead,
the balance of power has been tipped
and no one knows what'll happen!
This is the beginning of a new era
the likes of which no one has ever seen!
The news of the Navy's victory in the war of Marineford,
the biggest war of the Great Pirate Era,
spread all over in the blink of an eye
and people are celebrating the news around the world.
East Blue.
East Blue
Hurrah!
Whitebeard is dead!
Yeah!
We're safe now!
I'm so glad!
West Blue.
West Blue
The sea will be at peace now!
Hurrah!
South Blue.
South Blue
We'll have a bargain sale today!
So are we!
The Navy has won!
I'm so relieved!
North Blue.
North Blue
Yes! I'm so happy!
Let's drink, everybody!
We have enough for everyone!
Grand Line.
Grand Line
What should we do tomorrow?
I wanna play tag!
Hide and seek!
Alright!
God! Thank you!
As with all historical knowledge
the facts of the story get altered as it spreads.
"Navy Victory."
These two words dance on the ocean breeze.
The people, overjoyed at the news,
failed to notice something...
W-What's going on?!
Look at you people! That's hilarious!
Whitebeard said the great treasure,
the One Piece, is real!
I'm gonna find it!
There is so much more out there! Let's set sail!
"Navy victory."
This result did not necessarily bring peace...
New World, Foodvalten Island
Y-You can't take another step!
Don't come into town!
With the loss of a deterrent—
namely, the threat of Whitebeard—
the world of the seas is thrown into turmoil...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
Here you are!
We've had word from Impel Down!
Is Magellan alright?
He's been beaten terribly. He's barely alive.
The medical team is doing their best to save him.
Being the kind of man he is, he's very upset at this failure.
They said if he could move right now,
he might even kill himself.
Don't let him do such a stupid thing!
Y-Yes, sir!
What's been going on at the prison?
In short:
The situation on Level 6
is particularly bad. It's in shambles.
In shambles?
Underwater Prison Impel Down
Level 6
What's up?
You prisoners're doomed to be stuck behind bars forever!
You've got nothing to do except wait for death!
Then how about this?!
Why don't you fight each other in your cells?!
I'll free the survivors and let them join my crew!
Really?!
Get me out of here!
Let me be your crew member!
So he took the strongest
of the world's worst criminals?!
Yes. But only 4 prisoners were taken.
San Juan Wolf, Avalo Pizarro, Vasco Shot, Catarina Devon.
Obviously there are many more
who are missing from the cells in Level 6!
Which means...
I see. You mean other prisoners
from Level 6 have escaped.
If even a single prisoners from Level 6
manages to hide in a country somewhere,
it will put the people in great danger!
Hurry up and figure out who's missing.
Get their names and send
wanted posters around the world!
What's wrong?
Well, I...
I'm under orders from the World Government
to keep this Level 6 matter secret.
They say any more blunders will harm
the Government's reputation.
Damn them!
You bastard!
Doflamingo!
Moria, you're far too weak
to bear the title of Warlord.
"Died in the Paramount War" sounds better...
...than "done in by the Government".
Whose idea was this?! Sengoku?!
No, someone much higher up the ladder!
It's hot... Too hot...
Why is it so hot? I can't take it.
Could you shut up already?! You're making me feel hot too!
You're hairy. I don't blame you.
I don't like it when we submerge.
We have to stay in such a cramped place...
...with messy people.
You're the messiest!
I can't take it! I have no choice but...
...to make you feel the same!
Stop it!
You're so hot!
That's gross!
Come on!
I beg you! A little bit is fine! Let me get some fresh air!
Alright! Now, stop rubbing your sweat on me!
Surface! Let's surface now!
How refreshing! It's so nice outside!
Now I'm cool! Right side—okay!
Left side—okay!
Front...
Snake—okay! Snake?!
What the hell?!
How did a snake get here?!
Oh no!
What's a Navy ship doing here?
Inform the captain!
Someone's there!
A Warlord—the Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock!
Don't worry. I turned all the Navy soldiers to stone.
So how is Luffy doing?
Is it bad? He'll recover, won't he?
How did you know
that we were gonna surface here?
I was scared thinking
that the Navy was still chasing us.
I made Salome follow you underwater.
I see!
Don't change the subject, you fuzzy beast!
I'm sorry!
He folded so quickly!
How is Luffy doing? Tell me now...
Oh, Captain!
Heart Pirates Captain
Trafalgar Law
I did everything I could.
You mean, he's okay?
We were able to stabilize him. However...
...he suffered greater damage than you'd think.
There is no guarantee that he'll survive.
That's to be expected!
Who said that?
Straw-boy couldn't even stand up
in Impel Down at one point!
Straw Hat kept risking his life!
We got out of prison thanks to him!
Because of him, we can make our dream come true:
To go to the Kamabakka Queendom!
Let's go!
From New Kama Land to the New Kamas' homeland!
What are they?
Prisoners of Impel Down.
It would seem that they're Luffy's friends.
They snuck onboard the ship.
Vi can't believe he pushed himself that hard!
That's how much he wanted to save his brother—Ace!
That's right!
We know how much he pushed himself!
But that very brother died in front of his eyes...
in order to protect him...
There is no justice in this world!
It's no surprise he broke down!
Damn it all! Hang in there, Straw Hat!
You've got to live! You have to, Straw Hat!
How tragic! I wish I could take his place!
Poor Luffy!
I'm jealous...
To have the Pirate Empress care about you that much...
Yeah, yeah...
By the way, are you a friend of Straw-boy?
No, I didn't have any obligation to save him at all.
If you're concerned about my motivations,
I can come up with a reason.
No, that's okay.
Sometimes your instincts tell you what to do.
Hey, wait!
You can't walk around yet!
Don't push yourself like that!
He told you to rest!
The wound could open up!
Where are you going?
Jinbe!
You're Trafalgar Law
from the North Blue, aren't you?
Uh-huh.
Hey, is it okay for you to move around like that?
Thank you!
You saved my life!
Go lie down. You could die.
I can't put my mind at ease. It's impossible!
What I have just lost was too important to me!
That is why I know what Luffy-kun must be going through is far worse!
At least, his protective instincts
made him lose consciousness back there!
Even if he survives,
I can't stop worrying
about the moment he wakes up.
You, fuzzy beast, do you have a Transponder Snail?
Yeah... I mean... yes, ma'am!
I'm sorry!
I'm jealous. He's like her servant...
Yeah, yeah...
I'm gonna call the Kuja's ship
so we can go across the Calm Belt
even with this submarine.
If the Government finds out Luffy's alive,
they're gonna come after him!
We'll harbor him at Maiden Island!
What?!
As long as they still see me as a Warlord,
Luffy can rest there safely!
Luffy...
At Hancock's suggestion,
Luffy is taken to Maiden Island
to recover from his injuries,
and there he finally regains consciousness.
But as his memories of the battle return,
Luffy is overtaken by deep despair.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Landing at Maiden Island
The Harsh Reality Falls upon Luffy"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Landing at Maiden Island
The Harsh Reality Falls upon Luffy