Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece...
head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and in order to move on
to the next stage—the New World—
they set sail for Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
Gum-Gum...
Elephant Gun!
Hey, Ankoro! You can't do that!
Don't eat ships!
D-Did he help us?
Let's go! We have to get away anyway!
He is a monster too!
What the hell is that?!
Undersea Volcanic Eruption!
Drifting to Fishman Island
Dead men tell no tales, they have no desire.
Is that...
In the dark land where even crows can't fly.
me?
Dead men don't need jewels on their finger.
You can't even see somebody's sorrow in the dark.
Look for it! Look for it!
Sunken treasures are mine!
I am the richest person
in the world—Captain Vander Decken!
Don't tell me it's...
Even in the sea?!
A ghost ship?!
You shouldn't be so scared!
I turned!
For no reason!
Oh no!
It's a ghost ship!
We thought that you were a ghost at that moment!
Th-That is the real one!
Look at that sail!
The infamous Flying Dutchman!
It shouldn't exist in the real world!
It happened several hundred years ago.
One stormy day, the captain
of the pirate ship suddenly lost his mind
and killed all his crew by throwing them
into troubled waters one by one!
And he even cursed the gods!
The name of the captain was Vander Decken
and the ship was the Flying Dutchman!
The gods got mad at him
and set him adrift forever under constant torture!
And the ship right in front of us
is Captain Vander Decken's haunted ship!
Calm down!
We thought that Brook's ship was a ghost ship but it wasn't.
What we found on that ship
was nothing special—just this funny skeleton!
Franky-san is harsh!
And 30 degrees is hard!
You're right!
Ghost ships aren't something that you see often.
We just saw the Kraken which was believed
to be an imaginary monster
so it's not that surprising to see a ghost ship.
Then maybe that's...
A real ghost ship!
I'm scared!
Robin, you can't entertain yourself
by making them upset.
Captain Vander Decken!
Wadatsumi and Ankoro got a pirate ship!
Stupid humans!
But they have quite a good ship.
They have a whole bunch of treasure! I suspect!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Please come back!
Shut up!
We have to get through this by ourselves!
So Luffy and the others can come back to us!
The water temperature
has been increasing for quite a while.
Could this be...
Ankoro! Wadatsumi!
We can't seize their treasure if you eat the ship
so knock it down!
I got it!
Oh no, the Sea Spirit is...
He's our enemy after all!
Franky, use Coup de Burst!
I can't!
The fuel has run out!
I have to fill up the cola in the energy room!
We don't have time!
Nooo!
He's gonna get us!
Kraken!
The Monster of the Arctic—Kraken?
You bastard!
Alright, that's enough. Stop!
Good job!
Hey!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
I'm glad that you're all alive!
What were you doing?!
Nami-swan! Robin-chwan!
We've been looking for you guys!
They're so high-maintenance. They got lost!
Sanji, no!
He's relapsing!
He needs rehab with less stimulating pics!
Hey! Wake up, Wadatsumi!
Avenge yourself! Get back at it!
Well, Sanji's bubble and mine popped
so we got into Zoro's.
I thought I was gonna die!
Don't make us worry!
Alright, here's a song to celebrate your return.
Lots of space!
There's no place like home!
Luffy! I was scared!
You all have an amazing ability to survive.
I can't believe it!
You really tamed the monster octopus?
And are you gonna use the Kraken?
Yeah, I'm gonna use him like experienced people do!
Right, Surume?
That's a squid snack!
Surume!
The Kraken is an octopus
but he named it Surume, oh yeah!
Alright, draw the Sunny, Surume!
Well, instead of making him draw the ship,
we have to make sure
that he's not gonna smash it up.
Captain, the pirate ship is...
Don't let it get away! Go after it!
Yeah!
What is it?
This is no good, Captain Vander Decken!
Oh no, the undersea volcano's gonna erupt!
What?!
We are too close to it!
Everyone!
Let's go back for now!
Roger! Captain Vander Decken!
Ankoro! Wadatsumi! Draw the ship!
Oh, okay!
I am the richest person
in the world—Captain Vander Decken!
Oh no!
Luffy, tell Kraken to get away from here now!
Yeah!
Hey, Surume—
Wait, don't need to!
He's running like hell already!
That's a terrible look for such a mythical monster!
Nice! Maybe we can hit it off!
He runs awful.
Don't say that.
That's how horrifying the eruption is!
That's right!
And what is he doing?
Wow! Yes!
Come on!
It's rehab!
But I wanna see the eruption!
Evacuate to the front of the ship!
Yeah!
It doesn't change anything!
It's only a few meters.
Lava's flowing along to the sea floor!
The temperature is soaring!
Feels like I'm in boiling water!
I'm gonna be cooked!
The ghost ship and the Sea Spirit!
Run, Surume!
You can do it!
Go faster, Surume,
or you're gonna become boiled octopus!
Boiled octopus?
That's great! I wanna eat some!
Because of the difference in temperature, the sea current's starting to swirl!
Nami-san,
which way is Fishman Isla—
Even at a time like this?
Sanji, you have to focus on your rehab!
Keep going straight!
We're getting close!
Jump into that trench!
What?!
In there?!
No!
It's a sheer cliff!
You've got to be kidding!
It's darker than dark!
Are you sure that Fishman Island is in there?!
It's hot in the back!
It's totally dark in the front! Scary!
I'm sure there'll be another monster!
I don't think we can make it home alive!
Luffy! The darkness is a bottomless pot
that connects to hell!
Iron pot! Tea caddy! Tea-tea caddy!
Jump in, Surume!
It's erupting again!
What is that?!
Right above us!
Rocks?!
Mud?!
It's an avalanche of rocks and earth!
The eruption caused it!
I think even the Sunny would break apart
if one of those giant rocks hits it!
Get away, Surume!
I'm gonna go out and cut them!
Luffy! Hold on tightly to my leg!
Okay, I got it!
Zoro, no!
Hey, let me go!
Why are you stopping him, Robin?
We're 8,000 meters deep now!
If you go out,
you'll be crushed by the water pressure!
Then what should we do?!
If we can buy some time to get away from the cliff!
Leave it to me!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Sargasso!
The sea plant popped out!
It stopped...
The avalanche.
That's so cool, Usopp!
Cool!
It only holds for a while.
Now is the chance to get away, Surume!
Just in time!
Usopp, that was great!
Yes, it was great judgment!
We made it through!
It's not like I was fooling around
for the past two years.
Let me tell you about it!
It's a very touching story!
The days of the relentless diet
with Master Heracles'n...
Maybe next time.
Why next time?!
Nami-san is harsh!
Surume, you did great too!
We're safe now!
Thank you, Surume!
Surume! Surume! Hey!
Surume! Hey! Surume! Come on!
Su—
10,000m below sea level, "The Deep"
(Bottom of the oceanic trench)
I... I'm alive!
Light? This deep in the sea?
It's too bright!
My eyes are dazzled!
But I don't have eyes to be dazzled.
Hey guys, come here!
Look at that!
I can't see it—it's too bright.
Hey Nami, is that it?
Yeah, there's no doubt.
The needle is pointing at that island!
That is...
Fishman Island!
It's huge!
It's in a big bubble!
There are clouds? Maybe there is air inside.
That's Fishman Island
so we're 10,000 meters deep now!
How is there such a big tree this deep in the water?
Yeah! We made it!
It's a popular site in the Grand Line!
They made it there!
The Mermaids dance around here.
The beautiful Mermaids!
I'm finally here!
The paradise that I've been dreaming of since I was a kid!
Mermaido! Mermaido!
Mermai—
Sanji! You're not ready!
You shouldn't even think about it!
Sanji!
I'm sorry, Sanji!
The rehab didn't work yet!
You shouldn't look at real Mermaids.
Doctor! It was his dream
to see the Mermaids on Fishman Island!
But he's gonna die if he sees them!
No!
I don't care...
Sanji!
Rather than live longer without a dream,
I wanna die staring
at the Mermaids in a disgusting way!
You're scum!
I'm gonna look at the Mermaids!
He's burning!
The flame of his eroticism!
I can't wait!
I wonder what kind of meat is in their dishes!
Luffy, wipe your drool.
Can you give an order to Surume?
Let's look for the entrance.
Hey, what are they?!
Who are they?
A group of sea monsters!
We're dead!
After we got all the way here!
They're so cool!
Sea monsters!
Somebody's riding it!
Mysterious Fishmen
block their entry to Fishman Island.
They mention Arlong,
whom the Straw Hats had defeated,
and call themselves the New Fishman Pirates.
To evade the menacing sea beasts,
Luffy and Co. decide to force their way onto Fishman Island.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Landing at Fishman Island
Beautiful Mermaids"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Landing at Fishman Island
Beautiful Mermaids