Ugh! It's almost like
the ship's gonna tip over!
Look at that light!
Is that a lighthouse of the island?
It's a "guiding light."
The entrance to the Grand Line
lies ahead of that light.
We're finally here! The Grand Line!
Okay, then!
Shall we hold a launching ceremony
for setting sail on the great ocean?
Sure!
In order to find the All Blue!
In order to be the Pirate King!
In order to become a master swordsman!
In order to draw a world map!
I-In order...
...to become a brave warrior of the sea!
This is...
...a story of the early days of the pirate
Monkey D. Luffy and his four friends
who are heading for the Grand Line in order
to claim the Great Treasure of One Piece!
A special episode to celebrate the
20th anniversary of the manga series:
One Piece Episode of East Blue:
Luffy and His Four Friends' Great Adventure.
This is a small seaport village.
At the port, a pirate ship has been
anchored for a year or so.
A wind is blowing from the east
over this peaceful village.
Hey, Luffy! What are you trying to do?!
Monkey D. Luffy
A Village Boy
I'm really serious! I'm so pissed!
I'm gonna prove it to you!
Yeah, do it! I don't know
what you're gonna do, though!
Ouch!
You idiot! What are you doing?!
Cheers, guys!
To Luffy's guts and our great journey!
Oh, it didn't hurt at all!
That's a lie. Don't do such a stupid thing.
It's not a lie!
I'm not scared of getting hurt!
Take me on your next voyage!
I wanna be a pirate, too!
As if you could ever be a pirate!
'Red-Haired' Shanks
A Pirate Boss
It's a fatal flaw for a pirate
to be an anchor!
I'll be okay as long as I don't fall off of
the ship! And I'm good at fighting, too!
I'm well-trained,
so my punches are like pistols!
Pistols? Oh, really?
What's that mean?!
Luffy!
You're in such a bad mood!
Have fun at whatever you're doing!
Yes! Being a pirate is fun!
The sea is broad and vast!
We travel to various islands!
Above all, we're free!
Guys, don't teach him such silly stuff.
But it's true! Right?!
Boss, why not take him on just one voyage?
I think so, too.
Then somebody trade places with him.
Okay, we're done talking! Let's drink!
Didn't you side with me?!
In short, you're too much of a kid.
I'll consider it when you're ten years older!
Stupid Shanks! I'm not a kid!
Now, now. Don't get so mad.
Have some juice!
Wow! Thanks!
See, you are a kid!
That wasn't fair, Shanks!
I'm tired now!
Luffy, you gotta try to
understand how Boss feels.
First mate!
There's no denying that he's
the head of a pirate group.
He knows how tough and dangerous
being a pirate is more than anybody.
Don't you see? It's not like
he wants to break your spirit.
No, I don't! Shanks is just
making fun of me!
Anchor!
See?!
I guess you're having fun as usual.
Yeah, I like teasing him.
Luffy, do you wanna eat something, too?
Uh-huh! Put it on my treasure tab!
The treasure tab again?
That's fraud, you know?
No, it's not! Once I become a pirate
and find a treasure, I'll pay for it!
I'm counting on it.
Shanks.
What?
How much longer are you
gonna stay in this village?
Let's see...
We're gonna go on a couple of voyages,
then leave this village to head north.
A couple of voyages, huh?
I'll practice swimming while you're here!
That's good. Knock yourself out.
Pardon us.
So these are pirates.
Look pretty damn dumb.
We're mountain bandits.
But we ain't here to tear up the place.
Sell us some booze.
I'm sorry. I just ran out of alcohol.
These pirates seem to be drinking
something... What is it, water?
No, what they're drinking is the last of it.
My apologies. Looks like we
drank the whole place dry.
Sorry!
You can have this, if you'd like.
It hasn't been opened yet.
Hey, you bastard!
Who do you think I am?
One bottle ain't even enough
for a bedtime drink!
The floor's all wet!
Look at this.
There's an eight-million-Berry
bounty on my head.
I've killed 56 people.
They were all impudent like you.
So be careful hereafter.
But since we're in the mountains
and you're on the sea,
I don't think we'll see each other again.
Sorry about that, Makino-san.
Do you have a rag?
Oh, I'll do that!
Seems you like to clean. Then maybe
you'll find this more fulfilling.
Later, wimps!
Captain-san, are you all right?
Oh, no problem at all.
Talk about lame, Boss!
He got you good!
Why are you laughing?!
That was so uncool!
Why didn't you fight them?!
You're not men—or pirates—
if you laugh after something like that!
I can understand how you feel,
but he only spilled some booze on me.
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
Hey, wait, Luffy.
I've had it! I don't wanna
be a coward like you!
His arm stretches!
Don't tell me you...!
What's going on?!
- It's gone!
- What?!
The Gum-Gum Fruit that
we stole from our enemy!
Luffy, don't tell me you ate a fruit like this!
I-I did... It tasted so bad.
The Gum-Gum Fruit is a hidden treasure
of the sea known as a Devil Fruit!
Eating it turns your body to rubber,
and makes you lose the ability
to swim for the rest of your life!
Eh?! No way!
You dumb-ass!
Can I have fish, fish-shop pops?
Hey, Luffy! I heard that you didn't
get to go on a voyage again!
That's okay!
Because I got to become a rubber man!
It's making me way happier than a voyage!
It's been a while since Captain-san
and his crew went on a voyage.
I bet you miss them.
Not at all! I haven't forgiven them yet!
I thought Shanks and the others
were cooler pirates!
Yeah?
I think it's cooler to pay no mind and laugh
after someone humiliates you like that.
You don't understand. There are times
that men have to stand up and fight.
I guess I don't understand these things.
Make way for us!
Those damn pirates
aren't here today, huh?
We were walking by again,
so we dropped in.
Why are you just standing there?!
Bring us booze!
Mayor, we have a problem!
What is it, Makino?
Luffy's in trouble with mountain bandits!
- Let go! Let go! Damn!
- What an interesting body...
Say you're sorry for that!
- What kind of animal is he?
- You bastard!
Damn! I'm gonna make you pay!
We can sell him for good money.
You're so persistent.
Brat!
Did I say something to offend you?
You did! Now apologize!
Get your foot off of me!
Let the boy go!
Please!
I don't intend to fight with you!
If you allow it, I'll even pay you!
Spare the boy's life!
Leave it to senior citizens
to know how the world works.
But no.
It's too late for him now.
After all, he's made me angry...
Oh, please...
I'm irritated from being
messed with by this rubber squirt!
You're the bad guys! You mountain apes!
We're not gonna sell him.
Let's just kill him!
- Luffy!
- Please! Let him go!
No one came to greet us at the port...
So I wondered why...
They're the mountain bandits from before.
Captain-san!
Luffy! I thought your punches
were as strong as pistols.
Shut up!
So you pirates are still here, huh?
You'd best leave before you get hurt.
Any closer and he'll shoot
your head off, wimp.
He said no closer!
Don't make me blow your head off!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
What the hell're you talkin' about?
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
N-Now you've done it!
These bastards fight dirty!
Dirty?
Cut the crap. You think you're
dealing with saints or something?
You're looking at pirates!
Shut up! You got nothing to do
with this in the first place!
Listen, bandits.
Whether I'm splattered
with alcohol or food,
most of the time I'd just laugh
and forget about it.
But...!
No matter what the reason,
anyone who hurts my friends has to pay!
Shanks...
Has to pay, huh?!
Lousy pirates! Kill 'em, men!
I'll handle this. Should be easy enough.
Come on! Come on!
Ouch!
Don't get cocky, bandit.
If you wanna fight us, then go drag
a warship here or something.
So strong!
Unbelievable...
Hold on! The kid attacked us!
You're a wanted man anyway.
A smokescreen!
- Come with me, brat!
- Let go! Let go!
Luffy!
Crap! I let my guard down!
Luffy's gone! What do we do, guys?!
Quit freakin' the hell out, Boss!
It won't take us long to find him!
I can't believe this guy...
I made a clean getaway!
I got no use for you anymore!
You bastard!
So long!
Dammit! Dammit!
Those guys are scum, but I couldn't
even hit them once! Dammit! Dammit!
You see the looks on those pirates' faces?!
Pirates are just a bunch of wimps.
Stop it!
Stop making fun of Shanks and the others!
Stop, Luffy!
Silly brat.
Wh-What the hell?!
Help...!
It's gonna eat me!
Help!
Shanks...
Get lost!
I'm in your debt, Luffy...
Makino-san told me everything.
You fought for us.
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
But... Shanks...!
Your arm!
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
I'm just glad you're all right...
Luffy learned the reason that
Shanks didn't take him on a voyage—
The harshness of the sea,
his powerlessness.
And most importantly, he learned
the man named Shanks' greatness.
He truly thought that he wanted to
become a man like him someday.
Shanks, aren't you gonna come back?
No. It was a long stay,
but now we part ways.
Yeah, I won't ask you to take me anymore.
I've decided to become
a pirate on my own now!
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
You'll never be a pirate!
I will, too!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a crew
every bit as good as yours,
and I'm gonna find the greatest
treasure in the world,
and I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
You're gonna surpass us, huh?
In that case...
...I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Come bring it back to me someday!
Once you've become a great pirate!
He's got quite a future.
Yeah, he's so much like the kid I used to be.
Set sail!
Then, a decade later, the boy's adventure
started at the same port.
10 years later
He's finally leaving, Mayor.
It's a dishonor to the village
to become a pirate!
What a nice day for setting sail!
What the...?
Here comes our local sea monster!
You don't know who you're messing with.
Look at this technique
I've been practicing for 10 years!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
We gather together our dreams
And go in search of our desires
That will learn ya, stupid fish!
I've only a pocket of coins,
But do you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on the cruise!
All right! Let's go!
I'm gonna become...
We are!
...the Pirate King!
Episode
of Luffy
Episode of
Zoro
In order to become a master swordsman!
Roronoa Zoro
A Pirate Hunter
Hey you!
Could you untie me? I'll return the favor.
I'm a man of my word.
Who are you? Do you wanna get killed?
I made you some rice balls!
You must be hungry!
This is my first time, but I worked
really hard to make them!
I ain't hungry! Get the hell outta here!
But...
I don't want 'em!
Don't make me kill you, kid!
Little lady, you brought him
those tasty-looking rice balls?
Oh, no!
Yuck! Too damn sweet!
Those're full of sugar!
But I thought they might
taste better sweet—
Salt goes on rice balls!
I can't eat this, you fool!
No, you're ruining them!
Don't worry. Ants will eat them.
How dare you!
I worked so hard to make those...
No one can stand against me!
Because my father is a Navy captain!
I am... great!
What do you want? Are you still here?
I'm Luffy. I'm looking for people
to join my pirate crew.
Pirate? You're not gonna say, "I'll untie you,
so lend me your support," are you?
I wasn't gonna ask you to join me yet.
You'd better ask someone else
to join your stupid crew.
I've got other plans.
Okay.
Hey, wait a sec!
Could you pick that up for me?
You're gonna eat this?
It's mostly a mud ball now.
Just shut up!
Give it here! Every last piece
of it that's on the ground!
Told you so. Do you wanna die?
Could you tell that kid something?
What?
"It was good. Thanks for the food."
I can't afford to die in a place like this!
There's something I gotta do!
The winner is Kuina!
You're still as weak as ever!
Especially for a boy.
Damn it! Why can't I beat that girl?!
I'll set out to sea someday and become
the world's greatest swordsman!
I shouldn't be beaten by a girl
like her even at this point!
Kuina, fight me with a real sword!
Sure.
My win!
Damn it... This sucks...
I'm the one who should be
crying out of frustration.
When girls grow up,
they get weaker than men...
You're lucky, Zoro. I want to be
the world's greatest swordsman, too!
If only I had been born a man...!
Don't be whining like that after you beat me!
That's not fair! You're my goal!
Zoro...
Promise me!
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
We'll compete to see who gets there!
You dummy. You're so weak...
It's a promise!
- Zoro-san!
- You're...
If you help me escape, you'll be killed!
I can't stand to watch the Navy
like this! Just run now!
I got shot!
This is some interesting stuff
you guys've pulled!
Were you guys planning
a coup or something?!
Aim!
I...
...can't afford to die here!
I promised her...
Zoro! Listen!
Kuina fell down the steps
at home and died...
Dammit!
You promised me yesterday!
Aren't you gonna keep your word?!
Sensei... Let me have her sword...
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
I'll be the world's greatest swordsman
so that my name will reach heaven!
I promised her...
I can't afford to die here...
Kill him!
What are you—?!
That doesn't work!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm the man who's gonna
become Pirate King!
Which is yours? I couldn't tell,
so I brought three of 'em.
All three are mine.
I use the Three-Sword Style.
If we fight together now,
you'll be a government-defying villain!
Would you prefer that, or dying like this?
What are you, the devil's son?!
Well, whatever. I'll be your pirate,
if I'm just gonna die here instead!
You fools! Everyone who
opposes me gets executed!
So cool!
Stay still, you bastards.
Move and you're dead.
I'll be a pirate. I promise you that.
But I tell you now,
I have my own ambition!
To be the world's greatest swordsman!
At this point, whether it's
as a criminal or whatever else,
I will spread my name throughout the world!
Since you asked me to join,
if I wind up having to give that up,
you'd better accept responsibility
and apologize to me!
The world's greatest swordsman?
That sounds great!
The Pirate King would need
no less than that on his crew!
You sure talk big.
What're you standing around for?!
Slaughter them this instant!
Duck, Zoro!
Gum-Gum Whip!
What the hell are you?
Guys!
If you value this guy's life, don't move!
Gum-Gum...
Listen to me!
I am a Navy captain!
...Pistol!
Nice!
Zoro.
My pleasure, Captain.
Then, Zoro went on an adventure with Luffy
and witnessed an unbelievable scene
at the sea restaurant Baratie.
Hawk-Eye Mihawk, the world's strongest
swordsman, suddenly arrived on the scene.
Is it possible... that's...
'Hawk-Eye' Mihawk
World's Strongest Swordsman
...Hawk-Eye!
Dammit! What grudge do you
have to come after us?!
Just killing time.
Don't mock us!
He missed!
He averted them.
He gently changed the course of the
bullets using the point of his sword.
I've never seen swords moving so gently...
There is no strength in swordplay
based only on force.
Did you use that sword
to slice up this ship as well?
That's right.
I see... You're the strongest...
I came out to sea to meet you.
What's your goal?
To become the strongest!
You've got spare time,
right? Let's fight!
How pitiful, weak one...
If you are a competent enough swordsman,
you should be able to see the disparity
in our abilities even before
we cross swords.
Is it your courage or ignorance that
causes you to turn your sword on me?
It's my ambition!
And it's also because of a promise
I made to a dear friend!
What kind of fight will it be...?
I'm no beast that goes all out
when hunting a rabbit.
Unfortunately, I don't carry any sharp
instrument smaller than this one.
Better not regret it when I kill you!
Frog in the well...
Know how big the world is.
Demon...
...Slash!
I can't move them!
What did he do?! No one has ever
seen through this technique!
This... can't be happening...!
That can't be right! There's no way
that our abilities are this far apart!
The world's strongest can't be this far!
We can't be this far apart!
This is too far a gap in abilities!
I didn't pursue swordsmanship all this time...
to be dealt with... by a toy like this!
What ferocity your swordplay has...
To defeat this man...!
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
Only to defeat this man...!
I'll be the world's greatest swordsman
so that my name will reach heaven!
What do you bear on your shoulders?
What do you desire once you've
obtained power, weak one?
Tiger...
The world's greatest swordsman?
That sounds great!
The Pirate King would need
no less than that on his crew!
...Hunt!
Are you just going to let me
pierce your heart?
Why aren't you withdrawing?
I don't know why...
But if I withdrew even a step,
I feel like those various important
things such as pledges and promises
in the past will be shattered...
...and I won't be able to come
back to where I am now...
Yes, that's what defeat is about.
Then all the more reason
I can't withdraw...
Even if you'll die?
I'd rather die.
What a strong heart!
So he chooses death over defeat!
Kid! State your name.
Roronoa Zoro!
I'll remember it, strong one.
I haven't seen anyone like you in a while...
As a swordsman's courtesy, I'll sink you
using the world's strongest Black Blade.
So this'll be the last hit...
If I miss, I'll die. Will it be
the world's strongest? Or death...?
Fall!
Three-Sword Style Secret Art:
Three Thousand Worlds!
I lost... I'm no match for him.
I never imagined I'd ever lose...
So this is the power
of the world's strongest...
What are you...?
Scars on the back are
a swordsman's shame...
Admirable!
Don't live so hastily, young man.
Zoro!
Big Bro!
My name is Dracule Mihawk!
It's still too early for you to die.
Learn about yourself! Learn about
the world! And become strong, Roronoa!
No matter how many years it takes,
I will hold this seat of the strongest
and wait for you.
With the raging mettle of your spirit,
surpass this sword!
Try to surpass me! Roronoa!
Zoro?
Luffy!
Did I worry you...?
You need no less than the world's
greatest swordsman, right?
I will not...!
I will not be defeated ever again!
Until the day I defeat him
and become a master swordsman...
...I'll never... be defeated!
Got any problems with that,
Pirate King?!
Nope!
Episode of
Zoro
I-In order...
...to become a brave warrior of the sea!
Episode of Usopp
Terrible news! Terrible news!
Pirates! Pirates are attacking!
Pirates! Everyone run away!
Pirates are attacking our village!
What, pirates?!
Oh, I guess it's time to go to work.
That guy's so persistent.
It's just a lie!
Usopp
A Village Boy
Did you all get fooled?
- You exaggeration-spewing kid!
- Get back here, you damn kid!
Here they come!
Just try and catch me!
Dammit! Where the hell'd he go?!
Another job well done today!
I sent the wind of excitement
into this boring village!
All right, I'm gonna go see her next.
Say, Klahadore...
What is it, Miss Kaya?
I want to see Usopp-san.
That will not do. That man is
the village's biggest exaggerator!
How petty.
"Petty" will do just fine.
No means no!
Heya!
Usopp-san!
You seem as down as ever!
I'm sorry! I'd really like to invite you in
as a real guest, but Klahadore...
Well, this is better for me!
After all, I am a brave warrior of the sea!
So what adventure are you
going to tell me today?
The story of when I fought the giant
goldfish at the South Pole!
What first shocked me
was the immense size of its poop!
It was so big that I landed on it
thinking it was solid ground!
He's doing it again.
Captain's so kind.
He tells his special made-up stories
to cheer her up every day!
Captain! Captain!
T-T-Terrible news!
Pirates... Pirates are coming to attack!
What? No way.
It's true!
This is serious! There are three of them!
Only three?
Yes!
All right! Let's go, Usopp Pirates!
Shh...
Is that them?
They don't look scary at all.
But there's a skull on their flag...
He sees us!
Hey, you fools!
Ugh! Oh, no!
I am Captain Usopp, leader of the great
pirates who reign over this village!
You'd better not attack this village!
My 8,000 subordinates won't sit by quietly!
You're lying.
Yikes! She saw through it!
You're funny!
Looking for crewmates and a big ship?
You're on a big adventure!
That's right.
Kaya is the only person
who can supply you a ship.
Kaya?
Yeah.
She's a weak girl who is confined to bed.
Her parents died from an illness.
They left her a vast fortune
and a huge mansion.
But no matter how much money
she has, she's still unhappy.
Hey, you listening?
Forget it. Let's go
somewhere else for a ship.
- Yeah.
- Okay. Now our bellies are filled so let's go.
By the way, did you say that you guys
are looking for crewmates?
Yeah, can you think of anyone?
I'll become your captain if you want!
No thanks.
That was too fast!
Yo!
Wh-What the...?! Can't you
say hi like a normal person?
I was thinking earlier.
Your dad's Yasopp, right?
I met him when I was a kid.
R-Really?! You met him?!
Yeah.
Where is he now?
I don't know.
But he's a crew member of
my favorite pirate ship!
Awesome!
I could even shoot an ant
right between the eyes!
I got a kid just about your age!
You've already told me lots of times!
I'll tell you more!
It was sad to say goodbye,
but there was no other choice!
There was but one reason:
The pirate flag was calling me!
Yasopp was a great pirate!
Yeah, huh?!
He was!
I'm proud of my old man, who leapt
onto these possibly endless seas...
...to live with his life on the line!
I'm planning on setting out
to sea like him someday!
In order to become
a brave warrior of the seal!
Is that...
...the butler from Kaya's house?
What's that butler doing out here?!
So, preparations for the plan
are ready, I hope?
Yeah, we can start anytime...
The Rich Girl Assassination Plan!
What?!
Don't call it that, Jango.
Sorry. It was an accident, Captain Kuro.
Don't call me that, either!
Do you understand the plan?
We can't simply kill her.
I know. Make her write a will
before we kill her, right?
Using my hypnosis!
That's right. It's gotta say: "I leave my
entire fortune to my butler, Klahadore."
Don't forget to give me my share.
What're they talking about?
That's what I'd like to know!
But I know the name Captain Kuro.
He's a pirate who's known
for his calculated plunders.
But I thought he was
executed three years ago.
We heard something really bad!
Kaya's going to be killed!
They're gonna attack the village, too!
Bad! This is seriously bad!
Oh, hey!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Kaya's gonna be killed! The village's
gonna be attacked! This is very bad!
This is serious! I gotta tell everyone!
Everyone in this village I grew
up in is going to be killed!
Kaya's going to be killed!
Even though I love them all!
Even though I love this village!
Terrible news, terrible news!
Pirates! Everyone, run away!
Pirates are going to attack this village
tomorrow morning! Everyone, run!
The second time today.
Don't listen.
Pirates aren't coming for real.
Everyone, run away! Please run!
Pi... Pirates are...
Everyone... run!
All right, Usopp!
- Enough is enough!
- Listen...
No! It's the truth this time!
You always say so!
I'm usually just joking,
but this is for real!
If we believed every story you ever told,
we'd have fled the village
hundreds of times by now!
Please, believe me! We gotta get out of here!
They really are going to kill everyone!
If you were as honest as Klahadore-san,
then we'd believe you!
Oh, come on... Please believe me!
Dammit!
We'll execute the plan at dawn tomorrow.
Destroy the village to your hearts' content!
Because I'm a liar, they were never
gonna believe me from the start.
But pirates are gonna come, right?
Yeah. But everyone thinks it's a lie.
That's why...
I'm going to stop the pirates at this beach
and make sure this stays a lie!
That's the only logical thing
for a liar like me to do!
I love this village...!
I want to protect everyone...!
You're one hell of a nice guy.
All right! We'll help you out!
I have dibs on all the pirates' treasure!
What? Why are you guys...?
"Scared" is written all over your face.
N-No way!
I'm perfectly okay!
Because I'm a brave warrior of the sea...
Dammit! I don't want your sympathy!
You guys can leave! Leave!
We ain't laughing! We're helping
'cause we think you're honorable!
As if we'd risk our lives
because of sympathy!
You guys...!
What can you guys do?
Cut.
- Stretch.
- Steal.
- I can hide.
- You're gonna fight!
It's daybreak.
Go ashore, men!
I don't see them.
No! What about the north shore?!
No! We can't let them enter
the village! Dammit!
- My money!
- Is that what you're worried about?!
What the—?!
There's someone at the top of the hill!
My name is Captain Usopp!
I'm completely ready to fight!
Turn back now if you don't wanna die!
Who are you?
I'm warning you!
Turn back now while you still can!
Or else my 100 million crewmen
will beat the crap out of you guys!
What?! One hundred million?!
He's obviously lying!
Yikes! They saw through it!
How dare you trick me!
Captain! Shocking news!
We found a lot of money on those weird boats!
Maybe five million Berries!
What?!
Why is there that much money
on those guys' boats?
That's my treasure!
But you can have it!
You'll give us the treasure?!
That's right! And in exchange
for that treasure...
...I ask that you turn back now!
What?!
You fool. We're obviously
going to take this treasure,
but it's not good enough
of a reason for us to turn back.
You have a point...
Guys, we have no time to waste! Advance!
Damn! Special Attack—
Outta the damn way!
Do you seriously think you can stop us?
What is he doing?
I can't... let you get past here...
Because I only lied like I always do...
So the village is going to have
just another ordinary day...
Let go!
I won't... let you get past this slope...
Shut up!
What's wrong with him?
I'll kill you!
You fools! Attack the village already!
If we screw up Captain Kuro's plan,
he's gonna kill us!
Dammit... Don't go to the village...!
Stop! Please don't kill everyone!
You guys are that strong?!
Yeah!
Hey, men! Don't tell me
those brats did you all in!
We don't have time to play around here...
Oh, no... Let me explain...
What is all this?!
I didn't sense his presence at all.
You idiots. To think that
these brats have held you back...
I'll kill every last one of you... as well as
the others with my own two hands!
The Cat Claws! Is he serious?!
Klahadore!
Kaya...
I can't believe... that you're a pirate.
These past three years, I spent so
much time with you as your butler.
Together we suffered, together we rejoiced
and laughed... I devoted myself to you.
Do you understand?
It was all so that... I could kill you today!
Damn you!
Do you know how it feels?
I'm a pirate, but I had to smile humbly
for some snot-nosed girl.
I went against my nature and sucked up to you.
Do you understand these daily insults?!
Kuro!
I'm going to kill you first!
What? His arm...
Now!
The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
Why are you guys...?!
Stop that, you guys!
All right! We'll let you off with just that!
You guys just gotta get out of here!
Captain! Don't be such a poophead!
We're gonna fight, too!
You idiots! Get out of here, now!
Jango!
I'll handle these fools.
You take care of Miss Kaya.
Kill her!
I'm on it.
Dammit... I can't move...
Usopp Pirates!
Y-Yes, sir?!
Protect Kaya!
Usopp-san!
Take Kaya and get away from here!
That's the most important task there is!
Don't tell me you can't!
Okay!
He sure knows how to talk all big.
Kaya-san! This way!
He basically just told 'em to run away...
They can't run!
Whoa!
You stay there.
Zoro!
Go, Jango!
Okay!
I won't let you!
Just go!
I know!
Dammit!
How pointless. I know very well
just how weak Kaya is.
You lived with her for three years!
Don't you even have a shred of pity?!
No.
I refuse to let you... have your way...
Usopp!
Dammit... I can't... move...
Just stay on the ground there.
You'd be no match for Jango anyway.
Even if I am no match for him...
I will protect them!
...will... protect... them...!
I'm captain of the Usopp Pirates!
I'm a brave warrior of the sea!
I won't let you lay a finger on the village!
I will... protect them... no matter what!
Laugh at Usopp again...
and I will thrash you all!
Luffy! Me and Usopp are gonna
chase that freak! That a problem?
Nope! Hurry!
Who gave you permission to pass this hill?
I did! Go, guys!
And another!
Why is an outsider like you
butting into this village's business?!
Because there's a man
I don't wanna let die!
What a cheesy reason!
Gum-Gum Whip!
And Pistol!
Out of the Back Attack!
I won't let you escape!
Kaya-san, are you okay?!
There you are!
That's them!
There they are!
- Put me down—
- I'll be back!
That's far enough!
You're one step too late!
I wouldn't say so!
Yes! That branch was in the way!
What?!
Damn! Let go!
Gum-Gum...
My plan will not be disrupted!
Special Attack...
...Bell!
...Exploding Star!
Can you keep everything
that's just happened here a secret?
- What?!
- How come?!
You could be the village hero!
You need to clear up
everyone's misunderstanding...
Misunderstanding?
I was only called an exaggerator, like always.
Nothing ever happened.
It was all a lie.
Usopp-san...
And this incident has helped me
finally come to a decision.
By seeing you guys, I've come to
a decision to set out to sea
to become a brave warrior of the seal!
That's good!
You guys take care!
Let's meet again sometime!
How come?
How come? Maybe we'll
meet on the high seas!
What're you talking about? Get on already.
What?
We're friends now, aren't we?
I... I get to be captain, right?!
Don't be dumb! I'm the captain!
Episode of Usopp
Episode of
Sanji
In order to find the All Blue!
Sea Restaurant Baratie
Sanji
Sous Chef of the Sea Restaurant
Eat it.
Thank you...
I've never eaten food so delicious!
I thought I'd die.
I thought I was done.
It's damn delicious, isn't it?
I found a good cook!
Hey you!
It's a good thing that he gave you food!
Hey you, cook! Join my group!
Huh?!
So you're a pirate.
In any event, don't do anything
stupid to this restaurant.
The owner of this place used to be
a cook in a famous pirate group.
And the others are all hot-headed, too.
I see...
Anyway, you're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together.
Join our group.
I refuse.
There's a reason that I have
to work in this restaurant.
What a huge ship!
Hey, that flag is...!
Don Krieg, Commodore of the pirate fleet!!
This is going to be messy.
H-Hey, wait!
This is a good restaurant.
My ship became a wreck,
so I wanted a new one.
I'll take this ship.
Don't underestimate us seafaring cooks!
You damn worms!
So golden!
Steel armor? What a piece of crap!
Attack him at once!
You're damn annoying!!
Bullets from all over his body...!
I'm the strongest!
I'm gonna seize the One Piece
and become the Pirate King!
Hold on a second!
I'm the one who's gonna
become Pirate King!
Did you say something? Back off, kid.
I can't back off on this.
This isn't a game.
Of course not!
We have no time for an idiot!
Kill those cooks and take the ship!
Let's go!
Protect the Baratie!
Pops, can I stop doing chores
if I drive them away?
Suit yourself.
All right!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
He's a Devil Fruit user.
Boy...
What're you guys doing?
They're just cooks!
Pearl-san!
Don't be beaten by mere cooks!
Mere cooks, you said?
Ha! How impudent you are to beat them
using only kicks. Is that your policy?
To cooks, hands are most important.
I can't have them hurt in battle.
I'll take you down with this leg as well.
Oh! That's so cool!
Brat!
If you're not paying attention,
you'll get hurt!
Go to hell!
Fire Pearls...
...Surprise!
How dare you set the place on fire!
Aren't you afraid of my Fire Pearls?
I'd be unfit for a cook
if I was afraid of flames!
Damn Pearl! How could he set fire
to the place?! I'll sink you all!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
The ship...!
You...
Please stop, Sanji-san!
I don't want to kill you.
Ghin-san!
Ghin? Is he one of them?
Please, leave the ship without a fight.
Leave the ship?
No way!
Point that gun at me.
Why?!
If you want to die so bad, I'll kill you!
You—
Don't do it!
He'll pull the trigger!
Why? If you abandon this restaurant,
everyone's life will be saved!
This restaurant is
that damn geezer's treasure!
I took everything away
from that damn geezer...
His power... His dream...
So... I don't want that damn geezer
to lose anything else!
Little brat...
Watch out!
Pearl Cymbals!
The All Blue?
Yeah! It's a legendary sea.
Well, we're seafaring cooks, so we've all
dreamed of that sea at one point.
Right?
A sea where fish from all four seas live...
To seafaring cooks,
that's an irresistible paradise!
I'll definitely find that sea someday!
There's no way that it could exist...
It's probably a big lie told by
a dreaming cook somewhere...
Pirates!
Steal everything!
Dammit!
I'm not gonna be killed...
I-I will find the All Blue someday!
So you've come to, little brat?
Pirate...! Ow, ow, ow...
You're very lucky.
We've been washed up here
on this desolate rocky mountain.
We have to wait for help.
I'll give you that bag of food.
You watch the other side of the sea.
As soon as you see a ship, let me know.
Okay?
Damn geezer!
I'm not gonna let him know
even if I see a ship.
I'm gonna survive on my own!
I wonder... if he's still alive...
There's that much food!
Did you see a ship?
Shut up! To think you have
this much food all to yourself...
Hey... What is this?!
This is all treasure!
How did you survive until today?
Where's your food?
What happened to your leg?
In order to save me,
you gave up your leg...?
That's right.
What about the food?
Did you give me all the food you had?
That's right.
What...?
I didn't ask for your help!
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
Why...?!
Why did you?!
Because you...
...you had the same dream as me.
The All Blue...
But they say it doesn't exist...
Of course it does!
Head to the Grand Line.
The All Blue surely exists there.
He gave up his leg so that I could live.
I can't repay the damn geezer
for his kindness...
...unless I risk my life for him, too!
Why...?
Why do you get up?
In order for this place to be a
restaurant as long as possible...
You can attack me...
...if you don't mind us killing the geezer!
Gum-Gum...
Stop it! Don't attack!
...Battle-Axe!
What do you think you're doing?!
I'll sink this ship!
Are you crazy, you bastard?!
If I destroy the ship,
they'll lose their objective.
What do you know about the significance of
the kindness I received and this restaurant?!
So you're gonna die for the restaurant?
What?
Dying isn't something you
should do to repay kindness!
That's not what he saved you for!
Being given life and yet dying...
...is something that a weakling would do!
Then is there any other way
to settle this matter?!
Cut the crap!
You guys can't do anything anyway!
Ghin!
Out of my way...
Ghin! You...
I'm sorry. He saved my life.
At least, please let me
bury him with my hands.
I'm sorry, Sanji-san,
but you can't defeat me.
You think so?
See you!
You damn bastard!
Saniji!
I can't... Don Krieg...
No one has treated me... so kindly before...
You coward!
Throw that gas mask away!
You're no longer one of us!
Is he gonna use the gas bomb?!
Deadly Poison Gas Bomb... MH5!
Dive into the sea!
I... I'm saved...
Ghin! Let go...!
Where's your mask?!
Ghin!
What an idiot! You used your mask
to help someone else.
Ghin... It seems that you picked
the wrong man to follow.
So you're actually sympathizing
with that idiot scum?
Krieg!
This will be your graveyard!
That's too reckless!
Gum-Gum...
Hit me if you can!
What the hell is that? How dirty!
...Bullet!
With just this cape of spines and spears...
...don't think you can send me to my grave!
Sanji.
Watch him closely.
Even if hundreds of weapons are built in,
that person can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
In a life or death battle,
if you fear death for even a moment,
you'll fall to pieces.
What're you talking about?
At least that kid
doesn't have any hesitation.
Is it about weapons to survive...
...or a faith that conquers the fear of death?
Faith...
The ultimate force means
the strongest equipment and power!
This will be it, anchor boy!
A bomb?!
The strong one is the one who survives.
Then that'll be me!
Get out! It's a trap!
Gum-Gum...
I knew that's what you'd do!
...Bazooka!
No good! After all, that's all you've got!
Drop dead!
Is it about weapons to survive...
...or a faith that conquers the fear of death?
Gum-Gum...
He...
...Bazooka!
What?!
Don't get carried away, brat!
Below us is the ocean. The game is over!
If I can get my arms and legs out,
the game is mine!
He doesn't flinch even for a moment.
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Hammer!
If Krieg's fleet and numerous
weapons are all power,
then the spear that the kid holds
in his heart is also power.
Faith...
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
I'll come along...
...on your journey to
become the Pirate King.
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Is that okay or not?
It's okay! All right!
I got a new friend!
For example, Saniji...
However villainous they may be,
if these damn bastards badly want to eat
and find their way to this restaurant,
there may be a point in our continuing
to fight at this restaurant...
Let's go.
You don't have to say goodbye?
That's okay.
Hey, Sanji!
Don't catch cold.
Owner Zeff!
Thank you for all the damn things
you've done for me over all these years!
I'll never forget your kindness...
for the rest of my life!
I'll miss you, dammit!
I'll see you again, you damn bastards!
Let's go! Set sail!
Episode of
Sanji
Nami
In order to draw a world map!
You're really strong!
Who're you?
I'm a thief who steals from pirates!
The name's Nami!
Wanna team up with me?!
Steals from pirates?
Big Bro!
Are you all right?
Where are the Merry and Nami?!
Big Sis Nami took all
the treasure and ran off!
Wh-What'd you say?!
They were nice guys...
I wonder if they'll let me join them again
when I see them next time...
I wanna be free...
Bellemere-san...
Oh, Nami! You're back!
How was your haul this time?
Couldn't have gone better!
But I feel like there's a hole in my heart.
'Saw-Tooth' Arlong
Captain of the Arlong Pirates
Betrayal is your forte!
Oh, is it?
Nami
A Leader of the Arlong Pirates
Cocoyashi Village
(Nami's Hometown)
Everyone! It's good to see you again!
Nami!
Nacchan!
You have as horrible a reputation as ever.
I guess. But Arlong's a reasonable guy.
Money will fix all this.
It's just a little more until our agreement.
No matter what, I'm going to earn
100 million Berries and buy this village!
The girl has a gift!
With Nami's sea charts,
we have no one to fear in these seas!
She's definitely vital to have
for the creation of the Arlong Empire!
But you promised to let
Nami and Cocoyashi Village go
once she saves up 100 million Berries.
Yeah, I'm a man who'd die
to keep my money-related promises.
You guys...
Why are you here?
What're you talking about?
You're our friend. We came to get you.
You're a big problem.
Friends? You're just a pathetic bunch
of people cooperating with each other.
Don't butt any more into
our affairs, you outsiders!
You can have your ship back,
so just get the hell out of here!
Goodbye.
Nami...
What's wrong, Nami?
Nothing.
We agreed you could
tell me anything, remember?
Now I see...
To think that someone
really showed up for her...
Friends, huh...
The most painful word for her...
I fell asleep?
Just a little more, Bellemere-san.
Just a little more,
and everything will return!
The village, the tangerine orchard...
and even my dream!
First you learned how to draw sea charts,
and now land maps! Amazing!
Yeah!
I'm gonna use my navigation skills
to travel around the world,
and then I'm gonna make
a world map of everything I see!
So this is your first step
toward your dream, then?
Yeah!
All done, Nami! A super
custom-made Bellemere brand!
No! Another hand-me-down from Nojiko!
I want new clothes, too!
Okay, let's do some work in the orchard.
You get my stuff 'cause you're my baby sister!
But I'm not your real sister!
We're not related by blood!
How could you say that?!
Nami!!
So what if you're not related by blood?!
Never say anything stupid like that again!
Whatever! You're not
our real mother, either!
You'd be better off
without us, wouldn't you?!
I wish someone richer
had adopted me instead!
Is that so? If you hate this house
that much, then leave!
Stop it, you two!
I will leave!
Nami!
Nami...
Is that why you came here?
Yeah, I ran away!
Bellemere-san would be happier
if we were gone.
Why do you think that?
Having two children costs lots of money...
You're old enough to
consider others now, huh?
Don't worry. She was like you two
when she was your age.
Bellemere-san was?!
She left the village and when she returned
as a respectable marine, we were all shocked.
A marine?!
I'll never forget that night.
It was very stormy...
Hey! It is Bellemere!
She's holding children!
Call the doctor! They have terrible fevers!
They're completely worn out!
All right, but you're badly wounded, too!
Just hurry!
Save those kids' lives!
That was you as a baby
and a three-year-old Nojiko.
She told me that she herself
was barely alive on a battlefield
when Nojiko appeared
holding you in her arms.
Your baby sister?
No.
When she saw your carefree smile,
she no longer wanted to wait for death.
You girls have a bond that goes
far deeper than a real family's.
Nami! I thought you'd be here!
Nojiko!
Bellemere-san is waiting
for you making supper!
Now, go home. She came for you.
Okay!
Pirates!
You seem to be in excellent
spirits, pathetic humans!
As of this moment, this island
is now under our control!
It's the Arlong Pirates!
The pirates from the Grand Line?!
Nojiko! Nami! It's dangerous here!
Hide in the back woods!
But Bellemere-san is at home!
One hundred thousand Berries per adult.
Fifty thousand Berries per kid.
We'll only kill those who can't pay.
This is terrible!
Endure it for now! If money is all
that's needed, it's an easy price to pay.
Will Bellemere-san be okay?
Our house can't be seen from
the village. So she'll be fine!
All right! Time to go, brothers!
Arlong-san! There's a house
outside the village!
That smoke is coming from a house!
We almost missed it.
Bellemere-san!
Are they back?
It's open! Come on in!
Pardon me...
Too bad. I'm a former marine.
What brings Grand Line pirates
all the way out to Cocoyashi Village?
What's so funny?!
How powerless your inferior species is!
Let's escape with her out the back door!
Hold it!
Doctor!
I must tell you a somewhat cruel story!
Listen closely, you two!
Bellemere-san!
These guys are real monsters!
Nojiko! Nami!
Bellemere, you idiot!
Don't waste your life
for some pathetic sense of justice!
Some issues can be solved with money!
Gen-san...
That's right.
If you can pay 100,000 Berries per adult
and 50,000 Berries per kid, I'll let you live.
Bellemere!
How much do you own, altogether?
Not enough. A little over 100,000...
Come, Bellemere.
Hurry and pay for one adult.
Thank goodness you have enough!
Now everyone in the village is spared!
Gen-san...
She's single. There's no record
of her getting married or giving birth.
Listen, you two! There's no proof
that you two and Bellemere are family!
Leave this island now!
There's no other way for you to survive!
Why do we have to leave?
Is it because we're poor that I can't
be Bellemere-san's kid anymore?!
Family ties over your life?!
Don't be such a baby now!
Thank you for your 100,000 Berries.
Thank goodness. Now they won't kill.
All right, we'll leave the village!
Nojiko!
Because if we stay,
Bellemere-san will be killed!
Nami!
Bellemere-san...
Okay, let's get out of here.
Hold it!
That's for my two daughters!
I don't got enough for me!
Bellemere! What are you—?!
Gen-san, I'm sorry. I just can't
say I don't have a family...
Even if it costs me my life...
I want to be their parent, even if
it's only in name. They're... my kids.
So you have kids, huh?
- Bellemere-san!
- Wait, you two!
- Nami! Nojiko!
I'm sorry! I was never able to do
anything mother-like for you!
That's not true! We don't need anything!
Just stay with us forever!
Bellemere-san!
These're your girls, aren't they?
Yeah, that's right!
Bellemere-san!
Don't die!
Promise me you won't lay a hand on them!
As long as you die like a good girl!
Help!
Save Bellemere!
- Take up arms!
- Drive the Fishmen out!
Just handle 'em as you see fit. Don't kill 'em.
Okay.
You're our first example to the others.
Die with your pathetic love!
Nojiko! Nami!
I love you!
No matter what happens, don't have
hate for this era you were born in...
Never forget the strength
to be able to smile at any time...
If you survive, lots of fun things will happen!
Bellemere-san!
Nojiko. Bellemere-san said...
...that if we survive,
fun things will happen, right?
I'm going to join the Arlong Pirates.
Hey! Th-That's an Arlong tattoo...
To buy the village for 100 million Berries?
Uh-huh. In exchange, I have to
join his group and draw sea charts...
If I ask for help from anyone,
more people will get hurt.
And I don't wanna see that ever again.
I've decided not to cry anymore.
I've decided to fight on my own!
No one will ever find it here
in this tangerine orchard!
When this box is full,
that means I got 100 million Berries!
Stealing from pirates?!
I'm taking advantage of this Pirate Era!
It's taken a long time...
...but it's almost 100 million Berries now.
It'll all be over soon.
I will be free of Arlong.
Bellemere-san, and then, I think I can
finally smile from the bottom of my heart...
What does the Navy want with Nami?
You simply need to lead the way quietly.
Guess I'll get started on
my final act of plundering!
Are you...
...the criminal known as Nami?
Criminal? I guess I am. I'm a leader
of the Arlong Pirates. I'm a pirate.
Mess with me and Arlong
won't sit by quietly!
A pirate? I was just informed
that you're a thief.
Our information has it that
you steal treasure from pirates.
All of the property you've
stolen from criminals...
...inevitably reverts to the Government!
What?!
Find the stolen goods!
Yes, sir.
H-Hey!
You can't enter my house...
Stop!
Why?! Is this what the Navy
should be doing right now?!
Under Arlong's rule, all the people
on this island have been enslaved!
You're a thief. Don't talk all big.
Colonel! This tangerine
orchard seems suspicious!
Dig it up!
Stop! Keep your filthy hands
off of the tangerine orchard!
I won't let you have my money!
That money's for— That money's for—!
This girl's money is meant
to save Cocoyashi Village!
What gives you the right
to take it away, Navy man?!
How do you know about that?
We've always known, Nami,
but we pretended we didn't know.
Because our hopes would
keep you from running away
from the island if you ever decided to.
You can't be serious...
If you're not gonna save our village,
then get the hell out of here!
Nojiko!
Dilly-dally and Arlong'll
go after your ship, too!
Mr. Arlong will?
What?!
You still haven't found it?!
It's 100 million Berries here!
Not a grain of rice!
Hey, you! How do you know
how much there is?!
Huh? I just got the feeling
there's that much.
Don't tell me he...
Don't tell me Arlong sent you here!
Who knows?
What rotten scum!
I can't believe the Navy would stoop
to being pirate cronies!
Arlong!
They're in our way! Make them leave.
Yes, sir.
What is it, Gen-san?!
What happened in the back?
- Nojiko-chan!
- The Navy shot her?!
Nojiko! Nojiko!
Heya, Nami! What's up?
Need help with anything?
This has nothing to do with you!
Leave the damn island already!
Nami! Where are you going?!
Arlong! Arlong! Arlong!
Do you want me to return
the village that badly, girlie?
Gather up 100 million Berries
and bring it here.
Do so and I'll let the village go.
Honest!
It doesn't matter how many years it takes.
I'll honor our agreement.
Arlong!
Oh? What's wrong, Nami?
Why the angry look?
The Navy men you have under your control
came to steal all my money!
Why?! What happened to dying
before breaking promises about money?!
I would die.
When did I break our promise?
Don't play dumb!
You teamed up with the Navy to—!
When did I break our promise? Let's hear it!
Damn you! Damn you!
No more of this!
Take up your weapons! Let's fight!
Gen-san! Everyone!
Please! Don't be hasty!
You can't die! It'll all be over!
You have to survive, or everything will end!
No matter how painful and
insulting it was to be ruled by them,
we swore to fight the patient fight
as long as Nami was cheerful!
But this is their answer!
Now our village has no hope for freedom!
More than that, we must make those Fishmen
pay for toying with that girl's kindness!
Wait, everyone!
Nami!
Just wait a little more! I'll work hard again!
I'll save up the money again!
It'll be easy this time!
So everyone, just a little more...
You can stop now.
Joining them must've been even more painful
for you than being cut through the heart...
You fought very well.
Gen-san...
Leave the village now.
What?
Stop it, everyone! I don't want to see
anyone else get hurt by them!
You'll die, you know!
We know.
It's no use! We've made up our minds!
No... Please, Gen-san...!
Get out of our way, Nami!
Let's go, everyone! Even if we can't win,
let's show 'em what we're made of!
Arlong!
Arlong! Arlong!
Arl—!
Luffy...
What do you want?
You don't even know anything.
Yeah. I don't know.
This has nothing to do with you!
I told you, leave the damn island already!
Yeah. You told me.
Luffy...
Help me...
Of course I will!
Luffy...
Let's go.
Yeah!
Which one of you is Arlong?!
Who the hell is he?
Arlong-san!
Don't make our navigator cry!
I guess you want to die!
Here we go, Roronoa!
Six-Sword Style...
The Tentacle-Sword Overload!
Demon...
Octopus Pot Stance!
...Slash!
Dragon...
The Octopus-Fritter Frenzy!
...Twister!
Hachi! Dammit!
Collier!
Epaule!
Cotelette!
Poitrine!
You bastard! The Thousand-Brick Fist!
Big Guffaw Palm Bo—!
Mouton Mallet!
You can't escape!
The Lipoweritzer!
Special Attack! Fire Star—
It won't work!
Special Attack!
Alcohol?
Lead Star!
How impudent!
You feeble species!
You know...
...alcohol catches fire!
Special Attack! Fire Star!
Gum-Gum...
...Bell!!
And... Bullet!!
Gatling!
I cried as much as I wanted.
I've whined enough, too.
I have to go. Everyone's fighting!
How dare you bastards
beat my dear brothers...
Aren't you getting
a little too carried away?!
The one I wanna beat up...
...is you!
Screw you!
Tooth Attack!
Oh? Where did he go?
Shark Darts!
A torpedo?!
Gum-Gum...
Shark Darts!
...Finger Net!
And...
...Spear!
You inferior human!
What did you do...
...to me, a Fishman?!
What the—?
Luffy!
That room is...
What's this room?
This is Nami's room.
These're all sea charts that
she drew for eight years.
The girl has a gift.
Could you use her...
...as efficiently as that?!
"Use"?!
What do you think you're doing?!
I finally figured out how to save her!
This room is the problem!
If she doesn't want to be here...
Luffy...
...then I'll just destroy it all!
Gum-Gum...
Don't get cocky!
Arlong Park can't ever be
brought down by you inferior beings!
Go to hell!
...Battle-Axe!
Luffy!
Nami!
You're my...
...friend!
Yeah!
Episode of
Nami
Ugh! It's almost like
the ship's gonna tip over!
Look at that light!
The entrance to the Grand Line
lies ahead of that light.
Okay, then!
Shall we hold a launching ceremony
for setting sail on the great ocean?
Sure!
In order to find the All Blue!
In order to be the Pirate King!
In order to become a master swordsman!
In order to draw a world map!
I-In order...
...to become a brave warrior of the sea!
We're going... to the Grand Line!
Yeah!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
In order to seize the Great
Treasure of One Piece,
this group of pirates
is entering the Grand Line.
Straw Hat Luffy and his friends'
adventure has just begun!
We gather together our dreams
And go in search of our desires
One Piece!
Things like compasses only slow us down
Gripped by excitement I take the helm
With a dust covered old map,
We can make sure it's not a legend!
If someone else's personal problems
Are riding on your own biorhythm
You're just over thinking things!
We gather together our dreams
And go in search of our desires!
I've only a pocket of coins,
But do you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on the cruise!
We are!