Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats reach the New World at long last,
the harshest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
It's erupting again!
It's right there! Who cares about the needles?!
Hey, what's this? The Transponder Snail is crying!
Hey, what's wrong?! You have a stomachache?
Fool! That's an emergency signal.
Somebody's calling for help.
If I pick it up, can we hear them?
Wait, Luffy!
More than 50 percent of emergency signals are fake!
Help me!
My colleagues are getting cut one after another!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
Samurai?
Hey you, what's your name?! Where are you?!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
...Punk Hazard!
It's hot!
This is the place. The name matches.
So this is Punk Hazard...
Those were probably not people's houses.
I think there were some kind of Government facilities here.
What's wrong, Luffy?
Is that...
What?!
Huh? Does it actually exist?!
No, it's a mythical creature! There's no way that it's real!
But look at those features...
I don't think it could be anything else!
A Heated Battle!
Luffy vs. the Giant Dragon!
Aw...
Awesome!!
How cool is that!
D-Don't be so impressed!
Cool!!
I'm outta here!
Wow! I like how he snarls, too!
Cool! So cool!
Who are you?
Don't come after me!
What're you doing, you fool?!
Hey!
The dragon just talked!
No way! You're hearing things!
You think so?
I-I'm not even sure it's a dragon!
Is it really a dragon?
Yes, it's hard to believe but...
...it has a lizard-like body with giant wings.
It looks exactly how it's described in myths.
No way!
Oh no!
H-He breathed fire!!
This creature is unreal! Am I dreaming?!
How exciting!
It's my turn!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
Bullet!
It didn't work!
He's well-armored!
Behind you!
Luffy!
He's looking at us!
Come on!
Don't provoke him!
I sense your presence-bu!
What?
Luffy was right!
That dragon just said something!
Three-Sword Style:
Ultra Tiger Hunt!
Damn! He's so strong and durable!
Take this!
Luffy!
I heard him talking!
See?!
I heard it too! But how?
Oh no!
He's flying!
Cool!!
Bu! Are you people allies of the Seven Warlords too?
The Seven Warlords?!
What're you talking about?
He's gonna breathe fire!
He's right above us! We can't get away!
It's hot!
Wait for me, Nami-san!
I'll keep making good desserts for you!
Oh yeah!
Let's change our perspective.
Pretend that you're in a sauna. It feels good, doesn't it?
I am breaking out in a super sweat of cola!
It's strange.
The sky above the island is divided.
One half is burning hot and the other is freezing cold.
I wonder why.
I hope Luffy and the others are not melting.
Huh? What was that?
What's wrong?
I don't know. I feel faint...
I feel lightheaded...
Maybe it's heat stroke...
Is this...
...what they call de-cola-ration?
Y-You guys!
Oh? I'm losing it too...
It's hot!
It's hot and that dragon said something again!
He said "the Seven Warlords."
Does he have something against them?
Oh no!
Luffy! Leave him up to me!
I'll cut him up this time!
All right!
In that case...
Ow, ow, ow!
Let me knock him down first!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
His body is hot!
Bu! It's strange but it's cool here!
Bu! The flames are cool-bu!
Oh no, not there! It tickles-bu!
Stop it!
That's enough-bu!
That's what I thought!
Hey!
You're not gonna believe this!
Somebody's stuck in the dragon's back!
Huh?! What's going on up there?!
Then the talking voice was...
You bastard!
Eat your own wing!
Fool!
Zoro! Here he comes!
Usopp!
All right!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Trampolia!
One-Sword Style,...
...Draw:
Lion Song!
He did it!
This dragon looks yummy!
We can grill it with the fire on the island!
That sounds great!
Cien Fleurs!
Nami-san!
This time I made a cold crepe with the Giant Shellfish!
It'll pair nicely with champagne...
Huh?
Oh? Are they sleeping?
Fog?
No, it's not!
Damn! I inhaled too much!
The gas made them sleep!
Is it a natural phenomenon, indigenous to the New World?
Or did somebody sneak into the ship?
I hope those four
that went to the island took a Baby Transponder Snail with them.
I have to let them know... somehow...
Two humans...
...one cyborg.
And their pet.
Tie them all up!
Alright!
It's good that they're pirates.
No one will care if they go missing.
Let's take them to the Master!
Luffy and crew have saved someone from the dragon...
But they are extremely shocked when they see his bizarre appearance.
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others have been captured by someone
and are locked in a mysterious room.
It is there that they see an unbelievable sight!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Straw Hats Astonished!
Enter the Puzzling Samurai's Head!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Straw Hats Astonished!
Enter the Puzzling Samurai's Head!