Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
However, there they find the New Fishman Pirates
have been plotting to destroy Ryugu Kingdom,
arm in arm with Vander Decken, who has been
stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil.
Then, two people rose up on Fishman Island, to change our hopeless history.
One was Queen Otohime.
And the other is the hero who freed the slaves - Fisher Tiger.
Let's talk. They were two monumental figures!
But what was their hidden angst?!
The Hero Who Freed the Slaves
Tiger the Adventurer
I'm going to tell you about...
...an incident that made Arlong rampage through the East Blue.
I want you especially to know about this.
Alright.
It all began...
...16 years ago.
Sixteen years ago, Fishman Island
Outta my way!
Thief!
Somebody, catch him!
He stole a lot of money!
Hey, outta my way!
I-If anyone comes close, you won't wanna see what I'll do with this girl!
Your Majesty?
Oh, Your Majesty! Wait!
Don't get involved with such a thing!
That's our responsibility!
--Wait! --Queen Otohime!
Who is that?!
Stay away! Or I'll shoot you!
I-I warned you!
Did I miss?
Dammit! Stay away!
I got you!
King Neptune's Wife
Queen Otohime (Goldfish Mermaid)
It's... Otohime-sama!
--Ouch! --Really?!
--My hand! --Doctor!
Your Highness! Let me see it!
It's a compound fracture.
With one hit?!
I don't mind!
Queen Otohime!
Queen?
Why have you done such a senseless thing as robbing someone?!
Shut up! You're from a wealthy, royal family - you don't understand!
I have 10 kids at home, who are crying from hunger!
All the more reason to not do it!
Q-Queen-sama! Stop hitting him!
You're far more fragile than all of us!
I don't care! I have to do this for him!
I have to teach him even if it shatters my hand into pieces!
Would your children be happy being raised by stolen money?!
Live a life of which your children can be proud!
However...
I have to... apologize, as well!
I'm sorry!
I didn't notice your struggles
even though I'm your queen and I'm living in the same country!
Your worries and your pain are killing me!
You must have had some awful reason to do what you did...
I didn't want to do it!
But I had no choice!
My store burned down. Somebody set fire to it and stole all my money!
I lost my job and my debts were increasing. And my poor kids were starving!
So that's why you did it. I understand... I understand how you feel...
--But you can't do that! --What?!
If you do the same thing to others, it will never stop!
I'm sorry!
But I'm sorry! We are guilty of not being dependable...
That's very generous... That's very generous of you to say...
But you can't do that!
I'm sorry!
But you can't!
I will change my life!
Thank you for crying for a good-for-nothing like me, Queen-sama!
Don't mention it. Good luck!
It's already unusual for someone from the royal family to come out of the palace
and walk around...
But to slap a citizen and sob over his story!
Otohime-sama is a very unconventional queen.
She's a woman of boundless compassion. Look, even kids love her!
Otohime-sama!
Oh!
I will do my best for you children!
What?!
Your nose is running! I hit you for your own good!
You look like a fool having snot running out of one nostril.
It's better to have to come from both sides.
How touching!
Yeah?
She was so passionate and full of love. Queen Otohime...
...went down to the island everyday and addressed the nation.
We have to relocate Ryugu Kingdom on earth!
We have a different skin color. We look different.
That's what humans say. And instead of waiting for the day when they'll understand us,
we should move closer to them to understand them!
The seafloor is 10,000 meters from the land.
That is also the distance between our ways of thinking.
Don't get the wrong idea!
The humans who come to this island are the kind called "pirates."
And the humans who buy people from kidnappers are the Nobles who are in power.
We've only known the bad sort of humans.
We don't know anything about humans yet.
There are so many kind humans on earth, I assume.
We should relocate the kingdom under the same sun!
Let's express our intention to relocate at the World Summit this year!
I need you all to sign here!
Well, even if it's Otohime-sama's idea...
The idea of moving closer to humans is... Right?
Don't say that.
Let's take the first step instead of doing nothing.
Well?
I'm sorry.
It's no use. History has proven it.
I'm home, kids!
Welcome home, mother-sama!
I'm home, Shirahoshi!
Oh, Shirahoshi, my consolation. I'm sorry to be late.
Oh, your nose is running but you're beautiful!
We were here with her so she was safe, mother-sama!
She was safe, she was safe!
Thank you, my princes.
Mother-sama, is your hand okay?
It's nothing.
The future that you four will live in,
I will change it!
If Otohime-sama wants to make a speech, she could do it by video.
Her strong Perception Haki by nature makes her the way she is-jamon.
She prefers to face people to win their hearts rather than speak from the palace above.
That's one of Otohime's guiding principles. And not even I can stop her.
But there are a lot of human pirates staying on the island.
She is protected by your friend, the pirate - Whitebeard's influence to some extent...
but you never know what could happen!
She knows that, too.
The world that Otohime dreams about is...
...exactly the same as...
...what our ancestors dreamed about
but couldn't make come true several hundred years ago-jamon.
What do you mean by that?
I can't stop Otohime.
Be sure to keep her safe!
Yes, sir!
Hey, fish girl!
--Yes? --Stay here and serve us!
I'm sorry. We don't do that sort of thing.
Huh? Don't be such a snob!
You're just a Fishman!
What? Does anyone have something to say?
Shut your mouth!
You make my sake taste bad.
O-Okay...
Jinbe, 30 years old
A soldier in Ryugu Kingdom's Neptune Army
So Otohime-san was a very unusual woman.
You're a crybaby just like your mother, huh?
Well... I-I don't know...
Were you a soldier of the kingdom?
There weren't that many options for a man from the Fishman District...
...who knew nothing but fighting.
The Fishman District?
That's where you're from, right, Hachi?
Sounds like a bad neighborhood.
Yes. It used to be a big orphanage where they housed children without any relatives.
But the orphanage started to get out of control
and was too much for the administrators to handle
so it became a lawless area that drew misfits from all over the island.
Fisher Tiger was the leader figure in the Fishman District
but he left the country to chase adventure.
And I was his lieutenant but I joined the Neptune Army.
Macro and the others became kidnappers even though they were Fishmen themselves.
And all the others went their separate ways as well.
But one day...
--Give them back! Please! --Take them if you want them!
Give them back to her! Do you know how many signatures there are?
I don't care!
What can you do with these papers? Huh?!
Hey! Cut it out! You're Arlong from the Fishman District, aren't you?!
Arlong from the Fishman District?
L-Let go of me!
You're a bit wrong.
Arlong, 25 years old
Captain of the Arlong Pirates
I'm Captain Arlong of the Arlong Pirates!
I make a living by hunting those lowly pirates who can't even breathe in water.
We're doing it on behalf of all of you - the Neptune Army!
Thank me with your money!
B-Boss Jinbe, don't just watch - help me!
Jinbe?
Hey, punk! Let go of that rookie soldier.
He is my man, in a way. And the papers with signatures.
I have no interest in them but they're important for the Queen. So give them back.
--That's Boss Jinbe of the Neptune Army! --Great!
"Boss"? That's a good title.
Sounds like you're running a gang!
Do as I say, Arlong!
Alright. Here.
Here!
Don't be mad, brother.
What? Brother?
It's been a while, huh? I'm your family from the Fishman District!
I'm not like you. You're still a pirate, aren't you, scum?
--Don't call me "scum," brother! --How about trash?
"Trash"?! I've let you say what you wanted, but that's...
Hey, everybody! It's the adventurer - Fisher Tiger-san!
--What? --Tiger-san's back!
--Tiger-san! --How was the trip?
--Brother Tai! --Big Brother!
Jinbe! Arlong! Looks like you guys are doing fine!
It was a long trip, wasn't it?
Yeah, a lot happened.
Stop by at my ship!
Maybe later. I need to go to Ryugu Palace first.
I'll take you then. He doesn't have use for a pirate!
Huh? Big Brother wouldn't say such a thing!
Guys, don't fight!
You are going to free the slaves?
Are you serious?
I am serious. I can't take it anymore.
It's like a living hell to be a slave isn't it?
As we speak now, they are not being treated like men.
But...
My mind is set.
I just wanted to tell you and the Queen in advance
since it will cause you trouble.
Please don't tell anybody about this.
What did you see during your trip?
I saw humans!
And then before long, something big happened.
Something's happened!
What is it?!
B-Boss Jinbe! T-Tiger-san...
...attacked the Celestial Dragons!
The Celestial Dragons?!
Fisher Tiger's attack on the Holy Land of Mary Geoise!
People called him the hero who freed the slaves.
And at the same time, he became a criminal.
I'm leaving the army today.
Jinbe, are you going to walk away from your mission?!
Surprisingly, I enjoyed my role of protecting the island.
But sometimes, paying a debt of honor is more important
than carrying out my mission!
Big Brother Tai did it at last!
We Arlong Pirates will join Fisher Tiger now!
Let's go, guys!
And that was how the ruffians from the Fishman District
who admired him assembled.
Welcome to the pirates' world!
We'll fight against the world from now on.
Those of you who are ready, come forward!
In order to make it impossible to distinguish
between those who were slaves and those who weren't,
everybody used the Sun mark to cover over the mark of slaves...
...and the Sun Pirates were formed by Fishmen!
Fisher Tiger attacked the Holy Land of Mary Geoise
and freed Fishman slaves from the Celestial Dragons.
Pursued by the Marines, they fight the humans in battle after bloody battle,
until he has a fateful encounter with a human girl with a painful past.
And a certain man finally makes his move.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Yellow Monkey Arrives!
A Trap to Catch Tiger!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Yellow Monkey Arrives!
A Trap to Catch Tiger!