Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
Ending the Matter
Whitebeard vs. the Blackbeard Pirates
Shiryu! You bastard!
What happened to Magellan?
What's going on at Impel Down?
How did you guys get here?
I think the fact that we're here is the answer to your questions,
don't you think?
Fleet Admiral Sengoku-san?
If you wanna know more,
why don't you check it out yourself later.
At any rate, I've teamed up with these guys.
Keep that in mind!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
I didn't have a chance to tell you but...
...I got a report that
the Gates of Justice have opened again
and an unidentified ship passed through a while ago!
That must've been them!
But the control room is under Navy control
and I didn't hear about any unusual circumstances!
How did they get here?
I'm sorry.
That's quite simple.
Before we, the Blackbeard Pirates,
set off for Impel Down,
I hypnotized the Navy soldiers in the control room...
...to open the Gates of Justice
for any Navy ship that approaches.
It turns out that it helped the others too.
Straw Hat and the others, you mean?
If I were regarded an enemy to the Government,
the Gates of Justice would've never opened for me
and I couldn't have snuck into Impel Down!
That's why I wanted the title
of the Seven Warlords!
But I don't need it anymore!
So you just wanted to free your crew members!
Correct! That's all I wanted from the start!
And that's all that matters!
You'll see why!
I don't give a damn about any of this!
Teach!
Look out! Captain!
That was close! That was close! We barely made it out in time!
You don't have any mercy, huh?!
Well, I guess that's to be expected!
You're the only one
that I refuse to call my son, Teach!
You broke the one and only iron rule
on my ship and killed a member of the crew!
I will avenge the 4th division commander—Thatch
by taking this fool's life thereby ending the matter!
Pops!
Marco!
Keep yourself out of this!
Pops!
Do you hear me?!
Let's get it over with, Teach!
I'm looking forward to it!
What is that black stuff coming out of his body?
Smoke?!
Black Hole!
This is the power of the Devil Fruit that I stole after killing Thatch!
The mightiest Dark-Dark Fruit!
Have a good taste!
Hey, Pops! Thatch is dead and so is Ace!
I looked up to you and yearned to be like you but you grew old!
You couldn't even save
a single one of your men from execution!
I tried not to kill Ace at Banaro Island for you!
That bastard!
Now, now—it's no use!
There's no Devil Fruit power that works against me!
Vortex!
Do you like my darkness, Pops?!
It drags in and nullifies
even the powers of Devil Fruits!
In other words, you can't create earthquakes anymore!
I can't believe he landed a hit on Pops!
Oops!
Don't you get it yet?!
How do you like my power?!
It's no use!
What a poor sport, Pops!
Ouch! Damn!
It hurts!
Arrogance, thoughtlessness... Those are your weaknesses!
Hey, don't!
Pops, don't!
I'm your son!
How can you kill me...?
You did it! Pops!
No, look at that!
Damn! I can't believe it! He's tough!
A final blow! Give him a final blow, Pops!
Just one more hit!
Finish him off!
Pops!
Pops! What's wrong?!
He isn't moving!
I don't think he stopped by choice!
On top of his worsening health,
he's been taking a lot of damage from all this fierce fighting!
Pops' body is already beyond it's limit!
Y-You damn monster!
You stupid old man!
Shut up and die already!
Pops!!
Kill him, guys!
Shoot him! Riddle him with bullets!
Pops!
Did you say that you're gonna die soon, Roger?
Yeah, it's only a matter of time.
Do you want me to tell you
how to get to Raftel, Whitebeard?
I won't go even if you tell me.
Not interested.
Do you know what
the World Government calls me these days?
"Gold Roger."
What? Is that your real name?
No, no!
My name is Gol D. Roger.
I meet people with "D" in their names sometimes.
I have a crew member who has it. His name is Teach.
What does "D" stand for?
Ah, you want to know?
Alright, I'll tell you.
It's a story from long ago...
Whoa, I'm out of bullets! Hey, give me another gun!
You don't need it!
Whitebeard is unconscious now!
He's gonna collapse
if you push him with your finger!
It's not you!
You're still alive?!
The man Roger is waiting for...
...is definitely not you, Teach!
Just as there are people who inherited Roger's will,
someone will eventually do the same for Ace!
Even if you sever his bloodline,
you'll never be able to extinguish their flame!
It has been passed down like that
throughout the ages!
And someday in the future,
carrying hundreds of years of history on their shoulders,
someone will throw down the gauntlet
and challenge the whole world!
Sengoku!
You and the World Government are afraid of...
...the gigantic war that will engulf the whole world one day!
I've no interest in it but...
...when someone finds the treasure, the world will turn upside down!
And I'm sure somebody will find it!
And that day will come!
The One Piece...
...is real!!
You bastard!
What great last words!
Pops!
Pops...
Forgive me, my sons.
I raised such a ridiculous fool.
You guys gave me everything.
This is it for me.
I've been traveling a very long time.
Let's sail out!
It was a great voyage!
That's odd! What kind of a pirate is he?
What is it that you want?
Hey, Newgate!
There is something
that I've wanted since I was a kid.
Oh, you have something? Why don't you tell us?
A family.
"A family?" What is he talking about?!
I owe you everything.
Farewell, my sons!
Old chap...
He-He died...
...standing!
Whitebeard passed away!
Even in death, his body wouldn't collapse!
And the way he mowed down his enemies
with wounds all over his body...
...was truly monstrous!
The total number of sword wounds
he received in this war was 267!
The number of bullet wounds: 152!
And he was shot by cannons 46 times!
And yet,
on his proud back...
...over the course of his whole pirate life,
there is not a single scar
he received while running away!
The Navy sweeps in
to wipe out the pirates as the loss
of Whitebeard slows their retreat,
and Red Hound stands once again
in front of the unconscious Luffy.
Meanwhile, Blackbeard prepares to reveal
what he's really plotting to the whole world!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Show Begins
Blackbeard's Plot is Revealed"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Show Begins
Blackbeard's Plot is Revealed