Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Now at Level 4 the Inferno Floor,
Warden Magellan has ambushed him!
I'll find out all about when
and how you broke in...
...after I pass down your sentence!
I'm not gonna tell you
even if it means death!
No!
Straw-chan!
Bon-chan!
Why did you do that?!
I told you that you can't fight!
The poison will harm you
if you get it all over you
but even one touch will be lethal!
Venom Road!
No matter how hard you try...
...you can't get away from me!
Magellan guards the worst prisoners
in the worst prison in the world!
He's the master of hell!
Make up your mind, Bon Clay!
There's no way to beat Magellan!
I'm sorry!
We have no chance to win!
I'm sorry but I gotta run!
I'm sorry, Straw-chan!
I'm sorry!
Don't you wanna give up now?
I'm not gonna let you execute Ace!
I don't wanna lose to you by not
touching you because you're poisonous!
I'd rather touch you and...
...give you my arms!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazooka!
Victory or Defeat?!
Luffy's Last-Ditch Attack
How thoughtless you guys are!
If you'd have just shut up and gotten away,
I could have laid the blame on Warden!
I'm at the staircase to Level 3!
We have some casualties
caused by the escapees' raid!
Yes, we have Buggy the Clown
and Mr. 3 in custody!
I told you to just be on your way
but you just had to fight me!
You stupid bastards!
H-H-He's strong!
Surprisingly strong!
Damn Hannyabal!
I don't wanna be tortured!
If I'm going to get tortured, I will...
...bite off my tongue right here!
Okay... I'm gonna bite... now!
I'm really gonna do it!
H-He's coming!
Hey! Get out of my way!
Outta my way, you fools!
If you don't wanna get hurt,
just let me go through!
Let's get Mr. 2!
Damn! Don't stand in my way!
Drunken Swan Soirée!
There's no way we can beat him!
I'm not gonna dream an impossible dream!
If I'd stayed there any longer,
I'm 200% sure that I'd be killed!
I've gotta run!
Don't look back!
All I can do is run!
Straw-chan!
You seem to have brought me to my knees!
We never know what a cornered rat will do!
But now you got enough poison on your hand...
...to affect your whole body!
It must really hurt, poor boy!
You still don't give up?!
Gum-Gum...
...Twin Jet Pistol!
Venom Blowfish!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
Hydra!
...Pistol!
It didn't hurt him at all?!
Fog?
Venom Cloud!
Damn it!
It's no use!
That poison fog is a part of me!
It's alive!
Your vision's blurry?
Your ears are ringing?
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
I said "it's no use!"
Why can't you see that?!
No matter how hard you try,
there's no way out for you!
I assume that you can't use your hands now!
My poison will take...
...everything from you in time!
Level 4, in front of the staircase
I'm going to bite off my tongue now!
I am really doing it!
You can't stop me!
I can't do it!
Dammit!
Take them away!
Yes, sir!
Fools!
Wait... D-D-Don't do this to me!
Please don't!
T-Torture stinks!
Stinks like ass!
You're right!
Wait right there!
W-Who is it?!
He sounds familiar!
Isn't he...?!
Swan Arabesque!
W-Who are you?!
You!
Mr. 2!
The third escapee?!
Damn!
That's enough!
Take this! And this! And this!...
Un, deux, trois! Un, deux, trois!
Un, deux, trois! Un, deux...
Take this 'n this 'n this!...
Un, deux, trois! Un, deux, trois! Un...
You're quite a fighter!
But you can't get away!
Ack?
Who are you?
So cute!
W-W-What are you doing?
You really don't know when to give up!
You want to rescue your brother that much?
It'd be easier if you just stop fighting.
Just close your eyes!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Hey, jailer!
Tell me the truth!
Is there something going on the upper levels?
No, there isn't.
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you so determined?
Portgas D. Ace is a major criminal
who is soon to be executed!
And you're an intruder who
wants to help a criminal like him!
I won't forgive any of those offenses!
Ace's execution in Marineford is...
...the absolutely final decision
provided for under the law!
There is nothing you can do about it!
Shut up!
Stay away...
Stay away!
Luffy!
This is pathetic.
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
Have you had enough now?
Gear 2!
Hydra!
Give me...
...Ace!
This is your punishment.
There is no way to neutralize the
amount of poison you have absorbed!
You will agonize for 24 hours
and then pass...
...to the real hell!
A... A...
Ace!
After being defeated by Magellan,
Luffy is tossed into Level 5.
Despite knowing there's no antidote for the poison,
Bon Clay makes a stand to save his friend.
However, standing in his way
is a pack of Army Wolves!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Because We're Friends
Bon Clay on a Suicide Mission"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Because We're Friends
Bon Clay on a Suicide Mission