Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and crew returned to Sabaody Archipelago.
And on their way to the New World,
they reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
...to invite you to Ryugu Palace-jamon!
Ryugu Palace!
Taken by the Shark They Saved
"A few hours ago"
We now turn the clock back a little.
This happened a few hours before
Luffy's group met King Neptune.
"Ryugu Kingdom, Mermaid Cove"
Ryugu Kingdom, Mermaid Cove.
It's sealed so tightly!
I wonder what's inside.
Let me guess...
If it were a treasure,
it would be in a chest.
Since it's just a barrel,
maybe it's full of expensive liquor.
It's... barely... budging!
Wait! That's good enough!
Loosening it up that much
is more than enough for me!
What? There's somebody inside?
No way!
Thanks a lot!
Thank you so much, my dear little Mermaids!
Don't run away from me!
Quick! Get to the water!
It's too late!
I'm sinking!
It's a swamp!
What's it doing on this rocky shore?!
You can't break free from this swamp!
It's bottomless!
I'm a Devil Fruit user!
I ate the Swamp-Swamp Fruit and became a swamp man!
The more you struggle...
No!
the more you'll sink!
Help!
Now just shut your mouths!
Don't worry! I'm not gonna kill you!
Somebody—
I told you to stop it, didn't I?! You fool!
Ishilly!
I just need you to take a nap for a little while!
My body is bottomless!
Now how much were Mermaids going for again?
If I remember right, they sell
at auction for seventy million each.
So with three, that'll be...
You have my gratitude, Straw Hats!
Thanks to them, I made it into Fishman Island
without even going through immigration!
I can hunt these valuable Mermaids
as much as I want!
This place is like a treasure island!
Ishilly!
I'm sure I heard them around here!
Ishilly...
"At the present time"
And now,
at Coral Hill, the port town of Ryugu Kingdom...
"Port town of Ryugu Kingdom, Coral Hill"
The Straw Hat Pirates?!
So they kidnapped the girls at Mermaid Cove?
No, I didn't say that.
They seemed like good people.
Besides, they're Camie's friends.
They may have threatened her.
No!
If we look at the facts,
the only ones there at the time...
were us guards, the Mermaid girls,
the gang from the Fishman District,
and the Straw Hats!
And now they're gone,
so who knows what they're up to?
Humans have a good reason for kidnapping Mermaids.
Young Mermaid girls are worth a fortune in the human world.
But you can't just suspect them blindly...
Have you forgotten how many pirates act friendly and then turn around and kidnap Mermaids?
Hmmm...
Prince Fukaboshi!
And Madame Sharley, did you really see
the vision you mentioned earlier?
That the pirate, Straw Hat Luffy,
will bring destruction to Fishman Island?!
Madame Sharley, have some water.
Yes, I did see that.
There's no denying it.
Your ability to foresee the future is well known, even to us in the palace.
This is very troubling.
I was going to thank them for saving my sister's pet.
Although the future's an uncertain thing,
I can't let them run loose!
We have no choice but to take them into custody!
"Around the same time"
Around the same time,
"High-class district of Ryugu Kingdom, Fishverly Hills"
in the high-class district of Ryugu Kingdom,
Fishverly Hills...
They're gone.
So who were they in the end?
To think King Neptune personally came
to invite them to Ryugu Palace.
Hold on tight!
Neptune!
Whale!
Shark! Shark!
Jamon! Jamon!
Neptune!
Why the stupid call, old man?
It sounds ridiculous!
Stop being so rude! Straw, you bastard!
I'm scared now! I'm scared of you!
That shark, Megalo, is my daughter's beloved pet-jamon!
She cried her eyes out while he was gone.
I wasn't aware he was
attacked by the Kraken.
You have my thanks
for saving him from danger-jamon!
That was just a coincidence, but I'm glad it worked out!
So that's the Mermaid Princess' pet?!
Huh, Pappagu-san?
But I thought you said you were
best friends with the Mermaid Princess.
Shh! Shh!
Ah, so it was a lie!
Anyway, I feel sorry for Sanji-san!
He wanted to meet the Mermaid Princess
more than any of us!
He was just born under an unlucky star, I guess
Still, a princess with a shark as a pet...
I-Is it really okay...
for us to go to Ryugu Palace?
He said, "Your friends can come-jamon."
so it should be fine.
Usually you're not allowed, right?
Then, why don't you just enjoy it?
I actually sent my sons to fetch you,
but they took so long I decided to do it myself!
Because I'm looking forward to the food
at the banquet as well! I can hardly wait-jamon!
I can't wait, either!
Hey, you two, quit drooling!
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
One of your friends is already there.
He's a swordsman.
He started drinking on his own
before the banquet even started.
It's more fun to have a banquet together—what a selfish lad.
I think his name was...
Is it Zoro?
Must be Zoro...
Zori!
It's Zoro!
My soldiers are still looking for your other friends,
they'll arrive soon, so don't worry-jamon.
Nami, do you know where the others are?
This looks like a great place to shop!
There's so many people here.
Maybe it won't be that hard to get some information.
You mean about Luffy and the others?
That too.
But what I'm most curious about,
is the whereabouts of my
shipwright master, Tom-san's, relatives.
This is Tom-san's homeland.
If his family's here, I have to tell them how he lived his life.
I know we just got back together, but let me do this alone.
It doesn't seem like there is any stopping you.
I have something I want to investigate as well.
You too, Robin?
Since ancient times, Fishman Island
has been rich with folklore.
So there must be one on the island...
a crucial piece of history.
A crucial piece... of history?
So we split up again.
Anything happen on your end?
Well, no, but also yes.
Hey, by the way, gramps...
Call him "God of the Sea—Neptune-sama"!
This place is 10,000 meters below sea level
so why is it so bright on Fishman Island?
It's not that it's bright on Fishman Island.
This is the only place in the world where light reaches the ocean floor,
which is why the ancient ancestors of the Fishmen decided to live here.
And that's how Fishman Island was founded.
The roots of the giant "Sun Tree Eve"
reach down into these depths,
and transfer sunlight
from the surface down to the deep sea.
They transfer sunlight?
You're saying there's a tree with glowing roots
that reach 10,000 meters underwater?
Yes, indeed.
The scientists have some complicated theories about it,
but, in essence, it's a mystical tree
that emits light from the surface-jamon.
And it's roots breathe, allowing us to get air from the surface as well.
So it's like the boss
of the Hustle Muscle Mangroves at Sabaody?
Hey, hairy old man, I'm hungry!
Hey!
We'll be there soon!
It's huge!
That's the entrance-jamon.
Yes?
It's me-jamon.
K-King-sama! I'll open the gateway right away!
Oh yeah, take this.
What's this?
It's a Bubbly Coral.
A tool used to easily create bubbles.
Most of the palace is filled with seawater.
You need a good bubble-jamon.
How handy!
Alright, let's go.
Neptune!
So fast!
Oh, I can't wait to see Ryugu Palace!
Wh-What should we do, Pappagu?
As a man who's been invited to Ryugu Palace,
I'll become even more famous.
Your face is twitching.
Here we are.
Ryugu Palace
Royal Palace of Ryugu Kingdom
Amazing! This is so cool!
Pappagu-san's house is nothing compared to this.
Don't compare them!
What a beautiful palace!
King Neptune is back!
We were wondering where you were!
Open the gate!
The gate is opening!
Welcome home, King-sama!
The palace looks fun!
It's my palace-jamon!
Make yourself at home!
I can't believe this!
How could you behave like this without a thought for your position?!
You left the castle without telling us again!
Going to the lower world
without your guards is simply irresponsible!
Oh, brother...
It won't happen again-jamon...
He's getting scolded...
It'll be too late once something happens!
Don't you know the situation in this country right now?!
Let's have the banquet already!
By the way, I brought the people who saved Megalo
when he was attacked by the Kraken-jamon.
Now let's welcome our guests!
Where is the Princess?
What is Princess Shirahoshi doing?
Well, King-sama,
just a little while ago...
What?! That's what happens when you don't guard the princess properly and keep her reassured!
Fools!
And don't you understand
that when you disappear,
you make it that much harder for us to do our jobs, King?!
In the first place...
It really won't happen again-jamon...
He's getting scolded again...
I sincerely apologize for bringing this up
Ryugu Kingdom, Minister of the Right
(Seahorse Merman)
when you've just brought guests here,
but I have important news.
Yes, we just received word from Prince Fukaboshi.
Ryugu Kingdom, Minister of the Left
(Catfish Merman)
Oh, brother...
Fukaboshi? What was it about?
You see...
I wonder how long they intend to ignore us?
Oh? Where's Luffy?
He was just here!
Can't he keep still for even a minute?
What's he thinking, wandering around
in the holy palace of the God of the Sea!
There's no mistake!
I can smell food mixed in with the seawater!
It smells so good!
Is it this way?
There's no water here?
The smell is gone!
It must be through those doors then!
Maybe this is the banquet hall!
He said Zoro's here already.
What huge, thick, solid-looking doors!
These walls look pretty solid too.
They look straight out of Impel Down.
There must be really good food inside!
It's pitch black.
Is this not the banquet hall?
But there is delicious smelling food here!
Then, is this the food storage? Well, whatever! I'll have some!
I'm starving!
What's this? It's all soft and squishy.
What the hell?
There's nothing but coral everywhere on this island.
What's this? It's soft!
Oh? Did I just hear somebody?
This coral's like pudding!
Is someone there?!
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing on my body?
Who are you, sir?!
Woah?! You're a huge lady... I mean, Mermaid!
H-Have you come to kill me too, like the others?!
I'll have you know that I'm not afraid of you!
Because I'm Neptune's daughter!
So I'm not afraid!
Not afraid at all...
Somebody! Father-sama! Brother-sama!
Whoa, whoa! I didn't do anything to you, did I?!
Oh, damn! What's with you?!
The enormous Mermaid, Princess Shirahoshi...
Due to Vander Decken's dogged pursuit,
she's had to live in the Hard Shell Tower for years.
Then, Decken hurls an axe at the tower
in an attempt to take Shirahoshi's life.
Meanwhile, Nami's group has been surrounded
by soldiers of the Neputune Army!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Weakling and a Crybaby!
The Princess in Hard Shell Tower"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Weakling and a Crybaby!
The Princess in Hard Shell Tower