Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
Only to defeat this man...
Three Swords Style Technique!
Better not regret it when I kill you!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Zoro!!
The Deadly Leg Technique Bursts Forth!
Sanji vs. the Invincible Pearl
All right!
They want to fight, too!
I'm getting fired up!
Pops! You promised, okay?
Once I drive them away,
I'll quit doing chores. Okay?
Couldn't ask for more.
If you do chores for a year,
this place will get messed up.
All right!
You said you were gonna become Pirate King. Are you serious?
Yeah, of course!
I'll definitely be the Pirate King!
I've come across tons of roughnecks.
But you're the first one in a long
time who said that so clearly.
I heard that you were an incredibly strong pirate.
Were you gonna be the Pirate King?
I forgot about the past.
I'm the owner of a restaurant
now and that's enough for me.
Guys! As long as we take that ship,
the Grand Line is nothing to be scared of!
We can get closer and make a surprise
attack on enemy ships more effectively
than pretending to be a Navy ship
or raising the white flag of surrender.
We can make a definite sneak attack.
It's true that no one would think...
that pirates are on board such a silly-looking ship.
B-But, Don... Even if we enter
the Grand Line again using that ship,
if we come across someone
like Hawk-Eye Mihawk again...
Are you still afraid of someone like that?
Huh?!
N-No...
You think an ordinary human
can slice up a large sailing ship?!
That's probably the power of a devil fruit.
Although those with devil fruit powers
are considered by society to be legends,
the Grand Line is crawling with them.
Mihawk must've used some strange
power when he sliced up the ship.
Even that straw hat brat is a mere
pirate once he enters the Grand Line.
But Red Leg Zeff traveled there for a year.
I can't but think that he had ways
of confronting those monsters.
And those methods must be written in his logbook.
If we're lucky, so is information on the One Piece.
I see... That's our Don Krieg!
So long as we have that ship and the logbook,
we'll find a way to the One Piece again!
Got that, guys?! Let's go!
We'll take over the restaurant!
– Yeah!
This ship belongs to us... to the cooks!
We can't let them have it...
no matter what happens!
N-Now... what do we do to operate this again?
Hurry up!
As it stands, the restaurant will be a battlefield...
I wish there was a restaurant
in the middle of the sea...
I was thinking that if I could leave this place alive,
I'd build a restaurant as my final purpose in life...
A restaurant as my final purpose in life...
Go to the operating room and open up the fins.
What? Open up the fins?
That's gonna give a foothold to the enemy!
That's fine. We can't make the inside
of this restaurant a battlefield.
If it becomes a battlefield,
that damn geezer will complain.
Did you say something, you damn brat?
Yeah, I said you like to complain!
Now, go.
O... Okay...
Here they come! They're finally coming!
Here I come! Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Ugh! He's flying over here!
And Gum-Gum...
...Giant Scythe!
Hey, that chore boy is pretty good!
– J-Just what the heck...
– ...is he...
The Grand Line is crawling with guys like this?
– Sanji!
– Hmm?
Watch carefully how he fights.
Don't take your eyes off him until
the moment this fight comes to an end.
To think that you attack the restaurant after they gave you food...
I'll beat up an ungrateful jerk like you!
So you actually want to fight on
the water when there's little foothold?
Those with devil fruit powers are
helpless in the sea. I know that much.
– Anchor boy!
– Instead, I can stretch.
Sanji! The fins are gonna open up now!
– Hmm?
– What's going on?
From the sea...
...a foothold has appeared!
Whoa! Check that out!!
We'll fight to the utmost, you damn pirates!
I see. You set up that battlefield so that
the restaurant itself won't be damaged.
That works out for us too,
since that ship's gonna be ours.
I want this ship all the more.
We won't let you have this restaurant!
That's right! Don't make light of us!
We're fighting cooks!
Take sail!
The Baratie's sea battle weapon, Mackerel Head 1!
If you don't wanna die, get out of here now!
What the hell is that?
That's so cool! I want it!
– Paddle faster!
– I'm paddling as fast as I can!
Fire!!
I'm gonna sink!
– All right! Good job!
– Patty! Carne! Get them!
They're pretty good!
Don't look away! We're aiming at him!
Yeah!
Krieg! Be prepared!!
Watch how powerful the Sea Restaurant
Baratie's sea battle weapon is!
What? Did we bump into something?
Hmm? We can't move!
I'm Don Krieg!
I'm the man who will rule the world's oceans!
I told you that's gonna be me!
I don't have time for your games!
What Herculean strength he has!
It's coming this way!
The restaurant will be destroyed!
– Sanji!
– W-With one kick?!
Wh-What strong legs!
He kicked back that weird boat!
That leg technique...
There goes! Sanji's kick!
He's pretty good!
You son of a bitch, Sanji!
Are you trying to crush your allies?
– Yeah...
– Don't "yeah" us, you crazy stew!
You almost lost powerful assets,
you stupid spaghetti!
Do you really think you have
time to crack jokes, cooks?
Let's get them!
Even with a weapon, a cook's a cook.
We're expert fighters who're in
a whole other league from you.
Now, be good little cooks and go
find a land restaurant to cook for.
Hey, you guys! Why are you letting
those guys beat you up so easily?!
Do you still call yourselves fighting cooks?!
Well, they're strong!
They're totally different from
those we've fought before!
Don't lump us in with those average pirates.
We're the Krieg Pirates,
the rulers of the East Blue.
Just decree to them... that the ship
already belongs to the Krieg Pirates!
Don't be mistaken.
We won't let you take even
one step into the restaurant.
He's exactly right!
I've been a cook for more than ten years.
I visited 300 restaurants.
I got fired for causing a scuffle
all the time and I lived a rough life.
This is the place we finally came to
after going to restaurant after restaurant...
Anybody there?!
Is this the restaurant run by Red Leg Zeff?!
This "Damn Cooks Wanted" better be true!
Yeah, it's true.
Be they arch rogues or jail breakers,
if they badly want to eat and
find their way to this restaurant,
we'll feed them until they're stuffed.
Can you handle that?!
Y-Yes, sir!
We can't serve such a nasty
soup to the customers!
What did you hit me for?!
That's a sign for determination!
Shut up!
Scuffles... cooking...
We're allowed to do whatever we like.
There's no other restaurant as good as this.
So they say. Got that, Krieg?
Committing ourselves to cooking
every day is a fierce battle.
Compared to that, the pirates
we're facing today are nothing!
He's exactly right!
– Fight!
– Yeah!
– Protect Owner!!
– Protect the restaurant!!
Th-That's...
Hmm...
Just what're you guys doing?
What's with that guy?
Unassailable! Hence invincible!
When someone says,
"Pearl-San, the Invincible Shield
of the Krieg Pirates," they mean me!
Pearl-San!
Patty! Carne! Are you all right?!
They're not all right, because they
took my killer punch, "Pearl Surprise."
Whoa! This is a nice knife. I'll take it.
Hmm? Hey, let go. Give it to me!
Let it go, you damn loser!
He's really got some good kicks!
I didn't come to like him for nothing!
A kitchen knife is a cook's soul.
Don't you amateurs carelessly put hands on it!
Sanji...
Hold this tight and stay down there.
I'll take care of them.
We won't be beaten by a mere cook!
A mere cook, you said?
I'm gonna cut you in three, you bastards!
Ha! How impudent you are
to beat them using only kicks.
Is that your policy?
To cooks, hands are most important.
I can't have them hurt in battle.
I'll take you down with this leg as well.
Take me down? That's impossible.
I'm an invincible man that won
all 61 of my battles unharmed.
I've never shed blood in a battle,
not even a drop.
Winning unharmed is the very proof of my power.
I'm a shield man and a gentleman.
I'm refined, aren't I?
Was that supposed to be a gag?
It wasn't funny at all.
Hey, straw hat brat!
If you're not paying attention, you'll get hurt!
Even battleship cannons don't work on me.
I come out of any attack unharmed!
Boy, that startled me.
Good thing I didn't fall in the sea.
What?
Ahh... This isn't good.
Blood! Oh, no!
Pearl-San, don't worry.
– It's just a nosebleed!
– It's not a wound from fighting!
– Please calm down, Pearl-San!
– What's going on?
Th-Th-Th-These guys are dangerous!
What's with him? He's acting strange.
What about his nosebleed?
Stop it, Pearl! It's just a nosebleed!
Don't lose your cool!
What the heck is he about to do?
Danger! Danger! Danger!!
Oh, no! It's started!
When Pearl-San gets upset, he catches fire!
What was that?
Fire Pearls... Special Treat!!
Ouch!
Pearl-San! Please stop!
Burn!
With this flame and the flame shield,
you have no idea how invincible I am!
That idiot! Is he going to burn down
the ship that we're gonna take over?
– Ow, ow, ow, ow...
– Dammit!
Crap! There's no escape from a sea
of flames in the middle of the sea!
This isn't good!
The restaurant will catch fire!
This restaurant will burn?
– Burn! Burn!
– You son of a bitch!
You idiot! You'll get burned, Sanji!
I'm not just gonna let you...
burn this restaurant down!
H-He's so reckless!
Does he want to turn into a human torch?!
When even fierce animals would
stay away from Fire Pearls...
You fool! I'd be unfit to be
a cook if I was afraid of flames!
D-Dammit! What a refined guy he is!
Here I come!
Ahh! That hit him good!
He broke through Invincible Pearl-San's wall!
What's with this cook? He's really crazy.
Y-Y-You son of a bitch!
Fire! I need more fire!
I need to feed more Fire Pearls!
Ahh! The restaurant will catch fire!
If the fire gets into the kitchen,
the restaurant will be blown away!
Owner! Please get out of there! Owner!!
M-My Fire Pearls...
Something like that is child's play!
The gust from his kick put out the flame!
What the hell?!
That's definitely a divine technique!
So Red Leg Zeff is still strong?!
Pops is really cool! I'm impressed!
Now that it's come to this,
I'll sink you all with the fins
before the restaurant catches fire!
Sanji! Watch out!!
Oh, no! He's surrounded by fire!
– Ow, ow, ow...
– Chore boy!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
– Ow, ow, ow...
– He hit that iron ball back!
Ow, ow, ow!
Pearl-San is really down this time!
– Pearl-San is...
What the heck?
That guy sure is dumb.
Geez... They're all...
In the end, I can only count on myself...
The battle ends here.
That's right! Shoot Red Leg Zeff!
All we need to do is kill him.
Then the restaurant will be ours!
There's no way I'm gonna
let them take this restaurant!
Taking a hostage! That's dirty!
I'm gonna kick that bastard's ass!
Butt out, chore boy!
Keep your hands out of this!
Then, is it okay to use my legs?
I'm gonna cut you in three,
you damn Straw Hat!
I can't let the damn geezer's
purpose in life get taken away!
Next time, on One Piece:
Zeff and Sanji's Dream!
The Illusory All Blue!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Zeff and Sanji's Dream!
The Illusory All Blue!