We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for... ONE PIECE
Compasses and stuff'll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Blast through the stingy night!
We've no interest in treasure chests
Pockets bulging with dreams, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
So you're gonna join our crew now, right?
I promised one of my comrades something.
I must tend to that first
or I will lose face!
Yeah. You're talking
about Laboon, aren't you?
I know all about it.
Franky and Robin told me.
Huh? Oh, that's right.
Laboon! That is the name of the whale.
He is at a certain cape--
Listen, Brook! We met Laboon
at Twin Cape. Honest!
J-Just a moment, please!
I'm shocked! This is so sudden.
Is it true? Did you actually meet Laboon?
Yup.
Is that right?
He's doing well?
I have never been this happy in my life!
Brook's Past
A Sad Farewell with His Cheerful Comrade
Laboon...
Rumbar Pirates
Musician & Swordsman
Hi, everyone! I hope you're doing well.
It's morning!
Brook
[Fifty years ago, 38 years old]
Let's start the day with a song!
Eh... This week, Power
Tune will be presenting
the famous song, "The Black
Handkerchief of Happiness."
Everyone, feel free to join in!
White handkerchief,
don't let him find you
Run for it
White handkerchief,
Don't let the octopus catch you
That's a stain
And now a squid is coming
S-Stop it! Not so loud in the morning!
There is another stain
I'll get up! I'll get up, Brook!
White handkerchief
I'm up! I'm wide awake!
Covered in stains, you're
the black handkerchief of happiness
Hey, Brook. Play that one
song--ballad version.
Roger! That's your favorite, Captain!
It's a whale!
It's the one from yesterday...
You're still here? Go look for your pod!
Isn't it adorable?
Hey, how long are you gonna follow us?
I bet your mama's worried.
Here! Eat up, Laboon!
Oh, man! When did you name him?
We're under attack!
Are you two okay?
P-Please help us! He's severely wounded!
Captain, an injured man fell overboard!
Toss him a life preserver!
We'll save him later.
It's not like I can swim...
I guess that's all I can do.
You're a lifesaver, Laboon!
Hey, we're okay!
Laboon!
Shhh! No, no, Laboon.
Don't wake everyone up.
I'll sing for you when the sun rises.
All right! Everyone, sing that song!
Laboon, are you cold?
Treasure! We found treasure, Laboon!
We're gonna party today!
Sea monster sighting!
What?!
Protect Laboon!
Yeah!
We won't go easy on anyone
who picks on Laboon!
Yay!
Laboon!
Laboon, are you all right?
Thank goodness!
I'm so glad!
That's not an option, Laboon.
Please hang tight and wait here.
Be a good boy, okay?
I think like he likes you best, Brook.
No kidding!
It's because Laboon loves music!
Nope! The shape of your head
makes him think you're kin.
Huh?
Is that right?
Could you try to reason with him?
We tried to talk to him,
but he wasn't willing to listen to us.
You understand, don't you?
We aren't strong enough to
protect him from here on out.
He's still a child.
There is no way we could
take him to the Grand Line.
Please hear me out.
Now, now! The music will have to wait.
It's true that we're comrades,
but you're a whale and--
The Grand Line is dangerous! Honest!
Maybe you could come if you were an adult.
But there will be ferocious beasts unlike
anything we've seen in the West Blue!
Laboon, listen to--
Nope. He wouldn't listen to a word I said.
He wouldn't?
Maybe we should sing that song for a while.
That would have the opposite effect!
Captain!
Forget it! I know it's hard,
but avoid eye contact with him.
You are not allowed to sing or play your
instruments until Laboon leaves our ship.
Laboon...
The sails are about to rip, Captain!
The rudder isn't responding!
Keep the rudder steady! Pull up the sails!
We'll ride the storm!
The entrance to the Grand Line
awaits us on the other side!
Captain, there's light! Light dead ahead!
Look! The guiding light points
to the Grand Line's entrance.
Sweet!
Yay!
Captain, it's time!
Does anyone see Laboon?
No, I haven't seen hide
nor hair of him for a week.
I feel bad for him, but
it was for his own good.
With any luck, he can return to his pod.
Men, are you mentally ready for this?
Yeah! We're ready when you are!
Let's go to the greatest ocean in the world!
Yeah!
I am Crocus, the lighthouse keeper.
Congratulations on crossing Reverse Mountain.
Welcome to the Pirates' Graveyard.
Oh, ouch! Don't jinx us, man!
I'm the captain of the
Rumbar Pirates, Yorkie.
In the West Blue, I've made a bit of a
reputation for myself as "Calico" Yorkie.
Sorry, Crocus-san, but our ship
took a pretty bad beating...
You're welcome to stay as long as you like,
but provide my meals while you're here!
Dang! You want to sponge
off a bunch of pirates?
Okay, cool! Please celebrate with us.
We're going to throw a party today!
By the way, is the whale
that came with you a pet?
Geh!!
Laboon!
You came with us? That was--
Brook!
Laboon, thank you! This
is great! I'm so happy!
You're injured?! I can't believe
you braved those stormy waters!
That was nuts, Laboon!
Hey, Brook! Let's sing that song.
Captain, you sure love that song.
You bet! It's perfect for pirates!
Laboon, you like it too, don't you?
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho!
Time to ship out Binks' Brew!
The sea breeze blows us to who-knows-where,
let the waves be our guide!
O'er across the ocean tide, the sunset stirs, going wild!
Look to the skies! Watch the circling birds as they sing and pass us by!
Crocus-san, would you like to make a request?
Brook, you can play anything, can't you?
Fare thee well to the weaver's town,
to the harbor as well...
Sing a booming song, a song for us casting off!
Pirates love to sing!
Oh, the gold and silver waves, all of 'em turnin' to sea spray!
As we journey off t'ward the ends of the high seas!
Please understand. You can't
repeat what you did last time.
The Grand Line is too dangerous.
I'm afraid that you are simply
too small to take with us!
Listen to me.
We have no idea what to
expect from here on out.
Now what do you think everyone would do
if harm should come your way?
We wouldn't hesitate to save you.
We'd try, even if that spelled
the end of the Rumbar Pirates!
Please understand! I'm begging you.
I don't want to leave you, either.
You don't know how hard
it was for me last time!
But... But...!
We aren't leaving him.
Captain!
Laboon! Wait for us!
We're going to travel straight--
just straight--across this ocean!
And you know what, Laboon?
Amazingly enough, our ship will return
to the other side of the Red Line.
We'll cross the wall again
and return to this cape.
Please wait for us!
You just have to hang tight
for two or three years.
Then you'll get to see everyone again!
Captain!
Isn't that right, Brook?
Yes! I swear that we will come back for you.
By then, you should be big and strong.
--Later!
--See ya, Laboon!
Take care!
Laboon, let's go on adventures
together all across the ocean!
We're buddies!
--Thank you!
--Goodbye!
--Laboon!
I'm so glad you understand!
Thank you, Laboon!
Laboon! We'll now go into the
Grand Line and travel around the world.
But you wait for us here.
"Three Years Later"
"Florian Triangle"
I will deliver this. I swear it!
It holds the song that Laboon,
the captain, and the rest of us loved!
I promised my crewmates
that I would take it to him.
It has the choral number of a lifetime
performed by the Rumbar Pirates,
who make crying children laugh!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Binks' Brew
The Song Connecting Past and Present"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Binks' Brew
The Song Connecting Past and Present