Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and crew returned to Sabaody Archipelago.
And on their way to the next stage, the New World,
they reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates are plotting to destroy Ryugu Kingdom,
arm in arm with Vander Decken,
who is stalking the Mermaid Princess.
Nice to meet you, Hody Jones!
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up
in the turmoil little by little.
Isn't there anywhere you wanna go?
Huh?
Of course...
there are a lot of places I want to go to...
That's what I thought.
Then let's get you out of here!
If something's thrown at you again, I'll deflect it!
He's formidable!
Take this!
Zoro!
I thought you'd been captured!
I heard the sounds of a festival...
so I let myself out!
An Emergency Breaks Out
Ryugu Place Under Siege
What the—
How did he get out of jail?!
What a fighter!
He warded off the God of the Sea, King Neptune's, attack easily!
If you resist, we'll have casualties on both sides.
Surrender with good grace-jamon, Zori!
It's Zoro!
You guys! Rupture the bubbles
around them at once!
Minister of the Right!
It's better for us to fight them in water.
Hurry up!
Ah, we've been driven to the wall.
You're right. This is no good. Hey, Nami!
Oh? Nami?
Wh-What the...
What?! All the water is gone?!
Sorry!
I just found a Bubbly Coral—this big.
Wow, that's huge!
Now...
let's continue where we left off.
Wait, wait. I'll fight him-jamon.
No! Don't bother, Neptune-sama!
No, that man is strong.
And I don't want anyone else to get hurt anymore-jamon!
Well, hurry up and get ready!
Let's go out, right now!
Huh? R-R-Right now?
B-But I... I mean, I still...
Still what?
I-It's too sudden so I still... Um...
I can't sort out my feelings.
Could you give me a little more time?
It's just a walk, no big deal.
Boy. Don't take too long.
I don't like you after all.
Alright, alright.
I'll wait so just make up your mind.
What have you guys done?!
No matter how I look at it, this is overkill!
He's right! You should regret your actions!
You guys started this fight!
That means you're my accomplices, you idiots!
We were gonna just intimidate them and run!
I was just enjoying sightseeing and shopping.
What's done is done!
Stop complaining!
"What's done is done"?!
Stopping by Fishman Island and occupying the palace
accidentally—what are we? Some kinda evil pirates?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Then we should've just
allowed ourselves to be beaten?
I kept telling you, we should've waited for our chance and ran!
I don't know the way out
and Luffy is missing!
That's right. Luffy is missing!
Where'd he go?
Dunno.
We really have to go
so don't be mean and tell me!
Yeah, where is Luffy...
Where's the treasure chamber?
No!
What? Why?
Stop pretending you're naive! Be sensible!
Hey, everybody!
When you're sad, let's sing and be happy!
Come on!
It's gonna be alright! It's gonna be alright!
Even if it's not, you're gonna die
someday anyway, yeah!
Shut up already, Soul King!
Neptune-sama, are you alright?
I can't believe that this is happening
to King Neptune, the Great Knight of the Sea!
I can't fight when I've thrown out my back...
I-I got old...
It's my fault-jamon. I'm sorry.
We should've broken their bubbles
and made them fight in the water earlier.
I can't believe we let them drain all the water...
Can't take it!
Hey, you bastards!
When the three princes of the Neptune Army—
Fukaboshi, Ryuboshi, Manboshi—come back,
you're going to regret this!
Yeah!
In any case, we can't stay here on this island.
Where's the Sunny?
Let's get everyone together and set sail as soon as possible.
But the coating on the Sunny came off
when we entered the island.
The Log Pose hasn't been
working right for a while either.
It's been unstable since we got here.
I can't take it! That Pose is not good enough
to sail across the New World.
You ignorant pirates!
What? This is not good enough?
What do you mean?
I'll tell you if you untie me.
Ding dong!
It must be Prince Fukaboshi!
This is odd. What are the guards doing?
Clank.
Hello? Who is it?
Don't pick it up!
Prince Fukaboshi!
Help us!
Shut up, you guys!
Prince Ryuboshi!
Prince Manboshi!
I think—Brother—something is going on-la-ti-do!
I agree! Are Father and Shirahoshi alright?
It's me, Fukaboshi. What is going on in there?
Lower the gate immediately and let us in.
And then what?
I can't do that.
Hey! What are you saying?!
Just be honest and tell him!
Yeah guys, tie me and Camie up too! They'll think we're your accomplices.
Zoro-chin's scary!
Prince Fukaboshi!
Help us!
Are you a member of the Straw Hats?
Fukaboshi! That's the Three-Sword Style
swordsman of the Straw Hats—
Pirate Hunter Zori!
It's Zoro!
Father!
You have Father too?!
Like you just heard,
we have Neptune and many other hostages.
If you don't want me to kill them,
prepare for us to set sail!
We'll need is our ship,
the Sunny, re-coated.
We don't know where it is so go find it on your own.
Also, the rest of our crew, a gloomy woman,
a robot, a raccoon dog, and a dirty water imp.
And Zoro, one billion berries in cash.
No, you stop!
"Dirty water imp"... That's funny!
I can't stop laughing!
Stop laughing, you fool!
"Dirty water imp"...
What about "gloomy woman"...
I understand your conditions.
I'll make arrangements for you to leave this country
with all of your crewmates immediately.
However,
I want all the hostages back alive!
That's fine.
Brother!
We have no choice.
This gateway is the only way
to enter Ryugu Palace, even for us.
It's impossible to break in elsewhere
since it's covered in several layers of bubbles.
There is one more thing. Zoro-kun?
I wouldn't normally tell you this
under these circumstances...
but I can't ignore my duty to Jinbe.
What is it?
This is from the former Warlord,
First Son of the Sea Jinbe. to Straw Hat Luffy.
He left two messages for me
to give to you when you arrived.
Jinbe...
Boss Jinbe...
Jinbe?!
Luffy said that he became friends with Jinbe!
Ah, he was in the newspaper with Luffy-san.
Although he's a pirate, he's a big figure
that people on the island trust.
Luffy's not here but I'll tell him later. Go ahead.
First, he says to not fight against Hody.
Second, he'll be waiting at the Sea Forest.
That's all.
Clank.
The Sea Forest?
Hody?
And that's what happened.
So I want you to find the Straw Hats' ship and the rest of the crew as soon as possible.
Roger that.
Hey hey, did you hear that?
The Straw Hat Pirates really did it!
They took over Ryugu Palace!
What do they want?!
No way! They looked like really good people—
I can't believe they'd do such a thing!
I can't believe it!
Can't believe it!
Yes, I can believe it.
Maybe I can't either.
I can't believe it, so what?
I bet they're the ones who kidnapped the Mermaids
and the prediction's right about them!
That's how things are progressing!
They finally showed their true colors!
I heard the two of them are hiding in the back of the Mermaid Café.
Guards are heading there to catch them!
What is this animal?
He transformed!
Kung Fu Point!
Sanji just got better!
Stay away from him!
"Come to Ryugu Palace"?
You're trying to catch us, aren't you?
Hey, guys...
Sanji, you should still be in bed!
Hey, are you ready?
Let's go out!
I'm sorry. I can't go...
Why? You said there's places you wanna go, didn't you?
But if I do something like that, it's going to cause a lot of trouble for everybody in the palace!
If I stayed in here for ten years, I'd go crazy!
It's in return for the food—I'm coming with you!
Where do you want to go?
Well...
The S—
The Sea...
The Sea Forest!
No, but it's just a dream.
I can't do such a selfish thing.
I can't just go out...
Why are you crying
just from saying where you wanna go?!
I-I'm sorry. It's because I summoned
all my courage to say it.
Please don't get mad!
You are scaring me, Luffy-sama!
You're such a pain in the butt!
What is that? That was so loud!
Is he throwing something again?
What a rude guy!
What's this?
What's this noise-jamon?
Don't tell me it's Decken again!
It's coming from Hard Shell Tower-jamon!
Shirahoshi must be in danger!
Are there guards with her?!
No, they're all tied up here!
What?!
Hey, pirates! Go see if the Princess is okay!
Huh? What are you talking about?
Neptune-sama! They'll find out about the Princess!
We have no choice-jamon!
Hard Shell Tower is on the northeast side
of the palace! You guys, go there now!
Why are we being ordered around by our hostages?!
Silence! Shirahoshi is my only daughter-jamon!
Somebody is trying to kill her day in, day out!
If something happens to my daughter,
I'll shove you all off the end of an ocean trench!
So she is the Mermaid Princess, am I right?!
Then I'll go there as soon as possible!
And...
can I ask her to show me her panties?
Hey wait, Brook!
Oh, I can't take it!
He's heading there with lascivious intent!
Now she's in a different kind of danger!
Wait, Skeleton!
You don't have to untie me but take me with you!
I have jurisdiction over the tower!
If something happened to the Princess, I would be beside myself with regret!
I assume... you...
wanna see her too!
Don't be ridiculous!
How lecherous!
He's wrong!
Sanji-san, excuse me for seeing her first!
I've always wanted to go to the Sea Forest.
For these ten years.
But everybody is kind enough to tell me
that it's too dangerous to go out of the tower.
And I am scared of going out, too!
Luffy-sama, are you really going to take me out of here?
Uh-huh.
Are you really going to protect me?
Count on me! You're gonna be fine!
Whoa-whoa, I'm not gonna take you if you cry.
Plus, to be accurate,
you have to take me since I can't swim.
I-I am so sorry. I am too delighted...
You really are a crybaby, huh? And a weakling.
But once you go out,
everybody will recognize you.
Yes, I'm sorry.
So I have an idea!
Mermaid Princess?! Are you alright?!
Hey, Skeleton! Look at the tower!
I can't believe this!
Those aren't knives or axes like usual!
It was the sound
of human pirates hitting the tower!
How eccentric! He's not normal,
that man—Vander Decken!
Huh?! V-Vander Decken?!
Oh, this is no good!
They're getting on their feet!
Does this mean the impregnable Ryugu Palace...
has been invaded by enemy forces?!
It's a surprise attack! The King is in danger!
The Princess is in danger!
The attack stopped, huh?
Let's go, Wimpy!
Y-Yes! We are ready, Megalo!
Go, Shark!
Megalo?!
Luffy-san?!
To the Sea Forest!
When Shirahoshi is discovered missing, Ryugu Palace is thrown into a panic.
Furthermore, a group of unknown pirates
have infiltrated the palace.
These pirates seem driven to attack
the Straw Hats at all costs.
Meanwhile, in Coral Hill, a critically wounded Hachi
appears before Sanji and Chopper!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Ryugu Palace in Shock!
The Shirahoshi Kidnapping Incident"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Ryugu Palace in Shock!
The Shirahoshi Kidnapping Incident