Until I can reach that great sky,
I believe, to that one tomorrow, hey
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one dream
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the good times
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Stumbling into the darkness, fumbling about to find the answer
Freezing up when there's no goal in sight
Umm you and me, yes, in this world where we share our feelings
I feel the beat guiding me, and begin to walk, oh yeah
Share the music, anytime
Share the one dream and believe in each other
Share the good times holding hands
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style
Beginning, expanding, this flavor is beyond imagining
I feel so good throughout my body, I know I can be free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far
Share the one dream, by telling each other
Share the good times and laugh
Share the one world now
I'll keep going until I can reach that great sky
Let's overcome it now, I believe, to that one tomorrow, yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall
I'll be there soon, I believe, to that one world, yeah yeah...
Come on, let's go everybody, oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go baby, baby, oh, we share the one world
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Seeking a ship coating craftsman
to help them reach Fishman Island,
the Straw Hat crew landed on Sabaody Archipelago,
where they met Rayleigh, a craftsman and the
former first mate of the Roger Pirates.
Luffy and company headed into town to
hide while Rayleigh coated the Sunny,
but Admiral Yellow Monkey, an assassin
dispatched from Navy Headquarters,
has already arrived at Sabaody Archipelago...
Hello? This is Yellow Monkey. Hmm? How odd...
Hello?
--Now! Take this!
--S-Stop...!
Hello?
Fierce battles broke out everywhere
between the Navy and the rookies...
It turned big--!
What's going on?!
He didn't do anything himself!
Well, actually, if I can't find him,
then that leaves me with spare time...
And if I'm not busy, I obviously
can't let a wanted man go...
Especially one like you,
with a 249 million bounty...
...Magician Basil Hawkins!
Speed is weight!
Have you ever been kicked
at the speed of light?
Captain!
Impressive. You far surpass what I imagined.
And yet another "Bartholomew Kuma"
appeared before Luffy and company...
--Get back, Luffy!
--He's one of the Warlords of the Sea!
A Warlord?! How come you guys know that?!
Don't let that attack hit
you! It's a shockwave!
What is this?!
He can do this, too?!
Hey! You lied about it being a shockwave!
Gear 2!
We know he's strong, so let's
go all-out at the very start!
Something's off here...
He seems different from last time.
He better hurry.
They're going to...
...get rid of all the rookies!
Overwhelming!
The Navy's Fighting Weapons, the Pacifistas
Unbelievable...
From his hands and his mouth...
Frightening!
Here comes another! Here comes another!
Here it comes!
Wh-What the hell are those things?!
They're beams, obviously!
Beams of light would make incredible
weapons, but that's just fantasy!
Wait... what are you doing?
Playing dead.
He's already seen through that!
Three-Sword Style...
...Gum-Gum...
...Diable...
...Mouton...
...Jet...
...600-Pound...
...Phoenix!
Yes! Did they get him?!
They're amazing!
This is a Warlord of the Sea.
I don't think it'll be that easy,
judging from their expressions...
He's that different?!
Maybe he's a twin, then?!
Yeah, it's a possibility!
Anyway, the real one would've
teleported and dodged our attacks...
More than that, he doesn't use shockwaves,
and doesn't got paws, either!
But if this is a fake,
then that's the real problem.
That'd mean there are
two guys who're this strong.
You gave me quite a thrashing.
Don't think I'm the same
as I was before, though!
Karma Exposure!
That must've hurt a little...
Mad Monk Urouge, a man who has
continually escaped death to this day,
has such power after growing in size...
So how can this be?
Hot!
That was Yellow Monkey's laser!
Vegapunk! You've recreated
Yellow Monkey's offensive abilities
using Bartholomew Kuma's body?!
I had no idea the Pacifistas
had already reached this point!
This is no ordinary situation!
Definitely not! Not even three
people worth over 100 million
can survive against a
Warlord and a Navy admiral!
Rear Admiral Drake.
Oh, I mean former Rear Admiral.
Don't tell me you're here to
conduct surveillance on them?
Go ahead, try fighting it.
I think your inside knowledge will make
your despair all the greater, though.
I suggest that you little
hatchlings exercise caution.
I'm here too, you see!
What another incredible sight!
A rare ancient Zoan type!
I've never seen one before!
Oh? I'm surprised red blood flows inside you.
What a rare sight...
As I said, I'm here too.
All you people worth over 100 million
are monstrous and frightening...
Demon-Conquering Form!
He disappeared?!
M-My eyes!
Captain Hawkins!
I... can't see...
I don't know what power you have,
but you do have a physical form.
You don't seem to be a Logia type...
Captain!
This is bad!
He's going over his damage limit!
He's really gonna die!
You'll be the first to go...
You did well to journey all this way.
Who is that?
Yo! Yo-yo-yo! Yeah! Yo!
Is this music reaching you?!
If you can hear it, stay tuned!
Navy Admiral Yellow Monkey!
Yeah! Yo-yo-yo! Yo!
He's "Sea Roar"...
Everybody! Listen to this fighting music!
Scratch!
What's this?
Here we go!
Check it out!
Got 'em!
Though I doubt that'd be
enough to beat a Navy admiral!
Whew, I managed to see
so much interesting stuff!
Well, it's time for me to scram! So long!
How terrible...
What a shock that was...
Yata Mirror.
What's that?
Hello?
Huh? Hello?
Oh, here it is.
This is Borsalino.
What the hell, Uncle!
You do have a Baby Transponder Snail!
Why didn't you contact me?!
Oh?
Oh, Sentomaru-kun!
Don't give me, "Oh!" What are you doing?!
You're on the island now, right?!
Oh, I wasn't able to get
ahold of you, you see...
Don't tell me you were talking into
the Black Transponder Snail again!
I told you before that the black one
on your wrist is for eavesdropping!
Oh, yes...
Whatever! Just get to work now!
The culprits have split up!
Straw Hat Luffy,
Captain Kid, Trafalgar Law...
Which do we start with?
Oh, you don't say? In that case...
108-Pound Phoenix!
Concasser!
108-Pound...
You idiot! What're you doing?!
Zoro!
Hey, Zoro! You got hurt so
much you can't even move?!
Forget about him, Luffy!
We need to beat this thing first!
Yeah...!
He hasn't even had the chance
to fully heal from last time!
Just standing up to him
must be pretty damn painful,
judging by that look of his again!
Bastard...
If you ain't Bartholomew Kuma,
then who are you?!
You look exactly like
the Warlord of the Sea...
What the hell's goin' on here?!
Another enemy?!
I got the toughest defense in the world!
As such, my mouth is sealed just as tight!
Who are you?!
I have no reason to answer anything!
I'm the most tight-lipped guy in the world!
And my name is...
You're gonna tell us, then?!
Next time, on One Piece:
"An Even Stronger Enemy Appears!
The Battle Axe-Carrying Sentomaru"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
An Even Stronger Enemy Appears!
The Battle Axe-Carrying Sentomaru