Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy had landed on Marineford
to save his brother, Ace, from execution.
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught,
Luffy finally succeeded in freeing Ace, however...
Admiral Red Hound dealt a fatal blow to Ace.
Pops!
Everybody!
And you Luffy.
Thank you...
...for loving such a good-for-nothing like me...
...who carries such despicable blood in his veins...
...up to today.
Thank you!
The Navy Headquarters Falls!
Whitebeard's Unspeakable Wrath!
Ace...
Did you think that I was dead?
But...!
Why are you crying?! I'm not dead, fool!
I promise that I'll never die!
How can I leave a wimpy brother like you behind?
Garp!
Look after my child!
His name is Gol D. Ace.
Did you know? We can become brothers if we exchange this cup of sake!
From now on,
we're brothers!
You've got to be kidding me!
Ace...!
Ace!
Ace!!
Fire Fist Ace is dead!
Straw-boy!
He's losing it!
His life is in danger!
It's Red Hound!
I'll get you this time for sure!
Straw Hat!
I'm not gonna let you kill him!
Luffy-kun! Luffy-kun! Stay with me!
Move out of my way!
The war is not over yet!
Take Ace's brother with you, Jinbe!
All right!
Straw Hat's life is how Ace will live on!
Commander... Marco!
We will protect him at any cost on Ace's behalf!
If we let him die,
it'll dishonor the Whitebeard Pirates!
Luffy-kun, hang in there!
I told you that I won't let the brothers get away!
Straw Hat!
Red Hound-san!
Pops is furious!
Guys, we gotta get out of here!
Hell Hound!
Pops!
This is the end!
Pops!!
Pops!
Pops.
Navy HQ is collapsing!
You bastard!
Whitebeard!
Admiral Sakazuki!
Don't fall!
Hang on!
Is it over?
How's Pops?!
Pops!
The plaza has split in two!
The pirates are on the other side!
We're completely separated from Pops!
Pops!
He still has this much power left
after his whole torso's been burned?
You haven't seen anything yet.
From now on,
I'm the only one who you have to deal with!
Bring it on!
Everybody, get on the ship!
Pops!
Think about why Pops stayed on that side
and the wish that he left for us!
Cry after you get on the ship!
Pops! Ace!
Hurry up!
Gather all seaworthy ships at the bay head!
We won't let you get away!
Hurry up, everyone!
Salome! I can't stop worrying about Luffy!
Forgive me for disobeying you and staying back to watch, Pops.
Hey, look! What is that?!
There is something behind the HQ building!
Oh, they found me!
And not just him!
Who are those people on the scaffold?
Ah... They finally noticed us.
It's you! How did you all get here?!
Why are they here?!
You bastard.
They're the most heinous criminals
who were so brutal
that they were erased from history.
He's the biggest of all living beings!
The pirate "Great Battleship" San Juan Wolf!
"Great Battleship" San Juan Wolf
Oh, not only did they find me but they know who I am!
"Corrupt King" Avalo Pizarro!
"Corrupt King" Avalo Pizarro
How nice it is to taste freedom again!
"Heavy Drinker" Vasco Shot!
"Heavy Drinker" Vasco Shot
Am I allowed to kill them all?
"Crescent Moon Hunter" Catarina Devon!
"Crescent Moon Hunter" Catarina Devon
I like you guys, too.
And the Jail Manager of Impel Down
Shiryu of the Rain
Shiryu of the Rain!
They're the Blackbeard Pirates!
Long time no see!
I'm glad that I'm present at your death!
Pops!
Teach...!
It all started with this man.
Blackbeard, driven by
his hidden ambition, attacks Whitebeard.
Whitebeard fights back, intent on avenging Thatch.
The fated battle begins at last!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Ending the Matter
Whitebeard vs. the Blackbeard Pirates"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Ending the Matter
Whitebeard vs. the Blackbeard Pirates