Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue his brother, Ace, who will be executed!
Inside the bay, Luffy and the Whitebeards are trying to get to the scaffold
but the Navy stands in their way.
The battle is heating up!
Why did any of them come?!
I deserve this! They don't have to risk their lives for me!
Don't do this!
Everyone! Why are you doing this for a guy like me?!
I'm your brother!
Kuma! Kuma, that's enough!
It's me! Did you forget my face?!
If you don't stop, I'm gonna fight back
although I'm a gentle person!
I don't know how you know him but you may as well give up!
It's no use talking to him, Emporio Ivankov,
commander of the Revolutionary Army!
You...! What do you mean?! What's wrong with him?!
You're a friend of Bartholomew Kuma I suppose.
He was once called Tyrant Kuma and now he is...
...dead.
Your power is not enough to beat me!
Damn! Get your jitte off of me!
You! Leave him alone!
She got me although my body is smoke!
Th-That's...! The Pirate Empress saved Straw Hat!
Hancock! What are you doing?!
Are you gonna resign from the Warlords, too?!
Shut up! I'm deafened by my own anger!
How could you hit and pin down my beloved?!
I won't let you survive!
I have never felt this much anger before!
I'm gonna cut you up and feed you to beasts!
That's the Haki of Kuja!
Kuma's Transformation
Iva-san's Blow of Anger
Wh-What's going on here?
Why did the Pirate Empress save Straw Hat?
No, she didn't save him!
She's gonna turn Straw Hat to stone!
I always believed that you'd make it here alive.
Take this.
It's your brother's handcuff key.
What?!
That's how diabolical the Empress is!
Straw Hat can't move now!
Has he turned into stone?
Hancock!
You just said my name again!
Luffy's hands... Luffy's hands touched mine!
Hancock!
Yeah!
You're so...! You're so...!
Thank you! I mean it!
N-No... No problem...!
Never mind me, you've got to...
You've got to keep going, Luffy!
You're right!
Thanks!
No way! He beat the Pirate Empress?!
He must've fought back
and thrown his weight high into her!
See? She looks so tortured!
He beat the Warlord so easily! How strong, Straw Hat Luffy!
Like that! Like that!
Like that!
I wasn't expect him to hold me so tight like that!
I can still feel Luffy's body in my arms and on my chest!
Is this...
Is this what they call...
...marriage?!
Snake Princess-sama!
Congratulation, Big Sis!
So beautiful!
Best wishes to you!
Luffy!
Hancock. You look very beautiful.
H-A-P-P-Y!
I'll make you happy for the rest of your life.
Honey.
Yes!
Honey...
Honey!
Luffy! I see it! I can see it!
A string that links us together!
A string that no one can ever cut!
It's a thick red string of fate like a big snake!
Luffy!
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat!
Perfume Femur!
You outrageous fool, stand back!
I won't let you pass through here!
Look! She's really looking down on him!
Looking down so much that she's leaning back!
Do you know what's
gonna happen to you after messing with the Navy?!
I can do whatever I want!
Because I'm beautiful!
This is great. She helped me out again.
Wait for me, Ace!
What did you say?! Kuma is dead?!
Then, who is this right here?!
He's alive! Stop talking nonsense!
Iva-chan! Ah?!
That's the bear guy!
Be careful, Iva-chan!
If you get blown away by him...
I'm okay. Now, Kuma, move out of my way!
Iva-chan, do you know him?
Yeah, sort of. But he's acting strange.
Seems like you both have memories of Kuma.
But the Kuma that you both knew and this one are not the same!
N-Not the same? What is he talking about?
That can't be true!
I'm absolutely sure that he's
the Paw-Paw Fruit user—Kuma!
Say something, Kuma!
He's pissing me off!
Although he has always been quiet.
I told you that it's no use talking to him.
It was just days ago...
The Government scientist—
Dr. Vegapunk modified him for the last time
and he turned into
a complete human weapon at last!
To be precise, he's the former Bartholomew Kuma!
Modified? Weapon? What are you talking about?!
In fact, he volunteered to be a guinea pig for a study to build a human weapon...
...run by the Government.
First, his hands. Second, his legs.
While his mind worked,
they modified his body piece by piece.
Stop lying! Kuma hates the Government!
He wouldn't sacrifice his life for them.
I know that he wouldn't do that!
Stop yelling.
I don't know what kind of deal he had with the Government.
Only a few days ago,
he still had his personality.
But now, he doesn't even remember
that he was born human
so he is no better than dead.
He is a monster who fights as the Government tells him.
He is Pacifista PX-0!
So you better forget about the past!
Kuma! What's happened to you over these past several years?!
Now I remember him saying...
We will never meet again.
Farewell...
...At that time.
What's wrong, Kuma?! It's me! Ivankov!
Wh-Where'd he go?!
Watch out, you guys! Heads up!
Pad Cannon.
Kuma, you bastard!
Face...
...Spectrum!
I'm watching you!
Galaxy Wink!
Heehaw!
How could you attack my sweet candy boys?!
I'm not gonna go easy on you anymore!
Here!
Kick!
That's how strong he is!
Among all people that I've met...
My face!
No one has ever forgotten my face in my entire life!
Oh, uh, hmmm.
But...
...even if you've lost your memory,
if you can't remember how scary I am,
I'm gonna beat it into your body!
Be ready for it!
He's recovered, so quick!
I'll take it from here!
You guys, go ahead and back Straw-boy up!
Roger!
Okay, let's go, Straw Hat!
Thanks, Iva-chan!
Get to the scaffold!
They suddenly disappeared in ice!
It doesn't seem like
Admiral Blue Pheasant used Ice Age again...
Where did they...?
This ice is not cold!
What's wrong?
Alright, guys.
Listen carefully.
Blah-blah-blah... Buggy is great.
Dah-dah-dah... Buggy is genius.
Right? That's how we want it.
That's nice!
And we want the world to be shaken by the arrival of the new hero.
That's a perfect plan!
Y-You sure?
Let's go, guys!
How annoying, Straw Hat!
Don't fall behind! The plan is called "Take Captain Buggy to Fame!"
Now is the time to execute it!
When we succeed, the whole world will be stunned!
All of you, do as we planned and watch what you're doing!
Are you sure about that plan?
Crocodile!
There're too many!
I'm too far away from him.
I won't let you get near Pops!
Don't stand in my...
...way!
What a pain in the ass. He's still messing around.
Brilliant Punk!
He's giant but so fast! How can I avoid him?
The 3rd division commander—Diamond Jozu!
How did you get out of prison, gator guy?
Did you like the Blood Pool?
Doflamingo, mind your own business.
Or I'm gonna kill you!
You have a dirty mouth. He-he.
Hey, why don't you team up with me?
Stop here!
Don't get in his way!
Keep going, Straw Hat!
Thanks!
Ace!
I'm sorry, Red-Haired.
I will not hold back my power.
That's...
...Hawk-Eye!
Now, I wonder if fate...
...will end the life of this child of the next generation here.
Or, if it will save him from this Black Blade!
Dracule Mihawk,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea, stands before Luffy.
A single slash by the world's strongest swordsman
easily splits a massive wall of ice in two.
How will Luffy fight back
against such immense strength?
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Great Swordsman Mihawk
Luffy Attacked by the Black Blade"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Great Swordsman Mihawk
Luffy Attacked by the Black Blade