Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After receiving an emergency signal, they landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
A branch of the Navy - G-5 - led by Smoker
reached the island while chasing after the Straw Hats
and got into a fight with Trafalgar Law who appeared out of nowhere.
It's you! Do you remember me?
Thank you for your help the other day!
Shambles!
What did he just do?
If there is some mastermind behind Law
and if "CC" are his initials,
I think I know who it is.
He is the former colleague of Dr.Vegapunk.
He is a scientist named Caesar Clown!
"The Worst in the World! A Scientist of Terror - Caesar!"
Caesar Clown?
Who is that?
Um, I have something on my mind, too.
If I remember correctly,
there were a lot of child abduction cases taking place around here recently.
Child abduction?!
That's right.
By the way, I can't get used seeing you like that, Captain-chan!
It can't be helped! You have to deal with it for now!
Hey, Tashigi! What are you talking about?
I haven't heard about any child abductions!
Please button up, Smoker-san!
I like how open that Captain-chan is but she's scary inside!
Shut up!
All I know is accidents at sea happen frequently in this area.
But in fact, I was wondering why accidents involving children are so prevalent here.
Oh yeah, that's true, isn't it?
Yeah!
I actually go to the communication department often...
Oh, I don't have glasses...
And I've heard the G-5 gets many child abduction reports.
But when it appears in the newspaper, it's often labeled
an accident at sea or the work of pirates...
...or simply a child gone missing.
Of course, it could be the reporter's mistake but...
I... I thought maybe it's possible that they were really...
Is it hard to say, Tashigi?
If that's what you think, just say it clearly!
We saw a bunch of kids earlier
and you're thinking maybe there really have been many abductions.
And you think the kidnapper is on this island.
But if that's the case,
those news articles were false...
...meaning somebody in the G-5 covered up those child abduction cases.
What?
Does it mean somebody among us is working for the kidnapper?
Wh...
What?!
Hey, Smo-san, don't insult us!
Maybe we are a spoiled group in the Navy
but we take pride in being Navy soldiers!
He's right! None of us is doing that!
Shut up!
So scary!
You fools are not even worth suspecting!
What?!
But, all of you guys, don't expect too much from the Navy.
As long as it consists of a group of people,
there is no organization that is perfect.
If you assume too much, you'll miss the enemy.
Don't be fooled by appearances.
Roger, Captain-chan!
Never mind, fools.
I-I'm the Captain!
Oh yeah!
We got fooled by their appearances!
Smoker-san, I'm not so sure about my theory though.
That's okay. We'd better keep it in mind anyway.
But since my heart and body are in Law's hands,
I can't leave this island.
One third of you should leave here by ship, to make a report.
What are you talking about, Vice Admiral?
Our warship's been destroyed.
I said I saw their ship.
Steal it.
Oh yeah! I hadn't thought of that!
You're a bad person!
Be careful! Before it gets too late,
I'll try to take back my heart and body,
and reveal who's really behind this!
VEGAPUNK'S FORMER THIRD LABORATORY
I finally got through to him.
Clank.
We have permission to kill.
The Straw Hats, G-5, and Foxfire Kin'emon.
No matter who dies on this island,
Joker will make it look like an accident at sea.
Catch as many of them as possible!
The more guinea pigs, the better.
Yes, Master.
But you can just kill the ones who can't be taken with poison.
Where did Law go?
He left the room a few minutes ago.
All right.
One of the enemies has a 400-million-berry bounty.
Don't push yourself too much.
The other members are in a broad range of 120 million to 50 berries each.
All of them are wanted pirates
and their bounties are 800 million 50 berries in total.
But they have been inactive over the past two years
so their bounty hasn't moved up.
They could be more powerful than the numbers show.
You always study hard, Monet.
Master!
Oh, what happened to you? It's extremely cold and you didn't wear a coat?!
We were robbed by some pirates.
More importantly, they took Boss Brownbeard with them!
Please help him!
Oh really? I'm sorry to hear that!
Don't worry about Brownbeard.
We'll get him back at any cost.
Go to the backroom now!
You're so lucky.
We just made a new medicine.
It will warm up your body and heal your wounds.
Really?! That'd be nice!
Please help the others, too!
Of course, I will.
But first, you have to get treated.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
What the hell is this, Usopp?!
It's kind of super!
I don't care anymore...
Thanks, Usopp!
It spoils Nami-san's beauty!
Cut the crap!
We get confused if nothing is done.
Brownbeard?
Yes. I'm sure you heard that name before.
That was what I used to go by.
No idea.
Are you kidding, you fool?
Go away, brats!
What happened to you? You were clammed up a while ago
but now you're talkative.
You guys are done for!
Law's gonna come to save me!
I despise pirates from your generation
but Law is an exception.
What do you mean our generation?
Don't you know anything, fool?
Eleven rookies with bounties over 100 million
who arrived at Sabaody at the same time two years ago
plus Blackbeard...
People call you twelve "the Worst Generation."
You twelve are troublemakers...
...who were born at the change of the era
and hold the key to the future of this war-torn world.
After Whitebeard died, you all came to the New World and raised havoc.
When something big happened,
there was always somebody from your generation involved.
Blackbeard! Kid! Law! Drake! Hawkins!
Basil Hawkins was the one who shattered my pirate group.
I lost both of my legs and ended my career as a pirate thanks to him.
My crew were annihilated.
I fled for my life and arrived here...
...on Punk Hazard.
Do you know what this place is?
This place... This island...
...used to be a lush green treasure house of life.
Really?
It's nothing like that now.
And it housed a laboratory
of Dr.Vegapunk, a Government scientist.
They were experimenting with and developing weapons and chemicals here.
Instead of going to prisons, they brought some prisoners here
and performed experiments on them like they were guinea pigs.
But four years ago,
Vegapunk's chemical weapon test went wrong!
And two of the three laboratories exploded!
This is the remains of that laboratory.
THE REMAINS OF VEGAPUNK'S FORMER FIRST AND SECOND LABORATORY
I see. So there was a huge explosion.
That's why this place is a mess.
The explosion belched intense heat and toxic substances,
and killed each and every living thing on the island.
But in that critical situation,
the Government left those guinea-pig prisoners
and escaped from the island then shut it down completely.
The prisoners stayed in the Third Laboratory,
the only building that remained intact,
and sheltered themselves from the poison gas that was all over the island.
Even those who survived were paralyzed mainly in their lower body
because of the nerve gas
and lost hope in their future.
But...
...a year later,
our merciful Master came to the island!
He purified the gas all over the island with his special ability
and gave those prisoners who couldn't walk mechanical means to move
and took them on as his lackeys.
Master!
Master-san!
I landed here a year later after that,
two years ago.
There were still some toxic substances left in the air
and I felt nauseous when I breathed in.
Just when I thought I had no energy left to live and this was the end...
I saw the prisoners who lost their legs like I did
and the Master!
His kindness saved my life as it did to the others.
Vegapunk was a devil because he paralyzed my comrade's legs
but the Master was our warm-hearted savior!
Master!!
And then a few months ago,
the second savior--
Trafalgar Law who had gained the title of Warlord...
...came to the island.
Using his special ability,
he gave those of us who couldn't walk as we wished, legs.
The legs of living animals!
We thought we would never walk again
so we couldn't stop crying from happiness!
What a touching story!
So the Tra-guy is a good guy as I thought!
He saved my life, too!
Vegapunk is a horrible person!
That's why there were those half-sheep people at the laboratory.
Centaurs and the bird woman, too.
It all makes sense.
But wait. What about the dragon?
Oh, did you see the dragon?
That's an artificial being that Vegapunk created to guard the island.
It can adapt itself to any kind of environment.
I heard some Celestial Dragon liked it and named it.
I forgot the name but if you see it, you better run.
It's extremely aggressive.
All right.
We already ate it.
Anyway, now you know who rules the island.
No one wants to come near it.
Punk Hazard is our Master's property now!
Rejoice!
The Master is still doing research today for the future of mankind!
He needs only a few guinea pigs and you can become one!
You can't get away!
Hm? What's the matter?
Master!
Master! I can't breathe!
What kind of...
...medicine is this?
Master!
Master...
Get me out of here!
You need to hang on.
How do you feel now?
Feeling nauseous and coughing, huh?
That's good.
Do you have a headache?
It hurts!
Feels like it's gonna split open!
Uh-huh, I see.
What? It wasn't Vegapunk?
Then, Smo-san,
who caused that huge explosion?
The one who made the weapon
and let it go off accidentally...
...was Caesar Clown!
Caesar Clown was
the second-in-command in the science department at that time
but since he had an inhumane streak,
he was always butting heads with Vegapunk.
M-Master...
H-Help me...
How are your eyes?
Do you see anything?
Huh?
Oh... there is... a giant snake in the room!
No way!
All right, that's good. Goodbye!
When the accident happened,
Vegapunk's name came up only because he was a person in charge.
Of course,
it was a crime to develop a mass-killing weapon that belches poison gas.
And since it had been brought to light by the accident,
Caesar got arrested.
But with his formidable ability,
he managed to escape from a prison ship
and had been missing ever since.
If Caesar is still doing research on this island,
we must stop him now!
He's gonna do something horrible again!
"Not good."
Another failure?
Failure?
Watch your tongue!
A FORMER GOVERNMENT SCIENTIST BOUNTY: 300 MILLION BERRIES MASTER CAESAR CLOWN
My experiments never fail!
Even what happened four years ago!
Everyone talks nonsense as usual!
A failed experiment?
I "killed" the whole island with the weapon!
It wasn't a failure, World Government!
I'm capable of killing more enemies than anyone else.
I carefully document my victims until their final moment.
You just wait!
I'll make them realize who is the greatest scientist in the world!