Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war against the New Fishman Pirates.
Luffy finally defeated Hody in a fierce fight
and thwarted his plot.
All right! Spread the sail!
Let's set sail!
Take me out for a fun stroll again!
I want to go to a real forest above ground!
Okay, fine!
I'll take you there next time!
We promise!
Once we pass through this deep sea,
we'll get to the ultimate sea!
Let's go!
Guys!
To the New World!
"To the New World! Heading for the Ultimate Sea!"
After leaving Fishman Island,
the ship ascends toward the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
--It's going very well! --Yeah, almost too well.
I'm starting to get hungry. Let's do it now!
Wait until I finish making this, Luffy.
How nice!
It's called Shower Tempo. Do you wanna use it?
Oh? Me?
I'm okay. I just brushed myself 2 days ago.
By the way, doesn't that cloud look like cotton candy?
You can't eat it!
Oh yeah? It's not sweet, sweet cotton candy?
What? There is something sweet and yummy in the bathroom?
Oh yeah! Looks pretty sweet and yummy!
Nami-san, please! Turn around!
Chopper, step away from the cloud.
How scary! I don't wanna eat that cloud anymore!
It's so relaxing!
My first bath on the Sunny in 2 years!
It's so luxurious with a view of the deep sea - it's as beautiful as the night sky.
Don't they need you on the deck?
It's okay. I'll go up before we ride an upward current.
If a sea monster strikes, they can take care of it.
Hurry up, Usopp!
Just one minute.
We want a giant fish so the ropes gotta be strong!
Okay, I think this is good.
Finished!
Ta-dah!
Oh? You guys are having fun.
I hadn't even thought about it on our way to Fishman Island
because I was excited to see the island
but if we catch a deep-sea fish now, Sanji can cook it for us!
I hope it'll go with cola!
Cook, huh? That's a good idea!
Can't wait to have a drink in celebration of entering the New World!
Now, which one should we catch?
I want something that looks yummy!
That one would taste good fried up with some salt!
A fried fish with salt sounds good!
How about slicing it in half and grilling it?
Like an eel, huh?
Oh! That one looks good too! It would be yummy with some mayonnaise!
Which one?
No, it doesn't look good at all.
No matter how you cook it, it won't taste good.
You think so? Well, whatever's fine with me!
Gear 2!
I'm sure Sanji can cook up any fish!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
I knew you wanted that one!
Hey, isn't it a little too big?!
Hurry, hurry! Catch it!
Special Attack - Capture Star!
Yeah!
We got a deep-sea fish!
I wanna eat it already!
Are you sure it's a fish? Looks like an old man!
An old man?
It got eaten!
Hey, hey, not again! They keep coming!
Reel it in already, Usopp!
I can't, I can't! The ship is gonna flip over!
I can't believe this! Is it a Russian doll?
Do you think something happened?
The ship is shaking and I hear them yelling on the deck.
I shouldn't have trusted them!
One-Sword Style: 360-Pound Phoenix!
Nice, Zoro!
What's going on here?
Hey Sanji, look at that!
I see! That's great!
A deep-sea fish, huh? Can't wait to cook it!
Well, first of all, how did you get burned?
Listen to this! You won't believe it!
There are 2 more fish inside that one!
But, is the ship really moving forward?
It feels like we're sinking...
No way!
What is that?!
What?
It's a giant sea snake! No!!
Alright, get closer! Let's eat that too!
We have too much to carry already!
Wait! Don't tell me it's...
Whitestrom!
It's a giant whirlpool that appears out of the blue in the deep sea,
like a living dragon!
What?
A whirlpool in the deep sea?!
What the hell is that?! This is dangerous, isn't it?
Damn, those fools!
What?! Oh no! It must be the Whitestrom!
When a ship gets caught up in the whirlpool,
it'll end up somewhere far off usually missing its crew.
What?! That means the crew all died, doesn't it?
This is dangerous! Let's get away!
A ship will end up somewhere far off?
So it's like the wormhole of my dreams?!
No, it's not, you fool!
Guys! We have to get away from that whirlpool now!
There! Our navigator's back! Let's go, fools!
Augh! What is that fish doing there?!
Oh, we caught it!
What do you think you're doing?! We can't advance if we're pulling that!
See? The fish got caught in the whirlpool!
--No! Get it back! --Yeah!
No! We're gonna cut it loose!
What?! We wanted to eat the deep-sea fish!
Which is more important to you - the fish or your life?!
How could you get in this much trouble while I was away for only 10 minutes?!
Franky, Coup de Burst?!
No, it's super too late for that!
--Huh? --Stop "Huh?"-ing me!
We're gonna get caught in the whirlpool!
We're in big trouble!
Oh no!
--It's too late! --I don't wanna die!
Hold onto the ship!
How fun!
This is super not good!
Even the Sunny can't endure a whirlpool this wild!
I blame Luffy and the rest of you!
My head is spinning!
Can't we get out of the whirlpool somehow?!
There are no records of someone escaping the Whitestrom! Because...
No one has ever survived!
Instead of the New World, we're all going to hell!
It stopped.
The Sunny was not destroyed.
We hit something and got bumped out of the whirlpool.
In any case, we're alive!
Where are we?
What's this black wall?
It doesn't seem like the Red Line.
A ghost!
What is it?
It's gonna eat us!
A monster!
What is that?!
It's going away!
A fin? Don't tell me it's...
I can hear it singing. It must be...
Wow, it's a pod of whales!
Oh, those scars!
We'll come back to see you again.
When I come back, let's fight again!
Laboon?!
Laboon! Wait for us! We'll come back here for sure...! For sure!!
Laboon! You got so much bigger!
Don't be ridiculous! Laboon should be in the first half of the Grand Line.
He's gigantic! He can't fit through the hole in the Red Line!
Amazing!
It's like a miracle to come across a pod of Island Whales.
Some of them have scars like Laboon.
Yeah, the scars look the same! I can't believe it! But it's not Laboon?!
Time to ship out Binks’ Brew!
Laboon! Stop! Listen to me!
It's me from the Rumbar Pirates! Brook!
Come to your senses! That's a different whale!
Laboon!
We're not on a whale watching crew!
It's still dangerous out here!
Now, let me call the roll to make sure no one got lost in the whirlpool!
--Nami-san! --Yes!
Robin-chan!
Here.
Okay, we gotta get out of here now.
The ship will be destroyed if those giant whales crash into us!
Why didn't you call our names?
Sanji-kun! Six more of us are alive and well here too!
Nami-san, what should we do?!
Let's not do anything.
Yeah, we shouldn't do anything, fools! Let's watch the whales now!
What's wrong with you?!
Since they're such giant whales, they're creating a current.
It'll be dangerous to go against it!
Tighten the sails!
Turn the ship in the direction that the whales are heading!
Okay!
Oh yeah! This is where Laboon came from.
Are any of you related to him?
Be careful, Brook!
Is anyone looking for a calf who got lost 50 years ago?
Don't worry! He's doing okay on the other side of the world!
According to Luffy-san, he's very big now.
So please don't worry! I think Laboon would...
Catch the stream!
Okay!
We're okay now.
We'll stick with the whales for a while.
That's kind of nice.
Oh? Brook?
Yo ho ho ho... Yo ho ho ho...
Time to ship out Binks’ Brew!
The sea breeze blows us to who-knows-where,
let the waves be our guide
O’er across the ocean tide,
the sunset stirs, going wild!
Look to the skies! Watch the circling birds
as they sing and pass us by!
Fare thee well to the weaver’s town,
to the harbor as well...
Sing a booming song,
a song for us casting off!
Oh, the gold and silver waves,
all of ‘em turnin’ to sea spray!
As we journey off t’ward the ends of the high seas!
Time to ship out Binks' Brew!
Pirates we, we'll divide and conquer all the seas!
With the waves to rest our heads, ship beneath us as our bed!
Hoisted high up on the mast our Jolly Roger flies!
Somewhere in the endless sky, a storm has started comin' by!
Waves are dancing having fun, it's time to sound the drums!
Hey, you're giving us a ride?
If we let blow winds of fear, then the end of us is near!
Let him take us!
Looks like they're gonna go upward too!
Even so, tomorrow the sun will rise again!
Yo ho ho ho... Yo ho ho ho...
It's the New World, the final sea of the Grand Line, up above us!
I can't wait!
Luffy?
That's it!
Finally!
Let's do it, guys!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6...
...5, 4, 3, 2...
...1!
--We're out! --In the New World!
--We did it! --We finally made it!
But it's not time to celebrate yet!
Oh, the whales!
We'll tell Laboon about you all if we see him!
Laboon's relatives! Take care of yourselves!
Thank you for everything!
I had heard about it but it's more than I expected!
The New World has...
...really bad weather!
The sky is filled with thunder!
The wind is so strong!
The sea is very rough!
The needle is going crazy!
I see some ships!
Pirates are having a party!
No, those are warships!
Couldn't ask for anything better!
The Navy?
The Straw Hats finally make it to the surface.
They encounter many grueling trials...
...including a mysterious girl small enough to fit in the palm of you hand.
However...
...it also brings to light a conspiracy...
...between pirates and the Navy of the New World!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Z's Ambition! Lily the Little Giant!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!