Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates,
who are plotting to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom,
alongside Vander Decken, who is after
Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi, move in secret.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
and involved in an all-out war!
If I am the only one who you want to kill, please do not harm the other people...
...of the Ryugu Kingdom!
Come and get me!
Damn Wimpyhoshi! I told her to stick with me!
Don't mess with me, Vander Decken!
But I like this idea!
I'll be counting on you to save my beloved Shirahoshi-chan!
You ready, Luffy?!
Go ahead!
Hurry Up, Luffy!
Shirahoshi's Life in Jeopardy
Th-The Noah is...
The Noah is turning away. It's not gonna crash into the island!
Princess-sama saved us by drawing the ship away!
--Princess Shirahoshi! --Please escape!
Where are you going, Shirahoshi? There's no way for you to run!
Shirahoshi!
I have to go out to the sea in order to keep the Noah away from the bubble!
The bubble can't take any more damage!
But the main entrance is too far from here.
If I am correct, Luffy-sama's friends were the last ones who left the Ryugu Palace.
Then maybe the gateway is still open.
Damn! Isn't there anything that we can do!
Our princess is risking her life to save us all!
It's not her fault that Decken is after her!
Not only is Decken on that ship but now Hody is climbing aboard one of the chains!
Princess Shirahoshi's life is in danger!
He betrayed me, that lunatic - Decken!
But he can still be useful.
Be careful for Hody, Luffy!
Fishmen are way stronger than humans in the water!
Got it!
I can't let him pierce the bubble and go out to sea.
I have to do it carefully - not too strong, not too weak.
Sanji!
Armee de L'Air Assault...
...Gum Shoot!
What a big chain!
Am I in between the bubbles?
Hody! He's still under the bubble.
Pull! Pull!
We don't have stop it! We only have to slow it down a little bit...
...before it catches up with Princess-sama!
--Pull! --Don't let the Noah go any farther!
Princess-sama! Get somewhere safe while we're slowing it down!
Damn! Stop!
Those fools!
Everybody!
They must be out of their minds!
They can't move it even a millimeter! How senseless is that?!
What?
Hey, quit it!
Shark Arrows!
Worthless scum!
Because of cowards like you guys, humans think they can make fools of Fishmen!
Your lives mean nothing to me!
People like you just keep bringing shame to Fishmen. Drop dead already!
Everybody...
That bastard!
Princess-sama, escape! H-Hurry...
I have to keep going!
I was right! The entrance to the palace was left open!
Hey, stay with me! Damn Hody!
Princess Shirahoshi is going...
...out to sea through the gateway!
--The Noah is going after her! --Princess-sama, go farther!
Oh, it's going up!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh no, the chain!
How inconvenient it must be to be a human!
You all act so tough on the ground
but you couldn't even win a fight with a Fishman child in the sea!
That's how weak you are!
I'll make you regret standing against me!
Hody!
Where do you think you are?!
You're not on the ground!
Humans become powerless in the water
but for a Fishman like me, this is where I
can use my true ability to the full extent!
It was very fortunate for me that Shirahoshi went out to sea!
Shark Arrows!
Devil Fruit users fare no better than ordinary people in the water.
Maybe worse.
Isn't it ironic, Straw Hat?
Pathetic and powerless! That's how you truly are!
No matter how big you talk!
You humans can't even breathe in the water...
Straw Hat, a piece of trash like you will never become the ruler of the sea!
You ought to regret what you did and beg for mercy!
You can't even do that now, can you? You pathetic, lowly creature!
Rot in hell, Straw Hat!
Damn you!
Are you okay, Straw Hat?
B-Brother-hoshi!
That stupid hanger-on - what a useless gesture.
You can't get away from me, Straw Hat!
Pull! Pull!
We don't have stop it! We only have to slow it down a little bit...
...before it catches up with Princess-sama!
--Pull! --Don't let the Noah go any further!
Princess-sama! Get somewhere safe while we're slowing it down!
I-In order to save the people of the Ryugu Kingdom,
I have to draw the Noah away from the island...
...as far as possible!
Shirahoshi!
How do you like your freedom?
You no longer have those walls of Hard Shell Tower
that were protecting you for last 10 years!
You have a choice of bleeding to death
or being crushed by the giant ship - Noah!
I'll give you one last chance, Shirahoshi!
If you say "Yes," I'll spare your life!
Have mercy, Decken-sama!
Marry me!
You're not my type!
Gee...
All right...
Then go to hell!
Drop dead and live in my heart forever!
As my beloved wife!
Now!
We're not gonna let her marry a guy like you!
She's our only baby sister! We're not gonna let you hurt her, Decken!
Brother Mamboshi-sama! Brother Ryuboshi-sama! Hoe-sama!
Brothers-sama!
We're not your brothers!
Brothers-sama! Some people at the plaza tried to save me and...
Shirahoshi! Don't cry now!
No! Brother-sama got mad...
I'm not mad!
According to Father, we can't even let the ship get damaged-la-ti-do!
So we have to return it to the seafloor without letting it hit anything!
Here it comes!
Oh no! In any case, you shouldn't swim near undersea mountains or trenches!
The Noah will get damaged!
Then where should I go, Brother Mamboshi-sama?!
Go up! There are too many obstacles down here!
Okay!
We'll go beat Decken!
You will never get away from the Noah and my unending love, Shirahoshi!
Thank you for saving me!
You got hurt before - are you okay?
Members of the royal family, soldiers, citizens... all of them got hurt or died.
And even Shirahoshi is trying so hard to save the Ryugu Kingdom while injured!
So this is not the time for me to suffer from such minor injuries!
I need to ask you a favor.
Maybe not now.
The Merfolk are the greatest swimmers in the world!
But to me, they look like stop motion!
That bastard!
Shark Slicer!
We're dead once it hits us!
Should I chop both of you up and feed you to the little fishes?
The pirate with a 400 million bounty and the prince of the Ryugu Kingdom.
What exquisite food for them!
He's coming!
Although his power is phony, he's fast!
Hang on tight!
He's pretty strong in the sea! Almost like Zoro!
You're not supposed to be impressed at a time like this!
No matter where you go, you can't get away from the Shark Slicer's blade!
Is he trying to escape in the cloud of dust?
The Noah is...
Shirahoshi!
--Shirahoshi! --Hey, go to the deck of the ship!
Damn Decken!
Is that what you wanted to ask me before? But why there?
Because of what Jinbe told me.
Do you think the ship is filled with water, Jinbe?
I don't know but I know Decken is a Devil Fruit user.
Which means there must be air for him!
It'll be easier for me to fight there.
I wanna kick the crap out of Hody and the guy who throws things!
I promised Wimpyhoshi when we left the tower, that I was gonna protect her!
Speaking of promises...
We three will become great warriors like our father...
...and protect Shirahoshi with our lives as we promised!
I have a promise to keep too!
We were defeated by that cheap hoodlum who relies on some
fake power from the Energy Steroid!
What a shame!
I'm sorry that we suspected you...
Don't mention it. Take me to the deck!
You wanna go to the deck?
Hody!
I can take care of Straw Hat anytime.
But there is something that needs to be done right now.
--Go after him already! --No, wait, Straw Hat!
Why?!
I'm sure you know it by now.
Hody has an advantage in the water since he is a Fishman.
--If nothing is done... --What should we do?
I have an idea!
Go up! Go up!
Like I said, it's no use, Shirahoshi!
As long as my Mark-Mark Curse is in effect,
there is no way for you to get away from the Noah!
Oh, Hody Jones!
What happened to Neptune? Did you kill him?
I'm tormenting Shirahoshi with the Noah now.
Don't you think it's a good idea?
Huh, Bro?!
I have a good idea too!
What is it? Let me hear it.
If you die now...
What'll happen to this ship?
Decken!
Hody suddenly attacks Decken.
His terrifying plan was to destroy Fishman Island!
Hody then attacks Shirahoshi to complete his ambition!
But then, Luffy's new attack is unleashed on Hody!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Start of an Intense Battle!
Luffy vs. Hody!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Start of an Intense Battle!
Luffy vs. Hody!