Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
rashinban nante jyuutai no moto
compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
delirious with fever, i take the helm
hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
if the dusty treasure map has been verified,
tashikameta no nara densetsu janai
it's not a legend!
kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
when it comes to personal storms,
biorizumu nokkatte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
omoi sugoseba ii
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
poketto no koin
a coin in my pocket,
soreto You Wanna Be My Friend
and do you wanna be my friend?
We Are
we are!
Raise the anchor!
Set the sails!
– Bring the ship forward!
– You idiot!
– Don't shake things, Sanji!
– Full speed ahead to the Grand Line!
Shut up.
If you're scared, then go down
and sleep like a good li'l boy.
D-D-Don't be stupid!
Of course I'm not scared!
Sanji! Breakfast!
Yeah, yeah!
I'll get started on it.
Hold on.
Good morning, Nami-san!
Good morning, Sanji-kun.
Hey. Hey, Zoro. Let's play tag.
Huh?!
What, what?! Tag?!
Let's play, let's play!
Are you guys stupid?!
You're pathetic, playing at your age!
I'm gonna get some more sleep before breakfast.
Oh?!
'Cause you don't like losing, huh?!
What did you say?!
I don't give a damn about that!
See! You're suddenly mad!
What?!
Hold it, you guys!
But it's the truth, isn't it?! Bleehhh!
Stop right there!
Does that mean you'll join our crew now?!
But I'm only teaming up
with you, just so you know!
Always remember that!
– I'm over here! Come get me!
– C'mon, Zoro! Chase me, too!
I'm not playing here!
Nami-san! Your meal's ready!
Hey, guys! Food's on!
Yeah!
Hold it! I'm not done with you!
Even after he said all that...
Huh? What, Nami-san?
No, it's nothing!
Whew, I'm hungry!
Food! Food! Food!
This looks yum!
Say, what do you suppose
happened to Buggy after that?
Buggy? Oh, that Buggy?
Who knows?
Maybe he's at the bottom of the ocean.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Pirates are a stubborn lot,
every last one of 'em.
Yeah?
You're the one who kept
chasing me stubbornly! Oww...
I hunted pirates for years.
I can tell.
Not that it matters,
but your food's gone, Usopp.
Here you are, Nami-san!
– A Special Yogurt Dessert!
– Luffy! You stole my food again!
– Oh! Thank you, Sanji-kun!
– Give it back, you idiot!
Alright!
I've finally finished my flashy raft!
Just you watch!
I, the great and world-renowned pirate,
Buggy the Clown-sama...
...will get my crew back together
and get my super flashy revenge!
No matter what obstacles lie in my path!
The score must be settled!
You damn flashy rubber man!
Just you wait!
I absolutely will beat you senseless
and make you cry uncle!
Go! Set sail!
Stuff like this already?!
I refuse to lose! Damn you!
Chase Straw Hat!
Little Buggy's Big Adventure
I managed to make it... to the next island...
Damn it! Don't scare me like that!
I'm not some kind of exhibit, dammit!
Why, you...! Are you mocking me?!
You got some real guts, ridiculing me!
I'm gonna eatcha!
I was just feeling hungry, too!
You've made me mad!
You're done for now!
I'm gonna eat you flashily,
so just give yourself up!
Chop-Chop Cannon!
Quit your flailing!
Just accept your fate!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Forgive me!
C'mon! C'mon!
My plan is flawless!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
I caught him!
I got caught?! Huh?!
How did things turn out this way?!
Stop! Stop! No!
Is this the end already?! This sucks!
Why, you...! Am I that bad-tasting?!
That's a little bit of a shock!
Hey, look! A hermit crab!
I wonder when he got on board.
At Nami's village?
Probably.
That, or maybe at Usopp's village?
If so, that's incredible!
That'd mean he's been traveling with us this whole time!
Dammit! Why does this happen to me?!
Did you just say something?
Huh? Me? I didn't say anything.
Nuh-uh.
That's weird.
Must've been my imagination.
Hey, Luffy! Quit slackin' off!
Oh! Sorry! Sorry!
There we go...
Where am I now?
Leave!
Who's there?!
I am this island's protective god!
Leave this island at once if you value your life!
Protective god?!
Hey, you! You're one of those, uhh...
...weird creatures!
I'm gonna kick your ass, you moron!
Listen!
Just try taking another step into the forest!
The instant you do, will you
receive my divine punishment
and meet your doom?!
How should I know, you flashy idiot?!
Why're you asking me?!
What are these things?
The animals of this forest.
Don't mess with them,
unless you want to die!
Oh?
These are some flashily interesting animals...
I told you not to go any further!
Blast it! He suddenly shot at me!
Damn! I missed!
There you are!
What is this?!
Gotcha!
– Come out!
– Oww! Oww! Oww!
Dammit! You have a Devil Fruit power!
So what if I do?! You're nothing-
You're-
What are you?
Are you a boxed and sheltered son?
Yeah. I've been overly pampered
since I was just a little boy...
Of course I'm not!
Don't do stupid gags!
Damn you! Don't get cocky!
I don't show mercy to anyone
who messes with them!
Oh? You wanna fight me?
I commend your bravery,
but don't blame me after you die!
Gotcha!
Blast you!
Flying weapons are unfair!
Then what's this thing here?!
Don't talk so selfishly!
Say your prayers!
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
Oww!
– How dare you?! Blast it! Oww!
– How dare I what?! Huh?!
I've had enough!
Don't move!
Too bad!
Anyone who messes with the animals has to pay!
They're this island's treasure!
Those weird animals are treasures?
Treasure refers to gold, silver,
and jewels, you flashy idiot!
Don't play stupid!
You came to this island to get these animals!
Why would I do that?!
I didn't come here 'cause I wanted to!
You mean you're not a poacher?
Don't be stupid!
I might not look it, but I'm a great pirate!
I'm Buggy the Clown-sama!
I'd never do anything as mean as that!
Pirate? You're a pirate?!
Huh?
Me, too!
I used to be a pirate a long time ago!
Oh, my bad! My bad!
So you're a pirate, too!
Whadya think? Good, huh?!
It's my own unrefined sake!
Yeah, this is the best!
How many days it's been since I last drank...
You can have as many refills
as you want! Drink up and up!
But I'm really sorry about earlier!
I just assumed you were a poacher
who came to get these animals!
That was some horrible stuff you did!
But it doesn't matter now!
Plus you let me have this delicious booze, too!
The only things in this world that
interest me are treasure and alcohol!
I'm likin' you even more!
You're a pirate, all right!
You're a real stout-hearted guy!
Tell me, why are you on this island?
Oh.
I originally came here in search of treasure, too.
What?! There's treasure on this island?!
Calm down.
If there was, I wouldn't be
hanging around here, either.
O-Oh. You have a point.
Anyways, some stuff happened
and my crew left me behind.
So I've been calling this island
home for the past 20 years now.
20 years?!
You've really had it rough!
It's not so bad, really.
These guys are here with me.
This way of life is actually pretty
nice once you get used to it!
I dunno. I'd much rather be living
the pirate life with my crew.
True, pirate life is nice! It's great!
Even I would gladly risk my life to
go on treasure-hunting adventures!
Right?! It's like, "Hurray for pirates!"
What do you say? When I get my
pirate crew back, won't you join us?!
Eh?!
I greatly welcome guys like you!
After all, you have the pirate spirit!
Well? Whadya say?!
You're... inviting me?!
I appreciate the thought,
but these guys are my friends.
When you live with them for
20 years, they rub off on you,
even if they are weird creatures.
I can't leave them now.
What? What's so funny?!
No, I was just remembering a young pirate
who asked me to be a pirate
again just like you did.
Don't be so upset, old guy!
It's a good thing we came after 20 years!
30 years later and you might've been dead!
Straw Hat...
He was such an incredibly nice guy.
I'm sure you and him'd be good friends!
I see.
So there are youngsters out there like that...
Not me, though.
I ran into this one horrible kid!
Assemble! Chop-Chop Parts!
Tadah!
Looking for these?!
My parts!
Way to go, thief!
S-Stop!
Go flying, Buggy!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
And that's how I wound up
on a wandering journey...
Just thinking about it now
makes me boil with rage!
I see. Sorry to hear what happened...
But it just goes to show there are
all kinds of youngsters out there.
In any case, let's have fun tonight!
We don't want this night to go to waste!
Yeah, huh?
To pirates!
And to us meeting!
Cheers!
Sorry for asking you to help make a raft, too.
Not at all. It was my pleasure.
So you're really going to stay?
Yeah. With all my friends here.
I see...
Alright! Take care of yourself!
You, too!
Farewell, friend! Take care!
Yeah...
You, too!
Set sail!
Alright!
Buggy...
There are many strange
creatures in these waters.
Be ever careful on your way!
Wait, I forgot to tell him that!
R-Run, Buggy!
Ahh! Look out!
Run! Get out of there!
W-What's that?
Pretty...
Who's that?!
She's super pretty!
Well, at least it looks like he's saved!
He had me sweating bullets there!
In any case, take care of yourself!
Thanks for the help!
I flashily thought I was a goner there!
There's no need to thank me.
You're Buggy the Clown, right?
How do you know that?!
Who are you?
I'm looking for a certain man.
You know him, right?
Damn rubber man!
Damn you!
Someday, I will settle the score with you!
Just you wait!
This is the guy you're looking for?
Come. I have a meal ready.
I see.
So that's why you helped me...
That's right.
So, what do you say?
Will you team up with me?
Sure, why not?
We both have the same goal.
Let's be friends.
That's great. Then cheers!
Cheers!
Sanji... Food...
You just ate...
Gimme a break...
Shut up, you guys...
I can't sleep...
You sleep too much...
Help out with work sometimes...
Sheesh...
I'm amazed they can hold
conversations in their sleep.
Talk about skillful...
Well, I guess I'll hit the hay, too!
Good night.
hamidashita kimochi tsunagara nakute
my overflowing feelings don't connect
kimi no te o gyutto ni girikaesu yo
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
hitori demo boku wa arukidasu kara
I'll set off by myself,
tooku made zutto mitsumeteite ne
so keep watching me intently as I go into the distance
kesa kara chotto kangaeteita
I was thinking about it a bit since this morning
doushite konna ni atsui no
why is it so hot?
itsu kara ka sonna koto bakari ga
starting from some point,
hanarenai yo
I haven't been able to get away from that
kakedashita kimochi tsukamaetakute
I want to catch those feelings that rushed off,
jibun sae mou oikoshite yuku yo
and I'm already about to overtake myself, even
tobidashita yume o dakishimetetai
I want to embrace my dreams that have jumped out
issho nara boku wa hashitte yukeru
with you, I can run there
Oh, yeah!
Buggy's henchmen were neat, too!
Yeah, you mean like the
unicycle guy and the lion guy?
Cabaji and Mohji, was it?
He had animals, too?!
Are they really pirates?!
Who do you think is their captain now?
Cabaji or Mohji, obviously.
Who knows? Maybe it's that lion!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Wait is Over!
The Return of Captain Buggy!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Wait is Over!
The Return of Captain Buggy!