It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement—there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail—let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag—together, we're one
One Piece
A-A frog is doing the front crawl!
What?!
It went to your side, so take a look at it!
--Is that true?
--Hey, Luffy...
Are you taking what that
stupid Admiral said seriously?
To start with, there's no way a frog
would do the front cra... Hey, it is!
A-A frog is doing the front crawl!
We'll follow it, guys!
Yeah!
Why is there a lighthouse in a place
like that? I wonder if someone's there...
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!...
It flew!
All right! The frog stopped. Corner it at once!
We ran ashore on something!
What's this sound?
Ow, ow, ow...
Go back! Go back! Turn 180 degrees!
The Dashing Sea Train
and the City of Water, Water Seven
What the hell is that?!
Just turn around! Now!
What the hell is this?!
Wh-Wh-What the hell is this lump of iron?!
A ship?
No! Something shaped like
this can't travel on the sea!
Hey, frog! Run! What're you doing?!
Ahhh! It got run over!
The ship was puffing out smoke!
Pirates...?
Grandma! Grandma! Pirates are here!
What?! Is that true, Chimney?!
Okay then, bring the Transponder Snail to me!
Okay!
This is a problem.
Someone came out of the building.
They're gonna call for help.
Here it is, Grandma!
Err... Hello?
Let's see... What was it? I forget.
So she's drunk?!
Oh? Paille, huh? It goes good with alcohol.
Whoa! This is good!
I'm Chimney. This is our cat, Gonbe...
...and Grandma Kokoro.
You guys aren't train robbers, are you?
I'm Luffy. I'm the man
who'll become Pirate King.
--Really?!
--Yeah.
What a funny guy.
Say, Chimney, that thing is a steamship, right?
But with a shape like that,
it can't go on a voyage.
You've never seen something
like that, have you?
Even if you look all over the world,
this is the only place you can find it.
It's a sea train called the "Puffing Tom."
Puffing Tom?
It turns paddlewheels using a steam
engine and runs on the sea railway.
Railway?
That's right. It runs a little
below the surface of the sea.
The train travels the same route every day,
taking passengers from one island to another.
It carries ships and the mail as well.
She's right. There really is a railway.
Then we ran ashore on that, huh?
That's right! There's both
a signal and a partition.
It's dangerous to come inside like that!
But the signal should face the other way.
Otherwise, how do we see it?!
Even if it's dangerous, that guy
wouldn't understand, right?
It wasn't nice to send him flying.
We were after him, you know.
What? "That guy"? Are you
talking about Yokozuna?
Yep, that front crawl frog.
Yokozuna wouldn't die from that.
He's the source of all our
headaches at this shift station.
He loves strength contests and
always tries to defeat the sea train.
He'll show up again.
Strength contests? Oh...
That's why he didn't run, huh?
He's sure got guts.
Give me a break! We're having problems!
The rail guard was broken many times, too!
Every time he shows up, it causes
the passengers a lot of trouble!
I see...
Okay, then! I'm not gonna eat him!
I'm not gonna eat a fighter!
You shouldn't have thought about
eating a frog in the first place!
So where do you guys wanna go?
If you're gonna take the sea train from here...
The town of the Spring Queen, St. Poplar...
The gourmet town, Pucci...
The Carnival town, San Faldo...
They're all fun places.
If you work for the Government,
there's a separate, special train.
The gourmet town, Pucci?
Oh, I see...
That's the place the guys we met on the
uninhabited island were talking about.
Oh... Come to think of it...
Then, we'll pick the gourmet town.
Obviously not!
Since we've got our own ship,
we won't take the train.
We'll just follow the log.
Oh...? Where is it pointing?
East of here.
I see. Then it must be Water Seven.
The train you saw earlier came
from that island's Blue Station.
It's called the "City of Water." It's a nice place.
Water Seven?
Above all, it's a city that made
a name for itself with its shipyard.
Their technology is No. 1 in the world!
The ships they build are the World
Government's favorites! Isn't that amazing?!
I see... Then there's gotta be
some amazing shipwrights, right?!
Not just "some"! It's a hangout
for the world's best shipwrights!
Usopp!
Yeah!
All right! I've decided!
We're gonna go there and get a
shipwright to join our crew for sure!
Oh, is that right? Then hold on a sec.
Oof.
--What's that about?
--Beats me.
Well, then... Here's a simple map
of the island and a reference letter.
Give this to a guy named Iceberg
and ask him to fix your ship good.
Water Seven is a big place. Don't get lost.
--Whoa!
--Kokoro-san! You have a big heart!
What a nice person you are!
We're gonna go back to Water Seven soon, too.
Yeah. If I see you guys again, I'll treat
you to a drink at my favorite bar.
Okay. I hope we'll see you guys again!
It'll take about a week for the log to
be stored in Water Seven. Take it easy.
Yeah! Thanks!
All right, guys! Get ready to set sail!
--Yeah!
--Well then, we'll get going!
Thanks for all your help, Kokoro-san! Chimney!
Be careful!
Watch out for the Government people!
Yahoo! Let's go! To the city of meat! Yahoo!
Were you even listening?
Hmm... What a nice wind!
We may be able to get to the city
of water sooner than expected.
I hope so.
Luffy, leave the shipwright search to me.
I'll find an incredibly pretty woman.
Are you an idiot?! It's a
shipwright we're talking about!
It's gotta be a big guy like
a mountain! Five meters tall!
But if he's too big, we don't know
if he could live okay on this ship.
All that matters is that he's skilled, right?
More importantly, the question
is if we could find someone
crazy enough to want to be on a pirate ship.
I'm looking forward to it.
We're gonna have another new friend!
We were lucky to stop at the station first,
since they drew a map for us.
If we go to the place on the map
and visit the Iceberg guy...
"Around here" "Water Seven"
I see...
Ha! Too simple to figure out!
Whoa! This is like Luffy's drawing.
"Shipwright
Five Meters"
So, we're gonna all look for a guy like this.
If there was a guy like that, I'd run.
Yeah, me, too. If I had a boat,
I'd escape to the sea.
But this guy seems to be related to octopuses.
He might follow me to the sea.
What the hell are you guys running on about?!
Well then, guys, come here!
I'll give you some allowance for
the week we're gonna stay there.
Seriously?! Yaay! I'm first!
Whoa! That's generous!
Hey! Stand in line!
Allowance! Allowance! Allowance!
What's the matter, Usopp?
This tinplate patchwork brings back
memories of battles and adventure.
I'm filled with deep emotions when I
think that she will be repaired soon.
--I do understand that, but...
--Hm...?
...especially since we entered the Grand Line, our journey has taken quite a toll on the Merry.
The deck squeaks and the leakage at
the bottom of the ship is bad as well.
If we don't do anything, both we
and the ship will be in danger.
Yeah, but we've got tons of money now.
We can have her repaired perfectly.
We can power her up, too!
All right! Let's get more cannons!
Then, let's get a bronze statue on board, too!
Hey, isn't that the one?
Hm?
The island! We can see the island!
Okay, guys! Paddle!
We've got enough wind.
Don't make us waste our energy!
How wonderful...
Amazing...!
What the hell is this?!
What a huge fountain!
Amazing! This is indeed an industrial city!
No wonder this place has a sea train.
Wow... This is a lot of water!
Where is that water springing out from?
How interesting... It looks like
the water comes from the fountain,
goes through the canals and falls into the sea.
Hey, do you wanna race on those water slides?
Race?
No! There's no way I'm doing that!
Dream on, you idiot. You can't even swim.
Oh, yeah...
More importantly,
what do those numbers mean?
Huh...?
--Don't know.
--Are they walls? Or...
I bet those are the entrances
for the five-meter shipwrights.
"Shipwright
Five Meters"
There's a bunch of them?!
The one up front must be the station.
It says Blue Station.
I wonder where the harbor is.
It must be in the town.
--Hey, you guys!
--Hm?
It's not good for you pirates
to be openly sailing in the front!
Go around to the backstreets over there!
Okay! Thanks!
Whoa, this is amazing! A city on the water?!
Wow! This place is cool! What a beautiful city!
But the city is flooded.
The houses are submerged in the sea.
That's not it. The city was designed
with the base being submerged.
--Huh?
--Look at the foundation
underneath the buildings.
You're right! The pillars are built higher!
I see... That's why it's called
the city of water, huh?
Hey, hurry up and dock the ship!
Hm?
Hey, hey, you guys!
Pirate ships shouldn't come in here!
What'd you come here for?! To plunder?!
No! We wanna get our ship repaired!
Would people normally ask
if we're here to plunder?
Then, there's a cape ahead of here,
so anchor your ship there for now!
Okay!
Thanks!
Again?
It can't be helped, right? We're pirates, after all.
This area should be okay, don't you think?
In any case, what a dull place this is.
All right, then! Furl the sail!
What're you doing?!
Nothing! I just pulled the rope!
Holy crap! The Going Merry
has gotten this rickety?
By the way, why aren't the people
on this island scared of pirates?
Probably because pirates are just
another customer to their shipyard.
Stop talking and fix it already!
Maybe because they have
bodyguards strong enough
to deal with pirates who cause a ruckus?
They probably do...
considering the size of the city.
Really?! Hey, what're we gonna do? This is bad.
Why would it be bad? We're customers.
Y-You think so?
Okay, then! See you later!
Wait, Luffy! Usopp!
You guys, come with me.
Hm?
To where?
First, we'll take the reference
letter from Kokoro-san
and go find the man named Iceberg.
We'll ask him to help us
arrange the ship's repair.
We also have to find a place
where we can cash in our gold.
I see... All right, then! Anyway,
let's go! To the city of water!
You're forgetting the gold.
Ah...
Zoro! Make sure you fix it good!
Be careful, Nami-san!
Ahh... I somehow missed
the chance to go with them.
Let's go out together later.
Really?! I wonder if they have a bookstore.
I'm sure they do.
Why don't we go to the
money-changing shop first?
Why? Let's go to the shipyard.
But we can't walk around the island
with this much gold. I get nervous.
Even after changing it to money,
the value is the same.
It's true, but it being this big will
attract people's attention, right?
What if we run into bad thieves?
We're the thieves!
He's got a point. If we change it
to bills, we can all carry them.
Hm? Your remark had a sting to it.
It sounds like me carrying it is a problem!
Yeah. You might drop it somewhere or lose it.
Yeah, he would. It's Luffy we're talking about.
What?! You guys! Don't you trust me?!
--Nope!
--Ah... Ahh... Ahh... That really hurt!
I may not be able to recover from thi-- Hm?
Is this the only entrance to the city?
A rental bull shop?
What's that?
What do they rent out?
What's "bull"?
Beats me. Bulldogs?
Can't be, right?
Excuse me! Please let us rent bulls!
Ask what they are first!
Welcome! You wanna rent bulls, right?
How many are you?
Three!
What kind of bulls would you like?
There're three ranks.
"Yagara," "Rabuka," and "King."
Well, for the three of you,
two Yagaras would probably do.
Okay! Please roast them nice and tasty!
Weird! That conversation is weird!
Oh? You followed logs to get here?
--Yep.
--That's quite an achievement, you guys.
Then you had no idea what bulls were, did you?
--Right.
--Well, to make a long
story short, those are bulls.
They're Yagara bulls.
They're everywhere in town.
In this area, there's a fish called
Yagara that swims with its head out.
This is the city of water.
There're more canals than walkways.
So bulls are a means of transportation
necessary to the residents here.
It's the same when you go
sightseeing on this island.
That fish is pulling a boat?
Rather than pulling, they're letting
people ride on their back.
Well, it's like horseback riding
or riding in a carriage on land...
Oof.
You see the fish pen there?
Well, try and ride on it. It's comfortable.
It'll be 2,000 Berries for two
two-passenger Yagara bulls.
Wow, they're cute!
It's a fish that looks like a horse.
You jerk! What'd you do that for?!
Oh? He must like you. Let's get him for you.
Can he carry heavy stuff okay?
Their power is incredible!
You can even use them for moving.
That bag, huh? What's inside?
Gold.
You're funny. Whatever it is, it'll be fine.
--See?
--Whoa! Give me some!
No way!
What an awfully honest old guy...
You too! Don't show it to others so lightly!
Why? It wouldn't hurt, would it?
My, my... What a surprise...
Well, then... it'll be a million
Berries for two Yagara bulls.
Hey, the price went up, pops.
Sorry. It'll be five million Berries.
It went up even more!
You noticed?
Geez... We can't be too careful.
Here, 2,000 Berries.
Thanks.
By the way, are there any
money-changing shops around here?
Yeah, there are, but with that amount of gold,
the shops around here probably
wouldn't have enough money.
You should go to the downtown
area of the shipbuilding island.
The downtown area of the
shipbuilding island? Where is it?
It's over there. Take this with you.
A map?
This'll be helpful! Thanks!
Pops, is the shipyard there, too?
Yeah. The world's No. 1 shipyard!
That's perfect. Once we get the money,
we can go to the shipyard right away.
Yeah. We can finally have
the Going Merry repaired!
And we'll find a shipwright, too!
I'm getting excited!
--Well, then...
--Shall we...?
All right! Go! Yagara!
Thanks for your business! Be careful!
Dash to the shipyard!
Yahoo!
We're setting off toward the distant orange horizon
Today's winds are blowing
across the morning sea
I can't sleep
The kind of passion I saw this very morning
cannot be stifled by anyone
Hope, frustration
and much more might come our way
but for now
we can just start from scratch
Some time ago, we had a dream
in which we followed our aspirations
so we'll raise our hands high
and embrace the shining sun in our hearts
We're going to make it to that place
Whoa! This is fun!
It's amazing that such a
convenient creature exists!
It doesn't rock much. It's comfortable!
Whoa! The canals even go above the rooftops!
I've never seen such a huge town before!
Yeah. This is a town built around canals!
Water Seven is getting me fired up!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Adventure in the City on the Water!
Head to the Mammoth Shipbuilding Plant"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Adventure in the City on the Water!
Head to the Mammoth Shipbuilding Plant