Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
However, there they find the New Fishman Pirates
have been plotting to destroy Ryugu Kingdom,
arm in arm with Vander Decken, who has been
stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
Meeting Jinbe again at the Sea Forest,
Luffy learns about Fishman Island along with
Nami, Sanji, Chopper, Franky and the others.
Yellow Monkey Arrives!
A Trap to Catch Tiger!
Fisher Tiger's attack on the Holy Land of Mary Geoise
and the Sun Pirates' raid - those events...
...had such impact on Fishmen's future.
15 YEARS AGO
I can't believe that he really did it.
It put Fishman Island in a bad position again.
We won't be welcomed at the World Summit for a while.
Now, what should we do?
But we couldn't stop him that day.
What did you see during your trip?
I saw humans!
Because I could hear that the scream from his soul so loudly.
Extra, extra! Read all about it!
He showed up the Celestial Dragons who no one dares challenge!
Fisher Tiger - the hero of Fishman Island!
Wow! A Fishman changed history!
Listen to me, everyone!
--Oh, that's Queen Otohime! --Her again?
We have been cowering, hiding and running.
But we have learned nothing from it.
If we cut all humans off because of the actions of only a few bad ones,
there will be no future for the Fishmen!
Now, let's live together with humans!
Learn about them under the bright sun!
--Learn about them? --Yeah, I feel sorry for her but...
You two right there!
Sign here!
I-I can't, Otohime-sama!
The whole island is applauding Tiger-san for what he did.
It might cause a rift between us and the humans.
But, after all, it's their fault, of course. So I can't...
Even though it's impossible now, think about 7 years or 11 years or 15 years from now.
Plan for the day that we will be able to participate in the World Summit again.
Please! Sign here! Please!
How great! Fisher Tiger!
Fishman District
He was leader in this town!
He made the Celestial Dragons mad!
Hody Jones
The Celestial Dragons!
He sure showed those annoying humans!
Arlong-san always said that humans were all jerks!
They're lowly creatures!
The Sun Pirates are pummeling humans as they sail around the sea now-dosun!
Cool-dosun!
If we were stronger, we could've gone with them-ch!
Awesome! It's so cool! I wanna do it too, someday!
Go, Sun Pirates! Kill all the humans!
Yeah!
Boss! Boss! There's an enemy ship-nyu!
Boss! Boss! Boss!
Boss Tai! We have a crisis!
Shut up, Hachi!
Why don't you calm down a bit?
How disturbing. Is it the Navy?
Nyu! I saw the Navy's banner!
What should we do, Boss?
That's a silly question!
There is no mistake! Those are the Sun Pirates!
Kill Tiger!
You missed!
Shoot them!
What are you doing?! Shoot at them!
But it's hard when they're in the water!
Oh no.
You Fishman bastards! Return all the slaves!
Then the charges against you will...
R-Rear Admiral-dono! Th-They're coming from below...
What?!
You fools!
Just give us back the slaves. What you guys are doing is a serious crime!
How dare you turn against humans! You guys are only Fishmen!
What did you say?
Let's hear...
Let's hear you say that again!
Help...
Slavery is okay but freeing slaves is a crime?
And you still want us to give humans a chance, Queen Otohime?
Shoot! Shoot!
Shoot at him! We got a tip!
You guys are hiding the former slaves!
No way!
The former slaves?
A-Are you a monster?!
Do you have any proof that we are hiding the slaves?
Check all of us. I heard all the slaves have a mark on their body.
Do you see it?!
L-Let go of me! Stop! What are you doing?!
Help me!
Don't worry, I'll let you go. I'm not like you humans.
Guys! Take their money, goods and food, and get back to the ship!
You deserve execution.
Being human is itself a sin.
Wait, Arlong!
Drop dead!
Vice Admiral Borsalino.
Marineford, Navy Headquarters
G-2 branch - Rear Admiral Kadar's ship has been defeated.
Oh? Why did they even fight them?
I just wanted to know where they were.
It's said if you get close enough to see them,
they'll surround you in the water before you know it.
Oh, that's scary! They aren't known as undersea professionals for nothing.
So, what are we up against?
Well, it looks like Arlong and his men,
who are conducting raids around Fishman Island, are among them.
But they're always in water so it's hard to tell how strong they are.
Arlong... Yes, I've heard about him before.
And they said there is a man
who is as big as Tiger and just as formidable but we don't even know his name.
Oh, that's not good.
Ouch!
So what? It's not so big a deal to get rid of one or two of those lowly creatures!
You two are going too far, don't you think?
We're not a group of killers. Stop acting like fools!
But Brother Tai - I mean, "Boss!" They're all trying to kill you!
If that's what they want, we might go a little too far! It makes us mad!
If you kill somebody, it's your loss! Do you want to be like them?
This is not revenge for their discrimination. Neither was what I did at Mary Geoise.
I broke that stupid unspoken rule but I did so to free all those mistreated slaves.
We Sun Pirates are all about liberation and freedom. There is nothing more to it.
If we start to seek revenge against the humans as we like,
it will only lead them to get back at us later and that's just tragic.
They will look on innocent future Fishmen as their enemies.
Don't you see?
We'll fight and rob those people who come after us but don't cross the line.
We won't kill anyone!
Big Brother! I always wanted to say one thing to you.
"It will only lead them to get back at us"?
We could just kill them so they can't get back at us.
Kill them brutally and scare the hell out of them!
Then they wouldn't dare think about getting revenge!
They don't know how strong and dreadful we can be!
Let it be engraved in their minds! The terror!
What do you think you're doing?!
Is that Jinbe?
Arlong is very hot-blooded and quite a pain in the neck, isn't he?
I don't blame him.
In fact, I have no right to say such a thing.
Brother Tai...
Jinbe, what Queen Otohime is calling for is great.
For her, there is no difference between Arlong and me.
What I'm most afraid of is the demon that is hiding deep in my mind.
At that time, I couldn't understand what Boss really meant.
Nyu! There's a pirate ship!
It's a big one!
They wanna beat us to prove themselves!
Now we have these kinds of enemies, too.
Well, if we sink them, we'll make an example of them!
We were fighting on a daily basis, as criminals wanted by the Government
while Queen Otohime was fighting against the world in her own way, too.
Sign here!
No, Your Majesty! We don't wanna live together with humans!
Please!
Hey, they put a bounty on Boss Tai and Jinbe-san!
What?!
Wow, 230 million berries!
Jinbe-san is 76 million berries!
Wanted posters! The reward has increased again!
Even the World Government is scared!
Destroy the Navy!
Sign!
Let go of me!
So 3 years passed like that and then we met a young girl on some island.
Mister, could you do us a favor?
Twelve years ago
This girl escaped from Mary Geoise like us 3 years ago when you freed the slaves.
Look.
But her hometown where her parents are is far from here.
We wanna take her home but we don't think we can cross the ocean safely.
My name is Koala. I'm 11 years old.
Thank you for helping me 3 years ago.
She might be a kid but she's still a human! Disgusting!
Why did you invite a human on board?!
It's just how things turn out.
Stop smiling! You're an aggravating brat!
Arlong-san!
Let go of me, Hachi! I wanna pound her into pulp!
He's right. She's constantly smiling and kind of creepy.
What are you...?
I'm sorry! I'll work! I'll clean without taking a break! So please don't hit me!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
--What are you doing? --I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
--Hey, you're bleeding. --I'm sorry!
I'll never ever cry - just please don't kill me!
Hey, stop it! Are you afraid of us?
Yes, I am. But I wanted to see my mother so I plucked up courage and got on board.
If I stop cleaning, maybe you men are gonna kill me.
I'll serve you well so please don't kill me!
She's used to living as a slave.
She must have seen other slaves get killed when they cried or took a break from cleaning.
So she has always been afraid that she might be next and she can't trust anyone.
Boss!
Please! Don't kill me! I'll do anything!
Bring this brat to my room.
What is he doing?
Lecturing her won't do anything. She's mentally ill.
Boss! What're you doing in there?!
Stop the bleeding!
I may have been rough on her but she couldn't forget being a slave with that mark on her.
Hey, are you alive?!
Oh, you're up!
Oh, I passed out.
I'm sorry! But I didn't cry so please don't kill me!
I'll never, ever cry so please don't kill me!
It's okay to cry!
Don't think that we're like those stupid Celestial Dragons!
Look closely.
What?
We won't kill anybody!
Let's go, guys!
We'll take her...
...to her hometown!
The Straw Hats and Toriko's friends have the crossover of your dreams!
Chopper has come down with Deap Sea Fever,
so Luffy and Toriko's groups must find a mysterious ingredient to save him.
But Chopper will only last until daybreak!
As the seconds tick by, mighty beasts rise up to block their way!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Team Forms!
Save Chopper"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Team Forms!
Save Chopper