We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for... ONE PIECE
Compasses and stuff'll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Blast through the stingy night!
We've no interest in treasure chests
Pockets bulging with dreams, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
Come on, guys!
What is going on?!
Didn't we take down Moria?!
Luffy!
Not Out of Danger Yet!
Orders to Annihilate the Straw Hat Crew
Hey, Zoro!
Robin!
Sanji!
Their bodies are vanishing!
Why?! Didn't we win?
Dang it! Were we too late?
They're vanishing!
Captain Lola!
Guys!
I thought we won, darn it!
A pirate ship on the Grand Line
I don't believe it!
Captain!
Please come to the deck, Captain!
Quit being stupid and hit the hay!
The morning light will fry you!
It's been two years since Moria
stole our shadows. We'll never...
But Captain, please take a look at my feet!
Huh?
You have... a shadow!
I bet your shadow has also returned, Captain!
O-O-Our...
Our shadows are back!
It's everyone, Captain!
All of our shadows have come back!
Captain, do you think someone defeated Moria?
No way! That's impossible.
He's so powerful that he went up
against Kaido of the Four Emperors.
Who could possibly take out Moria?
Various locations on the Grand Line and West Blue
It's back! I have a shadow again!
How many years has it been
since I've seen the light of day?
Our zombies in Thriller Bark
finally kicked the bucket!
Yay! It's great!
Hurray!
We're free from Moria's curse!
Boss!
I can watch the sunrise!
Look! I have a shadow! It's following me!
I have a reflection!
I can see myself in the mirror.
Hey! What was all that
commotion about, Margarita?
My shadow! My shadow has come back.
What?! Your shadow has returned?
As in the shadow that was stolen
by pirates ten years ago?
It's true...
Sir, I'm terribly sorry!
I was so surprised that I accidentally
dropped your prized dishes!
It's true I had hard feelings
towards plates, but I've reformed!
I didn't mean any harm.
I am really sorry. I will leave
the manor immediately.
How could you say that?
I don't care about those plates!
Did you get hurt?
Really, this calls for a celebration!
This is truly wonderful, Margarita.
You must be so happy.
I am!
Isn't it great, Margarita?
Phew!
I'm very much alive.
For a second, I thought I
was about to go to Heaven.
Sounds good to me! If we can go together,
I'd love to go to Heaven!
This isn't funny, you jerks!
We seriously thought you were dead.
You nearly vanished!
That was terrifying!
Goodness! That was bad for my heart.
Uh, not that I have a heart.
It's the morning sun!
I'm not afraid of the sunrise anymore!
I have a shadow!
I can kiss goodbye to life in the dark forest!
Hurray! Hurray!
It looks like all of them are okay, too.
We nearly ceased to exist
when the morning light hit us,
but our bodies were fully restored when
our shadows returned just in the nick of time.
It's probably along the same lines of
how Moria could alter a body's shape
by manipulating its shadow.
If I make his shadow round...
...Oars will turn into a ball!
Oars Ball!
All I know is that our bodies
and shadows have to match.
Relax! This is the only time we're ever gonna have the fun
of losing our shadows.
Anyway, I'm just glad we didn't lose anyone...
All of a sudden, I feel totally wiped out.
There any cola around here?
All of the strange creatures and phenomena
we've seen since coming ashore
were nothing more than
a ruse put on by Moria.
Now that he has been defeated,
there is nothing left on this island.
Just like waking from a nightmare in
the morning, everything has vanished.
I swear, this was one nasty haunted mansion!
Hey! Hey! Wake up, Absalom!
Come on, Absalom!
Hey, get up!
Lola!
Knock it off! I'm not going to marry you!
Don't make a scene!
She has already lost her shadow.
Hogback?
For the record, what happened to me?
I have no idea what happened to you!
I'd wager someone defeated you. Pathetic!
But more importantly,
I have bad news about Moria-sama...
What?!
Straw Hat defeated Moria-sama?!
Shh! Not so loud! Lower the volume!
You're being loud!
Why are you so riled up, Hogback?
You should be called Rileback.
Thriller Bark is of no use to me now,
but I don't plan on spending
the rest of my days as a loser.
What do you want to do?
Well...
Didn't Luffy shrink back there?
He told me that after he uses the Giant Gear,
his body shrinks for however
long he used that gear.
Don't you think Luffy's new fighting
style is too hard on his body?
I'm worried...
If the enemies waiting ahead of us
only continue to get stronger,
he's gonna keep pushing himself!
We need to pull our own weight better.
You're right.
Whoa, a zombie!
One of them still has its shadow!
No, I'm a severely injured old man.
That's confusing! Just pass
yourself off as a zombie!
Aren't you the old man
we met at the graveyard?
I can't believe it! I never dreamed I would
see the day I could walk under the sun again.
Thank you! How can I ever repay you?
Hey! Grandpa Spoil!
Gramps!
Honorary President of the Victim Association!
Oh, guys! So you pulled through?
Gramps, are you all right?
Yeah!
You know each other?
Oh! Come to think of it,
we still haven't thanked you.
We're grateful from the bottom of our hearts!
Sorry for all the trouble we've caused you.
When we saw all the mayhem you caused,
we figured if you couldn't do it, no one could!
Thank you, guys.
No one in Thriller Bark's Victim Association...
...will ever forget the debt we owe you!
Thank you very much!
If there is anything you'd like,
please say the word!
There isn't much,
but we have some food reserves.
Better yet, you're welcome to marry me!
--We'll pass!
--Five men turned her down all at once!
She's been rejected 4,449 times!
You really don't need to thank us...
Don't say that!
Remember what Luffy said, Gramps?
--I'm especially interested in you!
--We simply fought to suit our own needs.
--Will you marry me?
--We just saved you while we were at it.
How could you say that?!
They actually want to thank us!
Yeah! You should listen to her, Bro!
Let us do something for you!
We don't care if you
saved us on the side or not!
We're grateful that you defeated Moria.
I know, right?
Uh, your eyes...
I know! Why don't you swipe
all of Moria's treasure?
We'll load it onto your ship for you!
Oh, it's already on...
Oh, yeah! I forgot about something important!
What is it?
I had totally forgotten about him...
What's the matter?
We've got a problem!
I see...
It sounds as though my fears were justified.
So it would seem.
Who is that?
There he is...
Everyone, remain calm and hear me out.
During our fight with Moria...
...I forgot to mention this.
There is one more member on this island...
...of the Seven Warlords!
Wha--?!
What did you say?!
That's a...
...Warlord?!
Th-That's messed up!
What are two of the Seven Warlords
doing on the same island?!
We have finally found a
replacement for Crocodile.
It would look bad if another one of the Seven Warlords needed to be replaced.
Is he still breathing, even if barely?
I don't know.
If he is still alive, I would
like to wait for his recovery
and let him retain his position as one
of the Seven Warlords for a while.
We can take further measures later.
If we lose one Warlord after the next,
the title will cease to demand respect.
This information must not get out to the public.
I swear, those pirates
cause nothing but trouble.
I recognize him!
Nearly as large as Moria,
that pirate was called the "Tyrant."
He's Bartholomew Kuma!
That's Tyrant Kuma?!
You mean the pirate whose
cruelty knows no bounds?!
You understand what I'm saying, don't you?
Do not leave witnesses to testify
that Straw Hat defeated Moria.
The World Government is
assigning you a special mission:
Annihilate everyone on the island,
including the Straw Hat Crew.
That will be easy.
I just heard something!
H-He just said "annihilate."
Whoa, wait! Is he gonna annihilate...
...all of us?! Why?!
Give me a break!
We just got free from Moria's power!
No way! We can't fight two Warlords in a row!
It took all we had just to defeat Moria.
Guys, get back! I'll take him on!
Be careful! He uses some sort of power!
I saw someone vanish when
he touched her with his hand.
Negative Ghost!
And Special Hollow!
Th-The people he touches vanish?!
S-Scary!
And he can also warp.
Aren't you the Cat Burglar?
You're part of the Straw Hat Crew!
Is it true that Monkey D. Luffy
has an older brother?
Eh?!
What gives?! He got up there
in the blink of an eye!
We've got a freak on our hands!
His hands... are dangerous!
What?!
He's here!
He's huge!
When'd he get down here?!
I see. I'd definitely call that warping.
Damn it! We were finally set free!
There is no way I'm gonna die here!
Right! I'll never let someone stand
between us and our voyage ever again!
Guys, get him!
Yeah, you heard them!
Let's get him!
Stop, men! You don't stand a chance!
He pierced through the whole group
without even touching all of them...
D-Darn it!
Pirate Hunter Zoro...
I will start with you.
What is with the padding
on the palms of his hands?!
It repels all of my attacks!
It is my ability. Your time's up.
"When it rains, it pours."
I accept your challenge!
If I die, then that shows the limit of my ability.
Next time, on One Piece:
"It Repels Everything
Kuma's Paw-Paw Power"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
It Repels Everything
Kuma's Paw-Paw Power