Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is headed to Navy Headquarters in order to rescue his brother, Ace!
Now, there are only 3 hours left before the public execution of Portgas D. Ace...
Ticking Down to the Time of Battle!
The Navy's Strongest Lineup in Position!
Stand up.
Climb.
South Blue
It's in 3 hours now! I wonder if Whitebeard has arrived yet.
I don't know. Do you think he's really gonna be there?
He's a big deal but isn't he too old?
You think so?
He was around before the Great Pirate Era.
He must be senile by now.
We haven't heard his name in any big news for years.
How can you guys take this so lightly?
Because he's unignorable, Navy HQ has called up its elites and...
...is expecting him with all their forces.
I'm almost certain that Whitebeard is going to appear.
And then what's gonna happen?
I don't know. How am I supposed to know?
East Blue
He's a pirate of a different era.
Is it possible for him to beat Navy HQ?
It's not possible for any pirates to attack Marineford.
That's not true. I think it was 20 years ago,
a pirate called Shiki the Golden Lion invaded Marineford
and left Navy HQ half destroyed.
This time it's going to be worse.
No matter who wins, a lot of people will die.
It'd be better if he didn't appear.
If nothing besides the execution happens, that'd be for the best.
North Blue
Hey, we want drinks, old guy!
Are you asking me to open the bar on a day like this? We're expecting a big war in any minute!
Go home! If the world's still here tomorrow, I'll open it!
Then just sell us some drinks! It feels like we're the ones who're on the scaffold!
We can't do without drinking!
He's not just another old man.
West Blue
He hasn't lost it at all!
It was just a year ago, when we saw him sitting right there...
...we thought we were dead.
Grand Line
Is Whitebeard that outrageous?
Even those kids know it. They're singing as they jump rope.
The pirate Whitebeard is scarier than a devil!
Oh, God!
Where is this world headed?
On the island of Marineford home of the Navy Headquarters,
lies a huge city mainly populated by families of the Navy.
An evacuation order has been issued to all residents at this time.
And at Sabaody Archipelago at the evacuation site,
residents are watching the proceedings of the execution on monitors.
Reporters and cameramen from various places are...
...standing by here to break the news quickly to the world.
That's really the best of Navy HQ.
I assume that Whitebeard knows about this.
But still, will he venture to be there?
Every look-out ship that the Navy sent has been swiftly sunk
and there has been no report of a sighting of Whitebeard.
So the tension at Marineford continues to rise.
And there is less than 3 hours left until the looming execution.
"Navy"
I have problem with that. Is that really necessary?
This public execution is not just an execution of a pirate.
It has great significance for the future of the world.
That's why it's necessary to...
You are responsible for this matter since you are one of the parties involved.
Don't forget that, Garp.
"Absolute Justice"
Marineford
Navy HQ
Hurry and get ready!
Hey you, don't lag behind!
Don't slacken your pace!
No matter what happens, it'll last only 3 hours!
Then it's all finished!
Elite soldiers are summoned from all over the world—totaling almost one hundred thousand.
The crescent-shaped bay area and the whole island are surrounded by 50 Navy ships
and numerous cannons have been set at the bay area.
And in front of all the marshaled forces that can be seen from sea...
...stand 5 ruffians who hold the key to the war. Pirates—the Seven Warlords!
Bartholomew Kuma
Gecko Moria
Don Quixote Doflamingo
Dracule Mihawk
Boa Hancock
It's...
...the admirals!
I don't know why but I find them so intimidating!
Guarding closely below the scaffold are...
...the Navy's greatest powers...
...the three admirals!
Navy Admiral
"Blue Pheasant"
Kuzan
Navy Admiral
"Blue Pheasant"
Kuzan
Navy Admiral
"Red Hound"
Sakazuki
Navy Admiral
"Red Hound"
Sakazuki
Navy Admiral
"Yellow Monkey"
Borsalino
Navy Admiral
"Yellow Monkey"
Borsalino
Every force of justice imaginable is...
...now waiting for the Whitebeard Pirates
to stop them from rescuing Ace!
Listen, Luffy.
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
Uh-huh.
We gotta go out to sea someday...
...and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
I see it!
Hey! Jinbe!
I see the Gates of Justice already! That was fast!
No, it wasn't! If the wind were right, we could have gotten here faster.
However...
I warn you.
As long as we don't open the Gates of Justice,
you guys can't get to Marineford
or even get out of the Tub Current!
There is no sea for you all to get away to or to live on!
So now, how can we get through the gates?
You guys! It's almost time for...
Huh? What is it?
Time for Captain Buggy to conquer the world!
That's right!
Navy HQ is nothing!
Whitebeard is nothing!
Who's gonna be the next Pirate King?
Captain Buggy!
That's right!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Ace!
Hey, look! Fire Fist Ace has come out!
This is the man...
...who may trigger a war that will shake the world!
And he is the one who holds the fate of the world now!
Okay, Garp? I'll tell them everything!
So be it. I'll be downstairs.
Step aside for a minute.
Yes, sir!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
What's going on?
Give me a Transponder Snail.
Yes, sir.
I have something to tell you all.
Portgas D. Ace...
It's about the great significance of his death today.
It's not your fault.
Women are very sweet
at times like this, Tsuru-chan.
Ace, tell them the name of your father.
Father? Why is that important now?
My father is Whitebeard.
No!
Yes, he is! Whitebeard is my only father!
We looked for you with our eyes
wide open at that time.
Because we heard that there might be
a child of that man on some island.
Based on a small amount of reliable information from Cipher Pol,
we checked all newborns...
...and preborn children...
...and their mothers but we couldn't find you.
No wonder.
Your mother risked her life to bear you.
She used a trick that can be called mother's pride.
That has misled us... Indeed, the whole world.
There is an island called Batelira in the South Blue.
Your mother's name is Portgas D. Rouge.
She did something that completely defied natural law...
...for the love of her child.
She kept her baby inside her womb for 20 months!
No way.
And as soon as she gave birth to you,
she lost all of her strength and passed away right there.
A year and 3 months after the father's death,
the child was born with the blood
of the world's most heinous man in his veins.
That was you!
You know it, surely?
They can't blame a child whose not born.
Garp!
Look after my child!
Your father is...
...the Pirate King—
Gold Roger!
Fire Fist Ace is the son of Gold Roger?!
This is huge news.
Call the head office! Let's issue an extra!
Does it continue?
Still?
The bloodline of the Pirate King?!
The secret of Ace's origin has been revealed.
His father Roger's feelings, and his mother
Rouge's strong resolve lay behind it all.
At Marineford, Whitebeard's fleet silently approaches.
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Vast Fleet Appears
Here Come the Whitebeard Pirates!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Vast Fleet Appears
Here Come the Whitebeard Pirates!