Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and on their way
to the next stage—the New World—
they reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
But they have yet to gather
and are stirring things up as a fragmented crew!
Hody's Onslaught
The Retaliatory Plan Set Into Motion
Look at that, Luffy-sama!
That cloud looks like an animal called a "raccoon dog"
that I've seen before in a book!
Ah, that looks like Chopper!
Chopper?
Uh-huh!
Chopper is one of my crewmates!
Crewmates?
Something is flying...
I can't see clearly, it's too far.
Luffy-sama, what's wrong?
Ryugu Kingdom
Port Town of Coral Hill
Mom, what is that?!
Hey, look at that!
What is it?
Ryugu Palace! Ryugu Palace! Come in!
Border Control HQ, Main Entrance
Ryugu Palace! This is Border Control!
Hello? Hello?
That's weird.
Clank.
Why can't we reach them?
Is the Transponder Snail sick?
Why are they coming in flocks to Fishman Island?
I have no idea.
I know those dangerous people from the Fishman District
don't just come here for some shopping.
Listen, guys!
Today will be remembered as the day
that everyone on Fishman Island
is united under one flag!
All Fishmen, including Merfolk,
have to be like-minded!
We must dominate the humans
since they're such lowly creatures who can't even breathe in the water!
Let's correct the mistakes of history now!
Today will be the anniversary of our engagement, Shirahoshi!
No need to hurry.
Let's get married tomorrow!
That annoying faction from the Sun Pirates,
Jinbe's group, is not here-dosun!
Neptune, the God of the Sea, and the brothers;
Fukaboshi, Ryuboshi, Manboshi!
Much! If we can bring those four under control, Neptune's army can't stand against us-ch!
Let's bite all the soldiers' flesh off!
I'll just cut them—whatever you tell me to do.
Let's begin.
Go ahead and begin capturing your objectives!
The Ryugu Kingdom falls today!
And then we will dominate the sea floor!
Just in time.
The Sea Forest... I wonder what that place is like.
There's no mistaking her! Nico Robin of the Straw Hats!
Woman! You and your friends
are suspects in two ongoing investigations!
First, for multiple counts
of Mermaid kidnapping! Second,
you people are suspected of being
potential risks to Fishman Island,
according to Madame Sharley's future vision!
So we're taking all of the Straw Hats into custody!
I don't know what you're talking about.
And did you say "future vision"?
You people need to get your brains checked...
if you unashamedly believe in such unscientific things.
Madame Sharley's future visions are accurate!
Come with us!
No thank you.
I don't want to miss my bus.
Get her!
Mil Fleurs!
W-We have to report...
She... got... away...
"Sea Forest"
They had information as I thought. There is a Poneglyph somewhere here.
I think this kingdom holds
an important key to the Void Century!
Ryugu Palace
What's wrong with these guys?
One after another...
Why do we always get involved in trouble?
Stop whining, Nami!
The battle is on already!
They keep attacking us so we have no choice.
Shut up, Zoro! We don't wanna get ourselves into more trouble than we already have!
What's wrong with pirates fighting pirates?
There's no crime.
Boy, he never learns!
Guys, you're barely clinging to life—
why do you wanna fight so badly?
Let's settle this peacefully...
Do you think they'll give up that easily?
The switch for the gateway...
If we can't open it, they'll kill us!
Kill them!
Let me do it too!
You little—
They leave me no choice.
Die!
Why don't they get it?
Outta my way!
Oops!
I wonder what that was.
Luffy-sama.
Why are you so strong?
I've been training myself since I was a kid.
But there were people stronger than me.
Oh, there are people even stronger than you?
What's wrong, Shark?
You don't feel well?
Megalo?
Do you have a stomach ache, Shark?
That was close!
Be careful, Shark!
Don't make it sound like I cut them down
just for the fun of it!
But you looked like you were enjoying it.
You're a natural born manslayer!
Well then, if you were attacked by pirates,
what would you do? Serve tea?!
Well, serving tea and talking is one way to solve...
They wouldn't let you!
In any case, if you beat them all,
you won't be able to find out what they wanted!
Stop worrying so much about them.
It feels like things are going from bad to worse.
Why do most of our crewmates
tend to act like this?
Well, look at our captain.
You're right, there's no point even questioning it.
I wonder if Luffy-san's met
the Mermaid Princess already. I wanna see her too!
More importantly, untie me! Give me back Shirahoshi-jamon!
Why do you think we want to kidnap
the Mermaid Princess?!
I know Straw Hat Luffy did it-jamon! Shirahoshi!
I saw Luffy-san and Shark-san coming out of the room for sure,
but I didn't see the Mermaid Princess with them.
But she is not the kind of girl
who just sneaks out on her own-jamon.
Shirahoshi is as big as myself-jamon. Someone will notice her if she gets out.
What?! The Mermaid Princess is big?!
I'm a princess-jamon!
No way...
Oh yeah-jamon! Maybe, he hid Shirahoshi in Megalo's mouth and took her out!
Stop making us laugh under these circumstances, King.
Who would do such a thing? Even if he had the idea...
My nose is itching too.
Luffy-sama, did you catch cold?
I don't often catch cold.
I wonder what it is.
Shirahoshi!
In any event, our captain wouldn't kidnap anybody!
You better look for somebody else!
No, I can't think of anybody else!
If Shirahoshi doesn't come back safely,
you can't have your ship or friends back-jamon!
No! You can't do that to us!
I... I did it!
Looks like those human pirates pulled it off.
Sunny, are you alright?!
You're a super miracle ship just as I thought!
This place is like a graveyard of ships.
The tide brings sunken ships here.
Isn't it ironic?
Even though it's that kinda place,
it receives the blessings of the Sun Tree Eve—
corals have grown beautifully drawing fish and whales here.
That's amazing! There are a lot of whales and they are so much bigger than the Sunny.
Whales only come to fertile seas.
This place is wonderful!
I've been studying
this magical Sea Forest in the deep sea.
Yeah, it's hard to believe
that this place is in the deep sea.
Just like Fishman Island.
Treasure Tree Adam—it is so valuable. But you built one hell of a ship out of it.
You think so?
It's made with the same material
as the Pirate King' ship Tom-san made.
It's my greatest design of all!
I'll do the coating.
Count on me-don!
Oh, thank you...
Um... Can I ask your name?
I'm Den.
Den-san. You don't look much like him.
You're a Merman—not a cowfish.
I thought you'd look like him
since you're his brother.
Den (Tom's younger brother)
Shipwright and Sea Forest researcher
That's how a human would think.
Races on earth— family members often look alike, don't they?
Fishmen are a little different.
Fishmen and Merfolk each have different, ancient genes from their ancestors.
"A mother and son"
When an octopus Mermaid gives birth to a shark Merman,
that means one of her ancestors
was a shark Merfolk.
It's not so strange when kids don't look like their parents on Fishman Island.
That's why we can't understand
why you humans want to discriminate against...
those who don't look like yourselves.
Hmm...
By the way, one of your ancestors was a robot?
I'm a human.
Human? Oh, one of your ancestors
was a humanoid robot.
No, a normal human!
It's okay.
It's not okay!
Oh yeah, she mentioned you and Iceberg-kun in her letter.
Oh, that old bag Kokoro wrote to you?
What a thoughtful old woman.
So I know everything about what happened.
My brother lived life his own way-don,
to the very end!
And you traveled all the way here to tell me that.
He had a good pupil.
Stop it!
Oh, so you're a robot!
No... Well, let's just say that I'm a pervert.
Oh, by the way,
somebody's been sitting there for quite a while.
Oh, that's Boss Jinbe!
Boss?
He said he's expecting somebody.
He doesn't wanna enter the island
since he's a wanted man.
Entrance to Ryugu Palace
Gateway
Main Gate
Palace Gate
We have intruders!
How did you guys get this far?!
I can't believe this!
I was ready to start a fight right away
but Neptune and all his soldiers are tied up!
I didn't expect to see a present like this.
What a surprise.
That guy!
Why is he here?!
The hateful Vander Decken! You've shown up at last!
And that's...
Hody Jones from the Fishman District!
Why did he come back here?
Hody? That guy is...
He was once a decorated soldier in our army.
Is this some kind of trap?
It's too good to be true.
We've had visitors one after another.
What a lively palace.
Ah-ha! You guys are their accomplices! You let them in, didn't you?!
You know what, we wouldn't be here
if you guys didn't invite us!
They look formidable!
Who are those people?!
Hey, let us have our arms at least!
Please, let us fight!
Vander Decken!
Since you've shown up, there is no doubt!
You're the one who did it! Give me back my daughter!
We haven't even got married yet.
It's too soon for you to say that, Father-sama.
Don't call me Father-sama!
Where did you take Shirahoshi?! You'd better tell me she's unharmed!
What are you talking about?
You're talking like the Princess is missing.
Quit acting dumb!
Why else would Shirahoshi have disappeared from her room all of the sudden?!
My Shirahoshi disappeared?!
She's my... My daughter-jamon!
Neptune-sama, don't lose your temper
over his nonsense!
Calm down, Decken.
Look. All of the humans that you threw, aimed at the Mermaid Princess, are here.
That means Princess Shirahoshi was here
at least during that time.
Help me...
Plus, it doesn't matter if they're lying or not
because you know how to check where she is now.
Check where she is?
You're right!
Hody, you're a very smart guy! I suspect!
Huh? Is he leaving?
What is he gonna do?
Alright, you coral, fly to Shirahoshi!
It's not heading towards the tower!
We've been in love for a decade! Nothing will tear us apart...
except for death!
...And I had a very big fart!
Luffy-sama, that is so inappropriate to talk about.
Is it?
Before you become somebody else's,
I'd rather see you dead
with your blood splattered all over!
Shirahoshi!
A wall of the royal palace is destroyed and seawater begins rushing in.
Hody attacks Neptune's army with his full might.
The soldiers risk their lives
to protect Neptune, the God of the Sea
when Zoro stands to face Hody.
With the seawater is rising, Zoro will battle in dramatically unfavorable conditions.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Battle in Ryugu Palace!
Zoro vs. Hody"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Battle in Ryugu Palace!
Zoro vs. Hody