Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
rashinban nante jyuutai no moto
compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
delirious with fever, i take the helm
hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
if the dusty treasure map has been verified,
tashikameta no nara densetsu janai
it's not a legend!
kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
when it comes to personal storms,
biorizumu nokkatte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
omoi sugoseba ii
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
poketto no koin
a coin in my pocket,
soreto You Wanna Be My Friend
and do you wanna be my friend?
We Are
we are!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!!
Oh, no!
If I can get my arms and
legs out, the game is mine!
What?!
This is gonna end it... for sure!
He can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
All... Blue...
I'm the strongest man!!
Don Krieg... We lost.
Chief Commander!
Thanks for everything, Sanji-san.
When he wakes up, could you tell him...
Maybe... I can live only a few more hours...
It's kind of stupid that I'm resolved
because I don't have much time left,
but this time, I want to do it with
my own will... in my own way...
Then, there'll be nowhere
for me to escape, right?
You don't have to think about stupid
things like fearing your enemy
or how to keep from getting hurt...
I learned it from that guy.
Well, then!
We gratefully accept the boat.
We don't have to return it, right?
Right. If you have the courage
to come here to return it,
try it, you small fry.
He's right!
Just keep this in your brain!!
This is the sea restaurant Baratie, where cooks fight!
Hmph! What a scary restaurant...
Set Sail!
The Seafaring Cook
Sets Off With Luffy
Ahh! My hat! My straw hat!!
It's right there.
Huh? Oh, yeah. Here it is.
So you're awake?
Oh? Where're those guys?
They left... thanks to you.
Me?
Ghin said, "I'll see you again in the Grand Line."
Ghin did?
To you?
No, to you!!
Speaking of which, since I drove them away,
today is my last day to do chores, right?
Congrats.
By the way, will you...
I'm not going!
I won't become a pirate.
I'll continue to work as a cook here
until I get that damn geezer
to acknowledge my skills.
Okay, then I give up.
Your hand hasn't given up yet!
I can't leave here...
since they're all undependable...
But I'm hoping to go some day...
to the Grand Line.
Then let's go now.
It's not the right time yet.
Say... do you know the All Blue?
No...
Oh, you don't?! It's a miracle sea!
The East Blue, West Blue,
North Blue, and South Blue...
Fish from all those four seas live in that sea!
To us cooks, it's a dream-like paradise!
That's what the Grand Line is like.
So, have you heard...
He looks so happy...
That idiot...
Guys!! Meal time!!
Aw, man...
We can finally eat!
Food! Food! Food!
Hey, where do we sit?
Where's our food?
There're no chairs for you.
Sit on the floor and eat.
No chairs? That can't be true!
This is a restaurant!
Guess we can't help it...
They're acting kinda weird...
Hmph! Nothing new...
Hey!
Who prepared the soup this morning?!
Hey, I did it! I did! Isn't it good?
I made it especially good today!
I can't eat damn nasty soup like this!
What is this, pig feed?!
Hey, is human food not to your liking,
you damn raccoon dog?
Ha! When it's this bad, it's art now.
It makes me sick to my stomach!
I'm sorry, but I'm really
confident about today's soup.
There's something wrong with your taste buds!
Ugh! This is nasty!
I can't eat it!
Right, guys?!
I can't eat something like this!
This is damn nasty soup!
I can't eat soup like this!
This is terrible!
Someone, give me some water!
What do you think you're doing, you bastards?!
You're a sham Sous Chef after all...
You're just an old-timer.
We're sick and tired of you
settling matters with violence!
If the food's bad, we're gonna say so!
What'd you say?!
We're seafaring cooks.
Don't waste even a drop of soup.
Owner!!
You geezer!
What is this damn nasty soup?
It's like sludge!
If we serve something like this,
our restaurant will go out of business!
Don't be ridiculous, you damn geezer!
Just how is this soup different from yours?!
Tell me!
From my soup?
Don't flatter yourself!
Owner punched him...
He didn't kick...
It'll be a billion years before you can
give me a lecture on cooking, little brat!
I'm a man who has cooked
on seas around the world.
Dammit!
That damn geezer! I... I...
I'm not a "little brat" any more!!
This soup is super good, you know...
We know that.
Huh?
Sanji's cooking skills are
recognized by everyone here.
It's not bad at all.
Yeah, this soup is very well made.
Boy, that was scary...
He seriously snapped...
Yeah...
But that idiot won't listen unless we go this far...
Say, kid...
Hm?
You were saying that you wanted
a cook for your ship, right?
This isn't a favor that I'd
like to ask of you or anything,
but would you take that little brat with you...
...to the Grand Line?
The Grand Line... is his dream.
Man, Owner, you really
made us put on quite a show.
I was worried that he might figure
it out because of your bad acting.
Your acting was horrible, too.
I'll have another bowl of soup!
– Me, too!
I can hear everything, you damn idiots...
So what do you say, kid?
No.
What?!
I thought you wanted a cook for your ship.
Or are you saying that he's
not good enough for you?
He's good enough, all right.
I do want him to come with me.
But he says that he wants to
continue working here as a cook.
Even if you guys ask me to
take him with me, I can't.
So you're saying that you can't agree to it
until he tells you so himself, huh?
Exactly. More, please!
Well... fair enough.
But who knows if that twisted
damn brat can just say he'll go...
There's no way he can, since he's
an idiot through and through...
More, please!
Dammit!
Sanji!
What is he? A Fishman?
He came all the way from the
Fishman Island to eat our dishes?
Idiot! It's a human and a panshark!
Hm? What's going on?
Oh? Hey, it's you, Yosaku!
Oh, Big Bro Luffy!
Why are you alone?
Where're the others?
What happened to Nami?
It's not that we caught up with her,
but from the direction Big Sis Nami was heading,
we figured out roughly where she was going.
I see... We can bring her back then.
Well... If what we're thinking is right,
her destination is a crazy place...
In any case, we need your help, Big Bro Luffy.
Please come with me.
Okay! I don't really get it, but got it.
I'll come with you.
Wait!
Hm?
We both have foolish dreams.
In order to achieve my goal, the All Blue...
Sanji?
Yeah. I'll come along...
...on your journey to become "Pirate King"!
What?
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Is that okay or not?
It's okay!! All right!!
I'm happy for you, Big Bro Luffy!
Yeah!
Yaay! Yaay! We got a cook!
We'll have good food!
So that's how it is, everyone.
Sorry for causing you all sorts of trouble.
Ha! I don't like it!
I wanted to kick you out from here myself.
And you decide it so easily?
Sorry for making you resort to bad acting.
You knew?!
I could hear everything, since you're all stupid.
What?!
That is to say, you're willing
to go that far to kick me out,
huh, you damn geezer?!
Why do you always have to talk like that?!
You bastard!
Hmph! That's right, little brat!
I don't like kids to begin with.
Not a single day passed where I didn't regret
letting a useless one live, you damn brat.
Ha! Fine by me, you damn geezer!
Enjoy the rest of your life to the utmost.
Whoa! This is a nice ship.
Is it okay for us to use it?
Of course! It's Sanji's boat.
You still need more?!
Yeah. Give me more meat.
Just how many days will you be at sea?
Don't know...
Kid...
Hm? Pops!
Do you wanna take this?
It's a record of my one-year
journey in the Grand Line.
Don't need it.
I knew it...
I want that marbled meat, too!
Enough already!
Whoa!!
Damn geezer, is this the sea restaurant?
Baratie Employee Guidelines
1.
Serving customers... That is 'love'
And 'love' means 'restaurant'
2.
Motto! Motto! Service motto
3.
Service is about pleasant greetings
4.
The customer is king
For example, Sanji...
Hm? What is it?
Be they arch rogues or jail breakers,
if these damn bastards badly want to eat
and find their way to this restaurant,
there may be a point in our continuing to fight at this restaurant...
Yeah!
We're gonna be busy!
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
Ah...
Uh! Ow! Ouch...
Geez...
You peeled the skin too thick, little brat!
That hurt!
When someone's cooking seriously,
you should just watch quietly!
What?!
Don't get smart, you little brat!
I'm not a little brat!
You damn geezer!!
Try this.
Did you make it by yourself?
Yeah.
How is it?
Cripes, this is damn nasty, you little brat!
You damn geezer!!
Big Bro Cook sure is taking time...
Yeah...
This is for my longstanding grudge!
Be prepared, Sanji!
There's no way you guys can defeat him.
Let's go.
You don't have to say goodbye?
That's okay.
Sanji!
Don't catch cold.
Owner Zeff!!
Thank you for all the damn things
you've done for me over all these years!!
I'll never forget your kindness...
for the rest of my life!!
You asshole!!
I'll miss you, dammit!
I'll miss you!!
I feel sad, dammit!
You idiots!
Men should part without a word.
Let's go!! Set sail!!
I'll see you again, you damn bastards!
As long as you don't fear even death
because you have faith in yourself,
you'll find the All Blue... for sure...
Guys!
Customers are gonna show up soon!
Get to work already!
Chisana koro ni wa takara no chizu ga
When I was little,
Atama no naka ni ukandeite
I had a vision of a treasure map
Itsudemo sagashita kiseki no basho o
and I always searched for that miraculous place
Shiranai dareka ni makenai you ni
before someone else could beat me to it
Yume sae tsukamenai mama
If the world is going to change
Moshi mo sekai ga kawaru no nara
before I can even attain my dream
Nanimo shiranai koro no watashi ni
then take me to the time when I knew nothing
Tsurete itte omoide ga iro asenai you ni
so that my memories won't fade
It sounds like Nami-san headed to Arlong Park.
What's that?
It's a place dominated by Fishman pirates.
She couldn't be...
Considering her cuteness...
she might be a Mermaid...
A water imp?
I'll kill you!
"NAMI"
Then a half Fishman?
No meals for you!
Why?!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Worst Man in the Eastern Seas!
Fishman Pirate Arlong!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Worst Man in
the Eastern Seas!
Fishman Pirate Arlong!