We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for... ONE PIECE
Compasses and stuff'll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Blast through the stingy night!
We've no interest in treasure chests
Pockets bulging with dreams, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
The Promise from a Distant Day
The Pirates' Song and a Small Whale
Okay, close the gate.
Are you sure we should leave Perona?
We can't take someone we can't find.
Sheesh! Where in the world did she go?
Phew! Okay, you can stop now.
Lift your invisibility power!
We're free and clear!
I was terrified we'd get
caught the whole time!
I never did find out what brought
Tyrant Kuma to Thriller Bark.
About that, Absalom.
Tyrant Kuma came to tell us the name
of the successor to the
former Warlord, Crocodile.
His successor...?
Yeah, but that's not the important part.
The successor is a man called Blackbeard.
He's pulled a truly nasty stunt.
Read that.
"Fire Fist Ace, 2nd Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates...
...has been imprisoned in Impel Down"?!
It's well known that Ace is
one of Whitebeard's top dogs.
The government just got
their hands on a powerful card.
Definitely.
Depending on how they play it,
this could completely change the Pirate Era.
We've got a serious situation on our hands!
It's no time for Moria-sama
to be dead to the world.
I see where you're coming from,
but I'm more interested... in finding a wife.
Okay. Bring me a corpse that turns you on.
I don't want a zombie!
I wanna marry a living woman!
One day after defeating Moria
In the end,
everyone slept all day in that courtyard.
Well, sure. We were up all night fighting like mad.
I'm starving, Sanji!
Nibble on some cheese.
Cheese doesn't cut it!
Cheese doesn't energize me!
Then start hauling the ingredients
I need to the courtyard.
I'm sure the members of the Victim
Association don't want to budge.
So we're eating over there.
I'm sorry about that.
Everyone is just so happy to see
the sun for the first time in years.
They are crying tears
of joy while sunbathing.
Where did all of that energy come from?
It's so weird! It's a mystery!
Do you have enough food?
We have a mountain of additional food
on top of everything that was stolen.
We're doing great.
I wonder who did that. There are
some nice people out there!
And they even loaded your ship
with all of this treasure.
Even assuming it was Christmas,
this is far too generous.
This is bliss!
Oh, a glass armband!
This is cool!
I claim this!
H-Hey, you know what'll happen
if you take any of the treasure...
R-Right, Nami-san?
He can have it! There aren't any gems.
Huh? Is that how this works? Cool!
But I don't have a single
piece of treasure for you!
We wouldn't take treasure from
the people who saved us, Namizo.
Huh?
This is a nice knife!
What did you just say?
I'm sorry! This is out.
It's studded with gems.
Huh? It popped right out.
Who is Namizo?
Come to think of it, this is rather strange.
For some odd reason, I don't feel
like this is the first time we've met.
By any chance, are you Lola?!
Yep. Did I tell you my name?
So you're Lola!
I'm happy to see you again!
L-Lola...? Wh-Whoa, wait! Just a sec!
That boar zombie was her...?
You must be confused, huh?
I'll fill you in later.
Anyway, take this. It's
my way of thanking you.
Huh? Are you sure? You're thanking me?
Nami gave away some of our treasure!
I'm going on ahead. Is this everything?
A storm is coming!
Huh? A storm? Really?
This is the life!
The light is seeping into my body.
We're really alive.
Hey!
We brought food!
Straw Hat!
If you told us, we would have carried it!
We shouldn't let our savior work!
Is Zoro up?
He needs absolute rest,
so he's in the mansion.
Hey, wake up.
Chopper!
We brought the stuff you asked for.
Oh, thank you.
How is he doing?
I've never seen Zoro so badly hurt.
He nearly lost his life.
I think something must have happened...
...while we were unconscious.
Indeed. I sincerely doubt
that man simply left.
And it's strange how Luffy
is bursting with energy.
I have no idea what's up with that, either.
To be honest, I saw what went down!
I saw what happened from beginning to end!
I'll give you the dirt.
I'll fill you in on what happened!
Come.
Wait! No, wait a second!
--Hold up!
--Sanji?
Wait, why?! You were pretty cool yourself.
You were like, "Instead of the
swordsman's life, take mine."
Drop it!
Now start talking. What happened afterwards?
I want to know what happened
after I blacked out.
Okay...
That Warlord had yet
another shocking ability.
He pressed his paw against Straw Hat.
It repelled all of the "damage"
that Straw Hat had taken!
His damage...?
It was like a bubble of agony. And then...
If you want to take his place,
take all of his pain and
suffering unto yourself.
It will be impossible for you to survive
when you are already on the brink of death.
You will die.
Have a small taste.
Even the swordsman started
screaming bloody murder
when he touched a small portion of it.
I hate to say it, but I
thought he was a goner.
That's what makes it so touching!
It seriously made me cry!
I see. That explains why Luffy is
doing well while Zoro is bedridden.
That was rash!
Where did all of this blood come from?!
Hey, are you still alive?!
Where is he?!
What happened here?!
No...
Nothing happened...!
Come on! Let's tell everyone
about the Straw Hats' heroic story.
Yeah! I'm itching to tell them!
Wait!
Don't be insensitive.
He didn't risk his life out of
a desire to earn our gratitude.
What would happen if they learned that
Luffy's pain hurt a friend?!
Especially Luffy!
Just how badly are you
dying to tell everyone?!
We can't tell them?
You're killing me!
All that matters is that everyone is okay.
Come on! Let's go eat.
Th... Th-Th...
These guys are super cool!
Their captain is so lucky!
So that explains it.
Hey, you two!
Weren't you acting like you knew
what happened? What did you see?
Don't ask such an insensitive question.
All that matters is that everyone is okay.
I-I wanna tell them!
K-Keep that manly heroic story to yourself!
Wh-What gives?
Thank you for the food!
Delish! I've never eaten
such good food before!
Oh, here! Try this! This!
Yeah! It's been years since
we've eaten a decent meal.
I'm glad to be alive!
I cooked up a storm!
Don't let it go to waste.
To think I get to eat your cooking again!
This really is lip-smacking good!
Not that I have any lips!
You need to shut up and eat!
That skeleton is hilarious!
But honestly--oh, pardon me.
After eating until I was full
both yesterday and today,
I may have gained weight!
"Even though I'm a skeleton!"
I can't take it anymore!
Skeleton, you rock!
How come that skeleton is able to talk?
And he's a hoot!
You're a clever skeleton, you know that?
Why are you able to move around?
Hey, it doesn't really matter!
--Oh, dinner!
--Wow!
--Dinner!
--Yay!
--Oh, baby!
--Dinner!
--Come on!
--Super!
We didn't have a toast
and it still turned into a party.
He's sleeping right through all this noise...
And here he's the toughest guy in the crew...
Hey, Chopper! Look!
--Luffy!
--This is for Zoro.
Now drink away!
Don't give it to him!
Why not?! This will fix Zoro
right up, since it's his favorite.
What type of treatment is that?!
That won't work? Then how about meat?
Okay, okay. I'll gladly accept
your sentiment alone.
But only your sentiment!
There was a piano in this room?
Hey, I thought you only played the violin.
I can play most instruments.
Really? You're pretty good.
Um, I'd like to touch on
an earlier conversation.
To be honest, I also saw what happened.
I was greatly moved by what you two did.
Isn't it wonderful to have comrades?
Don't include me in that.
I merely made a fool of myself.
No, you bore the same resolve.
Would you like to pick a song?
I'll take a request.
Yeah? I can request anything?
In that case...
And then...
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
Wait, didn't you just ask for a request?!
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho!
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
Time to ship out Binks' Brew!
The sea breeze blows us to who-knows-where,
let the waves be our guide!
O'er across the ocean tide, the sunset stirs, going wild!
Look to the skies! Watch the circling birds
as they sing and pass us by!
Fare thee well to the weaver's town,
to the harbor as well...
Sing a booming song,
a song for us casting off!
Oh, the gold and silver waves,
all of 'em turnin' to sea spray!
As we journey off t'ward the ends of the high seas!
"Binks' Brew." I thought I recognized the song.
This takes me back.
Whee! Yahoo! Keep it going!
Hey, Brook! I know this song.
Shanks and the guys used to sing it.
Yeah. A long time ago,
all of the pirates would sing this.
They sang it in good times and bad.
So you're gonna join our crew now, right?
After all, you've got your shadow back!
You can hit the seas without
fear of the sun, right?
About that. There was one thing
I neglected to tell you.
What is it?
I promised one of my comrades something.
I must tend to that first
or I will lose face!
Yeah. You're talking
about Laboon, aren't you?
I know all about it.
Franky and Robin told me.
Huh? Oh, that's right.
Laboon!
That is the name of the whale.
He is at a certain cape--
Listen, Brook! We met Laboon
at Twin Cape. Honest!
I already knew that Laboon
had been waiting there for his friends
to return for the past fifty years.
Skeleton, what's wrong?
The tempo is getting slow.
This is the symbol of
our promise to fight again.
Until we come back, don't remove that
mark by hitting your head. Got that?!
All right!
See ya, whale! I'm leaving now!
Boy, was I ever surprised when I learned
that you're the surviving member
of the band of pirates he's been waiting for.
And you still remember your promise to him.
I bet Laboon would be thrilled if he knew!
J-Just a moment, please!
I'm shocked! This is so sudden.
Is it true? Did you actually meet Laboon?
Yup.
Even though fifty years have passed?
Laboon is still waiting for us at that cape?
Are you telling the truth?!
Yup!
We also bore witness.
We saw him with our own eyes.
Yeah!
Was he well?
Sure was!
He was as big as a mountain.
I'd love to see him!
When we left him, the cutie
was about the size of a boat.
He had a stubborn streak, but he loved music.
He was a good boy...
Even now, I can still...
...picture him...
Is that right?
He's doing well?
I have never been this happy in my life!
Where did that whale come from?
It's following our ship.
It must have gotten separated from its pod.
The poor thing. The ocean is a big place!
It looks sad. Well, it's still just a calf.
Captain Yorkie, why don't we play a song?
Great idea, Brook! Hey, everyone!
Grab your instruments.
Okay!
Let's show him what the
Rumbar Pirates that make
crying children laugh are made of!
Sounds good!
One, two, three, four!
Laboon, you are our dear comrade!
That's why we can't take you with us.
The Grand Line is so dangerous,
we want you to wait here.
We will swing around the Grand Line.
I swear we will come back
to this cape to see you again!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Brook's Past
A Sad Farewell with His Cheerful Comrade"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Brook's Past
A Sad Farewell with His Cheerful Comrade