Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and in order to move on
to the next stage, the New World,
they return to Sabaody Archipelago!
Did you know about this?
What do they mean by "Soul King"?
About Brook?
He might not...
want to be a pirate ever again.
Hey, look!
Hey, it's you guys!
Reporting from Grove #46.
The rookies joining the Straw Hats
are showing up one by one.
I can confirm the identities of four captains.
Big Guns Assembled
The Danger of the Fake Straw Hats
Thank you!
Thank you, baby!
Oh, there it is!
45 degrees!
Thank you!
I sure worked up a sweat!
Well done, sir!
Oh yeah!
How refreshing!
It's cooling my bones...
Ring, ring, ring...
Sabaody Archipelago, Grove #46
Reporting from Grove #46.
The Straw Hats' meeting spot
More than 100 pirates have assembled now.
If they all teamed up with Straw Hat Luffy, it would be—
Hey, what's wrong?! Respond!
This is bad!
Hurry up with those reinforcements!
Hey, hey, hey!
I was wondering who it was,
turns out it's a Navy soldier!
Oh gee!
What's going on here?
Oh! Oh! Don't tell me...
that you just called soldiers over?
What's going on here?
Are you from the Navy?
N-No, I haven't!
I was about to, but...
Oh no, I'd rather you don't!
You know, if you do,
I'll paint this whole plaza red!
In yours and your comrades' blood!
Isn't it right, Coribou?
Huh?! I'm sorry, brother, so sorry!
Over here, you fool!
I'm sorry!
Not there either, you dumb fool!
"Soldier's Bane," Caribou!
Enough fooling around.
He did it!
So the rumors are true.
Oh, Lord!
Have mercy!
Forgive this foolish soldier
who tried to kill me with a pistol!
Please have mercy on him!
I'm sorry, Lord! I'm so sorry!
Bury him, Coribou!
Bury this wicked Navy soldier alive!
Okay! I dig! I dig!
W-Wait!
Don't do that!
I didn't call the Navy!
That's enough, Caribou!
Let that insignificant soldier be.
Just leave him there.
Here comes Captain Straw Hat Luffy!
Listen men!
Look around you!
You may not know each other
but as of today, you're all my vassals!
You're all Straw Hat Pirates!
That means when I become Pirate King,
you'll be shipmate to the King!
But to make that happen,
in the ventures that lie ahead,
become my arms and legs
and fight for me till you kick the bucket!
It's like a dream come true!
That's the infamous pirate who wreaked havoc
on the three strongholds of the World Government: Enies Lobby, Impel Down and Navy HQ!
He's definitely one of the strongest candidates to become Pirate King!
This is what it means to bet on the winning horse!
Most of them are here already.
Is this it?
Can't wait to see everybody!
Shut up!
I summoned you here for one reason!
Your precious Big Boss, that's me,
has been insulted by a bunch of nobodies!
They're still somewhere on this island!
Find them and bring them to me!
Consider it done, Boss!
We won't forgive those fools!
But two years really changes a person, huh?
You guys are a lot quieter than you used to be.
This mustache guy seems to know
the real Straw Hats.
Who is he?
I don't know, but keep your mouth shut
and don't give us away!
All we have to do is hand him over to the captain.
Right.
And I don't remember you being so friendly with each other either.
I guess a lot changes in two years.
Like your faces.
Are you wearing disguises as well?
Hey, wait up!
Encore! Encore!
I see.
The Navy, huh?
I understand.
Please don't push!
Soul King! Come out on stage already!
I need a little more time.
Yes... My fans are calling for an encore...
and they won't stop chanting
so I have to go back out.
Sorry to keep you waiting, everybody!
Actually, there's something I have to tell you all.
Today, I, Soul King, will—
That's enough!
The concert is hereby canceled!
The Navy? Why are they here?
Acting captain of the Rumbar Pirates—
"Humming Swordsman" Brook.
You are suspected of being a pirate worth a bounty of 33 million berries!
On top of that,
we have information that you're one of Straw Hat Luffy's crewmates!
Soul King Brook!
Or rather, Pirate Brook!
You're under arrest!
No way?! Brook-sama is...
The Soul King is a criminal?
He's a pirate?!
But they said Straw Hat Luffy was dead!
It's all over, Brook.
I thought this might be your handiwork,
Manager.
When you announced your retirement backstage,
you honestly took me by surprise.
Your popularity is still on the rise!
We could've made a fortune off you!
But you betrayed us!
Our company's doomed!
Let's all die together, Soul King.
Grove #17, the Sunny's mooring island
Awesoooooome!
Isn't it?!
His body's incredible!
You're a robot!
Can you shoot laser beams?!
What about missiles?!
What can you transform into?!
Indeed! With the dreams and passions
of men riding on his back,
he springs into action!
His name is...
Armored Me!
He's a robot! A robot!
Calm down, Chopper!
You'll have a heart attack!
But wait, Franky.
How can you do detailed shipwright work
with such huge hands?
What are you talking about?
Whoa! More hands!
He's got hands in his hands!
Robin!
Nami!
You look great!
What's with that body?
Who knows?
I still haven't figured it out.
Oh, this is the coating?
Try pressing my nose.
Your nose?
Press and hold it!
For at least three sec—
Press and hold for at least three seconds, please.
He repeated it like a robot!
How thrilling!
Exciting!
One... Two... Three...
Heart pounding!
Your hair grew!!
Hair!!
Can you have any hairstyle you want?!
Of course!
Incredible!
Awesooome!
Hey, Nami!
What's up?
Yeah, yeah...
What's he been doing for the last two years?
Can you show me the weapons?! The weapons!
Don't be stupid! I won't do the main event
until Luffy is here-mecha.
He moved like a robot!
He added "mecha" at the end!
Everyone!
Rayleigh-san! Shakky!
I'm sorry to interrupt your reunion...
but the situation on the island's changed.
Pirate Brook!
Put your instruments on the ground
and your hands in the air!
Backup band!
Chorus! Dancers!
Would you please join me in one last song?!
It'll be alright!
My music's gained new power!
Are you insane?
It's over for you, Brook.
Manager, you helped me a lot these past two years.
I want to thank you
for bringing me to this island too.
This island holds the memory of our defeat.
It's an island of regret, but...
it's also an island of new beginnings!
I'm a musician.
It's my job to bring
greater excitement to our adventures!
Straw Hat Luffy, dead?
Ridiculous!
Tell the whole world!
The pirate—Straw Hat Luffy—is alive!
He'll become the king of the seas someday!
Head Office, can you hear me?
There's big news!
A calm, quiet departure doesn't fit him at all! Oh baby!
Soul King!
Love him to the bone!
Yeah!
To my beloved friends...
Listen to my last soul!
Yeah!
Luffy-san, let's go to the New World!
You fool! We said
the concert is canceled!
Shut up, Navy guy!
Just one more song!
Let him sing!
That's right! We don't care
who Soul King really is!
See? Music is always on our side!
One, two, three, four...
"New World"!
Oh yeah!
Children!
This is the tale of a hero.
The tale of a man who will become king.
There are no second chances in battle,
yet he still stands firm,
nothing but sandals on his feet!
Oh yeah!
Come on baby!
Those who reach for their dreams must worry,
at times their dreams seem much too far away.
Only after you confront yourself
will you truly succeed.
He wants to hold a dream greater than any other,
but I've got a feeling that he can reach it anyway.
Today is the day!
We've waited long enough.
No more anticipation,
we don't have to wait another night.
Today is the day!
It's the greatest day!
Kick the broken clock!
For the New World! For the New World!
For the New World! The world will change!
Once again!
What?!
You fools!
He got away because of you!
We finally had the perfect cash cow!
The Navy?!
That's right.
They think the impostors
are the real Straw Hats.
And they've mobilized their forces.
I know because I tapped
into their communications.
I've already warned Brook-chan
via Transponder Snail at the concert hall.
He should be coming here soon.
Really? He's giving up being a star?
I knew he had grit.
Nami-chan, you're the navigator, right?
I'll teach you how to control a coated ship.
It's vital that you learn it well.
Oh... okay.
I'll do my best!
Huh, what's going on?
It got tense all of the sudden.
But, Rayleigh! Luffy isn't here yet!
Don't worry about that!
Captain!
Huh?
Call me Big Boss, fool!
We couldn't find the real pet
but isn't this the guy you were looking for?
Oh!
Luffy's already on the island!
I can't wait!
I gave Sanji a Baby Transponder Snail
when he came here.
He's with Zoro right now.
Really? That's good.
But he'd better hurry.
The Navy is getting close.
So it's only Monkey-chan
that we can't get in touch with, huh?
But let me give you this Vivre Card.
It'll lead him to you.
Grove #42 should be a good place—it's on the coast.
Anchor your ship there and gather your crew.
This might get a little rough,
but it's time to put the past behind you...
and embark on a new journey!
Luffy is the only one still missing.
The crew awaits their captain's return on the Sunny.
But Luffy gets caught up in a battle
between the Marines' Pacifistas and the Fake Straw Hats.
The results of his two years of training are revealed!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Battle is on!
Show Them What You Got From Training!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Battle is on!
Show Them What You Got From Training!