Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy, depressed after losing his brother
Ace in the war against the Navy,
lamented over his weakness but soon
realized the importance of friendship.
At that moment, Dark King
Rayleigh appeared before Luffy.
I have a suggestion for you.
Back to Our Captain
Escape From Sky Island
and the Winter Island's Incident
What?
Luffy-kun...
Luffy...
I didn't expect that...
Rayleigh, what are you saying...
Luffy?
I think that's what you and
your friends need the most.
But don't you think what Luffy-kun
really needs now is...
...to get his body and mind healed?
But my friends will...
Yeah, I think they will
try to get to Sabaody.
The news about you has spread
all over the world already.
I bet it has reached your friends by now.
Then, I have to see them...
I promised them. I gotta go.
To Sabaody!
Then, here's my second suggestion.
Huh?
Meanwhile...
On the small Sky Island - Weatheria,
where scientists study the weather...
Is it really true?
That young girl...
...tried to escape from this island?
Yes, it's true.
Where are you going, young girl...
She suddenly disappeared
from the Weather Field
and showed up at the Balloon Terminal...
Please! Don't get in my way!
Then she hijacked a balloon
carrying a heavy load!
However...
What happened?! It's out of control!
Damn! What's wrong with this balloon?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Somebody stop this thing!
No!!
It's coming this way!
Run fast!
Move, move!
And that's what happened.
I had no clue that she'd
do something like that.
I wonder what made her do such a thing.
"Crime"
Let me out! I'll give you back what I took!
I gotta go somewhere!
Hey, let me out of here already!
Oh yeah! Haredas-san... Call Haredas-san!
Please!
We won't let you out! We don't
know what you'd do next!
How should we punish this young girl?!
A sentence of flooding or lightning?
You common cat burglar!
I won't do anything!
Just let me out of here!
No way!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Oh, Mr. Haredas!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
Hey! Hey, hey, young girl.
That's too much!
Seems like you're really in a rage again.
Ta-dah!
This can help. Let me show you something.
These are tightly tied Wind Knots!
Mr. Haredas!!
I said "let me out"! You want
another one?! I'm in hurry!
Mr. Haredas! Can you hear us?! Mr. Haredas!
Yes, this is Haredas...
She hit him rather than
talk to him! She's a devil!
Doctor! Call the doctor!
What?
She stole Weather Balls from the
Weather Field and our research notes?
As you see here, Mr. Haredas.
Young girl...
I used to be a thief and I'm a pirate now.
What's wrong with stealing?
She's the worst kind of human being!
We have such a villain in our country!
Like I said... I wanna
get out of this country!
Let me out of here! I'm begging you!
I gotta go now! You got
back what I stole, right?
Hey, let me out!
Don't get too close! She's very violent!
What's the matter with you all of the sudden?
You tried to hijack the balloon and
go down to the sea, didn't you?
Amateurs can't operate a
balloon. You could have died.
You were very eager to learn
the science of weather.
What happened to you?
It's in that newspaper.
Newspaper?
The "Luffy" in that newspaper
is the captain of our ship.
What?!
Oh, it's this guy.
They said he caused quite
a stir in the previous war.
He's a hot rookie with a Straw Hat.
Oh, I never would have thought
that this boy was your captain.
After his crew was separated,
Luffy must've been fighting
such a hard battle on his own.
And he took part in the Paramount War
in order to rescue Ace, and...
...he saw Ace killed right before his eyes!
And I didn't even... know about it!
I know that Luffy will be there
at the place where we promised to meet!
Before he is completely broken,
I wanna see him and support him!
Oh, hey, hey, hey, young girl!
Let her out now!
We're so violent! We abducted
a young girl and made her cry!
--Give the key to Mr. Haredas!
--The key, the key!
Here, you can come out now.
I'm sorry, young girl...
--Where did she go?
--I don't see Mr. Haredas, either.
Huh? How did she make it that far?!
Thanks! Bye!
Huh?! What the...!
She pretended to cry and now
she took Mr. Haredas hostage!
And she took the stolen goods, too!
--We can't let her get away!
--Catch her!
Weatheria's science of
weather must be kept secret!
Chase her!
I don't care where! Please
take me down to the sea!
--That's impossible...
--Make it possible!
Luffy! I know that you're okay!
I'm sorry!-- You've always supported us!
It's our chance to return the favor!
Catch her! Don't let her get away!
Oh, young girl, you haven't
stop pretending to cry.
Shut up!
Meanwhile, on the Winter
Island Future Land Baldimore
where the genius Vegapunk was born...
Grandpa! Grandpa! Grandpa!
Geek! Geek! Geek! Geek! Geek!
Geek! Geek! Geek! Gee...
I mean, god!
What's wrong, Kitton?
Well, the old man has become
another person again!
He's like a demon this time!
Is there a ship?!
Here he comes!
I bet you put something strange
in his stomach, didn't you?
Like habanero juice or kimchi soda?
No, I didn't!
Hey, grandpa!
I gotta go see my friend as soon as possible!
Give me a ship... A ship to take!
Ship?
No, I can't do that.
Because we don't have a ship on this island.
There is a liner that brings
us supplies once a month
and Navy ships that come irregularly.
When is the liner due?
It just came a week ago.
Damn! I gotta wait for 3 weeks?!
This country is surrounded by thick
ice. It's like a natural fortress.
In order to get here, you need an
ice-breaker with special equipment.
Damn it all!
I can build a new ship but
it'll take too much time!
Ol-Old man, you need to calm down.
Good smell... Flavor!
I don't have any time for this!
I have to get off of this island at any cost!
With all that he's going through now...
What am I doing here?!
Damn!
Old man.
Seems like you have a good
reason but nothing can be done.
Oh yeah!
If I remember correctly,
there was an
ice-breaker developed by Vegapunk at his laboratory.
He made it years ago, so I don't
know if it still works...
No! It's too dangerous!
I'm not gonna go this time.
It's that place again...
"Again"? Don't tell me
that you snuck in there!
--Yeah, a while ago.
--Uh-huh, a while ago.
What?!
I can repair it! Because I'm a shipwright!
Oh no, that's not what I'm concerned...
Let's go back there now!
Listen to me!
Too cold!
We have an intruder!
Someone's breaking into
Dr. Vegapunk's laboratory!
Don't use any firearms inside!
Remember that you're surrounded by
priceless treasures! Understood?
Roger that!
Stop!
Damn! I didn't expect Navy soldiers here!
They tightened the security after I broke in!
No, I shouldn't.
I'm not gonna shoot!
Don't let him get away! Go!
Treasure? That laboratory?
Yes, Vegapunk works for the Navy
as head of all the sciences
and we feel proud of him!
I mean, you can say that his
brain is a world-class treasure.
This is where Vegapunk spent his boyhood.
Take a look at that mountain.
It has an odd shape, doesn't it?
It does when I come to
think of it... What is it?
That's something he made when he was a kid,
to help the people in this
country from severe cold.
He converted animals in the forest
into a work force and almost finished it
but it's still incomplete.
It's an earth heating system that
will warm the whole island up.
But as with many of his ideas,
he couldn't make what was in his head real.
There wasn't enough technology
or money to make it happen.
But seeing him sad that he
couldn't make everyone happy...
...warmed our hearts.
It's super tearjerking!
Oh, is it?
We are always waiting for him to come home.
If you understand,
please don't ever go into
the laboratory with the self-destruct button.
What?
Did you just throw out the name of
the most unwanted button in the world?
I didn't know that.
Say old man, let's go home!
Let's go home and drink hot tea!
I can't do that!
Because that's the only place
that has an ice-breaker,
which I need to get off of this island!
I have to do it!
I just learned the news
of my captain's ordeals.
Bye! Thank you for everything!
Wait! Don't ever push the
self-destruct button!
Why would I, stupid?!
Why did he
put one in in the first place?!
Hey, I just saw somebody!
It's this way! Hurry up!
Where's the ice-breaker?!
Stop!
Hey, somebody broke into the laboratory!
Really? That's not good!
Even a blueprint from there is priceless.
Stop!
I think I outran them.
To all soldiers!
If you break something in the
genius Vegapunk's house while in pursuit...
--...it's a breach of the criminal code!
--Yes, sir!
It's all super brilliant! I can't believe
these are all from his younger days.
A lot of these ideas would need a couple
hundred years to implement fully.
They're right. As an engineer, I
don't wanna mess with anything here.
Oh, it's a pirate mark!
Can I ask you something? If I
push that button by any chance...
Old man?
Is it gonna be my fault?
Of course it is!
This incident on the Future Land
will be known around the world
as Baldimore's nightmare.
After hearing about the Paramount War,
Zoro races full-tilt toward the sea.
Mihawk watches him approach with cool eyes.
What will come of their reunion?
Meanwhile, Luffy sets a huge plan in motion!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Contact! The Great Swordsman, Mihawk
Zoro's Obstinate Struggle"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Contact! The Great Swordsman, Mihawk
Zoro's Obstinate Struggle