A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
Another group of illegal entrants
has already infiltrated this land.
Old lady Amazon informed us
that it's a ship with seven
Blue Sea people on board.
Seven Blue Sea people...
Could he mean us?!
Everyone, halt!
Heso!
Why, heso!
H-Hey, what're you guys saying?
So you're the seven illegal entrants
who came from the Blue Sea?!
I'll humbly bring Heaven's Judgment upon you!
Illegal entrants?!
Already Criminals?!
Skypiea's Upholders
of the Law
Hm? Illegal entry? What's that?
I-Is that right?
There's no use making excuses,
since Amazon, the inspector at Heaven's Gate,
sent us pictures taken by a Vision Dial.
Oh, no! That can't be true!
Isn't that some sort of a mistake,
Captain McKinley?!
They're not bad people like you say.
What do you mean by illegal entry?
Was the entrance fee 1 billion Extol per person?
It's true that we didn't pay that.
But that old lady said we could still
pass without paying, didn't she?
Yes, she did!
It's no use.
Please stop making excuses and admit it.
However, there's no need to get panicked yet.
"Illegal entry" is only an 11th degree crime
according to "Heaven's Judgment."
Once you accept your punishment,
you can become legal tourists on the spot.
Oh, you should've said so sooner.
I still don't like it, but just
what is this punishment?
It's simple.
Please pay ten times the entrance fee.
If you pay right now,
we'll humbly write off your crime.
10 billion Extol per person,
in other words, 70 billion
Extol for all seven of you.
S-Seventy billion Extol?!
S-So how much is one Extol in Berries?
Berry...
That's the currency in the Blue Sea, right?
Ten thousand Extol is one Berry.
Ten thousand Extol is one Berry...
One, ten, hundred, thousand, ten thousand,
a hundred thousand, million...
Ahh! How much would that be?
Then, 70 billion Extol is 7 million Berries.
That's expensive!!
Do you realize how much rice
we could buy with that?! Hey!!
After risking our lives coming up into the sky,
why do we have to pay that much just to enter?!
We can't agree to that!
What are you saying?
If that was the case,
all you had to do was pay
700,000 Berries when you entered.
I'm telling you that's still expensive!
Consider this a forewarning,
but we, the White Berets, are the
unit directly under God's priests.
Please be careful, as arguing
raises the degree of your crime.
Oh, whatever. Let's just forget this guy.
More importantly, we'd better go find Nami-san.
I'm worried.
She may be crying somewhere right now.
Those guys earlier knew that
we came to the sky island,
which means something may be
happening to Luffy and the others, too.
I have to hurry!
Okay, then!
As soon as the wind direction changes,
we'll go out for an adventure...
no, to look for Nami!
H-Hey, Luffy!
W-Well, Usopp, what's wrong?
No, no... I should calm down now
and somehow talk him out of it.
Hmmm, you know, if Nami is just
taking a little ride around here,
she may come back soon.
If she does, you'll miss her.
Taking a little ride?
But she's taking too long for that.
Listen!
Luffy's purpose is to go on an adventure
to the so-called "place where God lives,"
rather than finding Nami!
That's right.
He's planning to go there.
Right? If we go to that place,
we'll incur God's wrath and really be in big trouble.
That girl told us that, remember?
Then, what're we gonna do?
We should just wait quietly for Nami
to come back without making a fuss.
It's Nami we're talking about.
She must have a secret stash with some
small amount like 7 million Berries or so.
Actually, there's no way she doesn't.
What have you been blabbering about?
Come to think of it,
it seems one person is missing.
In addition to the illegal entry,
now there's suspicion of fleeing.
Ahhh, h-hold on a second.
She'll be back soon.
Then, we'll pay the entire amount.
So, please relax and wait calmly.
Luffy, you too! If you do something
stupid and make Nami angry,
you know what's gonna happen, right?!
Got that?! Just wait!
Hmm. Just a little bit, okay?
Sanji, you, too.
Yeah.
Then, guys, we break up for now!
Now, Robin-chan, shall we
have some tea over there?
Sure.
Phew...
I somehow managed things for the time being.
Hey, Chopper!
Hm?
Do you wanna go fishing or something?
That sounds good! Let's do it!
Conis! Is there any place around here we can go fishing?
Yes, there's one nearby. I'll take you there.
I can't wait to ride it!
I hope it can be fixed.
Oh?
That waver looks broken.
If you're the ones who broke it,
that'd be a 10th degree crime,
the destruction of sky island
property by Blue Sea people.
No, no! I'm sorry.
They had this one from the beginning.
He's right! This is mine!
From the beginning?
That's suspicious.
Wavers shouldn't exist in the Blue Sea.
If this was something stolen on the sky island,
the degree of your crime will further increase.
Shut up! I'll beat you up!
Hm?
Beat me up?
H-He didn't say anything!
Come with us, Luffy!
They're only Blue Sea people,
and yet they insult even the White Berets...
How foolish they are!
This is nice!
This puffy chair sure feels good.
What a strong pull!
Don't let it get away, Usopp!
Ahhhhh! It's trying to pull my rod away!
Luffy! Hurry!
Hm? Oh! Leave it to me!
We got it!
It's a big one!
Yahoo!
Ow, ow, ow... What the heck is this?
What a weird fish!
It tried to eat Conis!
Is this another one of the skyfish?
Uhm... I'm sorry.
Hm?
Thank you very much for saving Conis-san.
Father, look...
Hmm...
We're in trouble.
Well, well, well...
This skyfish is so rare that
it's forbidden to capture it.
Your action was a violation of the protection law,
and it's a 9th degree crime.
Why is it a crime?!
Zoro saved Conis!
Zoro, did you kill it?
I just smacked it.
I see. Then if we release it,
there shouldn't be any problem, right?
All right! It's very much alive!
Oh! It looks yummy!
Hey, wait Luffy! Don't eat it!
Ahh! Spin, spin, spin...!
If you eat it, you can't even give an excuse.
That's theft, an 8th degree crime.
This is hard. It's too hard to eat!
Ahhh! Never mind that and come over here, Luffy!
Hey, skyfish! Go back to the sea now!
Don't get caught again!
I kept quiet and listened to all your
nonsense about crimes and such, but...
...if you don't cut it out, I'll...
Wait! Wait, Zoro! Don't be hasty!
This is now far beyond arguing.
His speech and behavior just
now are unmistakably extortion.
So, that's a 7th degree crime!
Zoro wasn't extorting! He was about to say,
"if you don't cut it out, I'll laugh!" That's all!
That's his signature gag! A gag, you know!
That's not right!
Isn't he twisting what we do
into crimes on purpose?!
Chopper!
Don't you go making things worse, too!
But we can't do anything like this!
Can't do anything? Oh, yeah!
All we have to do is do nothing.
Let's take a nap.
Now, take a nap! Take a nap now!
They're producing tremendous
noises at divine Angel Beach.
You all... if your action falls under
destruction of the environment,
a 6th degree crime will be added as well.
Hey, we can't even snore?
Ahhh! How annoying!
I'm gonna beat up this beret-wearing old guy!
Shall we do it?
W-Wait! Hey, stop it!
Oh, no... There's already someone there!
I wonder if they're with those guys from earlier.
Please don't do anything stupid, everyone!
Don't be so hasty, Luffy, Zoro!
Listen. You know snails, right? They're...
Hold on a second!
Ah! Nami-san, you're all right!!
Luffy! Don't give them any trouble!
But they...
Nami!
Go ahead and pay them the 7 million-Berry fee
for our illegal entry using your secret stash!
Good! We can still get by with a fine, then?!
7 million Berries, he said...?
What?!
That's too expensive!!
Oh, shoot!
Because they demanded such an
unreasonably high fee, I unintentionally...
Hey...
C-Captain!!
Hey, mister, thanks for letting
me use your waver. It was fun.
No, no. I'm sorry.
More importantly, you all are in big trouble!
Captain! Please hang in there!
Everyone, let's get out of here!
Your wound isn't deep!
Why? I thought you started a fight.
How did this happen?! Captain!!
It's dangerous to have anything to
do with this God thing. Seriously!
By the way, what crime would that be?
I think it's probably a 5th degree
crime for obstructing official duties.
Good! That's still only a 5th degree crime!
That's not good!
When it's determined to be a 5th degree crime,
in the name of God Eneru,
you'll be banished to the clouds.
Banished to the clouds?
What's that?
Being banished to the clouds sounds kinda nice.
No, it doesn't! It's the death penalty!
D-Death penalty?!
He's completely out of it.
But the death penalty in God's Land?
That's harsh.
But it's the truth. It really exists!
It's a punishment where you,
together with your ship,
are put on a cloud that you can't escape from,
and you keep wandering until you become bones.
It's the death penalty!
I see.
That's why that ship fell from the sky.
What?! What're you talking about, Robin?
Remember that galleon that fell from the sky?
The St. Briss, was it?
They might have received that
punishment 200 years ago.
Hey, you!!
Do you realize what you've done to the Captain?!
What did you say?
Ahh! Sanji-kun, hold on!
Why, sure, Nami-san!
Don't be upset like that. That was by chance.
By chance?!
W-Well, how should I put it, I unintentionally...
Unintentionally?!
Uhm, you know... it was like an accident.
An accident?! An accident, you say?!
That's right! It was an accident!
An accident!
'Cause it's hard to control
and ride a waver, right?!
On top of that, I rode it today for the first time,
so I made a little mistake
while turning the handles.
I'm clumsy, aren't I?
I guess beginners shouldn't push
too hard, after all, should they?
She wasn't having troubles riding it,
she looked like she was having lots of fun!
Hey, Luffy!
Oh, no, Luffy!
Nami's trying to fool them into
thinking that it was an accident.
That's impossible!
Don't say anything unnecessary.
Oh, really?
Uhm, I'm sorry,
but I thought it'd be better
to treat Captain McKinley first.
I'm sorry.
Th-That's right!!
Captain McKinley!!
Then, let's carry him over to my house.
We appreciate your assistance!
Heso!
All seven of you, don't go anywhere!
Understood?!
Captain!
They're crawling again?
Why can't they just carry him normally?
I know you're not bad people.
So, please use this chance
to get away from here!
H-Hey!
Let's do as she said.
I saw it with my own eyes.
An island with these scary guys on it!
So you did go to the place they
call forbidden sacred ground.
"The place you're never to step foot in."
"Scary guys"...
Ah! Don't listen! Don't look! Don't talk!
God... guerrilla...
That place is no good for sure!
In any case, we're leaving! We're leaving!
Ahh...
It's heartbreaking to be apart from Conis-chan,
but if that's what Nami-san says...
If we stick around, those two
may also get in trouble.
That's right!
Those guys will just make them
out to be our accomplices!
So, if we make it so that
we run away on our own,
it shouldn't cause any trouble for them.
Right?! Okay, that settles it! Let's go!
What're you doing, Luffy?!
Why are we running away?
Because we'll be in big trouble!
We're always in big trouble.
Like I said, it's not just us,
but those two may get arrested, too, you know!
Those two have done nothing wrong.
The one who arrests them is wrong.
I know that's true, but...
Please... hurry up...
There's no place for them to escape to.
How long will you two be arguing?
Come up already!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
If we stay here, we'll be in big trouble,
and so will those two!
Either way, we're in big trouble.
Please run!
Hurry!
Oh, darn!
You shouldn't, Miss.
If you say something that defends criminals,
you two are also going to pay.
As you know, those people are felons
who should be sentenced to be
banished to the clouds as punishment
for their 5th degree crime, caused by
all their abusive language towards us
along with their obstruction of our official duties.
Like I said, it was an accident!
C'mon, already!
Arrest them!
Please get out of here!
They're beyond your power!
Fire! Milky arrows!
Arrows?!
You go ahead, Nami!
Okay!
What're these?!
Clouds?!
Go, White Berets!
What?! What's going on?!
Let's go!
It's so fluffy that it's hard to run!
Watch out!
How foolish... to think you
could get away from us!
I see... Those're the skating type.
That's neat!
You guys have fun stuff!
What?!
What is he?!
What?! His arm... His arm stretched!
Oh, my...
Gum-Gum...
Can't be...! Devil Fruit?!
...Fireworks!!
By the way, Nami!
What's our financial situation?
We have 50,000 Berries left.
50,000? We're that poor?
Normally, that'll last a day or two at most.
Why are we so poor?
As your captain, I gotta say this.
You should think more about
how you use money and...
It's because you eat so much!!
Alright!
In any case, the "Formation B"
that I instructed them to use
during the fight was successful!
Really?!
They defeated...
...the White Berets!
Normally, up here, the athletic abilities
of Blue Sea people decrease.
You fools!
You can't go back now!
Hm?
You should've just behaved
and done what I told you to...
We, the White Berets, are the gentlest
upholders of the law in God's Land.
However, they are not as nice as we are!
You are now 2nd degree criminals!
No matter if you cry or scream...
...you'll be judged...
...by the priests of Upper Yard!!
Heso!!
Aa hateshinaku tsuzuiteru sora no mukou ni
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
Itsuka mita asu o ima egakihajimete iru
The future that I once saw is now starting to take shape
Jibun ni makesou ni naru hi mo aru
There are days where I almost lose to myself
Sonna toki wa
When that happened,
atataka na basho ga atta
there was someplace warm I could go
Hokoreru mono itsumo kitto
The friends I took pride in always, without fail,
Boku no senaka oshite kureta yo ne?
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Aa hoshi-tachi ga furisosogu kono sora no shita
Ah, the stars are pouring down underneath the sky
Nido to nai ima o hora
This unique moment...
We were tricked!
What's the fuss? We're used to being pursued.
Alright, then! Get ready for an adventure!
He's definitely planning to go there!
Hey, something's wrong with the ship!
It seems there's nothing we can do.
It's already started.
Heaven's Judgment, huh?
Next time, on One Piece:
Is Escape Possible?!
God's Challenge is Set in Motion!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Is Escape Possible?!
God's Challenge
is Set in Motion!