A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
West Block
East Block
North Block
South Block
The feelings of those who are in anguish
are crushed by a dry cloud of sand.
There are those who seek hope,
and those who cling to hope.
Their feelings cross each other,
uncertain what to do,
marking an era of history ending in sadness.
West Block
South Block
East Block
North Block
Vivi and her friends continue to fight in
order to save Alabasta from its crisis...
In addition to Usopp and Chopper's victory...
...Sanji crushed Mr. 2 Bon Clay.
Meanwhile, Nami was engaged in
mortal combat with Miss Doublefinger,
who has Spike-Spike Fruit powers.
Take this!
Tornado Tempo!
– What?
– The doves tangled up on me...!
As a result, Usopp's invention,
the Clima Takt, led Nami to win the battle.
The only battle left was the one
between Mr. 1 and Zoro.
So basically, your body is hard as steel.
Unless I'm capable of cutting even steel,
I can't cut you down, huh?
That would be correct.
Smashing and cutting attacks don't work on me.
I see. This bites.
Since I'm not yet capable of cutting steel,
I can't defeat you now.
Humph... Then what're you going to do?
Well, I'll sympathize with you.
What?
I've been waiting for a difficult situation like this.
I've been thinking that it's about
time for me to go to the next level.
When I defeat you,
I'll be a man who can even cut steel.
Secret of Powerful Swordplay!
Ability to Cut Steel and
the Rhythm Things Have
Humph... When you defeat me... huh?
This might throw cold water
on that enthusiasm of yours,
but ever since I gained Dice Dice powers,
I've never been given even a scratch by
those who call themselves swordsmen.
No swordsman can defeat me.
Ahh... I get the picture...
...but you can store all those
old tales away in an album.
I don't know how many swordsmen
you've fought in the past,
but we've never met before, so...
It seems that at least your tongue is sharp.
Thanks, baldy.
We'll see how long you'll last.
No, how long you'll last.
Demon...
...Slash!
Tiger... Trap!
I told you, didn't I...?
It's a little shocking that you
didn't even get a single bruise...
This is also the first time
my opponent is still standing
when I thought my attacks were solid.
Of course...
...since we've never met before...
That's right!
This guy's entire body is a blade.
So his blades don't have a front or back!
Sparkling Daisy!
Th-This is...
I'll blow you away.
When it comes to training,
I've done it more than anyone else.
I've also been in many difficult
situations that had me on the brink.
When I defeat you, I'll be a
man who can even cut steel.
I've never been given even a scratch by anyone.
What is it that I lack...?!
Teacher...! Teacher!
Hm?
Is it true that there're men in this world
who can cut anything, even steel?
Yes, it's true.
Now, watch this paper carefully, Zoro.
Teacher, you didn't cut it.
Listen, Zoro.
There're swordsmen out there
who are capable of cutting nothing.
But they can also cut anything,
even steel... using the same sword...
The strongest swordsmen are able to
protect that which they want to protect
and cut that which they want to cut.
Swordplay that harms whatever it touches...
I don't consider it real swordsmanship.
Do you understand?
Teacher, I'll be a swordsman who can cut anything!
Zoro, were you listening to what I was saying?
Humph... Hurry up and try cutting me.
You can't cut my body down if you just defend.
Unfortunately, I don't think I can show
you my valiant figure cutting steel...
...because when I cut steel, that's when you die.
Makes sense...
I'll cut... everything up into pieces!
"Swordplay that cuts nothing"... huh?
How pointless...
I'll cut everything up into pieces!
Swordplay that cuts nothing...
Cut nothing... but cut steel...
I don't understand what it means at all!
Thrust and Thrust...
This is the secret of powerful swordplay!
Atomic Spar!
I'll just cut you up!
Crab... Grab!
What an odious bastard...
The feeling is mutual.
Let me tell you one thing.
Don't consider me a swordsman.
I have many weapons that can tear your body up.
Spiral Hollow!
If you're not a swordsman... then an excavator?!
I'm an assassin!
Sparks?! Just how fast is it spinning?!
They'll be repelled!
I can't do excavation...
because I'll drill and cut everything up.
Crap!
What a momentary misjudgment invites is...
...death!
You're still breathing...
I won't show my back to him...
How're you gonna struggle
with your bare hands?
You're not even a swordsman.
You won't understand even if I explain.
Humph... I'm not even interested.
Spar... Break!
Die in peace...
I have... bad luck with stones today...
You guys!
Make sure you deliver Vivi back to her home!
See you at the Alubarna Palace!
Are they... all okay...?
Why is he standing...?
After being cut so many times...
Did he dodge all those falling stones?
I dodged... these stones?
No...
I could tell... the place where no stones would be falling...
Swords...
There's one underneath that stone... I can tell...
What's he doing...?
I've experienced this feeling before...
It's awfully quiet around me...
I can hear my heartbeat very clearly...
Is this... precisely what it feels
like when close to death...?
I sensed a hint from the falling
stones as if they're living things...
No, it wasn't a hint...
It was clearer than that...
Rhythm...
Stones'... rhythm...
Trees have their own rhythm...
Soil has its own... Is that what it is...?
Listen. There're swordsmen out there
who are capable of cutting nothing.
Does "cutting nothing" mean...
know the rhythm...?
That's... the ability to cut even steel...
You... what the hell did you do?
After receiving such an enormous attack...
When you're bleeding that much...
There's no way you can be still alive...!
I can hear... the rhythm of his steel...
My will is flowing into the sword...
Fine... I'll completely finish
him off with the next attack.
The only question left is...
...whether or not I really have the ability to cut steel...
It's hard to think that you can defend
my attack using only one sword...
That's all right. I won't defend any more.
So you're now prepared. Fine by me!
One-Sword Style... Lion Song!
Atomic Spurt!
I give you my thanks...
I can become stronger still!
He's indeed... become stronger...
during this fight...
Are you... going to cut diamond or something next...?
That would be a waste...
You win...
Alubarna - North Block
Battle in front of the Mehdi Assembly Hall
Winner:          Zoro
Doko ni mukatte hashireba
Which direction should I run towards
Motto suteki na ashita ni aeru?
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
Kaji o totte mune ni shimatta
I took the helm and opened the
Kiseki no chizu o hirogeta
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
Sora o mezashite yume o sagashite
I aimed for the sky and sought out my dreams,
Michi ni mayotta toki mo aru
though at times I got lost
Yume ja nakute kimi to deatte
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
Suteki na jibun o mitsuketa
I discovered the wonderful person in me
Chiisana yuuki kara
With just a bit of courage,
ookina mono te ni shita
I gained something grand
"Negai" o ima koso "chikai" ni kaete
Now's the time for my "wish" to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Mirai no monogatari o egakou
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
Atarashii kaze ni subete no omoi nosete ima...
I'll put all my feelings in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
Doko made mo oikakete Shining ray
I'll chase after you wherever you go, Shining ray
Why're you crying?
Because that mole hag said that Luffy's dead...
Is that true?!
You guys believe that?
Of course not!
Then stow your snot away.
There's no reason for you to fight any longer!
Surrender right now...! Royal Army!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Battle is Over!
Koza Raises the White Flag
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Battle is Over!
Koza Raises the White Flag