Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece...
head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and on their way
to the next stage—the New World—
they reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
But they have yet to gather
and are stirring things up as a fragmented crew!
Luffy set out from Ryugu Palace with Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
Robin got information about a Poneglyph that's hidden somewhere on Fishman Island.
I think this kingdom holds
an important key to the Void Century!
Franky found the Sunny at the Sea Forest—
a resting place for sunken ships.
I'll do the coating.
Count on me-don!
Oh, thank you...
Um... Can I ask your name?
I'm Den.
Oh, by the way,
somebody's been sitting there for quite a while.
Oh, that's Boss Jinbe!
He said he's expecting somebody.
Zoro, Usopp, Nami, and Brook having unintentionally taken over Ryugu Palace...
come face to face with a rebel force led by Hody
and Vander Decken,
who are plotting to destroy the kingdom!
My Shirahoshi disappeared?!
She's my... My daughter-jamon!
We've been in love for a decade! Nothing will tear us apart...
except for death!
Before you become somebody else's,
I'd rather see you dead
with your blood splattered all over! Shirahoshi!
The Battle in Ryugu Palace!
Zoro vs. Hody
That's an octopus-san!
That's a blowfish-san!
Oh, there is a killifish-chan as well!
Wimpy, you only see fish!
Look, a rice ball and a donut!
Meat!
Luffy-sama, you're only seeing food!
Am I?
Jamon! Jamon!
Jamon!
What is it all of the sudden?
F-Father-sama!
He must be worrying about me at the palace now...
Boy, you're such a pain.
Here, Wimpy!
Luffy-sama!
Why are you laughing?!
Swallow her now!
Vander Decken is going after Shirahoshi!
Neptune-sama!
I beg you-jamon, you people!
I'll give you anything you want!
Let me go after Decken!
You can take silver, gold and jewels...
or my soldiers' lives or anything!
Huh?
No no, King!
He's gonna catch Shirahoshi! My treasure—Shirahoshi!
How pathetic, Neptune.
I never thought my fated enemies, the Straw Hats,
would help us conquer Ryugu Palace!
"Fated enemies"?
He's got Arlong's mark, too!
Jinbe told me there was something going on
in the Fishman District!
I can't believe you, a former proud soldier of Neptune's army, are the ringleader!
Shame on you, Hody!
Shame?
I'd feel shame if I had felt any real pride
to be in Neptune's army.
The only reason I joined the army
was to learn fighting skills in actual combat.
And that's all.
You bastard!
I became stronger thanks to you.
What do you mean?
You all have failed to notice
what's been going on on the island.
Since I was a child, I've seen Fishmen oppressed
at the hands of irrational humans.
Help me-dosun!
We've gone through all the trouble
to get to Fishman Island,
why don't we take a Fishman back with us?
L-Let me go-dosun!
Give us back our friend!
You kidnappers!
Do you Fishman brats wanna mess with us humans?
They're worth far less than Merfolk
but we can make some extra money
by selling them as a set.
I can't take it anymore!
They can't even breathe in the water...
but no matter how much we kill them, these damn humans never go away!
I admired Arlong's ambition
to knock those humans down a peg!
We're gonna restore his dream!
We're the New Fishman Pirates!
I was training myself to become Arlong's right-hand man one day...
when he set out to conquer the world from the East Blue as he planned.
But...
unfortunately he was stopped by some humans.
So these Fishmen are followers of Arlong?!
What?! Arlong?!
Just kidding! I've never had Arlong before...
Ouch! Hey, Usopp-san, why did you kick me?!
Just shut up for now!
Enough with the chit-chatting. Let's get down to business.
Stay away!
Wh-What the...
Shark Grip!
What a strong grip!
What the hell is he doing?!
No! I tell you this is no good!
What should we do?!
Nami-chin?
Camie, do me a favor!
What?
Is that his own strength?
Yeah, he hasn't taken an Energy Steroid yet.
The walls are broken!
Dammit!
He's flooding the place!
Oh this is no good! Especially for me!
We're gonna drown!
Oh no, water drops!
Get down!
He's gonna do it!
Shark Arrows!
Those water drops are like arrows!
You bastard!
Attacking my soldiers at random!
Stop it!
You fool!
King-sama!
Don't do that!
No-jamon! You guys are my subjects-jamon!
Neptune-sama!
What an idiot! What kind of king becomes a shield for his men?!
You don't have what it takes to be king!
King-sama!
Damn Hody!
How awful!
He's shooting at the unarmed!
And he's way stronger than Arlong!
One-Sword Style:
Bird Dance!
Hey wait, Boss Hody! It's...
That bastard!
He used one of his own men as a shield!
Hey guys, untie the soldiers!
What?
The negotiation with the kingdom
has broken down.
We couldn't keep our word
to give them all the hostages back unharmed.
He's so trustworthy.
Alright, I got it!
Oh, my foot is in the water!
I'm losing my strength!
Help me, Nami-san!
Oh? Where is Nami-san?
Huh? Nami is gone?
Where did she go?
Camie is missing too!
Boy! First Luffy and now Nami? But we have to untie them first!
Hang on for a minute, Brook!
He's driving my bones too hard...
Why don't you run now?
Please untie the others.
I have no energy left...
Untie the others and take up your arms!
Don't let them do a damn thing!
Destroy all of Neptune's army and the Straw Hats!
Sure-Kill Green Star: Rafflesia!
Whoa! A flower from the surface blossomed!
I've never seen such a flower before!
Take that!
Oh, it stinks!
Damn! How stupid!
How's that?!
I can't take it anymore...
Zoro! The water is rising!
I have a favor to ask!
Let those two get out of here!
What about you?
No one can get away
with that guy chasing after them!
Don't stand in my way of conquering this country!
Okay! Nothing's been broken.
Sorry that I pushed you so hard all of the sudden.
You can rest here for a while.
Do you want me to help you with the coating?
No, every man knows his own trade best.
Okay, thank you!
Oh, there you are, Sunny!
Robin!
Oh, she your friend?
Yeah. Did you finish your business?
Not yet.
I still need to confirm something...
Over there.
Hey hey, outsiders should stay out of there!
Thank you for your suggestion.
She's odd, isn't she?
Look who's talking.
You were the only one
who could see my arrows earlier.
Is it because you've seen Arlong's?
Avoiding that attack the second time you've encountered it, that's impressive.
But no matter how skillful you are, no one can beat a Fishman in the sea!
You can't deflect them in the water!
Three-Sword Style: Dragon Twister!
Oh, seems like I can have some fun.
I don't have much time!
Shoreline of Coral Hill
Stay with me!
It's gonna be okay!
Hurry up and get out of here!
Don't worry about us now! Just think about yourself...
What do you guys want?
We want the Mermaids back!
You humans only see us as novelties!
Huh? What are you talking about?!
Don't play dumb, you pirates!
We heard that three more young Mermaids disappeared at a beach in the south.
Where are those girls?
I don't know what you're talking about!
Why do you think that we did it?
It might be true that...
I love Mermaid-chans so much that I wanna take them away!
But we didn't kidnap them.
See? You just said that you wanna take them away!
Why are you guys arguing? Be quiet!
I knew humans did it!
Get out!
Ouch!
There's some left in it!
Don't waste it!
Shut up, human!
Oh? Sanji! Chopper!
Hey, Sanji!
Has your nosebleed stopped now?
Is that Luffy?!
What's that blowfish?
A human gentleman and...
a raccoon dog!
It looks exactly the same as in the book!
A-Are they your friends, Luffy-sama?
They are my crewmates!
They are?
Look! That's their captain!
That straw hat...
He's the boss of the Mermaid kidnappers!
I don't want them to see me!
Megalo, close your mouth a little more!
I'm gonna go down there for a bit!
What?
He came down!
Hachi! I knew it was you!
Straw Hat...
What happened to you?!
Who did this?!
He's not telling us!
Get off of this island!
That's all he's been saying!
But if I'm correct, the pirate—Straw Hat—
is occupying Ryugu Palace now!
They're Mermaid kidnappers!
He left his men at the palace to kidnap more!
Maybe he's even gonna kidnap Princess Shirahoshi!
Don't be ridiculous!
That's impossible!
The Princess is a giant smelt-whiting Mermaid
and the God of the Sea, Neptune's, beloved daughter!
Some people might dream about kidnapping her,
but no one could pull it off.
What is that blowfish?
No!
What?!
Oh!
Huh?!
Princess Shirahoshi-sama?!
Um... Well, uh...
You found me!
She's big!
Don't tell me that that's...
the Mermaid Princess?
What? Is there anybody behind me?
No, Sanji!
Don't turn around at any cost!
Huh? What's going on?
If you do, you're gonna die, Sanji!
Oh, no.
They kidnapped the Mermaid Princess!
The crowd at the shore is enraged by Princess Shirahoshi's kidnapping,
and Luffy is captured.
And then, Vander Decken finally reveals himself!
Can Luffy escape his bonds
and safely take Shirahoshi to the Sea Forest?
And, upon seeing an attractive Mermaid,
Sanji is once again in danger!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Keep Shirahoshi Safe
Decken Close Behind"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Keep Shirahoshi Safe
Decken Close Behind