Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
I will definitely get you there.
Don't die... Nami... Sanji...!
The Island Where Snow Lives!
Climb The Drum Rockies!
Ahhh! Please look at that!
We found them, Wapol-sama!
Hold it, brat!
Huh? You guys're...
How dare you do many rude things to me!
I'll chew you guys up!
Get out of my way.
Humph! You're stupid, aren't you?
Why would I get out of your way?!
Looks like what you have on your
back and in your arm are half-dead.
Hold it!
Oh, I know!
Chess! I thought up a new law.
Write this down.
Yes sir!
Those who ignore the king are to be executed!
Ignoring me already?!
Guys! First, get the sick and injured ones,
who are ignoring me the most!
– Yes sir!
What'd you say?!
I'll take the woman on his back!
I'll take the man.
Take this! Marimo's Surprise!
Listen Luffy!
Don't you dare fight.
Whether you attack or get struck,
Nami-san will feel the whole impact too!
Damn you! You'll regret this!
Don't follow me!
Humph. What a coward...
It's no use.
I'll show him...
what a battle in a snowy area is like...
Huh...?
There's no one...
What's going on?
I wonder if they've already given up...
Now this is a true battle in a snowy area!
The white disguise!
Snow Powder Makeup!
Since they're so weak,
they'll be dead with just one shot.
Check Mate!
Stop it!
White bears...
Lapins?!
Did they protect him?
It's a coincidence.
Lapins never become attached to humans.
You are...
Thanks! You saved me!
Don't let him get away!
Yes sir!
What the hell do they think they're doing?!
Doctor...
So this is it...
I can't see the top.
I can find the doctor... up there...
Hang in there a little longer...
Nami! Sanji!
Avalanche...
We were swallowed by the avalanche...
Ah! U... Usopp-san?!
Usopp-san!
Usopp-san! Come on!
Wake up!
He's still alive!
Usopp-san! Hang on!
Come on! Usopp-san!
Usopp-san!
Oh Vivi... Don't wake me up.
I was just having a beautiful dream.
A field of beautiful flowers out of
this world and a beautiful river... Oh?
– You're almost in the netherworld!
– Isn't that Zoro swimming in the river...?
– Wake up! Don't sleep! Wake up!
All 74,000 Usopp Pirates, close in!
No! Wake up! Usopp-san, don't die!
Usopp-san!
Usopp-san! Usopp-san! Usopp-san!
Phew, you saved me, Vivi.
Talk about having a narrow escape from death.
I'm glad I'm alive. But...
– don't you think my face is kinda swollen?
– I-It's chilblains! Chilblains!
– My head feels kinda heavy...
– This is why it's not easy to be in a snowy area.
– Or should I say my view is kinda narrow...
– More importantly,
– we have to figure out our location and the situation we're in quickly!
– My lips are kinda big... Kinda...
– Yeah, I agree...
Ahhh! What's that?!
Ahhh... That was close...
I saw a field of flowers...
Suddenly hitting an avalanche in this cold...
I must've run out of luck.
But this is a sort of winter swimming, I guess.
Zoro.
Hm? Oh, Vivi.
Huh?
Hm?
Oh, it's you, Usopp!
What're you guys doing here?
That's my question!
What idiots!
That's what you lowly bunnies
get for going against the king!
Humph! I didn't think I'd use my
real power on mere bunnies, though.
It couldn't be helped...
since they're the most violent animal in Drum.
Just wait...
Straw Hat!
Doctor...!
Ah! Ow!
Sanji!
Th-That... that was close...
Winter swimming?!
Yeah.
After swimming in the river for a while,
I had no idea where I was any more.
So I was walking while doing muscle training,
and then I ended up in a forest.
Dressed like that?
You're stupid, aren't you?
Anyway, give me your coat, Usopp.
No way.
Nami-san might've gotten sick
due to mental exhaustion...
– Then your shoes!
– No!
– One of them!
It's your own fault, isn't it?!
Look over there! There're people.
Hm?
Hey... I remember those buildings...
What?
You're right! This is Big Horn!
We ended up... coming back!
Step back! Step back!
Dalton is already dead!
There's no way Dalton-san
would die from an attack like that!
You guys're Dalton-san's
ex-subordinates, aren't you?!
Don't you care?!
We're retainers of King Wapol!
If you become Wapol-sama's enemy,
you're dead meat!
Hey, what's the matter?
Wh-What's the matter?
What's the matter with you, dressing like that?!
Dalton-san's buried under
the snow of the avalanche!
What?!
Dalton-san is?!
Yeah. We can't dig him out
because those guys get in our way.
Step back! Step back!
If you have any objection,
go right ahead and bring it on!
Usopp, I remember their clothes.
They're the ones who attacked
us on the sea, right? Right?!
Yeah, that's right.
Then they're our enemy, aren't they?
They're our enemy, right? What's the word?
Are they on our side?!
Well, they're our enemy...
but why are you so...
You aren't so courageous
without Dalton, are you?
What?! Mr. Bushido!
Who's that?!
Hey you! Stop it!
If you attack them, you'll...
This is warm! I'm borrowing it!
You... asked me because of that...?!
– Look! They're angry!
– You!
You were on the ship with that
guy who blew Wapol-sama away!
Oh? You guys never learn, do you?
Are you guys looking for...
these?
Bring him down!
Hawk Wave!
Oh, it's already over?
What a disappointing bunch...
Amazing...
All right! Good job, Zoro!
Just as I instructed!
Let's find Dalton-san!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Hurry up! Dig everywhere!
So, what's all this fuss?
I'll explain it later! Let's help them!
Dalton-san! Please be alive!
Doctor...
Hang in there. We're almost there.
Don't you die on me!
We made it...
Doctor...
Doktorin...
The antibodies are responding.
Yeah, I figured that much.
Then, what's the cause? Explain.
Kestia...
That's right. Kestia.
You attend the girl.
Okay.
Who are you?
Nemuranai kono machi mo Ima dake wa madoromu
Even this sleepless town has dozed off for now
Kyou kara to kinou made
From today forth,
nani ka ga kawatte yuku
something's going to change
Kitto yarinaoseru hazu
I'm sure I can start fresh,
Datte hitori janai kara
since I'm not alone
Soba ni ite kureru dake de
Just by having you by my side,
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru
I feel I can become strong
Doko made ikeru kana
I wonder how far I can go,
mirai e tsuzuku basho
towards the place that leads to the future
Tooku de kagayaite sekai o tsutsumikomu
Off in the distance it shines, encompassing the world
Yoake mae
Before dawn
Hey wait, reindeer!
Don't run away, meat!
Hold on, Nami-san!
I'll cook a nutritious reindeer dish right away!
I don't care about the food.
I just want some peace and quiet.
Huh? Wasn't that reindeer speaking?
Come to think of it, I sort of
remember him standing on two legs.
He's a monster!
Next time, on One Piece:
Blue-nosed Reindeer!
Chopper's Secret
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Blue-nosed Reindeer!
Chopper's Secret