Wealth, fame, power.
A man who acquired everything in this world, the Pirate King, Gold Roger...
His final words at his execution, sent people to the seas.
"My wealth and treasures?"
"If you want it, you can have it! Search for it!"
I left it all at that place!
In search of the great treasure left behind by Gold Roger, One Piece,
many pirates went to battle under their flags.
During this time, there was one young man who also sets out in search of One Piece.
During his search for crew members,
he had many great adventures and became stronger.
His pirate crew, recognized as the face of a new era,
is the Straw Hat Crew!
Guys, are you ready?!
Yea!
So let's get started
Presenting the Straw Hat Crew... fashion show!
Obviously, being your presenter... anything looks good on me!
After all, I'm so cool and manly.
The Sniper King of the New World, Ussop!
And here performing with his afro,
is the user of the Yomi Yomi no Mi, the flamboyant musician...
Brook!
Hello...
And now, introducing our special model!
A sexy girl that steals the hearts of all men!
Our brainy curvaceous navigator... Nami!
Nami-swan~!
Makes sense, seeing as I'm so refined!
May I see your panties?!
Never!
Next, a mysterious and cool beauty!
An archaeologist who seeks the mysteries of history...
and the user of the Hana Hana no Mi!
Nico Robin!
I'll show you history with these hands.
Robin-chwan, you're so cool~!
What are they up to?
Now it's his turn!
The man who loves all women...
The warrior chef, Sanji!
Your meal, mademoiselle.
Let's continue!
The kind-hearted cyborg!
The shipwright of steel, Franky!
Super~!
Next up is a person...
Well, he's not really a person.
The reindeer that ate the Hito Hito no Mi!
He has a warm and tender heart. The Super Doctor...
Tony Tony Chopper!
Praising my skills... doesn't make me happy, you idiot!
This great swordsman... unforgiving and uncompromising...
What now?!
Zoro!
Change your outfit, Zoro!
I want to see his new outfit!
Go for it!
Now you should man up.
Or don't use anything.
He who aspires to become the strongest swordsman in the world!
Hey! What are you doing?! Stop it!
But his only flaw is his sense of direction...
Roronoa Zoro!
I'll slice you up!
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
And naturally, he'll be the one to close the show!
The user of the Gomu Gomu no Mi! The leader of the Straw Hat Crew!
He wants to find the great treasure One Piece and become the Pirate King!
Monkey D. Luffy!
I will be the Pirate King!
Even though fashion changes,
that Luffy always...
...wears his hat.
It's the Marines! They're heading this way!
Here comes trouble.
You just go on playing around...
I'll handle them myself.
What are you getting so excited for?!
Target located!
It has a pirate flag, fire!
Damn you!
It stinks!
Why are you falling asleep too?!
What's that?
It's huge!
Everyone, brace yourselves!
So, what do you think of Josephine's powers?
I don't know where these pirate ships come from, but they show up a bit too often.
No pirate can escape when in range of the giant cannon, Josephine.
Eliminate all pirates!
Of course, obviously.
In the land that I protect,
I will not allow pirates to commit crimes.
You're the best, Bilic-sama
I knew it, once we used the
Coup de Burst, no one could keep up with us.
We've totally ditched them.
Land ahoy!
What?! If we fall on the ground, we're screwed!
Hang on tight, everyone!
We have successfully landed.
YOU CALL THIS A SUCCESS?!
We're upside down....
We ended up in an awkward position.
That sent chills throughout my bones.
This place looks so green and peaceful.
Where are we anyway?
Hey, you two? What island is this?
Hand Island.
Hand... Island?
Pirates have fallen from the sky!
Hand Island...
I need to figure out how to move the ship.
I'll finish the maintenance tonight and then figure out how we can set sail.
So, we'll only need to stay here for one night?
I had just finished placing my special dishes too.
No damage over here!
But my medicine is all over the place.
We need to replenish our supplies.
Let's find the shops!
Alright then! Let's go!
Just ignore the apes.
They seem concerned.
Well, of course.
But, I sense some kind of hostility.
It's a commercial center!
I can do some shopping!
Does it have any good food?
Hey you.
Are you the pirates who just arrived?
Yea, that's right.
I thought I heard another cannon shot!
Cannon?
Well, take a look around.
There are a lot of nice things on this island.
Let's not exaggerate.
They can find what they need.
Um... that was quite a strange welcome, don't you think?
There are so many funny signs!
It's so you can tell what kind of store it is.
This earring is so gorgeous!
This necklace is wonderful too.
It looks handmade.
What remarkable workmanship.
Is this the first time you've visited the island?
Yes!
This is where the most skilled artisans in the New World gather.
An island of artisans?
So the best artisans can be found here on Hand Island?
This is a beautiful plate.
It'll be perfect for my special curry.
Thank you!
So, would you like that dish sir?
But of course~! I'm Sanji the cook!
Give me 100 of these dishes!
I'm sorry, we don't have a hundred of them.
Oh, I see, I'm sorry.
So give me 10, please.
Those two on the shelf are all we have.
Really?
They're all good tools,
but why are there so few of them?
Sorry. I wish I had more, but...
Did something happen?
Even if I wanted more,
the artisans are not on the island now.
Why not?
Isn't this the island of artisans?
Everyone works for the Marines now.
Even my husband.
I see. So you're taking care of the store now.
But tell me, do you understand medicine?
Not really.
I thought so, and your dad?
When will he be back?
I don't know.
That's why I saw only women, children and old men here...
We don't have the strength to opose them.
Um, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Aren't you afraid of me?
As long as you're a paying customer, it makes no difference if you're a pirate or a skeleton!
You're a great person.
Damn it! Where is the katana shop?
It's much easier to walk here.
There was a bombing in this area.
The old artisan's district is being
used as target practice for their cannons.
Oh, Brook, did something happen?
This is...
Higher, higher!
The base is already 82% complete.
If I push the artisans even further,
we will achieve 100% much quicker.
My beloved Josephine,
you're exactly what I need.
Even without any superhuman abilities,
I can become a Marine Admiral.
Marine Admiral, I love it! Josephine is the best! The best!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot at will! Destroy it all, and more!
If I can kill a target with a high bounty...
Bilic-sama will become an admiral, without a doubt!
Don't overdo it.
Excuse me, Sir! A ship has arrived from headquarters!
An officer has disembarked to meet with you!
Take him to my office.
What a bizarre place.
Be careful what you say, Captain-lieutenant Helmeppo.
I'm sorry, Sir!
There's no need to be so formal.
Let's go, Captain Coby.
I'm Captain Coby, commander of the ship!
I'm the second-in command,
Captain-lieutenant Helmeppo!
Thanks for coming directly from headquarters.
I'm in charge of the tower base, Commodore Bilic.
I would like you to sign this contract.
Is Yellow Monkey... I mean, Admiral Borsalino okay?
I've always respected Admiral Borsalino immensely.
Please give him my compliments.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
I got your signature, but it's in the wrong place.
What?
Sign here please.
But, I just missed the line.
It's not up to me. It's procedure.
Is that better?
Thank you. Good day!
Good day!
What's up with that attitude?!
Just becuase he's a Captain from Marine HQ!
I'm a Commodore!
Who does he think he is?!
The head of this base is Bilic-sama!
Obviously.
That blowhard! Those who oppose Bilic-sama flirt with death!
He must be punished! Let's kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
I guess I have no choice. He is a man of low intelligence.
Low! Low! Low! Really pretty dumb.
That man, I knew he was hiding something.
Eh? You used Observation Haki?
We need to investigate this base.
The real reason we came here...
is because of this letter of inquiry.
Let's get to work.
Yeah...
I'm hungry... what's with this island?
There's nothing to eat.
Ah! Food!
Itadakimasu!
This is horrible!
What's this?
Did you just eat that?
I did!
Say what?!
You really ate that?
I can't believe it!
Hey, old man, this food tastes horrible!
You eat without permission and you still complain?
What a strange guy.
Everything here is made out of wax.
I am the great wax artisan, Diego,
who makes realistic copies of original work.
This is fake?
Hey, old man, do you know a guy named Mr. 3?
Eh? Who's that?
You must have been really
hungry to have eaten that.
Come on in kid, I'll give you some real food.
What the hell?!
This Is terrible!
That cannon finally hit me!
The Sunny!
So we were the ones who destroyed your house?!
What?! That's your ship?!
Damn it all!
I am so sorry.
What's wrong, old man? Are you okay?
Don't worry. My back occasionally acts up.
Your back hurts?
No! A true craftsman is not discouraged
just because his house was destroyed!
I see. It has the same shape as a hand.
Now then...
The Sunny will be fine, won't it?
There's nothing wrong with the ship.
There's a river nearby, so I'm making preparations to go down there.
I see.
Nami-swan~!
I've made dinner with fish from the aquarium~!
Are Zoro and Luffy back yet?
Hey... Luffy is eating something over there!
Looks like he's with someone.
He can't help himself!
This food is delicious, old man!
I can make the real thing too, not just copies.
I knew I had seen your face before...
But I didn't expect you to be Straw Hat Luffy.
You're an interesting fellow.
But that hat, where did you get it?
This?
Shanks gave it to me, a long time ago.
It's my treasure.
I knew it.
Old man, do you know Shanks?
More or less.
In any case, I'd like to show you my greatest treasure.
I have to be very careful when going down the stairs.
Are you okay? Do you want me to help you?
I'm not so old that I need any help!
There's a basement?
Take a look over there.
Rayleigh!
Is that you, Rayleigh?!
It sure has been a while!
What's the matter? It's me!
What are you doing here?
First mate of Gold Roger's crew, Silvers Rayleigh.
But he can't speak.
Eh? Why not?
Because it's a wax statue I made.
Eh?!
This is a copy too?!
I'll show you more.
These are all statues of pirates I've met.
Edward Newgate.
He led the Whitebeard Pirates and dominated the New World.
They all look so real!
It's Ace!
Shanks...
Red-Haired Shanks.
He's a great man.
Hey, Luffy, what are you doing?
I'm not kidding!
I'm serious, just watch me!
Fine, show us!
I wonder what you'll pull off this time.
Knowing Luffy, it'll just be something childish.
Ow!!
You idiot! What are you doing?!
It hurts!
Men! Let's have a toast!
To Luffy's courage and our great voyage!
Cheers!
Sake! There's not enough sake!
Idiot, that's my meat!
Shut up! It's mine!
Ah! It didn't hurt at all!
Liar. Don't do stupid things like that.
I'm not afraid of hurting myself!
Take me to your next trip.
I want to be a pirate too!
Someone like you can't be a pirate!
You can't swim, you'd only be a burden!
So what if I can't swim?!
I'll just make sure I don't fall off the ship!
Also, I'm good at fighting!
My punch is as strong as a pistol!
A pistol? Really now?
What's with the attitude?!
Hey, Luffy!
You seem excited, boy.
Come have some fun with us!
That's right! Being a pirate is fun!
The sea is vast! And every island brings new adventures!
More importantly, the-
Don't encourage him, you guys!
We're just telling it like it is.
Not!
Captain, what could go wrong?
We could take him with us once.
I think so too!
Then one of you forfeit your place on my ship to him.
Oh... Enough talking,
Let's drink.
Weren't you on my side?!
In short, you're just a kid.
Come back in 10 years and I'll think about it.
Shanks, you're an ugly stupid head!
I told you I'm not a kid!
C'mon, don't get upset. Drink your juice.
Thanks!
See! Your just a brat! You're killing me!
How dirty!
This is tiring!
I even cut myself just so I could ask him.
Luffy. Try to understand how the captain feels.
First Mate!
How Shanks feels?
That's right.
He may not look like it, but he's the captain of a pirate crew.
Just as he knows how fun it is to be a pirate,
he also knows best how dangerous and risky it can be.
Do you understand? He knows you're determined to be a pirate. It's not like he wants to discourage you.
Don't be silly! Shanks does nothing but tease and make fun of me!
Hammer!
See!
True, he's having fun.
You're a blast as always, Captain-san.
Yeah! Teasing him is how I have my fun.
Luffy, want something to eat?
Yes! I eat on credit.
And how will you settle your credit?
This seems unfair to me.
You're wrong!
When I become a pirate and find some treasure, I'll come back here and settle my debt.
I'll be waiting.
Shanks!
What?
How much longer will you stay in the village?
Let's see... We've docked here for more than a year.
I think after two or three more trips,
we will leave this village and head north.
Two or three trips, huh?
I'll have learned to swim by then!
That's great, do your best.
Sorry for interrupting.
So these are pirates, huh?
It's the first time I've seen one.
They look like idiots.
We are mountain bandits.
However, we didn't come here to mess up the bar.
We want some sake.
Ten barrels.
Sorry, but we just ran out of sake.
That's strange.
It seems the pirates are drinking something.
Is it water?
All the sake that we have is out there.
That's not good.
It seems we drank all of the sake in the bar.
Sorry.
If you want, you can have this.
It's still unopened.
You bastard! Who the hell do you think I am?
Don't you dare try to make a fool of me.
One bottle of sake won't satisfy my thirst.
What a mess, the floor is all wet.
Have a look.
I have a bounty of 8,000,000 Beli on my head.
I'm quite the big shot.
I've killed 56 people.
Guys like you, you're just trash.
Get the message. You'd better be careful from now on.
Sorry, Makino.
Do you have a mop?
No, just let me clean it up.
Since you like cleaning so much...
You'll enjoy this even more.
See you around, cowards.
Since there's no sake here, we have no reason to stay.
Let's go to the next town.
Captain-san, are you alright?
Are you hurt?
Oh, I'm fine. No problem.
You look ridiculous, Captain!
He sure got you good!
Why are you all laughing?!
That was embarrassing! Why didn't you fight back?!
So what if you were outnumbered?!
You should have fought like real men!
Aren't you guys pirates?!
I understand how you feel, but it's just some spilled sake.
It's nothing to start a fight over.
Oh, yeah?
Go to hell! I'm not a weakling!
Hey, wait a minute, Luffy!
His arm stretched!
What the hell is this?!
Don't tell me you...!
What?!
The Gomu Gomu no Mi we got off the enemy, it's gone!
Luffy, did you eat this fruit?
Yes, as dessert. It tasted horrible.
That was the Gomu Gomu no Mi! One of the treasures of the sea called the Devil Fruit.
If you eat it, your whole body will become rubber, and you will never be able to swim!
Are you kidding me?!
You idiot!
Captain-san has been away for a while now.
Do you miss them, Luffy?
Not one bit!
I haven't forgiven them for the thing with the bandits yet.
I overestimated Shanks and the others.
I thought they were the coolest pirates.
What a disappointment!
Really?
I think being able to laugh even
after what happened is much cooler.
Makino, you just don't get it.
There are times when a man must fight.
Really? I guess I don't understand those things.
Yep, you don't.
Excuse me.
The pirates aren't here today. It sure is quiet.
We were passing through,
so we thought we'd stop by for a drink.
Why are you just standing there?
We're customers!
Give us sake!
Yes! Of course!
We had a great time that day.
Did you see the look on those pirate's faces?
They couldn't do anything, even after you drenched their captain in sake.
What a bunch of cowards.
Those pirates make me sick.
I had an urge to kill them.
Well, they were just pirates, not worth anything.
Stop it!
Don't talk about Shanks and the others like that!
They aren't cowards!
Stop it, Luffy!
Don't talk about Shanks and the others
like they're idiots!
Mayor-san, it's terrible!
What is it, Makino? Why are you in such a hurry?
Luffy was taken by bandits!
This body of yours sure is interesting.
Yeah, looks like punches and kicks have no effect.
Damn! Say you're sorry!
A rubber person, huh? I never
imagined there could be such a strange creature.
Damn jerk!
Shit! I won't ever forgive you!
A different type of human! He might be worth good money if we sell him.
You're really stubborn...
You brat!
All we wanted was a nice drink and to relax a bit.
Did I say something you didn't like?
Yes you did! Apologize! Damnit!
Let the kid go!
Please! We have no intention to fight you,
and we can even pay.
But please spare the kid!
Mayor...
This old man sure knows how the world works.
But it's too late!
I cannot spare him! After all, he made me mad.
I can't allow a kid to insult me in front of everyone.
You started it!
You ugly mountain ape!
Fine, I'm not going to sell you now.
I'll kill you instead. Here and now.
Luffy!
P-Please! Spare him.
There was nobody to welcome us at the port,
so I was wondering if something bad had happened.
Captain!
If it isn't the bandits from the other day.
Luffy! Didn't you say your punch is as strong as a pistol?
Shut up!
Pirate, you're still here?
Are you done cleaning already?
I don't know why you're here, but
I suggest you run away before you get hurt.
If you come any closer, you're a dead man, coward!
Didn't you here what he said?
Don't take another step, or else I'll blow your brains out!
Since you've drawn your pistol,
I assume you're ready to put your life on the line.
Huh? What are you talking about?
I'm saying a pistol isn't used for making threats.
You killed him! You bastards!
How could you do that?! Cowards!
Cowards? Don't be naive...
Do you think you're dealing with saints?
The people in front of you are pirates.
Listen, bandits.
You can throw food and drinks on my head.
I'll just laugh that off.
However!
No matter the reason,
I will not forgive those who hurt my friends.
Shanks...
Will not forgive, you say?
Pirates who float around in the sea
challenging bandits? What a joke!
Kill them all, men!
I'll handle it. I'm more than enough.
Ouch!
Don't flatter yourself, bandit.
If you want to fight us, you should bring a warship with you.
So cool!
Wait... This kid provoked us.
Whatever. Aren't you're a wanted man?
Come here, kid!
Luffy!
Let me go! Let me go!
Damn it! I got careless!
Luffy was... What do we do guys?!
Don't panic, Captain! Let's all split up and find him.
Seriously, this guy...
We got away.
They will never think of looking for a bandit at sea.
I brought you as a hostage,
but it seems I don't need you anymore.
I always kill those who irritate me. You will be the 57th.
Not if you die first!
Goodbye!
Damn! Damn! This jerk, I couldn't even land a punch!
What?!
What is this monster?!
Someone... help me!
Get lost.
Makino told me everything.
Thanks for sticking up for us.
Hey, don't cry. You're a man, aren't you?
But... Shanks...
Your arm!
It's just an arm, it's nothing.
I'm just glad you're okay.
You're really not coming back?
No. We've been here too long already.
Thanks for everything.
Aren't you upset, Luffy?
Yea!
But I won't ask you to take me along anymore.
I will become a pirate with my own strength.
I wouldn't take you even if you begged.
You don't have what it takes to be a pirate.
Yes, I do!
I'll gather my own crew that will beat yours
and find the world's greatest treasure!
No matter what, I will become the Pirate King!
Oh, you're going to be bigger than us, huh?
In that case...
I'll leave my hat with you.
It's very important to me.
When you've become a great pirate, give it back to me.
Your desire to live freely, it reminded me of Shanks.
I've always admired pirates because of the way they live.
Not just their free spirit, but their names echo throughout time.
Freedom and drive, these notions have inspired my work!
Luffy!
Where are you?
Eh? What are those?!
What are those?!
Who are they?
Ah, they're my friends.
This old man is incredible!
It's just like the real thing!
I see! So you made all those
signs at the shopping center, didn't you, old man?
You guessed right, long nose
With a special oil extract from the trees here on Hand Island...
and adding a little bit of this.
Look closely.
So cool!
Can't ever seem to show off my talent
without damaging the ceiling!
My wax isn't just for making copies.
I can make a material that's as tough as steel.
But it's weak against heat.
What's this?
A failure?
Hey! Don't touch that!
This is a copy of Whitebeard that
my son, Regis made when he was young.
Doesn't look like him, it's horrible.
Shut up! It's his first piece, even if it's not perfect,
it is a great achievement! I'll show you!
It's still very hard! See for yourselves!
Still intact!
With a parent like this...
Is this Regis?
He's not with you anymore?
He's still nearby.
Nearby?
At the next island.
Meaning...?
At the Marine base.
He enlisted in the Marines.
This is weird.
Considering the number of workers,
there's not enough food to go around.
Are they working under these extreme conditions?
Well, it's suspicious.
Did you hear? It seems that Regis is still in that cell.
What an idiot! Challenging Commodore Bilic!
He's just like his father. His father is famous on Hand Island.
He should've become a wax artisan
like him instead of joining the Marines.
That's right.
Hello Regis-kun, are you alright?
Regis, why won't you say it?
"I'm sorry, Bilic-sama! I was wrong."
If you do, I'll release you from this cell.
He's saying that you should apologize.
If you were going to talk, you'd
have done it already, wouldn't you?
Regis, unless you apologize, I can't help you.
Say something!
I...
I?
I... Just said... What I think was right.
What a stubborn guy. Not even scared.
Not scared at all!
Please! Stop firing on the island with your cannon!
You have the nerve to say that?
Telling a superior what to do.
I'll say it as often as needed.
You're wrong!
Go ahead.
Some people just don't know when to apologize.
A prison on a water wheel? That's just horrible!
What do we do? It's almost time to leave.
Before we go back to HQ,
I want to have a look around.
I'll go to Hand Island and talk to the locals.
Hand Island was Whitebeard's territory.
Thanks to Whitebeard's protection, the artisans could
study their craft in peace.
The island was full of life.
However...
In the war two years ago, Whitebeard died.
Since then, other pirates have
arrived to take over his territory.
And slowly, the situation kept getting worse.
There was too much chaos.
But thanks to the Marines building a base nearby, peace returned to the island.
However, a new commander arrived to take charge...
And everything changed.
By the power granted to me by the Marines,
We've cast out the pirates that threaten peace.
However, you should be able to
protect life on this island with your own hands.
Don't you agree, everyone?
I, Bilic, am now in charge of this region,
I'm a man that proudly follows the footsteps of the great Admiral Borsalino.
And so, for the sake of preserving peace on Hand Island..
Will you cooperate with us, the Marines
and please us with your hard work?
To prepare against threats from other pirates...
I propose we build a cannon of great power.
For this project I'll need your superior craftsmanship and skills.
Let's join forces and work together to protect peace and preserve order!
-Right, let's do it!
-I'll join in!
Leave it to me!
Are you kidding me?!
Why do we have to build a cannon?
Though some opposed it, most artisans believed in Bilic.
They committed themselves to protecting the island.
It was also the time that Regis enlisted in the Marines.
All my friends are working with the Marines.
I also want to do something useful for the island.
I'm tired of creating copies.
What did you say?!
Goodbye.
I will not permit it.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Wait, Regis!
Are you leaving this here? At least take it with you.
And so, a year later, the cannon was completed.
Great job, everyone.
Thanks to you, a cannon that has no equal to the world is now completed.
I really want to test it now.
Its trajectory... No way, are you aiming at Hand Island?
Fire!
Those fools!
They created the cannon that is being used against them!
People, do not panic.
The dissident of the island was a threat.
For the sake of peace on the island,
some sacrifice is necessary.
What peace?!
He deceived us...
Give me back my husband!
And now, in order to strengthen our base...
The men will have to work harder. And I promise you...
Justice will prevail!
Since then, they've fired the cannon on the island just for fun.
The artisans at the base suffer greatly.
And they can't act because their families are practically hostages.
They became artisans to create what they desire,
but instead they're forced to build cannons.
Why weren't you taken, old man?
An old man like me is no use to them.
Instead, I supply them with wax.
Are you going somewhere?
After this conversation,
I just can't stand around anymore.
I'm going to the Marine base!
But what will you do when you get there?
I'll deliver this to Regis.
He put his heart into making it.
He created this with his own hands and so he must keep it.
This will prove that he has a heart of an artisan.
If he sees this, maybe he'll remember who he was.
If only I could deliver this, surely something would happen.
Is your back hurting again?
Old man, don't overdo it.
I'll deliver the doll to your son.
After all, you let me see Shanks after all this time.
You want to sneak into the Marine base alone?
I'm just making a delivery.
But is it really necessary?
Isn't it a lot of trouble just to deliver an old doll?
It's not just some wax doll.
And I promised the old man that I'd do it.
That's not the point.
There's no way out of this, damn!
Anyway, we can't let him go alone.
Here, pick one.
Why is it always me?
Looks like they're okay.
Anyway, I hope he won't get them into trouble.
You can't know for sure.
Speaking of which, where's Zoro?
We can move whenever we're ready! I've prepared us to get to the river!
Oh crap!
How awful.
One, two, three.
Excuse me, are you Diego-san?
That's right.
Can I have a bit of your time?
I want to talk to you about Regis-san.
Regis?
Was this also done by the Marines?
If that cannon was to blame,
the Marines would've paid dearly for it.
The Straw Hat Crew had some trouble,
don't worry about it.
It was Luffy-san?
Seems you know him well.
I owe Luffy-san a lot.
What the hell are you doing?
Clean this mess up!
Sorry,  Alvida-sama!
The first time I met Luffy,
I was a prisoner of the Alvida pirates,
and was forced to serve as an errand boy.
Excuse me, this barrel is still full.
Huh? There's nobody here.
I'll be in trouble if I lose this barrel at sea!
What a good nap!
I thought I was gonna die!
Who's there?!
Who are you?
Hello...
I am...
I'm Luffy!
So... Where are we?
He didn't hear me...
This is Iron Mace's pirate ship, Alvida.
And I'm Coby. I'm an errand boy.
Are you a pirate?
N-No, I'm not!
I had gone fishing and somehow ended up on this ship!
For 2 years, instead of killing me,
they've made me work as an errand boy.
I truly hate pirates, so much!
You really are an idiot.
And you're a wimp too. I don't like you.
No need to be so frank.
Oh right! Can I get a boat?
Mine was swallowed in a whirlpool.
You were caught in a whirlpool?!
Yeah, if it wasn't for that barrel, I would have been a goner.
But Luffy-san, why do you like to be out at sea so much?
Me? I...
Want to be the Pirate King.
P-P-Pirate King?!
That's the title of one who's obtained
everything in this world!
You're looking for the treasure
that has it all; wealth, fame, power?!
The great treasure One Piece!
You're gonna die! Pirates all over
the world are searching for that treasure!
So am I.
Impossible! Impossible! Impossible! Definitely impossible!
You can't be the Pirate King! That means staying on top of this great pirate age!
Impossible! Impossible! Impossible! Impossi-
That hurt!
Why did you hit me?!
I felt like it.
I...
Don't mind dying.
It's my dream, so I don't mind if I die fighting for it.
You don't mind if you die?
Such incredible determination!
Even if you don't believe, I believe I can achieve it.
I never thought of it that way.
If I'm determined to die for it...
do you think I can get into the Marines?!
The Marines?
It's my dream! Entering the Marines, becoming an officer
and capturing villains! That's my dream!
But since you're a pirate, I would be your enemy.
Can I do it?
How would I know?
No! I can do it!
In order to join the Marines, I'll risk my life and escape!
And one day I'll capture Alvida.
Who will you capture, Coby?
Who is the prettiest of all the seas, Coby?
It's Alvida-sa~
Who is that fat old woman?
Hey!
How dare you?!
Luffy-san!
Take it back! She is the most...
The most...
It's my dream, so I don't mind if I die fighting for it.
I also want to fight for my dream.
The most...
Who is the most beautiful, Coby?!
The most ugly, fat bitch in the world.
You brat! You won't get out alive!
Well said, Coby. Stand back.
Luffy-san.
That won't work. I'm rubber.
That's impossible! My mace!
-It can't be!
-Impossible!
The boss...
Lady Alvida lost.
Get Coby a boat right away, he's joining the Marines.
Luffy-san!
One thing Luffy-san taught me was,
no matter what happens,
you must believe in yourself-
-and be willing to fight for your beliefs.
And so, I joined the Marines, while Luffy-san became a pirate.
And now I'm a Marine captain
and Luffy-san is a famous pirate.
We were together only for a
short time before we went our separate ways.
But thanks to Luffy-san,
I learned the right path to follow.
He's a great friend.
You're such a nice guy.
I'm glad to see there are people like you in the Marines!
You hate the Marines?
It's just that I don't believe in their claim of justice.
So why did your son join the Marines?
That, I don't understand.
I wanted him to be a wax artisan,
I taught him everything I knew.
Then suddenly, he said he wanted to enlist in the Marines.
Maybe if I could understand this drive to find justice...-
-but I don't get it, and my heart aches.
At this moment, Regis is in jail. It's a terrible situation.
This is bad, what do we do, Luffy?
Excuse me!
Who are you?
I'm looking for a guy named Regis!
I knew he was going to cause trouble.
I'm asking who you are!
I'm Luffy. I came to find Regis. Let me in.
Luffy?
It can't be! The most wanted criminal,
with a bounty over 100 million, Straw Hat Luffy!
Why are they shooting at us?!
What did you expect?!
I guess I have no choice.
Here we go.
Urgent report! The Straw Hat Pirates...
Have infiltrated the base!
What are you doing?! I'm just here to accompany them!
What? Are you telling me that my base was infiltrated by a wanted man with a bounty over 100 million?
Let's just swat that bug!
It seems that Straw Hat Luffy came to find Regis.
What? Regis?
We will do everything in our power
to capture him. No need to worry.
I like that!
I just had a great idea.
How did this happen?
It's obvious that this would
happen if we just come out of nowhere!
Well then, I'll go on ahead.
Say what?
Hey!
Hey...
Quickly! Don't let him get away!
Where is Regis?
That's cool!
I'll take it as a souvenir.
Intruder located! Troops, intercept him!
Don't move, Straw Hat Luffy! You're under arrest!
The pawn is escaping!
Get your hands up! There's no use resisting!
I told you, I didn't come here to fight.
I'm just here to deliver something to Regis and then I'm gonna leave.
Arrest him!
Hey! Tell me, where is Regis?
Why would I tell you?
I get it. You Marines don't just talk, do you?
Because of Luffy, I'm real angry right now!
Sorry about that.
In the cell! He's in his cell!
His cell?
Why is he in a cell if he's in the Marines?
I hope he's eating well at least.
That's not the problem!
What's this?
Is this the prison?
Are you Regis?
Hey!
Who are you?
Your dad asked me to give you this.
I'll leave it right here.
My father?
This is...
Well, it's delivered.
What?
That's a kairouseki cell!
Are you a devil fruit user?
Hey! What's going on?
Hold your breath before we go under!
Reporting in, Bilic-sama!
We've captured Straw Hat Luffy in the cell.
I never imagined he would fall for such a simple trap.
Do not take your eyes off of him until I get there!
This will be a breeze.
I thought I was gonna die!
Hey guys, how did it go?
You were just over there!
How'd you end up under water?
This isn't the time! Get us out of here, now!
What's the meaning of this?
We lost sight of him when he was underwater.
You idiot!
Before you start making excuses...
Apologize.
I'm terribly sorry!
Cursed Straw Hat!
Where'd he go?!
Thanks for saving me.
I'm Usopp. Thanks for delivering the doll.
It's a wax figure of Whitebeard. I made it when I was 6 years old.
Ah, you were 6 when you made it?
I'm sure I can do it better now.
My father really loved pirates.
He wanted to live freely just like pirates do!
I grew up watching my father create
wax works, and he always said that.
It's finished!
You know, this came out just right! Good job, Regis!
And it's hard! Not even a big man like me can break it.
The old man really treasured this doll.
But knowing that my father liked pirates, I opposed him.
Wait, Regis!
Are you leaving this here? At least take it with you!
I wonder why he asked Luffy to deliver the doll?
"Quit the Marines and come home."
Maybe that was the message he was sending?
I don't think that's it.
Maybe I was too hard on him.
But if he chose his path for the sake of the island,
and his conviction is strong, then I'm sure it was worth it.
That's my boy!
That's my son! He'll do great in the Marines.
He said that if we delivered the doll,
something would happen.
I see. My father... even after all of this time...
He still believes in me.
When will you learn? You damned old man!
No matter what happens in life,
keep following the path you believe in.
This is what it means to be free!
Live freely! It's why I admire pirates, Regis.
Actually, I really did want to be a wax artisan like him,
but all I've done is disappoint him.
I'm going back to the Marine base!
So this was all for nothing?
I'll destroy that cannon!
Sounds like fun!
We need to hurry!
An attack?
To all residents of Hand Island!
We know that the Straw Hat
Crew is currently hiding on the island.
Why are you protecting the pirates?
Hand over the Straw Hat Crew this instant!
Otherwise I'll destroy the entire island!
We are trying to protect the
island and you are hiding pirates! You idiots!
You idiots! Surrender the Straw Hats!
Unforgivable!
It was better when we were persecuting the pirates!
What do we do?
What is your son doing?
Regis-kun is fighting for the good of the island!
Pirates are infiltrating!
Fire!
A report, Mr. Bilic!
What is it?
The Straw Hat Crew have invaded again and we are confronting them as we speak.
Did the people on the island send them?
Josephine and I will make them pay!
He saved us.
Zoro-san! You're amazing as always.
That's Roronoa Zoro?! Incredible!
I need to make a model of him!
Diego-san
Before you get to work, I have a favor to ask.
A favor?
Yes!
How is this possible? Looks like something cut the cannonball!
Cut?
Cut the cannonball?
Impossible!
My mighty Josephine can't possibly miss!
Pirates are entering the base!
Take care of them! Use everything you can! I'll finish the one who cut the cannonball.
Release the spinners!
What is that?
How should I know?
What is it?
What is that noise?
Don't leave your seats! Get back to work!
Who's there?
Don't move, or I'll shoot you!
Regis?
Let's stop the cannon! Help me, everyone!
Quickly!
That cannon is persistent.
-Incredible!
-Samurai, you're awesome!
I got this.
Thank you!
Let's get started.
Careful! I'm pretty strong!
Do something, Sanji!
I have a feeling that something is going to happen soon.
Why are you being so carefree?!
They've arrived!
Ladies~! Now that I'm here, you can relax~!
We've come to help too!
Oh, sorry.
You're not sorry at all!
Great!
We got all the spinners!
Is it over?
What a relief.
Attack!
It's not over!
Not once, but twice?
Unbelievable!
Let's try a high angle trajectory!
It won't matter how you hit this!
You will be crushed! Die!
Don't tell me...
Impossible!
Damn it!
Keep firing! Throw everything you have on the island.
Kill everyone on the island!
I'll join in on the fun too!
What the hell?!
Damn it!
I'll kill you!
What the?
We are terribly sorry! Pirates are attacking and-
You're supposed to have taken care of them!
You are the hardest material on this island, I'm counting on you!
Unforgivable!
Run!
Luffy-san!
You did it, Regis!
Are you okay?
Now Hand Island will no longer have to fear the cannon.
I barely had a chance to participate.
I'm glad!
He got the fat guy as well.
Ouch!
Who is he?
Is this the wax from Hand Island?
Regis! Is this your doing?!
I did it to restore peace to the island!
Ah, give that back.
It's precious to his old man. The doll was made by Regis.
What are you talking about?!
This is just a puppet of one
of the pirates who threaten peace.
That's all! That's all!
Fortunately it's weak against heat.
Is weak.
Hey!
Just wait, you will have it back soon.
Damn you!
What did you do?!
What did I do?
This is how pirates live, threatening
people and robbing them of everything.
You just destroyed a precious asset of the Marines
and do you even care?
Unforgivable! I will not forgive! It will not be forgiven!
Unforgivable!
Is it over?!
Never a boring moment on this island.
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Elizabeth will pass judgment on you!
Pass! Pass! Pass! Will, yes!
That's cool!
Interesting!
So, you're a user of the Gomu Gomu no Mi?
Interesting. But as an opponent, you're nothing to me.
It's useless!
The kinetic energy, combined
with the speed and weight of the projectile
creates a much stronger impact, which can break your protection.
All thanks to a special type of fuse inside it!
Making it ideal to combat devil fruit users like yourself.
How did that feel?
Are you alright Luffy?
Yes.
I'll kick his ass!
With this speed, I don't have to worry about devil fruit users!
The speed of Elizabeth makes her untouchable!
Behold my secret weapon!
Now, I'll show you the true power of Elizabeth!
Kill him! Kill him! Finish him!
Fall! Fall! Fall! Fall! Fall! Fall! Fall! Fall!
I won't fall!
I'll play some more. Go, Giant Tops!
Like Elizabeth, with hard work, sweat and ingenuity, the artisans also created The Giant Tops.
Those artisans were idiots, but they did a great job!
I will not forgive you!
That's what I should say!
I will not forgive him!
Franky, Usopp, thanks!
Incredible, Captain Coby! I didn't even have a chance to participate.
No need for formalities. Let's hurry!
Yea, yea.
I see. I see!
What?
Don't think you'll win just because you have devil fruit powers.
Don't you see?
Even being a rubber man, with
all the projectiles exploding inside you...
Soon! Don't resist! Soon you will perish!
You got yourself in a bad situation.
It's not over yet!
Fire!
It is now!
It's so easy to defeat the devil fruit users!
Easy! Easy! Easy!
Luffy!
Hold on!
This is the final blow!
Die!
Are you crazy?!
I'll hit you with every shot!
Die!
Have a goodbye kiss.
Now die, pirate!
Gotcha!
You coward!
Let's go of me! Let's go of me!
I most certainly will not Let's go!
It's Admiral Yellow Monkey!
Admiral Borsalino!
We can rest easy!
Crap! It's Yellow Monkey!
Let's set sail!
I'll check our course!
I'm hungry!
You're not done fighting,
and already you want to eat!
Alright guys, let's set sail!
Aye!
Food! Food! Food!
The Marine HQ analyzed the situation.
It was decided that Commodore Bilic
will be arrested and court martialed!
Torturing the inhabitants of the island for his own ambitions
is something a Marine Officer should never do.
Don't you agree, Admiral Borsalino?
It's true.
The Marines should immediately stop attacks on the island and await orders from HQ.
Yes, Sir!
I want you to cooperate with the islanders!
Father?
That was close.
I never imagined that Yellow Monkey would show up.
But that Yellow Monkey wasn't moving.
Dad, I'm sorry!
Don't worry about it.
I made it in a hurry, so don't let them see the back.
But at least I was able to imitate his voice.
Yeah, that's true.
I did it!
Luffy, I still have a long way to go.
But someday, I'll catch up to you!
Hey, where's Zoro?
I totally forgot!
Let's just leave him.
We're not gonna leave him!
Hey!
I will be the Pirate King!