Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They learned about the ruler of Punk Hazard - Caesar's motive
and all while trying to escape Netherworld,
along with their pirate ally - the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar,
save the children, and escape from the island.
Catch me if you can! But I'm protected!
Doflamingo! The Four Emperors!
Do you even have balls to pick a fight with them?
--I don't think so! If you wanna run, do it now! --A fight?
Get out of my face!
I've been...
...picking fights all along!
The Shocking Conclusion!
Smoker vs. Vergo!
M-Master!
Ow, ow, ow... My nose!
You broke my nose!
How dare you! Dammit!
Ow, ow, ow...
Damn you! Were you even listening to me?!
You can't get away with this!
I have that crazy pirate backing me!
One of the Seven Warlords - Donquixote Doflamingo!
He is the behind-the-scenes string-puller of the New World!
Small arms, war weapons, drugs...
He's involved in every risky transaction!
He's the mastermind of the underground!
He's connected to all the notorious figures!
You're no match for him!
He'll bring you under in a matter of minutes!
You and your friends!
B-But I can still spare your life.
I-I-If you apologize now...
Think about how many monsters you will
piss off if you do something to me!
Okay?!
Hey, are you listening?! Hmmm?
I'm talking about the Warlords and the Four Emperors!
They'll make you...
...drown at sea in the blink of an eye!
I-If you apologize now, I'll let you off the hook...
Gastille!
That serves you right!
Yeah!
A gas burner attack that could melt iron!
Did he get melted away? Or incinerated?!
I-I-I-I know! It doesn't feel like it's real, does it?!
It's too much for a rookie who just came to the New World!
But one of those monsters is here in the lab.
It's Vergo!
No one can compete against his Armament Haki!
Smoker and Law are goners!
So are all of your crew!
I-I-I said you're all gonna die!
S-S-So why don't you listen to me...
I said...
...I don't care!
Smoker...
Vergo!
How dare you screw with the Navy!
You're too weak. You can't beat me.
You never learn.
My basic fighting skill and Haki are better than yours.
You still don't get it?
Too slow!
White Blow!
You keep on fighting because you're
angry at me for betraying the Navy?
I just want to settle the matter!
I have to finish you off with my own hands!
Pirate Vergo!
Your Haki isn't good enough to beat me.
Why can't you see that?
Netherworld is a lethal gas that petrifies human bodies and kills them.
And it is now flowing into the laboratory.
Hey, what are you doing?!
If you were going straight,
we should've been caught up with the kids by now!
Shut up! You're wounded - shut your mouth!
I am going straight!
No! Not that way!
No! You went too far!
How can you mess up something this simple?!
Shut up!
Hurry up, kids! Keep running!
I feel dizzy. It feels like I've been dreaming.
That's because of the sedatives.
They're harmless so don't worry!
Guys! Keep your eyes on the kids!
Yes, sir! Brother!
Yeah!
Mocha! Stay with me!
You're gonna be alright soon!
Come on! Get it all out!
The survivors are heading toward R Building, 1st floor -
the location of the last exit
and ground zero of the fight between Luffy and Caesar!
Meanwhile, Kin'emon is looking for his son Momonosuke...
What have I done?! Momonosuke!
What?! Momonosuke turned to a small dragon?!
Uh-huh!
I shouldn't tell anybody but it's true.
Maybe I...
...sliced up Momonosuke?!
Momonosuke!
I've done a terrible thing!
Kin'emon-san, you can't go back!
That area is filled up with the gas by now...
The deadly gas is right in front of us!
My spirit will carry me through anything!
Whether it's fire or gas!
Momonosuke!
No, that's impossible! Kin'emon-san!
The Sea Prism Stone handcuffs... Maybe, they're here.
No, they aren't!
Because I hear the "Usopp alarm" ringing in my head now.
Yes, let's just pretend that I checked this room.
That's it!
Tell them "I looked all over but the Sea Prism Handcuffs weren't..."
"...in that room!"
He's an enemy!
Why is this always happening to me?!
White...
...Blow!
Are you satisfied now, Smoker-kun?
No matter how deeply you believe in justice,
you can't do anything if you're weak!
What do you want?
If I can take my heart back,
I can kick your ass easily, Vergo!
Don't make me repeat myself, squirt!
It's Vergo-san to you!
Tashigi, I want you to lead the G-5 soldiers.
Where are you going, Smoker-san?
Don't tell me you're going after Vergo!
The law can't settle these matters, Tashigi!
I have to do it myself! He was messing around with the Navy!
Stop it, Tashigi!
Wouldn't you rather die than grovel before a pirate?!
Right now, we have to beg for our lives,
throwing ourselves at his feet if that's what it takes!
Because if we die here, we can't save our people!
And the children...
You're gonna die here, too, Law!
Smoker...
Do you still wanna fight, Smoker-kun?
You know you're no match for me.
What are you doing?
You shouldn't turn to smoke and spread yourself
thin when you're facing a better Haki user.
It just makes it easier for me to hit you!
Why do you keep using your Devil Fruit power?
Can't you even think straight?
It's not like you, Smoker-kun.
Enough playing around!
Demon Bamboo!
I know you wanna kill me for messing with the Navy.
But you have to be strong enough to do so, Smoker.
If you're just reckless, you can't make your people proud of you.
It's over.
Smoker, my heart...
Thank you for winning it back!
Now it makes sense! You bastard!
That's why you turned to smoke!
Now we're even.
Just finish him off already!
You don't wanna owe a pirate, huh?
It's a dishonor to a Navy soldier.
I'm too ashamed to be seen by my people.
But...
...that was just the help I needed.
It's over.
Vergo... -san.
You child!
Now you remember that I'm better than you?
I just want you to keep thinking like that.
But you can't stay sitting on that "throne" forever!
You two!
I know you're listening, "Joker"!
Vergo is a dead man, Joker.
You're about to lose your right-hand man.
And Straw Hatter will take care of Caesar.
That means you're also gonna lose SAD.
You couldn't see this coming because you were overconfident.
So why don't you just keep cackling like always
and think about your next move.
But you won't be laughing for long because...
...we're gonna do the unthinkable!
Nice try acting strong, squirt!
But are you sure you'll survive?
Look at Vergo in front of you.
Didn't you piss him off?
Do you remember what happened last time?
How did it go?
You pissed Vergo off and then what happened?
It must've been traumatic. You probably can't forget it.
You must be afraid of Vergo.
Even with your incomparable swordplay,
his Haki will allow him to block your every attack.
Both in terms of status and power,
you're no match for Vergo!
Here we go!
It's been two years since the Paramount War.
Did anyone actually accomplish anything?
All you did was stay calm.
All Whitebeard did was end the era.
The Navy Headquarters rounded up new forces.
The big-timers didn't take any action!
It was like everybody was just preparing for something.
That war was only a beginning.
You always told me...
...that the new era of the daring ones
is coming along with an unstoppable swell!
I broke... the gear!
Now,
there is no turning back!
Law's attack turns the tables in an instant.
The Straw Hats scramble and aim for a quick getaway.
But Caesar, at the pinnacle of his rage...
...unleashes a terrible attack on Luffy...
...that annihilates friend and foe alike.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Caesar Crushed!
The Ultimate Grizzly Magnum"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Caesar Crushed!
The Ultimate Grizzly Magnum