Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has made it aboard a Navy ship
in order to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been taken to Navy HQ!
There is nothing but despair ahead for you!
You can't get away no
matter how you struggle!
Can't you see that it's no
use? For pirates like you...
...The Gate of Justice won't open!
Are you sure about opening the gate?
Warden Magellan!
Bon-chan is...
It's me!
Bon-chan! Bon-chan!
Bon-chan, the gate's closing.
We...
...have to go.
Thank you!
--The gate is closing!
--We gotta sink them!
Do you wanna say something before you die?!
This is what I wanted!
Luffy has broken out of the world's
greatest prison Impel Down!
But the end is nowhere in sight...
Destination: Navy Headquarters
Embarking on Ace's Rescue Mission!
Why do you want to live so dangerously?
If I hadn't come here with an antidote,
Level 4: Inferno Hell
you guys would be dead.
You can't underestimate Magellan.
But we're alive!
The fact that you came down
here is a part of our fate.
But you're right! I thought
I was going to die!
We are...
...lucky.
Whether you die or not--it's up to God!
Those who harbor fear will lose!
We just need to live in the moment!
Don't we, Shiryu?!
I'm grateful for your
help! You have my thanks!
And again, welcome to our gang! I think
that we're gonna make a great team!
My future here is predictable.
I've been waiting to meet someone like you.
Ship route of the World Government, the Tub Current
All right, everyone!
Let's toast to our unprecedented
unheard-of breakout of Impel Down!
--Cheers!
Oh, that's good!
We'll have to do it without Inazuma from here on out.
What?! The infection
is really that bad?!
Vi was infected with just
one kind of poison and...
got it out of my system using my
Healing Hormone and Energy Hormone.
Heehaw!
But it's complicated because one will take years off your life and the other causes severe side effects!
It's better if he can rest
and recover naturally.
Nothing can help you to regain
the years lost by using the hormone!
Inazuma is an indispensable
New Kama of the Revolutionary Army!
We shouldn't allow him
to push himself too hard!
When I think about it,
he wasn't a bad guy after all.
I was looking forward to seeing him again...
But once more, he rushed to our aid!
Bon-chan!
--Brother Bon!
--Bon-chan!
Bon-chan!
Hey, how long are you gonna
mourn like that, guys?!
He was great but he's dead
and nothing can't change it!
Let's just party!
It's a breakout party!
Oh yeah, let's celebrate it
as a funeral for Mr. 2...
I knew I'd fall into the red!
We don't know if Bon-chan's
dead yet, you, big nose!
What did you just say?!
Your nose is red, round and stupid!
Well, your face is rubbery,
stretchy and stupid!
What'd you say?!
I couldn't care less about them...
I thought that talking to fish was
the special ability of Mermaids only.
But you can call out to sharks, too.
Is it so weird for a Fishman
to be a friend of fish?
Well, I can say that it's not normal.
I guess that you're a misfit...
...of the violent species.
I take it as a compliment.
I can't deny the fact that
Fishmen are violent.
Bon-chan's not dead!
Oh! Captain Buggy grew another red nose!
Luffy-kun.
You gave me an opportunity to save Ace-san.
I owe you a great debt.
Don't think of it in terms like
that. There'd be no end to it!
For me, it's just encouraging to
have you along! You're so strong!
I want to thank you and apologize
to you for the other case before this.
But, not today. There is
something more important now.
You can call me Jinbe!
I'm a Warlord but I'm sure
they'll revoke my title!
So let's run wild at Navy Headquarters!
We have to live up to the expectations of...
...that Queer-kun and rescue
Ace-san at any cost!
--A Warlord?
--Navy Headquarters?
What?!
Hey you! You're a Warlord?!
No wonder you're so strong!
Sorry that I hadn't introduced myself yet!
Everyone else knows that.
Hey! What's that about Navy Headquarters?!
Don't tell me that we're heading to Navy Headquarters!
--Yes, we are!
--No!
I know that you guys know about the
war between Whitebeard and the Navy!
--What'd you say?
--Navy HQ?
It's obvious. It's your faults
for being so clueless.
What?!
We passed through the Gate of Justice.
That means our destination must be
either Navy HQ or Enies Lobby.
The Tub Current that we're on
is exclusive to the Government.
It's a giant whirlpool that connects
the Government's 3 major facilities
We wanted to break out because
we have a role in the war.
Yeah! The real fight is on its way!
"The real fight is on its way?!"
W-We didn't know about this!
--Stop the ship right now, you bastard!
--Stop!
We can't stop because we are on the current!
Why don't you guys get off?!
--Okay, bye!
--Yeah, bye!
No, we can't!
Devil Fruit users
like us will definitely be killed!
Navy HQ and the Seven Warlords
versus the Whitebeard Pirates?!
That's more horrifying than hell!
I wanna go back to the prison
rather than entering this war!
Us from the Kama Land knew it.
Why didn't you tell us then?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
We can't escape death this time!
Mom!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Hey, do you hear something?
--It's a Transponder Snail!
--Who's calling?
Don't you get it? This is a Navy ship!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Why don't we just pretend we're not here?
--Clank!
--Hello?
He picked up!
This is Navy HQ.
Oh, this is Luffy.
Don't give your name like that!
We know that the ship has
been taken by escapees.
We received a report from the
Fleet Escort Force at Impel Down.
We determined who the two main suspects
of this great escape case were...
...from the insider information
before contact was lost.
Two?
A pirate--Straw Hat Luffy!
And another pirate Buggy the Clown!
-- What?!
-- W-What?!
No way!
Captain Buggy is the main suspect
although there're Warlords here?!
Who the hell are you?!
Why me?!
--Let me see the documents.
--Here you go.
We thought that you were
just a nameless pirate.
Buggy the Clown, I can't believe that...
...you were a crew member under
Gold Roger, Pirate King.
How'd you know that?
What?!
--"The ship" - that means Oro Jackson?!
--He's kick-ass!
He's a star! A star among pirates!
We also know that you're a sworn
brother of Red-Haired Shanks,
one of the Four Emperors.
What?!
How could someone like this
have laid low until now...
...without raising any alarms.
But now, you've made yourself known.
Well...
We can't see clearly your
connection with Fire Fist Ace
but we're sure that your goal is
the same as Straw Hat Ace's rescue!
Well... I don't really...
We know that you have
Jinbe, Crocodile, Ivankov,
and more than 200 ruffians who
are also escapees on board.
I warn you.
As long as we don't open the Gate of Justice,
you guys can't get to Marineford
or even get out of the Tub Current!
There is no sea for you all
to get away to or to live on!
Better make yourselves
comfortable! That's it.
Hey wait, Navy!
I'm gonna rescue Ace at any cost!
"Wash your potatoes" and be ready for us!
Potatoes?
Clank!
The expression should be "watch your neck!"
You don't wash your potatoes and
boil them at a time like this!
First of all, why did he try to
pick a fight with Navy HQ?!
Wait, before that... Captain Buggy!
Were you really a member of the crew?!
And a sworn brother of "Red-Haired"?!
Our savior is a hell of a pirate as we thought!
Oh, well...
Damn! If word gets around,
the Government will keep an eye on me!
So that's his background!
And yet, he's so weak.
With such a pedigree,
how could you be so dirty?!
So every ship has at least one blemish!
Shut up!
I didn't know that. But I remember...
Have you also heard of the East Blue pirate known as Buggy?
That old first mate mentioned it, too.
Huh? First mate?
The old man called Rayleigh,
I bet you know him.
What?! Have you seen Rayleigh-san?!
This takes me back! Where'd you see him?
They're talking about "Dark King"
Rayleigh! What a conversation!
Captain Buggy! I knew you were something!
No no, wait a second! It's all true but...
...if you spread this around, it'll
be bad for my future as a pirate!
It's amazing that you were the
member of the legendary pirates!
Buggy! Buggy!
H-Hey, you fools...
Stop it! I was an apprentice to be exact!
I don't want you to make
a lion of me with that...
Hey, you got the wrong idea!
Well, I don't feel so bad...
Oh yeah, wait a minute!
The Navy has overestimated me for
sure but it's not such a bad thing!
Yeah! Because it's all true!
I'm developing a reputation here!
If by some chance, I could...
If I could beat Whitebeard,
then I'd become the one of...
...the Four Emperors!
Oh no no no... I'd go way
beyond that and become...
...the Pirate King!
Yeah! These guys might have
higher bounties than me!
If I play my cards right...
...I can do this!
Captain Buggy! We'll follow
you the rest of our lives!
Give us an order!
Let's steal this ship from the ones
who want to go to Navy HQ!
And then, we're gonna be free!
Well, Straw Hat! You need to
give over this ship to us!
After breaking out, we don't
wanna go to Navy HQ!
We got Captain Buggy on our side!
Go ahead, Captain Buggy!
--Buggy! Buggy!
--This is no good.
It's better to just kill them all.
Yeah, I feel like I can do it!
Be quiet, you flashy fools!
You guys are all full of whim and fancy!
This ship won't stop!
We're heading to the center of the war!
And you guys are already on board!
Brace yourselves and think about it!
Soon, the man at the top of the
world is gonna show up in our midst!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance.
If you guys are real men, why don't
you live out a dream with me?!
Today...
I'll beat Whitebeard which means
that I'll conquer the world!
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
Captain Buggy!
We were devastated by the darkness of hell...
...And we almost lost the
most important thing!
Losing the jewels of our hearts
that we once had - called dream!
I will follow you!
I don't want a peaceful life!
That's right!
Let's go, guys! To Navy Headquarters!
Looks like it's over.
He has this kind of ability at least.
Captain Buggy! You should lead the world!
I'll follow you to the end!
Yeah, follow me!
Vi hope they are having fun.
The ship that carries Portgas D. Ace
will arrive at Marineford shortly!
Here he comes, finally!
Relax and go on board!
There's room for everybody so don't worry!
Be prepared for the arrival!
"Navy"
The sky island, Weatheria, still carrying
Nami, continues toward the Grand Line,
but it's traveling far too slowly.
Will Nami make it back to her friends?
And will Franky, now a gentleman,
ever return to his old self?!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Crew's Whereabouts
Weatheria Report and Cyborg Animals"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Crew's Whereabouts
Weatheria Report and Cyborg Animals