Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece...
head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and in order to move on
to the next stage—the New World—
they returned to Sabaody Archipelago!
Let's go to Fishman Island!
There's something at six o'clock!
Is it a creature? No...
Are you guys all ready?!
Yes, brother!
Yes, yes!
The target is right there!
Hey, guys!
There is a ship kind of thing coming from behind!
Charge!
It's a pirate ship!
Deadly Combat under the Sea
The Demon of the Ocean Strikes
Run!
Hard to port!
Go, Sea Cow!
They're coming after us!
That sounds so familiar...
They're so persistent!
What do they want from us?
Stop!
The bubble is gonna pop!
You're doing great, Sea Cow!
Yes!
Are they gonna come aboard?
Sea Cow?
Wait a minute! That's...
The bubbles are joined!
Brother, now is the chance!
Alright, should we do it?!
Yes!
Hey, Momoo! You're Momoo
of the Arlong Pirates, aren't you?
Do you remember me?
I'm Nami! I was there at the Arlong Park!
Hm? Hey, Luffy,
doesn't he look familiar?
Yeah?
Die, you damn thing!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Let's board their ship!
Yes!
Whoa! He's coming through the bubble!
No, somebody's coming!
We gotta fight!
Guys! Are you ready?!
Yes!
While they're dumbfounded,
kill them all!
Let's go!
Yes!
Guys, follow my lead!
What?!
What's the matter, Sea Cow?
Why, Sea Cow?
Oh no, we left Captain Caribou on that ship!
Brother!
Alright, by way of greeting,
fire the gatling gun!
Kill all the Straw Hats and...
Huh?
No! Don't throw me out into the water!
That's something...
you shouldn't do!
You have to value people's life!
The gods... the gods are watching over you!
Don't you think so?!
You're being inconsistent!
Weren't you gonna fire a gatling gun and kill us all!
No, that was just...
That was just a play on words.
That wasn't playing.
Who are you? You must be
the captain of the ship.
Oh, Roronoa Zoro!
No way! I'm not a captain! I'm just...
I was forced to be a slave for them!
Oh, I'm sick of being on that ship!
He's making ridiculous excuses.
Oh yeah! This is great!
Can I stay on this ship for a little while?
Please?
Well, he is kind of pathetic...
No way! He just made it up!
What?! He just made it up?!
Hey, where did you find the Sea Cow
who was drawing your ship?
Oh...
Here is... mmm... Cutie-san!
You're the Cat Burglar.
Stop looking at our navigator like that!
Nami-san! You're safe...
now!
That's getting to be a pain!
I just caught that sea monster somewhere...
Experienced people
have those animals pull their ship.
What?!
Is that so?
Stop! Stop, Sea Cow!
What happened?
Brother! I'll save you!
I wanna find a sea monster.
Hey, Luffy! What are you up to?
Oh, it's just a turtle... It's too small.
Come on!
Let's start his rehabilitation with some less stimulating pics.
Hey, Nami.
The direction we're heading is slightly off
from where Log Pose is pointing.
Yeah, that's fine.
The right course should be south west
of where it's pointing.
It's faster to go straight.
Why should we do that?
If you go straight, you'd be taken away by the sea current
and crash into an undersea mountain or volcano.
What?! Volcano?!
It's scary in the water!
But I thought the sea currents in the Grand Line were volatile.
Is there any stable current?
Yes, just one.
This is good.
Now stay still!
Everyone! It's gonna get colder from here on out
so wear a coat or something.
Yes, it's getting chilly—I can feel it on my skin.
Oh, but I don't...
You're a skeleton—you don't have skin.
Chopper-san, you can't do that...
You can't steal my line...
Are we going somewhere cold?
Not the deep sea?
Don't you know that the water
in the deep sea is cold?
Like in a bath tub, hot water
goes up and cold water goes down.
Oh yeah? I'm not a big fan of baths so I wouldn't know.
I see.
If the sea is the same as a bath tub,
it's gonna get colder as you go deeper.
The temperature isn't the only difference.
You're still depressed?!
In the deep layer of the sea,
there are giant currents called deep currents
that you don't get to see very often.
Those currents flow totally independently
from surface currents.
There are currents under currents?!
You know many things!
Because I'm really old!
All currents are connected.
One current flows eastward
and the other one flows westward.
They could also flow upward or downward.
It's like a giant dragon.
Deep currents flow really slowly.
Once they flow to the deep sea,
it takes 2000 years...
until they flow upward to the surface.
2000 years?!
Yes, that's why there are a number of myths...
about the dark and undiscovered deep currents.
Monsters! Curses! Spirits of the dead!
What?! There are ghosts in the deep sea?!
Huh? Really? I'm scared!
It's exciting!
Ghosts... I don't know about that.
But we're gonna get on a downward flow.
That's how we get to the deep sea.
Deep layer...
Surface...
Downward flow...
Submerge...
Twang-twang!
So there are wonderful currents...
You guys didn't understand a bit, did you?!
You wanna sing, Nami-san?
Shut up!
What is that sound?
This is it!
Nami, I see it!
Yeah?
The wonderful current?!
Where is it?
That's cool!
Oh!
What is that?
So that's the downward current!
The downward flow—Plume!
How... cool!
It's like a massive...
waterfall in the sea!
Interesting!
The sea is "falling" far below! At an extraordinary speed!
Nature's great!
What a spectacular stream!
I wonder how deep it is.
It's far greater than I had heard.
I can't see the bottom!
It's completely dark!
We're dead!
With that speed, we're gonna be slammed
into the bottom and die!
Is it really okay to go with the flow?
Don't worry about the ship.
Sunny is the strongest ship
built from the Treasure Tree Adam.
Alright!
Advance!
No way!
I didn't know that thing lives here!
It's a demon that rules the realm of water!
And the enemy of the human race!
Straw Hats! You should turn back now!
It's dangerous!
I had forgotten about you.
There is a monster!
What?!
What are you talking about? Cut that crap!
Those myths are just made up by someone.
It... It's right there...
Cut it out, guys!
B-Behind you...
What are you saying...
Be... Behind me?
Uh-huh.
Behind me...
It's the Kraken!
How huge! The monster octopus!
Looks like he broke a lot of ships!
Ships that had left for
the New World have been attacked!
Please! I don't wanna die! Go back!
If you just wait for a few days, it would...
Shut up!
I have a good idea!
Let's tame him!
Huh?
What did you say, Luffy?!
Let's tame the octopus and make him pull our ship!
No way!
Take a good look!
No, you don't have to take a good look since it's huge!
Oh, it's big!
We're dead!
It must've been around for several hundred years!
The Kraken appears
in countless legends around the world—
it's like a mythical creature!
It has no bones and I'm
a skeleton without any flesh...
It's the polar opposite of me.
I don't care!
You're quite good.
You can't see this kind of thing often, so...
Sketching? How relaxed!
I'll help you but do you have any plan, Luffy?
The problem is that we're in the sea.
No. No. No.
The problem is the size of it.
It would be dangerous even if we were on land.
What's wrong with them?
This is the kind of situation when everybody agrees
to run away at full speed!
Shift the helm to the south!
Hey, Nami, go straight towards the octopus!
Don't be a fool!
Whoa, whoa, Nami-san. I'm here for...
The octopus will—
here for...
for you!
You held out!
Good job!
Thanks to the rehabilitation and to Nami for wearing a coat.
It's dangerous to be on this ship!
I've got to protect myself!
Something's coming from behind!
Brother!
They came back!
Coribou! Guys!
We're gonna save my brother!
Yes!
You came back to save me, huh?!
Don't do it!
The coating popped!
That ship is even bigger than Sunny!
Oh... Guys!
They look like a school of jellyfish.
Shut up, Roronoa! Cut it out!
It's coming!
It's too big!
How can we fight against it?!
Gear 3...
No!
You'll break the bubble!
Chicken Voyage!
Can we... get away somehow?!
Don't do anything! I'll beat it!
No! You're gonna break the bubble!
Listen! If you wanna fight
against it that much, here is an idea!
Huh, what is it? Tell me.
Okay, that's good!
That's the extra-vehicular Flutter Kick Coating!
An extra-vehicular diving suit!
As long as you're in it,
you can fight as you want even in water!
If I let these fools do whatever they want, I'll be in danger too!
You shouldn't have done that, stranger!
We wanted to run away!
Now, they're gonna fight!
I told you guys to run from the beginning
but that Captain-san won't listen!
Would you rather they fought on this ship?
Okay, good luck! Go far away!
This rope is annoying.
Stay away from this ship!
Alright.
Okay, let's go!
Yeah!
Huh?
Wait! You have to attach the safety rope!
You'll be separated!
Nami-san's worrying about me!
You guys! Draw his attention for me!
I'm gonna beat him with one strong blow!
I could beat him right away!
You can't cut him!
I want the octopus as a pet!
Are they okay?
Stay as far away as you can!
Even a millimeter—
But it's attacking us!
Move aside, guys!
Franky...
Rocket Launcher!
Got it!
How powerful!
No, another arm!
Why does he keep attacking us?!
It's gonna hit us!
Guard Point!
They got a hard hit!
Are you guys okay?
H-He did it!
Well done!
Yeah, Chopper!
We're gonna hit the mountain!
Mil Fleurs:
Gigantesco Mano!
What big hands!
Yes!
Nice, Robin! You saved us!
Good. Although I'm in water,
I was okay because it was just a brief moment.
They did great.
Alright, it's my turn!
Here is the new technique!
Gear 3!
Facing the demon of the ocean floor, Kraken,
Luffy, Zoro and Sanji use the techniques
acquired during their two-year training.
But then, the Straw Hats
are scattered in the deep sea
by the massive current caused by the battle.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Lost in the Deep Sea
The Straw Hats Get Separated"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Lost in the Deep Sea
The Straw Hats Get Separated