Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle on Fishman Island,
the Straw Hats reach the New World at long last,
the harshest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
Navigating the treacherous Maubeugemour Sea,
they met a Giant girl named Lily,
who's eaten the Mini-Mini Fruit.
They got fired up to help her save her father,
Panz Fry, from a Navy convoy...
but a mysterious group called
the Neo Navy was out to kill him.
Surface and finish them off at once!
Yes, sir!
You're responsible for all the raids on pirates?!
Yes, I am! I'm gonna cut this guy's head off too!
And a three-way battle between the Straw Hats,
the Navy and the Neo Navy ensued.
You worthless pirates are no match for me!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Jet...
Finger Pistol Ten!
...Spear!
And they were able to bring down the menacing enemy - Shuzo!
But this was just the first foray into the New World for the Straw Hats.
All right, let's go!
Yeah!
Landing!
The Burning Island, Punk Hazard
Go!
Hey, hey, hey!
Whoa, whoa! Are we gonna be okay?
The Sunny will be fine!
What's that?
What?! That's impossible!
A red sea?!
Look! The volcano's erupting!
Let's go to that island!
What?!
Wait a minute, Luffy!
Just as I thought.
None of the needles point to that island.
Let's go to that island!
I said "Wait"!
Why?! There is a volcano! It looks like fun!
Who could resist?
Listen to me, Luffy!
None of the 3 needles is pointing at the island!
It's too peculiar even in the strange New World!
It's erupting again!
It's right there! Who cares about the needles?!
Let's just go there!
No way! We can't get any closer!
Because the sea is on fire!
I don't understand you!
It's perfect.
Hey, that's the Giant Shellfish Panz Fry gave us.
I thought we could cook this in that sea of fire.
Sanji! Now isn't the time for that!
--Sparks! --The ship will catch fire too!
No!
The Sunny is super not gonna let us down!
That's not the point!
There's something wrong with this sea!
Look at those fish bones, bones, bones!
Huh? Did you just call me?
Wh-What's that?!
Hey, what's this? The Transponder Snail is crying!
Hey, what's wrong?! You have a stomachache?
Fool! That's an emergency signal.
Somebody's calling for help.
If I pick it up, can we hear them?
Wait, Luffy!
More than 50 percent of emergency signals are fake!
It could be a Navy trap - one they use often.
If the line is tapped, they will find out where we are.
That's our Robin!
Hey, Luffy, you have to be careful...
Clank.
Hello? My name is Monkey D. Luffy!
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
You picked up too fast and said too much!
Help me!
What happened?
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
No, I'm not the Boss. Is it cold there?
My colleagues are getting cut one after another!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
Samurai?
Hey you, what's your name?! Where are you?!
Somebody please help me!
I'm on...
...Punk Hazard!
He got killed!
Th-That was...
I smell trouble...
He got killed - of course there is trouble!
Somebody just cut him!
The New World is scary!
Maybe he was acting and it's a trap.
How level-headed!
Come on, Robin-san!
Speaking of samurai, Brook...
Yes, what you think is right.
That's that name of the swordsmen from the Wano Kingdom.
The Wano Kingdom - closed off to the outside world.
It's not even affiliated with the World Government.
They say those swordsmen called samurai are so strong
even the Navy can't approach.
This renowned blade - Shusui - was once carried by a legendary samurai.
If you become its owner, the sword will be pleased.
I let this samurai's body... take the beating.
I feel bad.
I've never heard of that country.
But he said Punk Hazard, not the Wano Kingdom.
Did he mean the island of fire right there?
If he was using a Baby Transponder Snail,
that's about how far the signal can reach.
All right! Let's go help that guy!
No!
Luffy, think again! I think it's too late!
Samurai are scary!
I'm scared too!
Hey you, what's your name?! Where are you?!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
...Punk Hazard!
Smoker-san, that was...
Did he say Punk Hazard?
Damn!
How could they have gotten there?
The battle at Fishman Island, the incident after that...
If we plot the course they took from there...
Punk Hazard... It's possible they're there.
Don't do it! I'll do anything!
I'll do whatever you ask me to!
Then get charred!
Stop it, you guys! Stop bullying pirates!
Tashigi! Let's head for Punk Hazard!
But Smoker-san,
Punk Hazard
has been deserted since they sealed it
off after what happened 4 years ago!
There shouldn't be anybody there!
You're right.
I don't think any living thing can live there now but...
...it'd make sense to go check.
We are setting out for Punk Hazard, men!
Huh? Vice Admiral Smoker, it's a restricted area.
Don't you know that?
Don't tell me about the law, you scum!
Okay...
And who's going to the island?
Since there is uncertainty, we shouldn't all go.
--Franky, I need the Mini-Merry! --Okay!
Wait! Are you gonna go by yourself?
Do you have a problem with that?
Yes, I do!
If we let you go by yourself, you'll disappear without telling us!
Huh?
Okay, he needs some company but not the random belly-warmer guy.
What do you mean by that?! I'll cut you, kinky cook!
Company? I'll go with him!
Yeah, sounds like fun.
Hey, maybe we'll pass on this one. Is it okay?
I have no choice.
How about this?
We'll draw straws. No complaints, right?
What a pain! I'll go even if I lose.
Zoro! If I'm picked, go instead of me!
They say "Good luck lies in odd numbers"!
I'll stake all my life on this one!
#%=/+$!!!
All right, his companions are...
Us!
Can't wait!
Can't take it!
You won? How lucky!
I lost!
Please trade!
Here. I made a special Giant Shellfish lunch box.
Can't wait!
Milky Road!
Cool! You created a path of clouds.
We saw the same thing at the Sky Island.
Now you can make it?
Since it's made of clouds, you have to take it while it's stable.
Okay!
All right!
Let's go, recon team! Here we go, Mini-Merry!
Good luck, guys!
You guys are so lucky!
I'm sure we'll have a chance to go later.
--Take care! --Usopp, you can do it!
Please trade!
This Giant Shellfish is yummy!
Are you eating your lunch already?!
Oh, we're going over the flames!
This is fun!
We'll get across the sea of fire.
Are these clouds gonna be here when we come back?
I'm glad that it stopped raining.
--It's a nice day to scout an island! --But it's hot!
Nami-san, do those clouds reach the island?
I don't know.
But even if they don't, Luffy will find a way.
Nami-san's so reckless!
I'm glad that I didn't get picked to go.
I can't stand the heat.
But letting him go by himself wasn't an option.
They'll come back as soon as they find out there's no one.
I didn't know you planned it out so well.
You're so kind, Nami-san!
I'll make you a cold dessert with the Giant Shellfish!
Yeah!
You guys want it too?!
--Yeah! --I want it!
Oh, there is the erupting island!
See? I told you there should be an entrance.
Like I said, maybe somebody was living here in the past
but no one can live here now!
The emergency signal earlier must have come from somewhere far!
Right, Robin?!
It didn't look good but I like the taste.
You two are eating lunch too?
You're not gonna eat yours?
I don't feel like it now!
--Luffy, do you want this one? --Yeah!
Here.
He's an excellent cook!
Sanji-kun outdid himself again!
I can't believe it!
The disorder I had 2 years ago is recurring!
Hey guys, the truth is, I have a Fear-of-unknown-islands-osis.
I know.
Oh, I got a headache all of a sudden!
I feel a tightness in my chest too!
I have a stomachache!
It's hot!
This is the place.
Punk Hazard, Entrance
The name matches.
So this is Punk Hazard...
Let's beach the Merry!
Do you think the emergency signal came from inside?
Seems like no one's allowed to enter this island.
Oh, Luffy, look at that!
"Danger" "Keep out"?
There are marks of the World Government and the Navy!
That means even if somebody's here, he belongs to the Government.
What a wasted trip! Let's go back!
H-Hey, Zoro, what are you doing?
Don't tell me...
Good, it's open.
Open...
Too hot!
You guys! Trespassing is a crime!
But we pirates are criminals anyway.
Keep me out of it!
Do you wanna challenge the Government?!
Oh, we already did!
Oh, hey, wait!
It's too hot, really.
Everything is on fire.
But it doesn't seem like the island has been burning forever.
So was there a disaster? Or an accident?
Wait... Luffy!
That was close!
Hey, Luffy!
Those were probably not people's houses.
I think there were some kind of Government facilities here.
They shut this island down because it started
burning and became dangerous?
Or these facilities were hazardous from the beginning?
The fact that the Log Pose didn't point to this island troubles me.
Hey!
The guy from earlier - are you there?!
We're here to help you!
Hey! Come out!
Samurai!
Don't call them! They're murderers!
--Now you have an appetite? --It's stress eating!
You know I've been thinking.
The man on the Snail said "It's cold," didn't he?
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
You're right.
It's really hot here but he said it was cold.
Maybe he's stupid.
No way, Sherlock!
Is there a cold place on this burning island?
Or that he had a chilling experience?
Robin, you're scaring me!
What is it? What is it?
What is that noise?!
Oh, that's...
It's yummy, Sanji!
I thought I was gonna melt in the heat.
It's cooling me down!
Ow, I feel a sharp pain!
Are my teeth sensitive?
You guys only get to eat it because there are leftovers.
Thank Nami-san!
Oh, there are a lot for you, Nami-san!
Nami, what's the matter?
Yeah, the clouds...
I just noticed there's something strange about the sky above the island.
The far side looks like the Arctic sky.
No way!
A Giant?!
No,
it's bigger than a Giant!
So it was the noise of the wind.
What's wrong, Luffy?
Is that...
What?!
Huh? Does it actually exist?!
No, it's a mythical creature!
There's no way that it's real!
But look at those features...
I don't think it could be anything else!
A dragon?!
A legendary creature has suddenly appeared. A dragon!
It breathes fire and has razor-sharp fangs.
It's amazing destructive power
proves difficul for even Luffy and Zoro to handle.
Then, the dragon says something
which is even more shocking!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Heated Battle!
Luffy vs. the Giant Dragon!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Heated Battle!
Luffy vs. the Giant Dragon!