Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
rashinban nante jyuutai no moto
compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
delirious with fever, i take the helm
hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
if the dusty treasure map has been verified,
tashikameta no nara densetsu janai
it's not a legend!
kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
when it comes to personal storms,
biorizumu nokkatte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
omoi sugoseba ii
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
poketto no koin
a coin in my pocket,
soreto You Wanna Be My Friend
and do you wanna be my friend?
We Are
we are!
Luffy...
Help me...
Don't make our navigator cry!
Gum-Gum...
...Pinwheel!!
What the... What the...
People with Devil Fruit powers can't swim.
Though, even people without
powers would sink in this situation.
He's gonna throw him into the sea?!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Darn you!
Luffy!!
Damn you!
This is bad... I'm out of strength...
Luffy Submerged!
Zoro vs. Hatchan the Octopus
What do you think?
Isn't this a pretty fun game?
How many minutes will that rubber man last?
Or will you guys die before that?
This isn't good, Johnny.
Big Bro Luffy is in big trouble...
He can't help himself now!
We'll defeat him in five seconds.
Luffy! I'll come rescue you right away!
Hachi Ink Jet!
My hair! You bastard! I'm gonna...
...forgive you since it's just hair
and it's gonna grow back.
Huh?
Roronoa Zoro!
You can't cut me because I have six hands.
Go ahead and cut me if you can!
You Octo-Man!
Hachi's... Triple... Sword... Catch!
Ouch!
I don't have time to play with you!
He throws me out of whack!
Could he possibly...
If you're not paying attention,
you'll shorten your life!
Fish shouldn't go against a cook!
We're running out of time... No time...
Go down already!
Hachi Suckers!
So what?! Come down already!
You damn octopus!
That octopus bastard!
He's moving wobbly and slowly!
But then, if he goes into the sea now,
he'll be dragged to the bottom of the sea.
But at this rate, Big Bro Luffy's going to die!
We have to do something about it!
Yeah!
Wait!
Ouch!!
What're you going to do in
the sea with such serious injuries?
You can't do much like that.
If you're talking about that rubber
young man, I'll go and rescue him.
Y-You will?
Whether we can save that young man or not
is probably what will decide this fight, right?
I can tell that, too.
Gen-san!
I'll go, too!
Me, too!
No! If many of us go and take time rescuing him,
the Fishmen will notice and it will
cause these people trouble, if anything.
Gen-san!
It'll be pointless if we end up
putting a crimp in their fight.
So I'll do it alone.
That's okay with you two, right?
Sorry... Thank you!
I'll leave it to you.
Sorry, but please be quick.
Wait!
Gen-san, I'll go, too.
Nojiko, you're injured!
Those guys're fighting for my little sister!
Gen-san!
Okay. Come with me.
Let's hurry!
Okay!
I'm sorry...
If only we were a little stronger...
Please save... Big Bro...
You damn fish man!
Roronoa Zoro! Do you mind if I ask
you a question? You don't, right?
I heard you use the Three Swords Style.
Why are you using only one sword?
You're already losing big with one sword!
Sh-Shut up! I'm not fighting seriously!
Actually, there's a reason that
a human swordsman can't defeat me.
Wanna hear what it is?
You wanna hear it, right?
When you hear it, you'll be
surprised, scared, blown away!
Dammit! I can't be in pain right now!
My fever's getting worse, too!
I thought it would come down
while I was moving around, but...
Just as I thought, the wounds...
...from your fight with Hawk-Eye are...
Big Bro!
What're you doing?
Are you trying to fake illness or something?
I won't fall for that. Roronoa Zoro!
Just check out my true form!
Look! This is my true form!
Here comes Hachi,
user of the Six-Sword Style!
Hey! That's not where you're
supposed to fall! Don't mock me!
– Ah! Big Bro!
– So he was bearing the pain!
Yeah.
His injuries would kill a normal person
or leave them bedridden for half a year!
What?!
I thought something was strange.
He looked as if nothing had
happened right after that fierce fight.
Is he an idiot or what?!
I thought I warned you to pay attention.
I have a fortieth dan in Fishman Karate.
Wh-What? Someone went flying?!
B-Big Bro?!
Big Bro Cook!
Ahh...
Big Bro Cook!!
He's been taken care of, Arlong-san.
What do we do with Roronoa Zoro?
Just ditch him in the sea.
What weaklings... How boring!
That's all?
Geez, they sure did a lot of damage, though.
It's no big deal.
Arlong Park can't be destroyed
by this kind of damage.
Indeed...
How dare you, Roronoa Zoro!
You died from shock before I,
the great swordsman, could attack you?!
You could have left your name
in history if you died at least
after receiving my Six-Sword Style attack.
Well, no matter how you struggle or
even if the world is turned upside down,
you humans can't even give a
scratch to me, wielder of six swords!
Stop it, Hachi. I know how you feel,
but if you really go on a
rampage we'll be in trouble.
Are you going to destroy Arlong Park?
Oh! Ahh...
N-No... Sorry.
I got too worked up...
Don't get carried away.
You're right. Sorry.
The Six-Sword Style, huh?
What a joke!
Big Bro!!
Roronoa Zoro!
I'll tell you one thing, octopus.
There's a man I need to meet up with.
Until I see him again...
...my life can't be taken away
even by Death himself!
Damn that Long-nose! What speed!
That guy's face and ability
to run away aren't human!
If I keep one of the Arlong Pirates
leaders away like this,
it should be beneficial to
Luffy and the other's fights.
Good job, Usopp-sama!
How considerate you are towards them!
Though it just happened to turn out that way...
Whoa, as I expected, he isn't catching up.
Darn. This isn't good.
Looks like I've got quite a lead.
Fishmen are just turtles on land, after all.
He's far behind in no time.
Turtles... huh?
Hey! Hey! Turtle! You slow turtle!
Keep up with me if you can!
I'll outrun you again right away!
You waddling turtle!
Aren't you the one who'll have to waddle?
Ughhhhh!
Stop, you bastard!
He drank quite a bit of water.
We need to bring him up soon or it'll be too late.
Dammit!
I guess I can't break it in the sea.
The buoyancy is too strong.
Gen-san, hurry up.
No good. I can't smash the rock.
An oxygen cylinder would be helpful
but we don't have time to go get it.
And we can't carry him up
along with the rock, either...
Oh, yeah!
Hm? Ahh!
That man's still alive!!
Big Bro! Big Bro Cook!!
That Fishman's punch was
a fortieth dan punch? I see...
Then those kicks I used to take all
the time from that damn geezer
are four-hundredth dan kicks.
What is it, Roronoa Zoro?
I'm not sure what's going on,
but you look like you're in pain.
You think you can defeat my
Six-Sword Style in that condition?
Everyone in the whole world
thinks the same way.
That's none of your business.
Big Bro's in really bad shape!
He's probably got a fever from his wounds
and must be barely conscious.
If those wounds open up,
he's definitely going to die!
But it's no time to think about things like that!
Yeah! He's the only one who can
break through this situation!
I'll show you the Three Swords Style.
Yosaku! Johnny!
Let me use your swords!
Of course!
Big Bro! Catch these!!
Darn!
I feel like I'm about to pass out.
I wonder how long I can keep standing...
Big Bro! We threw our swords!
You said you wanted to use them!
Catch them!
Ha! I'll show you the wall that you
humans with two arms can't surpass!
Six-Sword Style:
Big Bro! Watch out!!
Tentacle-Sword Overload!
Big Bro!!
Three-Sword Style:
Streaming Wolf-Swords!
He did it!
He handled the six-sword random hits!
He's really amazing!!
What concentration!
What spiritual strength!
Ahh... How dare you have the impudence to do such a thing!
I'm really mad, you son of a bitch!
I'm gonna kill you!
If you just think about it, you should know!
I can hold six swords, so there's
no way you can defeat me
when you can hold only three swords!
Isn't that right?!
Just think about it?
What a big miscalculation.
What do you bear on your shoulders?
What do you desire once you've obtained power?
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
I'm going to get strong enough
that my name reaches to Heaven!
I'm going to be the world's strongest swordsman!
Whether it's three swords... or six swords...
...it doesn't matter!
Your sword and my sword carry different weight!
Weight, you said?
I see. So your swords are heavy.
But my swords weigh at
least 300 kilos per sword
though they may not look like it.
They weigh a lot more than you
humans' swords, you bastard!
There's no point in discussing with an idiot.
Six-Swords Style:
Octopus Pot Stance!
New Year's...
...Open!
Body Slam!
That's dirty!
He hit him right in his wounds!
That'll show you!
Big Bro!!
He's gonna die!!
I won't let you land while you're still alive!
Six-Sword Style Secret Art:
Waltz of Six Swords!
You'll be mincemeat if you touch it
even for a second! Become mincemeat!
Big Bro!!
What?!
Ow!
Big Bro!!
That bastard!
He rolled on my swords adjusting to the spin!
On top of that, he gave me
a free hand cutting service!
How dare he make fun of me!
I'm not a circus acrobat!
I'm completely angry now!
I won't let him get away!
I'm gonna really kill him good!
Big Bro... he looks like he's in a lot of pain...
His wounds might've opened with that attack.
Ahh... If I could, I'd wanna
take his place for him...
Even if it's an injury that knocks
ordinary people out, I must not fall.
Six-Sword Style:
Octopus Pot Stance!
It's all over!
Even if it's an injury that kills
ordinary people, I must not die!
New Year's...
In order to defeat the
extraordinarily strong Hawk-Eye,
I can't just be ordinary!
Dragon Twister!!
Hachi...
How could I be... defeated by...
the Three Swords Style?
Octo-Man...
You now know the difference between
the weight in our swords, right?
Are you happy now?
I cried as much as I wanted.
I've whined enough, too.
And I'm resolved as well!
I have to go. Everyone's fighting!
Sorry, but I don't care about that Octo-Man.
I have to hurry up and rescue Luffy...
Big Bro! Watch out!!
How dare you beat Hachi!
You...
You sure did send me flying!
Oh? I didn't know there was someone
in the East Blue who could survive my fist.
There're probably many...
especially at a certain restaurant.
You sure take me lightly, don't you?
B-Big Bro! That's reckless!
Hey, stop it!
You'll die if you go into the
sea with wounds like that!
Shut up! He's at his limit!
There's no time to wait until your fight is over!
Yeah, I know.
There's no time to waste any more.
I know that much.
I'm trying to stop you when
I'm fully aware of that!
You just shut up, you damn idiot!
You can't complain if I do this, right?!
This is interesting!
He wants to fight against me,
a Fishman, in the water?
He's a real idiot!
That's reckless!
Fighting in the water is what they want!
If I remember correctly,
he's from Cocoyashi Village...
His neck! Luffy's neck is stretched!
Sorry, I'm not strong enough
to pull the whole body.
Spit out water with your neck stretched.
Please at least breathe!
Come back to life!
I hope it's not too late!
I'd better hurry up before
I can't hold my breath any more.
I see... He can't break the rock,
but if Luffy's neck is stretched above
the water, he can at least breathe.
Which means if I kick and break that rock,
I can leave the rest to that man.
Fishman Karate... Forearm Sledge!
Realize... that you all are mere humans!
Come back to life!
Please... hurry!
This guy's persistent! Ughhh!
hamidashita kimochi tsunagara nakute
my overflowing feelings don't connect
kimi no te o gyutto ni girikaesu yo
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
hitori demo boku wa arukidasu kara
I'll set off by myself,
tooku made zutto mitsumeteite ne
so keep watching me intently as I go into the distance
kesa kara chotto kangaeteita
I was thinking about it a bit since this morning
doushite konna ni atsui no
why is it so hot?
itsu kara ka sonna koto bakari ga
starting from some point,
hanarenai yo
I haven't been able to get away from that
kakedashita kimochi tsukamaetakute
I want to catch those feelings that rushed off,
jibun sae mou oikoshite yuku yo
and I'm already about to overtake myself, even
tobidashita yume o dakishimetetai
I want to embrace my dreams that have jumped out
issho nara boku wa hashitte yukeru
with you, I can run there
Ughhh!
Dammit! That topknot bastard!
He's attacking me from behind!
This isn't good!
But in order to rescue Luffy...
Even if I'm at a disadvantage,
I'll beat him up for sure!
It's all for Nami-san.
So that's what you're thinking after all!
Waaaah!!
Shut up!!
Next time, on One Piece:
Proud Warriors!
Sanji and Usopp's Fierce Battles
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Proud Warriors!
Sanji and Usopp's
Fierce Battles