Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue his brother,
Ace, who was to be executed!
However, Ace protected Luffy from Red Hound's
attack and lost his life in the process!
And then, Blackbeard turned up
and brought further turmoil!
This is...!
That pose is...!
The Insatiable Red Hound!
Lava Fists Pummel Luffy
The HQ building is gonna fall!
Leave your post!
We're dead!
Is this for real?
Somebody please tell me I'm dreaming!
For centuries we've kept watch
over the seas from here!
I can't believe the fort of justice the Navy's citadel...
...is crumbling before my eyes!
Blackbeard, the one who caught Ace
and caused this war,
now has Whitebeard's power!
Look, all you people of the world!
Behold me and my power!
What's gonna happen to this world?!
I can feel the power coursing through my body!
Dammit!
What power! It feels like the entire world
is in the palm of my hand!
Bastard!
Hey, what's wrong?!
What are you waiting for? Doesn't anyone wanna fight?
I'm willing to fight you
to your hearts' content now! What a shame!
I have no choice.
Then, let's start with...
...sinking Marineford into the water!
What did he say?!
Shock Wave!
A building can easily be rebuilt!
But the island of Marineford
is the hub of the world!
Fleet Admiral!
To all the citizens of the world,
who fear the villains that roam the seas,
it is important that we are here!
Justice and righteousness will never perish!
Don't you dare speak lightly of sinking this island,
you little punk!
Such noble beliefs! Huh? Fleet Admiral-san!
Well, then:
defend this place—if you can!
Damn!
Hurry up and get the ship to shore!
We can't leave anyone behind!
Wait for us! We're coming now!
We gotta get out of here alive!
Hurry up, everybody!
The Navy's victory must be absolute!
We gotta survive and leave here as Pops told us to!
Let the pirates know
the power of justice through fear!
Justice...
...Through fear...
We're almost there!
That's right! Now is the chance
to let villains all over the world know!
Our power that will...!
...save the world!
We're safe now!
The power of justice!
Y-Yellow Monkey!
Now is your chance!
Take Straw-boy!
Thank you!
Inazuma!
You better stop, Jinbe!
You pest!
Let's finish this up!
I won't let you go any further!
New Kama Kenpo, 44 Aesthetic Arts:
Laser Surgery Fist!
My nails melted!
Emporio Ivankov of the Revolutionary Army!
You use some strange techniques,
as the rumors say!
New Kama Kenpo, 44 Aesthetic Arts:
Fat Suctioning Fist!
I like it hot!
I have no time to play with you guys!
Ouch!
I burned my lips, my lips, my lips...
...or not! Because of my over-applied make-up!
Ouch!
I-Iva-sama!
You bastards!
Don't let them get away! Shoot!
Isn't this too one-sided?
The winner has already been decided...
Is this really necessary?
Crush them! Completely and utterly!
Don't ever let them even think of challenging us!
What's going on?
We'll let them know...!
...The power of our justice!
Destroy them!
Destroy them!!
What is this?!
Red Hound!
Jinbe! Hand Dragon's son over to me!
I'll have an advantage once we get
to the sea! I can outrun him!
Oh no! It's frozen!
Blue Pheasant!
He's coming!
Looks like you've got nowhere to run!
It's no good!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I've got you!
Jinbe!
It went right through Jinbe and reached Ace's brother!
Are they still alive?!
I can't let him get hurt anymore!
You're in my way, Jinbe!
Luffy-kun, I'm sorry! I couldn't save you!
Fool! You should be worrying about yourself right now!
My aim was a little off because you were in the way.
If it hit his heart, it would've been easier for him.
Don't you think so, Jinbe?
Are you gonna keep protecting him
with that hole in his chest?
He's gonna die soon!
Jinbe, if I don't escape death...
I'm sorry but could you look after my brother?
I'm not helping him because he is your brother!
I think highly of Luffy-kun!
I've already made up my mind
to save his life even if it means my death!
I won't let him die!
Even if I die,
I won't let Luffy-kun die!
That's nonsense!
Crocodile!
Sables!
Somebody, catch them and put them on a ship!
Okay!
Crocodile!
You gotta protect the one you wanna protect!
Don't let them have their way!
Catch them!
It's over!
I'm sorry that I got carried away, everyone.
This is the end of Captain Buggy's legend.
Thank you for your support this whole time!
Jinbe!
They're not coming down...
What's going on?!
Captain Buggy!
He helped Straw Hat and Jinbe!
Just as I thought!
Huh?
Captain Buggy, you made us
believe you were gonna run
but you helped your fellow escapee, Straw Hat, when it counted!
How noble!
Your nobility is blinding!
They're being weird again!
Jinbe and Straw Hat!
How did you end up in the sky, covered in blood?!
Anyway, why is it so hot here...?
M-Magma!
Thank you, red-nosed man! You helped us!
I don't know what's going on
and I'm not helping you!
But I allowed Luffy-kun to get injured!
He needs to be treated immediately!
Shut up! I'm the one who needs help, fool!
How could we get him treated here...
Did you call me "red-nosed man"?!
They keep getting in my way
the moment I'm about to get him!
Rose Rondo!
You're fools, one and all!
Do you wanna die just to save that Straw Hat brat?
We all witnessed
his boundless determination and power.
Ace protected him and Pops acknowledged him!
Now it's our duty to send him off into the new era!
I thought all of you were smarter than that!
Not that it matters!
Whitebeard Pirates!
Red Hound!
The fear you see in that boy—
that makes you wanna kill him.
The potential we see in him—
that makes us wanna protect him.
They're the same, don't you think?
You guys got me involved again!
Are you even listening?!
H-Hey, Jinbe?
Don't tell me that you're unconscious! Where should I go now?!
Hey!
Whether he lives or dies,
it'll be like he's in hell regardless.
Might as well make him suffer while he lives!
Discussion is pointless, I suppose.
So be it!
W-We're dead!
It's Sengoku vs. Blackbeard over there.
And it's Red Hound vs. the commanders over here!
The fighting hasn't stopped!
Captain Buggy! Do something!
Damn it all, fools!
Give me a break... Honestly!
Captain, we've reached
a point where it's not frozen.
Surface.
What is that?! A ship came out of the water!
That's a submarine!
Is it another enemy?
Whose ship is that?
Put Straw Hatter on my ship!
"Straw Hatter"?
That sure is a strange way to call somebody!
Who the hell are you, brat?!
Straw Hatter and I
may become enemies in the future
but I have nothing against him.
There's no point in letting him die here.
Heart Pirates Captain
Trafalgar Law
I'll help him escape!
Leave him to me!
W-What?!
I'm a doctor!
The Navy's relentless pursuit continues.
As the meaningless battle rages on endlessly,
one young man stands
lost in grief on the battlefield.
That sadness gives birth
to a great power called courage,
setting the very world in motion!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Desperate Scream
The Fateful Moment of Courage"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Desperate Scream
The Fateful Moment of Courage