Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After receiving an emergency signal, they landed on Punk Hazard Island.
It was a strange island divided
into two parts; the Burning Lands and the Ice Lands.
To rescue Nami and the others who are held captive,
Luffy's group headed to the Ice Lands.
But they were unaware that some
former acquaintances were also on the island.
What brought you here - to my vacation home?
Asher!
"The Warlord! Trafalgar Law!"
Trafalgar! I know you're a Warlord but we need you to ask you to step aside.
Move out of the way!
We know somebody else is here on the island!
INSIDE OF DR. VEGAPUNK'S FORMER LABORATORY NAMI'S GROUP
Dad! Mom!
Hey, you said "We are not sick anymore" earlier, didn't you?
Uh-huh.
What kind of sickness did you have?
None of you look sick to me.
I don't know. But they told us that we were sick
and we'd get better in a year.
Get better in a year?
Uh-huh.
And people who were asked
to treat me by my dad and mom took me to this place.
That means your parents sent you to this place?
Not really, those people told me that out of the blue in
front of my house and took me here.
They said they didn't want my dad and mom to get infected.
So I couldn't even say goodbye.
That's what happened to you all?
--Un-huh. --Me too.
No way! It seems they were kidnapped!
Some strangers took them here
without letting them see their parents?
That could only mean...
...you're really very sick!
What are you, stupid?!
Are you all doing okay?
If any of you can't run, I'll carry you on my back.
They all look fine.
Yes, we are! The Master has been treating us.
The Master?
Uh-huh, the Master.
Master!
--Master! --Master!
But it's been over a year, hasn't it?
Chopper, why don't you examine them later?
Yeah, okay.
Oh no! This door is locked! We have nowhere to go!
What?
--They are coming! --What are you gonna do?
I have to hurry!
Nami, step aside!
One more! Hi-ya!
It's open. Wachaa.
--So strong! --You became very powerful!
That was cool, Raccoon Dog-chan!
No, I'm not a raccoon dog!
But you look like one now.
I guess you're right!
Let's go, kids!
It's freezing! Chopper, can I borrow your fur?
Oh, sure.
I mean, no way!
What is this place?
Is it outside? Or is it a freezer?!
It's too dark. I can barely see anything.
It's perfect for me!
Yeah, but you're from a Winter Island.
Isn't this a path? It's too dark and I can't...
Oh, I see it! There's a door!
Oh yeah!
Let's go! It's not a dead end!
Okay!
Sis! I don't like this place! I'm scared!
What?
--What's wrong, kids? --Let's go! They're coming!
When I first got here, I walked through this place!
Are you sure?!
That means it'll lead us to the exit!
It's really cold but hang on! Let's go!
No!
I mean...
When you look around...
Around?
There is something in the wall...
This path scares me because there are frozen people all around!
Huh?! What's going on here?!
Dead bodies in ice?!
There are more up there!
Down there, too!
N-N...
No!!
No, Sis, wait! Don't leave us!
Okay, I think I'm done.
INSIDE OF THE LABORATORY - BISCUIT ROOM SANJI'S GROUP
Hey, you blocked their path already.
That should be enough!
Let's go! I just felt Nami-san's inner scream!
Maybe she wants to tell me that she loves me!
By the way, what are those people?
They're half sheep.
I think there was a mythical creature like this.
Don't bother to think about them now.
We have to get the whole picture first.
Let's go save Nami-san now!
Wait! Leave me here! I want to stay here!
My boy was not among those children.
There must be other rooms so I'll stay and...
You can't even move on your own!
If we leave you here, we would feel like we're abandoning you!
And that's not a great feeling!
But I'm here to rescue my boy!
Don't irritate me!
Why don't you just ask me to find your body?!
Where is it?!
I don't wanna owe anything to pirates!
I wouldn't ask you even if it kills me!
H-However, if you want to look for my body...
I won't stop you.
You're just a severed-head! Don't be so arrogant!
Are you gonna use violence against me?!
I have no regrets!
I'm not gonna beg a thug for my life!
Hey, stop.
You're not gonna feel better by smashing a helpless severed-head.
When you took him out of the room, you already gave in to him, Sanji!
But...!
He's pissing me off!
I was so stupid to be moved by his determination!
I don't wanna help him!
Now, I'm not even capable of fighting back if someone hits me
so you can carry me if you want to.
Damn! We'll settle this once you get your body back!
You show no mercy even on a severed-head like me.
I better watch my mouth.
I wonder if Nami found the way out!
Let's find them!
I'm really... itchy!
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND - THE MIDDLE LAKE LUFFY'S GROUP
I got you, intruders!
No, he sliced it.
Take a good look.
They're so dull.
Good job, Zoro-kun! I have to compliment you!
Hey, I got Leg-maro too!
--He cut the shell in half?! --Damn samurai!
Don't hesitate! Fire!
We can't clear the air!
They look like they're dumb, so...
We should be friends!
Gum-Gum Leg-maro Balloon!
He's doing something again-bu!
Leg-maro has nothing to do with it!
What?! He repelled them all!
What's wrong with his body?!
He's a Devil Fruit user.
Then I know what to do!
Prepare to fire!
They're gonna shoot again.
They'll never learn. I'll be counting on you guys!
Wait.
They're aiming at the water!
They're gonna try to sink the boat!
What?! We have two Devil Fruit users on board!
Take good aim!
We'll let them fall into the water!
Rot in hell, Devil Fruit users!
Damn!
Fire!
Here they come!
Let's get behind an iceberg!
All right!
That was close.
Why aren't you rowing?
Devil Fruit users can't fight in the water!
Sink to your death, Devil Fruit users!
A SNOW-CAPPED MOUNTAIN NEAR THE LABORATORY BROOK
Gross! So gross!
What's wrong with that ghost?!
Suddenly attacking me!
Why do I have to get attacked?!
He's kind of strong too!
I hear something in the distance.
I don't have ears though.
You are so persistent!
I have no choice! I'll fight you!
I'll forget I saw it.
Oh, I don't have eyes anyway.
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF THE LABORATORY
Hello? My name is Monkey D. Luffy! I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
You picked up too fast and said too much!
Help me!
What happened?
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
No, I'm not the Boss.
My colleagues are getting cut one after another!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
Where are you?!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
...Punk Hazard!
The name of the island and the fact he said "It's cold."
There is almost no doubt that this man sent the signal from this island.
You know Straw Hat Luffy, don't you?
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Repel!
Room.
Shambles.
I've been killed!
When the incident involving the Roswalds,
a Celestial Dragon family, happened on Sabaody 2 years ago,
Kid, Straw Hat and you fought together.
And during the Paramount War...
Put Straw Hatter on my ship!
I'm gonna help him get out of here.
Let me take care of him for now!
When Red Hound was after Straw Hat, you...
...helped him get away!
What do you want?
I know you Navy people are good at forging those emergency signals.
I'm afraid it wasn't a trap that we set.
Oh yeah?
But I don't know anything so there's nothing more to talk about.
Cut that crap.
Let us see inside the laboratory.
It's my vacation home now. I refuse!
What's wrong with me - a pirate staying on an island you people abandoned?
I'm the only one here!
If Straw Hat comes, I'll chop his head off for you.
If that's all you have to say, go home!
So scary! Those frozen people!
I've had it with this place!
But look! There's a door! We can get out!
Yeah!
There is somebody else in there!
I made it out!
Outside?! It's freezing!
We made it!
I got out of the building! I can go home!
I can see my dad and mom again!
It's cold!
Get out of my way, kids!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Franky!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Tank!
Clear the way, clear the way, Super the way!
I'll run over you if you stand in my way!
But I avoid running over flowers!
I'm kind of sweet - Franky Tank!
All right! Here we go, everybody!
Yeah!
One, two, three...
Super!
The Straw Hats?! Children?!
I don't know where to begin!
A big raccoon dog, a woman in bikini in the winter, giant kids,
a robot, and a severed-head...
Am I dreaming?!
--Tank treads! --Cool!
--Awesome! --A tank!
The best!
Bad roads won't trouble me!
Nami-san! I'm glad that you're okay!
I like the way you shiver in the cold but I don't want
you to get sick so take my jacket!
Thank you, Sanji-kun!
You look familiar!
Yeah, he was there at Sabaody!
Are you the one who locked up these children?!
You brute! You can't take them back!
Oh, you're...!
I was wondering who this villainous guy was! Smoker!
And you, cutie!
This is not good! The Navy's here!
We can't escape from here! Let's look for another exit!
Get inside!
Hurry up, kids! Go to the back!
There should be a backdoor!
What brought the Navy to such a place?!
I don't know! Just run!
Oh? I thought the Navy were good people.
Why don't you go to them, then?
No, they look like gangsters!
You lied! You weren't the only one here!
Seems like I wasn't. I'm also surprised.
Everybody, let's catch the Straw Hats!
All right, let's go! Follow Captain-chan!
No, wait!
Room.
--Ouch! --Are you alright?
Those fools... They brought trouble!
Takt!
What's making that noise?
No way!
The warship is in the air!
Along with the bottom of the river!
What's going on here?!
I can't let you leave the island now.
I'm sorry that I said no one's here.
I knew he was dangerous!
Step back.
You guys are no match!
He'll chop off your hands and feet!
Go, Smo-yan!
--Kick his ass! --Show him the true power of G-5!
Law's power, capable of lifting even warships...
...overwhelms the Navy's G-5.
Sanji and Nami's group also ends up...
...in an unprecedented situation because of Law.
Meanwhile, Luffy's group comes upon a lake in the frozen lands...
...and encounters a crisis of its own!
Next time, on One Piece:
"In a Real Pinch! Luffy Sinks into the Ice-cold Lake!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!