Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Luffy Gets Angry!
A Dirty Trick Violates
The Sacred Duel!
H-He blocked the blow with his helmet!
If he was off by even an inch,
he would've died instantly!
What a fight...
Each of their attacks is a mortal blow
aimed at the opponent's vital point!
Those two have continued this
duel to the death for 100 years?
But this is good... We can use this
opportunity to get out of here.
Usopp?
Incredible...
Reason?
I don't remember.
Even without a reason,
they're fighting so seriously...
This fight sure is a bother.
You idiot!
This is what people mean
by a real battle between men!
What's that about?
To use an analogy, those two fly
a warrior's flag in their heart.
This flag is even more important than their life.
In no way do they want it
to be destroyed by others.
That's why they've continued to take
on each other for 100 long years!
Do you get it? This is unmistakably
a "proud duel" between "warriors"!
Whatever... Stuff like that doesn't interest me.
Now, hurry up!
I'm gonna watch this a little longer.
This is exactly what my goal is...
To be a "brave warrior of the sea"!
I wanna be a proud man like them!
I see... So you wanna be a Giant.
No!! Were you even listening to me?!
There!
Don't you have to watch them over there?
If there's a village with warriors like them in it,
I wanna go there someday.
I've got a good view from here.
They'll find you, Miss Valentine.
Come down already!
Don't worry, Mr. 5...
After all, they're absorbed in the fight.
They won't notice.
Just come down!
Okay, okay.
Hey, do you really get it?
This is a big job for 200 million Berries.
Of course...
Although I feel reluctant to do as Mr. 3 tells us...
I know... Let's go.
Okay.
We're both getting homesick, aren't we, Dorry?
That's why I'll beat you and go back to Elbaf, Broggy.
73,466 duels...
73,466 draws...
Dorry!
Actually, I got alcohol from my guests.
Great! It's been a while since I had a drink.
Give me some.
What was that?
First a long, strange earthquake,
and now this? What is it this time?
Are there weird creatures other
than dinosaurs in this jungle?
Well, that damn cook is probably the only one
who'd be happy to capture things like that...
Were those bird cries?
Even so, those were vulgar, unappetizing cries.
Although we're competing to capture a
big prey, we're still looking for food.
Not only does it have to be big,
it also has to be tasty.
That guy doesn't get it at all.
I see. His guests are your friends, huh?
I saw a man with a long nose and a woman.
That's Usopp and Nami!
Hah!
They said they wouldn't get off the ship,
but they really do like adventures after all!
Then you could also say that
I got this alcohol from you.
By the way, Dorry-san,
does it really take a year
for the Log to be stored?
Didn't you notice the human skulls lying around?
Those who come to this island die
before the Log is stored in most cases.
Some become dinosaurs' food.
Some suffer from the heat and starvation.
Some others are killed because they attack us. They all die...
It seems that one year on this
island is too long for humans.
What're we gonna do?
Even if we could survive for a year,
if that much time passes, I don't know
what will happen to my country by then.
Yeah.
I'd get bored, too, if we stay here for a year.
Isn't there a good way, old guy?
Hmmm...
We do have an Eternal Pose,
but it's to our hometown, Elbaf.
In other words, we're fighting for this Eternal Pose.
Do you wanna try taking it by force?
That's no good.
That's not where we wanna go.
We just wanna go to the
island after this one. Right?
Yes...
If we lose the route to Alabasta,
there's no point in moving forward.
See?
Then why don't you move forward randomly?
If you're lucky, you'll get there.
Maybe we'll do that!
We may actually get there, huh?
Come to think of it, there was someone
who left before the Log was stored.
What happened to him?
How should I know?
He must've gotten to the next island.
That must be it!
What's so funny?
I can't understand what they're thinking!
A brave warrior of the sea? What's that?
I'm talking about you guys.
I wanna be like you guys someday!
Hm? You mean a Giant?
– See?
– That's not it!
I hope to live proudly just like the warriors of Elbaf!
I see!
Especially since our life span
is longer than you humans',
we think about how we die.
Your assets, life...
Everything will eventually cease to exist.
But if we could die as a warrior of
Elbaf without destroying our pride,
that would be "dying with honor."
That pride is an everlasting treasure
that is passed on in the land of Elbaf.
So pride is your treasure...
That's so cool...
I've just decided... that I'll
call you Master from now on!
Huh?
Giant old guy!
What's going on?!
Why did the alcohol explode?!
That was the alcohol we had on our ship, right?!
It exploded in his stomach!
His opponent must've laid the explosive!
What the hell were you watching?!
They've been fighting for 100 years!
No way they'd do something like this!
Then who on earth...
You bastards did...
It wasn't Broggy.
We're proud warriors of Elbaf.
Who else besides you should I be suspicious of?
Let's get out of here for now!
It's probably no use saying anything to him!
It's probably no use even if we run.
Hold this and stay back.
Don't tell me! Are you going to fight?
I feel bad to do this to the old guy,
but I'll quiet him down.
Both of you, stop! Please!
Dorry-san, please listen!
We really don't know anything about it!
Anything about the alcohol that exploded!
So please don't fight!
You have to stay calm!
Your insides are in bad shape right now!
How dare you... do something so insolent?!
Gum-Gum!
I'm sorry.
Rocket!!
Luffy-san!!
So he has... the powers of a Devil Fruit...
I underestimated... him...
Luffy-san! Are you all right?
How's the old guy?
He's probably okay.
This is actually good.
Otherwise he wouldn't have calmed down.
I'm angry!
What?
Like the old guy said, this alcohol
explosion isn't the act of the other Giant,
and my friends would never
do a stupid thing like this!
Then who on earth...
There's someone else... on this island...
Games are heavily influenced
by people's state of mind.
They are confused right now...
...by the cryptic bomb service
from an invisible enemy...
First, about our first target,
Dorry the Blue Ogre...
I knew it was impossible to finish him,
but the damage he received in his
stomach still must've been quite large.
Now we can drink some tea and
wait for the next duel to start...
So we'll let the other Giant take
care of the injured Giant, huh?
That's right.
That's quite a roundabout way of doing things.
The Warrior species is the
same as wild boars, after all.
We don't have to fight seriously when
they're only good at going head-on
since even if we can't win power-wise,
we have brains that can make up for it.
Geez... Get it yourself, Miss Golden Week.
By the way, what're we going
to do with the Straw Hat gang?
Straw Hat? Oh yeah, the small fries
that found out the Boss's secret...
Well, we can just lure them out one by
one starting with whoever's convenient
to my "service set"...
My motto is "big crimes via cheap tricks."
There're many ways to defeat
enemies without actually fighting.
Mr. 3, refill please.
Hey, me too.
You guys! Take time to savor it!
Ah!
That mountain is... if I'm not mistaken...
This isn't good.
I'm running out of time...
Ah... Sorry.
Ahh! Let it go! I said sorry! Hey!
I don't have time to mess around!
Let it go!
The time-out signal has rung.
Having no prey isn't even funny... Damn...
There's the signal...
It's quite active today.
You're going?!
Your wounds from that last battle still haven't...
It's nothing!
We're both in the same condition!
Making excuses during a merciless
fight to the death would spoil my name!
Hey! Wait, old guy!
Don't go!
You can't go, Dorry-san!
You need to keep still!
You'll die if you push yourself too hard!
I, Warrior Dorry, am here...
At the very least...
...I will fight to uphold the name of Elbaf!
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Ah yasashi uta nee
Ah, gentle song
Todoke futari no tame ni
Make it there for us
Nami ga saratta chisana suna no oshiro
After a wave washed away that little sand castle
nagareru kumo o miagete naki souna egao
You looked up at the passing clouds with a sad smile
Moshi mo sekai juu ni teki shika inai nara
If you find the world is full of enemies,
senaka o makasete
I've got your back
Shinjiru kimochi o wasurenaide
Don't lose faith
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Ah itoshii hito nee
Ah, my love
Zutto daiteite ageru
I'll hold you in my arms forever
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Damn. I'm lost.
Nami has disappeared!
What am I gonna do?!
Huh, Luffy?
A duel that's been interfered
with isn't a duel anymore!
Who is it?! Who's doing this?!
Show yourself!
Hey, who are they?
Baroque Works!
So you're the ones...
How dare you violate the proud battle?!
You won't get away with it!
Next time, on One Piece:
Broggy's Bitter Tears Of Victory!
The Conclusion Of Elbaf
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Broggy's Bitter
Tears Of Victory!
The Conclusion Of Elbaf