Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue his brother, Ace, who will be executed!
Luffy and the others are fighting hard
to get to the scaffold
but the Navy has activated the barricades
leaving the pirates no way out!
Hey, what's wrong?! It should be fully activated!
I-I'm afraid that the wall
can't lift the giant body of Oars!
It seems like his blood
is running down in the system
and making it less powerful!
Oars! Y-You're...
We can't close it but...
...do it, Red Hound!
Execution Order Issued
Break Through the Barricades!
Why did it black out?!
Let us see the war!
Hurry and fix it!
They're having trouble with the Video Transponder Snail!
There's nothing we can do!
Is it true that the Navy
and Whitebeard had a secret deal?!
Do something!
Did Whitebeard sell out his allies?!
What's gonna happen to the war?!
What's gonna happen to the world?!
How ridiculous the Navy is!
This means it was just a sideshow up until now?
We came back just to see the war!
I can't believe there's trouble with the snail!
So you're buying into that?
You aren't?
You guys are such fools!
They're not showing it because there're things...
...that they don't want us or the world to see.
Captain Bonney...
Shut up! Just leave me alone!
"Whitebeard sold out his allies?"
That's crap!
He wouldn't do that. That's why he's a living legend!
Let's set sail, Bepo!
Aye-aye, Captain!
Come with us, Jean Bart!
That's right, Head Office!
And there's no chance of recovering the signal!
So I don't know what's going on at Marineford now!
Meteor Volcano!
They can't get away!
Melt the ice that they're standing on!
The ice is melting!
Th-This water is...
Ouch, it's hot!
The seawater's boiling because of the lava!
Get on the ice!
Hey, look!
They're blocking this side!
Can't we break this wall?!
Whitebeard!
Pops' blow didn't work! It's no ordinary wall!
Alright, let's finish this up!
The lava hit the back of the Moby Dick!
Put out the fire!
Hurry up, everybody!
Do whatever it takes!
Don't let it sink!
We were looking forward to sailing the world with Ace again on that ship!
Whitebeard! Your days are over!
The Moby Dick is...
Damn the Navy!
The ship of our glory!
Damn! Our ship!
They sank the ship that carried the Whitebeards for years!
I'm sorry...
We're running out of ways to get to the plaza!
What's going on inside the walls?!
You know it even if you can't see it!
They can't advance or back up
and keep being pounded.
These barricades are nothing
but the casket of the Whitebeard Pirates!
The casket...
The plan is going well!
Now let's move on to...
...the execution of Portgas D. Ace...
...immediately!
At a place we can't even see...
We won't let them kill Ace!
Yes! There is still a way!
Just one!
The way that Oars made!
We'll be sitting ducks if we go that way!
The Navy is expecting us to go there for sure!
There's no time to argue!
He's right! That's the only way to save Ace...
Ace!
Straw Hat...
We're coming too!
They shouldn't take such an obvious route!
Not yet! Let them approach as close as possible!
Fire!
Of course they're going to defend the only way out!
It's more like a trap!
Fire!
Ace!
We're finishing them off little by little!
Ace...
Ace!!
Fire!
Straw-boy!
Luffy-kun!
Luffy!!
Shoot everyone who came over Oars!
I'm gonna save you even if it means my death!
Proceed with the execution.
Ace... -kun!
Little Oars Jr.! He's still alive?!
Ace-kun!
Oars...!
I protect Ace-kun!
Oars!!
Oars!
Oars is alive!
Captain!
What guy!
Oars...
Captain Squard!
Captain... Squard!
You all...
Alright!
Are you okay, Luffy-kun?!
Honestly! You're too reckless!
Get ready to shoot!
Fire!
Oars!
They'll beat Oars again!
We gotta do something! We gotta hurry!
They'll execute Ace!
Yes, we have to stop them!
Jinbe!
I need you to do me a favor!
Ace-kun!
How tough!
He's barely alive! Keep shooting!
Oh, okay. Let me do it!
Yellow Monkey-san!
We have to finish the execution already!
I better take out his head at a time like this!
Oars!
Captain Oars!
Oars!!
It's over!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Lu...!
Luffy!!
Oh no! You finally made it!
You're standing tall, Dragon's son!
It scares me! His youthfulness!
The guy who jumped
over the wall was Ace's brother!
That brat!
I praise you just for your tenacity.
But you're not good enough to reach this stage yet.
What makes you think that you can beat us?
I'm gonna get Ace back!!
He's so reckless just like his brother!
Oars, stay there!
I need your power!
Pops!
Jozu, the trump card!
Okay!
Everyone, get ready!
We're gonna charge into the plaza!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp Gatling!
Luffy finally leads the charge into the plaza.
But the three admirals
form a heavy wall in front of him,
repelling his advance.
Meanwhile, in the bay,
Whitebeard prepares to deal his final trump card
to change the course of the battle!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Moving into the Final Phase! Whitebeard's Trump Card for Recovery"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Moving into the Final Phase!
Whitebeard's Trump Card for Recovery