It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement—there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail—let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag—together, we're one
One Piece
All right! All right!
There's nothing at all!
That ain't a giraffe...
It's got a long neck,
but it's a horse. A long-horse...
Gum-Gum Whip!
What's going on?!
Actually...
...I cut a bamboo tree and a spirit appeared!
What are they planning?!
We are the Foxy Pirates!
Don't be hasty! All we want... is a showdown!
A Davy Back
with the Foxy Pirates!
Come to my house! I'm in your debt!
Let me offer you some hospitality!
--All right! Food!
--Yeah!
It's good to see my house again!
It's custom in this village to treat
visitors to milk from our farm animals.
Village? Where's the village?
And your farm animals...
What do you mean "where"?
The village is gone! And the farm animals!
Get real. Villages don't just
disappear in ten years, you know.
Oh, actually...
Well, I can explain it later.
For now, let me treat you.
I believe I had some milk stored away...
Stored away? You realize you were
on those stilts for ten years, right?
Hopefully this cheese is to your liking...
Don't look away! That's obviously
your ten-year-old milk!
I see. That's a shame.
Please make yourselves at home then.
Huh? This cheese is edible, old guy?
Don't even try!
It's okay! It's only ten-year-old cheese!
Unlike you folks, I live a
laid-back life on this island.
It's made my stomach different from yours.
Honestly, now. Whippersnappers
these days are so frail...
Call... a doctor...
I told you so, you idiot!
Doctor! Doctor!
Th-That's me!
It's food poisoning.
Obviously!
You're funny, old guy!
You're nomads?
Yes. We're carefree nomads,
always on the move.
So that's how your village
disappeared after only ten years...
This is the island of
Long Ring Long Land. Welcome.
Thanks.
It's technically a single ring-shaped island,
but because of the sea, it's usually
divided into ten separate islands.
But on one day a year,
the tide gets especially low,
and for those few hours, the island
regains its true, singular form.
We use this fact to migrate from one
island to the next every three years.
So you got left behind
after the village moved?
I like you, old guy! You're a big dummy!
If they stay on each island for three years,
then it'd take 'em thirty years
to come all the way back here.
Taking away the time you
were stuck on those stilts,
you won't see them again
for about twenty more years...
Pretty much.
If I only I had a hooorse.
I could catch up to the others in five years
by crossing to a new
island once every year...
"Hooorse"?
Yes. The most beautiful
animals on these islands.
They gallop through the
grassy plains so gracefully...
They're absolutely necessary
to migrate from island to island.
They're strong and can carry large loads.
I can't migrate on foot, either--
the tide would come back in before
I even got across to the next island.
Can't you just take a ship?
We don't know how to sail.
Besides, even if we charged a Log Pose here,
it wouldn't point to the
next island in the ring.
All ten islands are actually
one big island, after all.
I'll just wait here twenty years.
You sure? It'll be lonely...
Oh, wait!
Is a "hooorse" a "horse"?
Oh, right! A horse! We saw one!
Oh! Shelly! You waited for me?!
Oh, Shelly! You're so adorable!
This sure brings back memories!
You've grown so long since I last saw you!
That's a good girl!
You must've been so lonely,
all by yourself all those years!
Thank you! Thank you!
I'll never leave you again!
She wants you to ride on her!
Ah, so that horse was waiting
for him the entire time...
She's great!
She must really like him a lot!
Man, that horse sure is
fast! I wanna ride too!
She really is graceful!
Shelly. Let's cross the sea
together on the next low tide day!
All those days with rain...
All those days with snow...
Thank you for waiting through it all!
Shelly... Do you really insist
on waiting for Tonjit-san?
We're going to take all
your friends with us...
Wait! Littonto!
Are you sure?
We won't be back here for 27 years,
and we have no idea where Tonjit-san even is.
You'll be all by yourself!
Take my advice, come with us!
I'm gonna stay too! I'm gonna
wait for Grandpa with Shelly!
No, you're not! You can't
stay here all alone!
I can too!
Grandpa's here! I know it!
I'm gonna wait for him too!
Live well, Shelly!
Shelly!
Whoa there, Shelly!
You know I'm afraid of heights!
Horse!
Old guy!
Shelly!
--You okay?!
--We heard a gunshot!
What's this net?!
--Just a sec!
--Old guy!
The horse is mine now!
Yeah! Yeah! That horse is our boss's!
Who are you guys?!
Who am I, you ask?
They're so rude!
Don't pretend you don't know this face!
I don't know your face! I'm gonna beat it up!
Th-They don't know me...
Oh, no! Boss! Don't get depressed!
He's lying! I bet he's just saying that!
He can't possibly know him.
Stop laughing, Hamburg!
My name is Foxy! I take whatever I want!
Let this be a lesson, you fools!
Why are you so worked up
about a single horse?!
Hunting is nothing more than entertainment!
Why, you...!
Gum-Gum...!
Stop, Straw Hat Luffy!
How do you know my name?!
Of course we know who you are!
We've done our homework!
Monkey D. Luffy, with a
100-million-berry bounty.
Roronoa Zoro, with a 60-million-berry bounty.
A total bounty of 160 million
with only seven people...
That's really something.
We Foxy Pirates challenge you
Straw Hats to a "Davy Back Fight"!
Stop talking crazy! Just bring it on!
If you wanna fight, let's fight!
Wait, Luffy... A Davy Back fight is...
Ah! That explains the ship
we encountered near here!
--Which way do we turn?!
--How should I know?!
--Someone, give orders! Navigator!
--Don't got one!
--Captain!
Hold on, Luffy! That game...!
Don't do it! We'll lose crew members!
What's the deal, Usopp?!
I'm telling you, don't agree to his game!
Fool! I heard you say it, Straw Hat Luffy!
You clearly agreed to my challenge just now!
Didn't he, Porche-chan?!
Yes, Boss! I heard him, too!
Do you honestly think you can back out now?
Well, you can't.
Or, what? You're not man
enough to keep your word?
I am too!
--Don't get talked into it!
--But... the horse!
Shelly... Oww!
Don't push yourself! You hit your back hard!
--You two! Step aside!
--Old guy!
Shelly faithfully waited ten
years for me! How dare you...?!
Wait, old guy! They're pirates!
A Davy Back Fight?
"Unruly"
That's right! The fight begins the
moment two captains are in agreement!
As we speak, our captain
is challenging your captain,
Monkey D. Luffy, to battle!
Challenging? What kind of
sleepy nonsense is that?
If you want a fight, just start one!
Hey, you've never heard of a Davy Back Fight?
It's not a fight. It's a pirate game.
Yes. A game that supposedly arose
long ago on "Pirate Island,"
which is said to be a pirate
paradise somewhere in the sea.
In it, pirates plunder each other
for top-notch crew members.
--Pirates plunder each other?!
--Yes.
I'm amazed you've survived this
long without even knowing that!
A Davy Back Fight is about
swiping crew members!
After each match, the winner can take
any crew member they want
from the opposing team!
Whoever's chosen must immediately
swear loyalty to their new captain!
In the name of Davy Jones,
the pirate of the deep!
So if you lose... you lose a crew member?!
That's right!
In addition, if the enemy ship
has no one of interest,
they can instead be stripped of their
Jolly Roger-- the life of their ship!
So crewmates and pride are on the line.
Winning will make you stronger,
while losing will mean a serious loss.
What a vicious game.
Wait, does that mean
that ship we ran across earlier
without an organized crew,
sails, or even a captain was...?
Oh? Did you run into the
Fang-Frog Pirates' ship?!
They fell prey to our game earlier!
Say hello to our new crewmates!
Yeah! Long live the Foxy Pirates!
I was the former captain of that ship!
--Former ship doctor!
--Former navigator!
Former shipwright!
We tried five three-coin
games, but lost 'em all!
Fourteen men and our flag,
taken just like that!
With so many people jumping ship like this,
it was more like a merger than anything!
Yeah!
Idiots. How can you be so happy,
ditching your crew like that?
Seriously. The ship's in
a watery grave by now.
Watery grave...?
Hmph! So what?!
There's no talking reason with you!
But we'd never agree to such a
ridiculous game in a million years!
Fool! A regular crew member
can't make that decision!
This game only begins when
two captains reach an agreement!
Like it or not, you're all in this game
if your captain nods his head!
They're right, Nami-san.
This is an unwritten rule
in the pirate world.
Run, and we'll be completely humiliated.
So what if we're humiliated?!
I'd rather die than live in shame.
What he said.
Are you two crazy?!
Forget about it. This is how men are.
Urgh! I gotta stop Luffy, then!
Don't bother. It's no use.
The captains will signal
the start of the fight
by firing shots at the same time!
Just sit here and--!
Please, no...!
He agreed to it...
Fine by me.
This should be interesting.
He's agreed to the game!
You idiot! You idiot! You idiot!
Why did you agree to it?!
You have no idea how horrific this game is!
Then we just won't lose!
Our challenge is now officially accepted!
Yeah! I'm gonna kick your butt!
That'll be the day!
I will too, Split-Head!
--Split-Head...?
--Boss!
How dare you?! Our boss is a sensitive man!
He has a heart of glass.
Doesn't suit him, though.
Hey! I told you not to laugh!
Look, Luffy!
Thinking about the horse and the
old guy makes me mad too, but...!
Use that anger to thrash 'em!
He got back up way too fast!
Leave it to me!
I'm going to teach you a thing or two!
Frankfurters! Get your frankfurters!
Rum and cheese! Crackers and salted meat!
I've got yakisoba noodles too!
It's time for the opening ceremony!
--Please quiet down! Please quiet down!
--Shut up! You be quiet!
--C'mon! Let's hear the odds!
--All participants, get ready!
This is looking fun!
These are all Split-Head's crew members?
Wow! There's so many!
Hi. Five jumbo yakisobas, please.
"Cotton Candy" "Yakisoba Noodles"
Stop that, old guy!
Okay, men! Simmer down!
--Porche-chan!
--Sexy!
It's time for the pledge to follow
these three rules about losing!
First, the only way to take back crewmates,
Jolly Rogers, or anything else
is through another Davy Back Fight!
Second, anyone taken by the winner
must swear loyalty to that
ship's captain immediately!
Third, if your Jolly Roger is taken,
you can't ever display it again!
Nami-san! I bought some cotton candy!
How can you guys be so calm about this?
Are you still moping about that?
Should you break these rules,
you'll be considered dishonorable pirates
and sent to Davy Jones' Locker!
Do you swear to uphold them?
--I swear!
Okay, Straw Hat! I'll let you choose!
One coin? Two coins? Or three coins?
Choose whichever you want!
Oh, Boss! You're so gracious!
What are they for?
It's the number of games.
Our boss is letting you choose
if it should be a one-match game
or all the way up to a three-match game.
The game'll be more fun with more stuff.
--So I'll go with...
--Luffy!
Got it!
Three coins!
You idiot! Why'd you add them?!
And include an enemy in the count?!
So many morons!
I hereby announce this three-coin,
orthodox-rules game...
...to Davy Jones!
Who's Davy Jones?
An old pirate cursed by the devil
who's said to live in the depths
of the sea to this very day.
He lives at the bottom of the sea?!
That's what the legend says.
All the ships and treasures
that sink into the sea
are said to go to his ship's bosun--
his "locker," in other words.
The bottom of the sea is scary...
Sweet!
Pirates call this a "Davy Back"
because you steal whatever
you want from the enemy,
just as Davy takes everything
that comes sinking his way.
Are you ready, Straw
Hat?! Let the game begin!
All right! Let's do this!
We're setting off toward the distant orange horizon
Today's winds are blowing
across the morning sea
I can't sleep
The kind of passion I saw this very morning
cannot be stifled by anyone
Hope, frustration
and much more might come our way
but for now
we can just start from scratch
Some time ago, we had a dream
in which we followed our aspirations
so we'll raise our hands high
and embrace the shining sun in our hearts
We're going to make it to that place
All right! The Davy Back Fight has begun!
I've never lost using
orthodox rules, you know!
A chef, a doctor, an archaeologist...
Who should I take?!
No, I want that one!
Let's get this first round started!
--I don't understand you, Split-Head!
--He said it again...
Next time, on One Piece:
"Round One!
One Lap of the Donut Race"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Round #1!
One Lap of the Donut Race