Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Yuba
Erumalu
Nanohana
Katorea
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
Erumalu
Yuba
Nanohana
Katorea
and a mighty swell.
Meanwhile, to reach Yuba,
where the rebel army is,
Luffy's group set into the desert...
...where numerous, unimaginable
hardships fell upon them!
Enter the Desert Pirates!
The Men Who Live Freely
So hot... Water...
Thanks, Zoro.
This heat is too much for me...
Don't act polite. It's stifling.
Nami-san! How far did you go?!
That side of you is wonderful too!
Huh?
What's the matter, Luffy?
This is much easier thanks to you, Lashes!
But will the others be all right?
They'll just follow the footprints!
Tsunami!
What now?
– A tsunami's coming!
– What's going on, Luffy?!
Maybe it wasn't such a good idea after all?
What wasn't a good idea?
I told him not to, but he said he
was so thirsty he couldn't stand it,
so he chomped down on some
cactus growing back there.
Cactus?
Yeah. Over there.
Those round things.
Eh?! Those are bad!
Those are mezcal cacti!
They're used to make hallucination drugs!
What?!
Oh no!
We're gonna drown!
Alright! Bring it on, if you dare!
I'll beat all of you up!
This is bad!
Gum-Gum...
Tranquilizer!
Way to go, Chopper!
Well? Do you see Nami's group?
L-Luffy?
What?!
Damn.
We're completely separated from them now.
And their footprints are disappearing.
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen Ace for a while, either.
When did he disappear?
I bet he got separated from us.
Sheesh! What a troublesome big brother!
We're the ones who got separated!
– All because of you!
– Quit acting so carefree!
What is it, Usopp?
Do you hear something?
A pirate ship?!
Aah! It's...!
Nami and Vivi've been caught!
Oh, and the camel.
What?!
– Hey! Luffy!
– Don't be rash!
Damn! Let's go, too!
Yeah!
Gum-Gum...
...Give-Me-Water!
Water?!
I'm out of strength...
Did I just hear something?
I wouldn't if I were you.
Oh, my bad!
I'm so thirsty I misjudged...
By the way, do you have any water?
You mean you didn't come to save us?!
I only came to get water.
Help, Luffy-san!
Lashes is about to be eaten!
That thing's edible?
We, the Barbar Sand Pirates, have a saying.
Saying?
Aside from friends, nothing alive
in the desert can't be eaten!
I'll even eat stuff off the ground!
That'll make you sick.
Then I'll be careful!
What a funny pipsqueak!
You're funny too! Well, let's eat!
Why?!
I'm Barbarossa, captain of
the Barbar Sand Pirates!
Luffy, was it? I'm sorry for our
rough treatment of your friends.
It's just that we're all so hungry...
No, I don't mind!
That's not for you to say!
But, Captain! We don't have any
wood at all to repair our main mast!
Without a main mast,
we won't have enough thrust!
Yeah! Yeah! What're we gonna do?!
If we don't do something,
we're going to die like dogs
in the middle of this desert!
– We're gonna die like dogs!
– Huh?! What?!
– The Barbar Sand Pirates are gonna die!
– Huh?
We sand pirates are born in sand pirate ships,
and we'll die in sand pirate ships!
Abandoning our ship is unthinkable!
Yeah! That's right! We'll die in our ship!
We'll die like dogs in our ship!
What is this?
That was fate, this was fate!
We sand pirates will never do
anything to defy the flow of sand!
Can't say I didn't warn you.
But there is timber at the Meriyasu Oasis.
Where is it?! I'll rush there real quick!
But the sands've changed lately.
It's dangerous for outsiders.
I'm responsible for it! I'll do it!
Yeah?! You will?!
Bring back wood with this sand-sled.
I'd say this is more of a canoe than a sled...
Zaba and Rasa will show you
to the Meriyasu Oasis.
– Rasa?
– Yes.
Rasa is our ship's finest sand-sledder.
A sand-sled can carry two people.
What'll you do?
I'll be fine on my own!
Come on, now!
Quit saying baseless things like that!
It'll probably be demanding work.
Want me to go with you?
Oh! That was cool, Rasa!
The others seem to be outsiders...
but you're from here.
Wow! How could she tell?
You must have some
experience with a sand-sled.
You'll come along.
Vivi-chan can't do anything that dangerous!
Yeah! That's crazy!
All right. I'll come with you.
Oh? So these go on top of the sand?
How does it work?
I'll pilot the sled.
I did this once long ago.
It's not too different from a ship.
This goes like this, right?
I-I'm back!
Don't waste your strength doing stupid things!
You can rest there, Luffy-san.
Now, let's see.
I believe this goes like this and...
Ugh. Let's go, Zaba!
Yeah, Rasa!
Yahoo!
This feels great!
If we borrow this, can't we reach Yuba right away?
It's hard to control sand-sleds.
It's not something easily mastered.
Then how come you can control it?
I used to practice with a sand-sled
I received when I was little.
But what should we do while we wait?
Want to eat the camel?!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
All for it!
Just joking!
Doesn't sound like a joke to me...
Hey, you! What's the big idea?!
Hey, Rasa! That's...!
Hey, Vivi!
We're getting pulled in more and more!
It's quicksand!
If we get swallowed into the sand,
we'll never come back out!
Rasa. Wasn't that going too far?
If luck's on her side,
she'll make it through alive.
Huh? You know that girl?
Yeah. As if I'd ever forget!
You alright, Vivi?!
We're in trouble if we don't do something!
We're done for!
Vivi! Duck!
Gum-Gum...
Despite how he seems, you can
always count on Luffy in a pinch!
Yeah. But what concerns me
more is the desert's fickleness.
The desert's fickleness?
Yeah. The desert is honest.
A slight change in weather or
people's hearts will change it greatly.
A change in people's hearts?
What's that?
Boss! It's them!
They're coming!
– Turn to starboard! Hurry!
– Battle stations!
You wanna get in my way, too?
– There are so many of them!
– Who are they?
Desert bandits!
Pests who're always desperately fighting us!
Conflict seems imminent these days!
That has them on edge, too!
Looks like you can't move!
You're finally ours today!
Men!
Don't let a single one of them leave alive!
Our pleasure! Our pleasure!
What is this, a pub?
The desert has pit us together!
Will the desert choose us,
the Barbar Pirates, or you?!
Let's let the desert decide our fate in battle!
Fool! Fool! The desert'd never choose you!
What's that?
– Grand Dung Beetle!
– There's a Grand Dung Beetle!
– Grand Dung Beetle?
– Say what now?!
Desert bugs that haul giant balls of dung!
No less than 100 people a year
are squished by their rolling dung!
Eh?!
Boss! It's headed right for our ship!
Leave it to me!
Thanks, guests...
We'll let you off easy this time!
Your lives are spared for now!
That deserves a warm shower of applause.
Rasa!
Don't you think you went a little too far?!
– They're not following!
– That's fine!
If she won't come however much we wait,
that's just the level of a person she is!
We caught up!
Yay!
This oasis is completely buried in sand.
It was once a flourishing city, but...
You've been here before?
The people of this city gave me
a small sand-sled as a memento.
That was a very long time ago, though.
I stopped by here once with my father
when he was traveling around the country.
I've been waiting all this time.
Back then, the king told us,
"If anything happens to this oasis,
I will come rushing to help.
The kingdom won't ignore any voice,
no matter how small."
So you were that girl!
Eventually, this oasis was
buried in sand and abandoned.
Every last person in town left.
Even so, I stayed behind and waited for you.
I believed in you...
But the king never came. Nor you, of course.
That's because similar incidents
were happening all over the country
and the king was busy every
day trying to combat it!
I don't want to hear your excuses!
I waited all alone in the
middle of this vast desert!
Eventually, I couldn't differentiate between dawn and dusk.
By the time Barbarossa took me in,
I couldn't feel anything,
not even the midday scorching heat
or the freezing cold after sunset.
The fact that I was even alive baffled me.
But, inside my head,
the king's words continue to ring.
Even now, I don't understand it.
Things were so difficult,
so what exactly was I waiting for?
Just what kept me going?
Hate? Anger? Or inexistent hope?
What was it?!
Someone tell me...
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry for making you wait...
I'm so sorry!
They sure ran off in a hurry!
Though it's too bad we didn't get
to swipe any of their food or water.
Sand pirates sure have it tough, too...
Everything living in this desert has it the same.
Long ago, I used to feel this
desert belonged to everyone.
But when I think about it now,
I feel like that's a bit conceited.
Lately, I've come to think that
it might not belong to anyone.
That we're able to live freely
because it belongs to no one.
Do you think the sea is the same way?
Good question.
That's something you'll have
to find out for yourselves.
There it is! We made it!
Luffy! Where are you?!
Kodomo no koro yume mita boukenka mitai de
Like the adventurers I dreamed of when I was a child
Omoi no hate ni tsurenatte yuku yo
I continue on to the ends of emotion
Sukuiageta tenohira kara
I scoop up my hands,
koboreochiru suna to jikan
and the sand and time that spills from them
Kono tame ni umarete kita to oshiete kureru
show me that this is what I was born to do
Korogeochisou na supido de
Let's continue swimming
Bokura oyogitsuzukeyou
at a near-tumbling speed
Soshite dare mo
Until we wash up someday
shiranai shirahama he itsuka
on a white sandy beach
Uchiagerareru made
no one knows about
– Say, Luffy. Where's your brother?
– Dunno.
He's worse at directions than this guy?!
Huh?!
Who're you talking about, Pervy Cook?!
Who else is there besides you?
Hey! I got food and water!
– Big brother! How?!
– Got it from the rebel army!
Come again?!
Next time, on One Piece:
False Fortitude!
Camu, Rebel Soldier at Heart!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
False Fortitude!
Camu, Rebel Soldier at Heart!