Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Rubberband of Doom!
Special Attack!
Fire Star!
Usopp Hammer!!
I win!
It serves you right!
I can kill humans like you
without even directly touching
you if I have some water.
That's the difference between Fishmen and humans.
Arlong!!
Big Sis Nami!
Nami-san!
Hey, Nami!
I was about to crush some pirates just now.
What did you come here for?
To kill you...
Luffy at Full Power!
Nami's Determination
and the Straw Hat
To kill... me?
You never learn, do you?
How many times did you try to kill me
during the eight years you were with us?
You tried assassination, poison, sneak attacks...
Were you able to actually kill me?
You must be completely aware
that you mere humans can't kill me.
Now, listen. I won't kill you...
...and you can't escape from me...
Nami...
You'll be our surveyor forever.
But, as you know, I'm a good-natured man.
If possible, I want you to be our
surveyor of your own free will.
So, how about this?
I'll be killing everyone here except you.
But if you happily come
back to the Arlong Pirates
and draw sea charts as one of the leaders,
I don't mind letting those people
from Cocoyashi Village live.
But I can't let these guys live.
They went too far.
The question is who you'll be with.
You either take my side now and
get saved along with the villagers,
or be on these weaklings' side and
try fighting against me with everyone.
But with these guys you
depend on in this shape,
it's obvious that it'll be a tragedy for you.
Nami...
Are you my friend?
Or... their friend?
Not fair...
If I say I'm friends with Luffy and the others,
everyone will get killed.
And if I say I'm Arlong's friend,
then everyone from the village will be saved.
With my words,
everyone will be...
That's despicable!
No matter what she chooses,
he's not going to give Nami freedom!
But!!
Luffy...
Help me...
Of course I will!
I must not doubt his words!
Everyone, I'm sorry!
Please die with me!
All right!
We'll go for it!
We'll fight!!
I see...
Everyone wants to be killed...
P... Please! Please!
Live! Live! Live! Live! Live!
Hm?
What the...?
Finally...
All we have to do now is
remove his leg weight...
Oh...
So that's what you meant...
Could it be?!
Big Bro Luffy!!
What?!
Hey, hang in there!
Come back to life!
30 seconds!
I won't last longer than that.
Zoro!
That'll be enough!
There isn't a fountain over there.
Could it be that rubber man?!
Don't worry about it.
It's nothing, you damn half-fish!
I thought I told you not to
say those words ever again...
...dying Zoro!
If I kick and break that leg weight,
he can fight.
Luffy, you're the only one who can fight now!
In the sea, one with Devil Fruit
powers is supposed to lose
even the energy to struggle,
as well as his powers, and die.
If he's still alive,
that means someone is
putting a damper on this game.
Are you all right?!
Glad you're okay!
Yeah! Oh?
What?! What's the matter?!
Pops, what did you do with your pinwheel?
That was a cool one.
Who cares about that right now?!
Putting a damper?
It didn't seem like a fair game from the start.
At any rate,
if there's a hindrance, I need to check on it.
Out of my way.
Egg Star!
I've got your back, Zoro!
Big Bro Usopp! Is he all right?!
How brave! What a gallant arrival!
Fight to the full extent!
That's where you are?!
Usopp!
Listen, Nami!
I beat one of the leaders!
One of the leaders!
The guy with a face like this.
Fishmen are a piece of cake!
You defeated... Choo?!
Serves you right!
With my arrival, the fight
comes to a climax at once!
It heads into the final chapter!
Hey, can't you somehow escape on your own?
Oh, that's impossible.
I don't have any strength at all.
Come out! Come out! Come out!
Big Bro Cook!
I don't know what's going on in the water,
but his action must be the key!
Big Bro Zoro!
Stand strong and stop Arlong!
Okay!
We have to somehow prevent
Arlong from going into the sea, huh?
I'll stop him from moving.
I won't let you have your way!
Hey, Arlong! Look this way!
Wha?! Big Bro Usopp!!
How brave!
Usopp!
– Rubberband of Doom!
– Standing in my way...
Looks like you want to die first, Roronoa Zoro.
Now! Go Zoro!!
What do you actually wanna do?!
No way I'll die.
I'll break your proud nose!
You fool...
It's a proud nose because it's unbreakable.
If you were at your full strength,
you might've been able to give it a scratch.
Big Bro...
Look over there!
Hm?
Ahh! That damn octopus is up!
And... what's he doing?
Dammit! I thought the rubber
band was going to fly at me!
What?!
See?! He was my target!
You were yelling "Arlong," weren't you?
Octopus...
Roronoa Zoro!
I won't let you have your way!
I'll crush your friend who went into the sea!
You don't have to be concerned
since you'll all be dead, after all.
Big Bro!!
Nami-san's big sister!
Leave the rest to me!
A Fishman!
Move away, Big Sister.
I'll break a rock like that with my kick!
That octopus!
Octopus-Fritter Frenzy!!
Big Sister!
Zoro!!
So that was it?
That was too quick.
What's up with these bandages?
Did you fall somewhere?
What's this scar?
How can he still be alive with a body like this?
How can he still be standing?!
What kind of eyes are they?
Are they the eyes of someone who's dying?
He's a man I need to kill for sure,
right here right now!
If a person stays put,
their wounds won't be opened...
That's right.
You find your situation amusing?
I'm not talking about me...
I'm talking about the Octo-Man.
What?!
I thought I told you...
We win this game.
Dammit!
That scared me a bit!
You're the one who made this whole
thing complicated in the first place!
All right!
Go and beat up that shark bastard,
you damn idiot!
Is it coming, kid?
It's coming!!
Wahhhhh! I'm back!!
Rubber boy!
Big Bro Luffy!!
Luffy!
That damn rubber man...!
You're late, idiot!
Zoro!!
Huh? Hey! Stop it!
You aren't gonna...
Let's switch places!
You idiot!
Gum-Gum... Bell!!
And, Whip!!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!!
Gatling!!
All right!
Did you do something?
It's not working!!
Yep. That was my warm-up.
That idiot!
I'm gonna kill him!
What a bunch of scum,
nobly hanging on...
You'd have been happier if you
died at the bottom of the sea...
Hm? Not really.
I'm happy that they saved me.
Can you understand my anger?
It's the anger of seeing my
dear brothers crushed by worms.
You'll realize soon enough that
you should've died without fighting.
Is Big Bro Luffy gonna be okay?
All his fierce attacks weren't effective at all...
More importantly, how far did Big Bro Zoro fly?!
Go Luffy! I've got your back!
You don't have to worry about his back.
If he loses, you guys will all die, too.
Yeah, we will...
If that happens, it's the
end of the East Blue, too.
What's the terrifying difference
between you and me?
Nose.
Jaw?
I wonder if Big Bro's joking...
No, he's definitely serious.
Webs!
Species!!
Such a fool!
He hurt himself by biting on a rock!
Now his teeth're brok...
He crushed the stone pillar with his teeth!!
Ahh! That's scary!
What a man!
If he gets you with that,
he won't just give you bite marks,
he'll bite clear through your bones!
You see?
This is the inherent power of a Fishman.
Heaven discriminated against you humans
and made you powerless creatures that bow before Fishmen.
You humans are inferior creatures.
We were on a different level
from the moment we were born.
I'll show you...
...the real difference between you and me...
Yeah, why don't you?
No way I'll lose against a fish.
I am...
...the man who'll be the Pirate King!
Oh? Where did Arlong go?
Luffy! The sea!
The sea? Whoa! There's a shark!
That's Arlong!
Oh, he ran away?
This isn't good!
His ability doubles in the water!
Ahh! Watch out!
Wahhh!
Luffy!!
Next time, on One Piece:
Explosion!
Fishman Arlong's Fierce Assault From the Sea!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Explosion!
Fishman Arlong's Fierce
Assault From the Sea!