Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Huge Duel!
The Giants Dorry and Broggy
So...
What's the answer?
Wh-What was that?
C-Could you repeat that?
I asked you if you have any alcohol.
We've got a little...
So you've got some?
I-It's not for drinking.
It's for cooking and disinfection.
But if you like, we'll give it all to you.
Dino...
Dinosaur?
I'm Broggy, the Elbaf's strongest warrior!
Now I've got meat, too.
I'll treat you, my guests.
H-Hey...
P-Pretend we're dead...
No matter what happens...
D-Doesn't pretending to be
dead only work on bears?
Whoa! What a great view!
I wanna have lunch here.
This isn't the time for idle chatter!
Ahhh... Oh? So there really are volcanoes.
And there's a mountain with huge holes as well...
It's dangerous! Come down already!
Huh?
Even if it's well-behaved, it's still a dinosaur!
This guy's no trouble!
More importantly, there're huge holes over there!
That's one weird landscape!
Forget about the landscape!
Just come down!
Say, I have a favor to ask.
Will you take me over there?
Hey, stop being so mean and take me there.
Over that way! That way!
Not this way... Here! This way!
Who'd do something like that?!
Oh... sorry. But, uhm...
Amazing!!
Luffy-san! Like I said, it's dangerous!
Come down already!
And those dinosaurs are taller,
so it looks like I'll have a better view.
That's not the point!
As I thought, I can see the holes better.
Hmph!
Oops!
Watch out!
Vivi! Wanna come over here?! It's fun!
The view from here is especially good!
Ah!
He's been eaten!
Where am I?
Whoa...
I was watching. What a lively human,
grappling with longnecks in this jungle.
You're the first guest in a long time.
You're huge! Are you a human?
You're asking me if I'm a human?
I'm Dorry, the Elbaf's strongest warrior!
G... Giant!
I've heard of them, but this is my
first time actually seeing one...
I'm Luffy. I'm a pirate.
A pirate?! Good for you!
Karoo! Wake up!
We're getting out of here while we can!
Oh yeah, the ones over there are
Vivi and Karoo. Nice to meet you!
Luffy-san had to open his big mouth...!
I'll invite you guys to my home!
It looks yummy.
How long do we have to pretend to be dead?
After all, this strategy doesn't
seem to work against a Giant.
Hmm... I guess it was my imagination.
Why'd you make a noise?
I couldn't help it since there're
tons of skulls lying around!
I know, but...
I wonder if we'll be eaten like that soon...
Don't give up!
But...
We don't have to wait here
like this just to be eaten.
It's yummy! It's yummy!
Dinosaur meat!
Grill it with red flame and take a big bite!
It's yummy! It's yummy!
Dinosaur meat!
– That way!
– It's yummy! It's yummy! Dinosaur meat!
– Dinosaur meat...
I-In any case... we were able to escape...
At least we got far away
from the Giant's stomach!
But it might've only gotten us closer
to a saber-toothed tiger's stomach...
No! No! No! No!
In this jungle, no matter what we do,
our fate will always be the same!
It's just a matter of whose stomach we end up in...
We did everything we could.
Let's accept our fate...
Oh, you guys're awake?
The meat is done. Have some!
It's in return for the alcohol.
Now, eat! Dinosaur meat tastes good.
I-I have no appetite.
Don't hold back!
I don't want to eat.
Dinosaur meat tastes good, I'm tellin' ya...
Is he trying to get us to
eat the dinosaur meat first...
...in order to fatten us up a little...
...and then eat us?
Yeah, he's acting like a Giant, all right.
When we're still so young...
Maybe we taste best when we're young...
What a waste...
It's good, I'm tellin' ya...
If we somehow keep fasting until
the Log is stored and don't get fat,
we may be able to survive...
But how long will it take
for the Log to be stored?
If I don't eat for three days,
I'm sure I'll get tempted by
this smell of meat and eat it...
Broggy-san! Can I ask you a question?
Hmm? What's the matter, young lady?
H-How long will it take for the
Log of this island to be stored?
One year.
What?!
Oh, no...
There's no way we can fast for a year...
I... definitely can't help eating...
Well, make yourselves at home!
This is yummy, giant old guy!
Your pirate lunch thing tastes good, too,
although it's a little too small for me.
Of course it's good!
That's a special lunch the
chef on my pirate ship made.
If you say it's bad, I'll beat you up!
Beat me up, you said?
What a funny squirt you are!
Th-They're becoming awfully friendly...
By the way, why are you
living here alone, old guy?
Isn't there a village or something?
Hmm? There is a village.
It's a warriors' village called Elbaf.
It's somewhere in the Grand Line.
Hm?
But there're rules in the village.
Rules?
For example, if we start a fight in the
village and both sides can't back off,
we are judged by Elbaf's god.
Elbaf's god always gives divine
protection to the righteous one
and lets the righteous one survive.
I see... Elbaf's god, huh?
I caused a disturbance,
and this island is currently the site
for a duel between a certain man and myself.
The righteous one will win the duel and survive.
But we haven't been able to
settle this for about 100 years.
You guys've been fighting for 100 years?!
It's nothing surprising, since our life span
is at least three times as long as yours.
Even if it's three times,
your interest in fighting would
wane in 100 years, wouldn't it?
Is there any point in continuing to fight?
It's a duel to the death, right?!
Well, I shouldn't be outdone by Zoro with this one.
It's decided that I'm the winner of the
competition to obtain kilos of meat.
I'm the winner of the competition
to obtain tons of meat!
Zoro!
Sanji!
I win!
You lose!
Look! My prey is bigger!
What?! This competition is about how
many tons of meat we can get, right?!
Mine is obviously huskier than yours!
Ha! It's all a matter of if
we can use it for cooking.
Your prey looks full of bones.
It has no more than 5 grams
of meat for cooking!
There's no way we can eat
meat full of sinews like that!
Tsk! There's no use in competing with such small prey.
I'll go capture a big one that'll silence you.
Okay then. I'll go capture a super big
one that you can't even touch this time.
Okay. The next eruption is the
signal to end the competition.
Bring back your prey to
the Going Merry by then.
Yeah, I'll take you up on that!
Whoa!!
That's a huge volcano eruption!
Well, time to go...
Hmm?
What's that?
An eruption...
Hmm?
His face suddenly got tense...
Sorry... I have to head out for a bit.
What? Head out?
Yeah. That was a signal for the duel
that I've been in for 100 years.
A duel?
With whom?
Where and for what reason?
Reason? I don't remember.
It became our routine before we realized it.
The eruption of the central
mountain is the signal for the duel.
What?! To have such hatred that you'd
try killing each other for 100 years is...
What on earth caused this fight?!
Stop it.
It's not like that.
Right. It's because of our pride.
I forgot...
...the reason a long time ago!
What? Wh-What's wrong?
Oh, boy... What a huge duel!
Hey, big lizard. You're in our way.
Let me take care of it.
10,000 Kilogram Press!
Oh hello, Mr. 5.
Ha! What an extravagant power you have,
building an improvised house in a jungle.
Let me tell you something, though.
This mission is still ours.
I don't want you to meddle in it.
We'll never goof up like that again.
– Goof up?
– Hmm?
That's not it.
You two are weak, Mr. 5, Miss Valentine.
Well, don't look so stern. Look at this.
I'd like to thank you for giving me
an opportunity to come to this island.
Dorry the Blue Ogre and Broggy the
Red Ogre of the Giant Warrior Pirates.
I've heard of them in an old tale.
This is a wanted poster from 100 years ago!
Yeah, but those guys now live on this island.
Their bounty then was
100 million berries per head.
200 million berries for the two of them.
200-million-berry bounty heads?
But they're Giants.
Superb criminals execute their
crimes by using their superb brains.
All you have to do is follow my instructions.
If we give it a little thought,
we can cut through any mountain.
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Ah yasashi uta nee
Ah, gentle song
Todoke futari no tame ni
Make it there for us
Nami ga saratta chisana suna no oshiro
After a wave washed away that little sand castle
nagareru kumo o miagete naki souna egao
You looked up at the passing clouds with a sad smile
Moshi mo sekai juu ni teki shika inai nara
If you find the world is full of enemies,
senaka o makasete
I've got your back
Shinjiru kimochi o wasurenaide
Don't lose faith
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Ah itoshii hito nee
Ah, my love
Zutto daiteite ageru
I'll hold you in my arms forever
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Hey, you! Capture a big one this time.
Ha! You'd better not bring back
a small lizard this time, either!
Shut up, you two!
A man-to-man duel has just started!
O-Okay...
What?! The alcohol exploded!
That's the barrel we gave them!
What's going on?
Next time, on One Piece:
Luffy Gets Angry!
A Dirty Trick Violates The Sacred Duel!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Luffy Gets Angry!
A Dirty Trick Violates
The Sacred Duel!