Listen, Luffy.
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
Uh-huh.
We gotta go out to sea someday...
and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
Ace, we're coming to rescue you!
Luffy!
Activate the barricades!
What is that?!
We're enclosed!
What the hell is this?!
Hey, what's wrong?!
It should be fully activated!
The wall can't lift the giant body of Oars!
We can't close it but do it, Red Hound!
Meteor Volcano!
Now let's move on to...
the execution of Portgas D. Ace immediately!
Ace!
Straw-boy!
Honestly! You're too reckless!
I need you to do me a favor!
Little Oars Jr.!
Ace-kun!
He's still alive?!
I'm gonna get Ace back!!
You're not good enough to reach this stage yet.
Gum-Gum...
Stamp Gatling!
You're too slow!
I don't remember saying that that was all of our ships!
Another coated ship is entering the bay!
Sink it!
No! Not the boat!
Shoot at Oars!
Get ready, everybody!
He pulled the boat out of the water!
They broke through the barricades!
Whitebeard has descended to the plaza!
Oars...
Guys! Rescue Ace and...
destroy the Navy!!
Garp.
Yeah.
Ace! I'll be there soon!
You just run straight!
Alright!
Inazuma!
Okay, Iva-san.
That's...
Crab-chan!
Luffy-kun, go ahead!
Inazuma of the Revolutionary Army!
Luffy!
I'm here, Ace!
I consider you my enemy!
Garp!
Ace!
Luffy! You..
Wait!
You can't get away from me!
What is that?!
Three! Why are you here?!
Gum-Gum...
Gigant Balloon!
Candle Wall!
I'll make the key!
Uncuff him right away!
Alright!
Fire!
Blow them away!
Captain Buggy!
There's Brother 3!
What?!
You never change! Luffy!
You never do as I tell you...
and always get yourself in big trouble!
Ace!
Ace...
I'm sorry, Luffy...
Ace, you need to get treated right away!
I couldn't make it all the way. I'm sorry.
What are you saying?
Don't be ridiculous!
How could we mess up this badly?!
I'll never forgive myself for what happened today!
How annoying!
Hurry! Give him first aid now!
It's no use.
I can tell that my life is ending.
So, listen to me, Luffy.
Ace...
Listen to what I'm about to say.
Could you tell them what I'm about to say now?
Pops!
Everybody!
And you Luffy.
Thank you...
for loving such a good-for-nothing like me...
who carries such despicable blood in his veins...
up to today.
Thank you!
Did you have a bad dream?
You're all sweaty.
Drink this.
"Overcoming Ace's Death! Luffy's Pledge to his Friends"
"15th Anniversary Special Episode"
After losing his brother, Ace,
during the Paramount War at Marineford,
Monkey D. Luffy suffered greatly, both mentally and physically.
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
I have a suggestion for you.
Of course it's up to you...
if you want to do it or not.
「Luscaina」
A deserted island northwest of Maiden Island
Accepting Rayleigh's suggestion, he came to Luscaina.
It's the power to feel
other's presence more strongly.
It's called Observation Haki!
Next, Armament Haki.
This power works as if
you're wearing invisible armor.
And watch this.
That was the power to intimidate your enemy!
Conqueror's Haki!
To obtain the power called Haki, the only effective
countermove against Devil Fruit users,
Luffy is now undertaking a two-year training course.
The pirate—Straw Hat Luffy will be...
on hiatus for a while.
Are you okay now?
Yeah.
I wonder what they're doing.
Your friends?
Yeah.
Think about it!
What is it that you still have?!
I still have my friends!
Zoro.
I have an ambition.
To be the world's greatest swordsman!
I will...
not be defeated ever again!
Until the day I defeat him
and become a master swordsman...
I'll never... be defeated!
Got any problems with that, Pirate King?!
Usopp.
Usopp!
I'm captain of the Usopp Pirates...
and a brave warrior of the sea!
I won't let you lay a finger on the village!
Get on already.
Eh?!
We're friends now, aren't we?
I...
I get to be captain, right?!
Nami.
Luffy...
Help me...
Of course I will!
Luffy!
Nami!
You're my friend!
Yeah!
Sanji.
Say... do you know the All Blue?
I'll come along on your journey to become "Pirate King"!
We both have foolish dreams.
In order to achieve my goal,
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Owner Zeff!!
Thank you for all the damn things you've done for me over all these years!!
Chopper.
Even if I don't have friends, I can still fight!
You do have friends!
I am your friend!
It's true... that I wanna be a pirate but...
I can't become your friend!
Shut up!
Let's go!
Robin.
Let me stay on this ship.
The pirates waged war on the World Government!
Robin!
Say that you wanna live!!
I...
wanna live!!
Franky.
If you want these shorts back,
you'll have to join us!
Don't be so cocky.
I feel sorry for the ship
when it's this great
but has no real shipwright on the crew.
I suppose I can take care
of it for you. I, Franky, will...
take on the role of shipwright for your crew!
I'm takin' off for a while!
Brook.
I learned Laboon is well
and still waiting after all this time.
My shadow is back.
We're out of the Devil's Sea.
Every day was filled with pain.
Truthfully, I didn't even see a glimmer of hope.
But Luffy-san...
I'm so happy to be alive!
May I join your crew?
Yeah, sure.
What?!
So easily...
...He joined!
I want to become stronger
and protect them.
I wanna be the man who can protect their dreams.
I suppose your friends are thinking the same thing
and biding their time now.
Uh-huh.
The sun will rise soon.
Get some sleep.
It's gonna be another hard training day.
Yeah, I'm going back to sleep.
You bastard!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
There's Haki!
Where did the gorilla go?
Gotta take care of this one first. Gear...
2!
Jet...
Pistol!
Did I get it?!
A rabbit?!
Ow, ow, ow!
You damn rabbit!
It got you!
That was a Toughness Rabbit. They can endure blows.
Dammit! That jerk!
Now you can use Armament Haki
about 50% of the time.
With your Observation Haki, you should sense not only
your enemy's presence
but also how strong they are.
You have good eyes
so you can't help relying on them.
What?
All right.
I can't see!
Leave it on like that for a while.
I can't see anything!
Like I told you, you have to strain all your senses.
You have to feel it.
No matter how good your eyes are,
you can't see things
that move at the speed of light.
But once you obtain Observation Haki,
you can tell where they are.
Alright! I'll do it!
It's coming!
Byojack, how many minutes have passed
since we started attacking?
Um... eight minutes.
So slow! It shouldn't take that long to sink three warships and a liner!
B-But it took so much trouble
for us to recruit those crew members
while you were gone!
Making up with number isn't good enough!
Nightin, Gairam, Sebastian.
Show them how you do it.
I'll give you one minute!
Okay!
I've been itching to fight!
Let's go already!
Who are they?!
They're gliding on the water!
Fire!
How are they doing that?!
They all look nice and young!
But I'm gonna kick their asses anyway!
Screw you!
Kanpo Kenpo: Antidote Granule!
I always thought these Navy ships were ugly.
Let me renovate it for you!
Cube Break!
Don't take too long!
I knew they could do it.
I'll take care of the rest.
What?
In fifty seconds!
H-Hey!
Y-You're...
Byrnndi World!
Let me borrow these!
More-More Hundredfold Gun!
How could you do that to my comrades! Go to hell!
What?!
Look up!
More-More Hundredfold Chop!
That's my World!
His strength hasn't faded at all!
That's for sure.
Overwhelmingly strong!
He's crazy!
He even blew up his own people!
What's my time?
E-Exactly fifty seconds.
Newcomers!
Just remember this!
If you fail to follow my orders, that's what happens to you!
They were all fighting hard following your orders!
They were taking too much time!
When I ask you to do something by a certain time, you can't be late!
If you can't do it, I'll kill you with my own hands!
I don't need you here
if you're not ready to fight and die for me!
Just go away!
World!
He's insane!
By the way, I'll also kill the ones who...
try to get away!
World...
Amazon Lily
Several days later
Severe winter is coming to Luscaina next week!
Kuja Castle
It's gonna be extremely cold. Almost negative 40 degrees!
He needs some warm clothing!
A sweater, a scarf, gloves, and earmuffs!
Oh yeah, long underwear, too!
"Long underwear."
And he's just eating wild beast meat—
that's not healthy!
He needs some sea food, vegetables, fruit, rice and bread!
Does he like pasta?
It seemed like he liked Penne Gorgonzola
with Sea King meat.
Cook a big potful of it, then!
Cook it on the ship
and deliver it to him while it's hot!
"A big potful... While it's hot." Okay.
What else?
What?
Snake Princess-sama!
I thought you made a promise with Rayleigh!
Luffy is in the middle of training!
It's not good for him if you spoil him!
Repress your desire to see him
and keep wishing for his success in your heart!
That's what a good woman does!
Speaking from my numerous experiences with men,
men don't like a meddlesome woman like you!
You're a Warlord!
Stop being crazy about a guy...
I know!
That's why I'm sending someone so I'm not gonna bother Luffy!
Stop getting on my back like that!
Princess-sama is so mad!
After a week of severe winter, spring will come along!
Get some spring outfits that suit Luffy!
"Spring outfits with lace frills."
Let's set off as soon as you got it all!
Yes, ma'am!
How could you do that to an elderly person!
Is it a Carrier Bat?
It's from the World Government.
Wh-What?!
I-It's a big deal, Snake Princess!
The World Government
is summoning the Seven Warlords!
Are you listening, Snake Princess?!
Oh, Luffy!
It feels like my heart's gonna explode
when I think of you!
I'm gonna send my love to you soon! My dear Luffy!
I can't believe you really built it, Gairam!
No way!
With just a single shot,
it destroyed the island!
Well, it was nothing!
I'd been trusting that you'd return for thirty years!
So did we!
Sebastian and I put all our efforts
into getting materials to build the ship!
Don't try to take all the credit!
She's right!
What did you say?!
Stop fighting.
Thank you all!
The ship that we were
dreaming about, thirty years ago.
We finally got it!
And this giant cannon.
The barrel is already pretty big but with my More-More power,
I can make the balls 100 times bigger!
With this, we can even blow up Mary Geoise,
the capital of the World Government, in an instant!
It's all set!
Now, it's showtime!
World, I don't think we can carry out the plan so easily.
What?
Because of what we did the other day,
the World Government now knows
the former great pirate Byrnndi World is back.
I wanted to let them know that.
It's not a big deal.
But they're looking out for our attack...
and they summoned the Seven Warlords.
Is that true?!
The Seven Warlords?
What the hell is that?
Oh yeah!
You've been locked up in Impel Down for thirty years so you don't know it.
The Seven Warlords are a group of pirates
who are sanctioned and granted amnesty by the Government.
In return for that, they can be summoned
when an emergency arises, as "Government dogs."
But they're not just "dogs"—
their strength is unquestionable.
And?
I'm good at collecting information.
They were summoned this morning
so they're gonna come to
the Government HQ within a few days.
I don't think your plan's gonna work out...
Wait a minute.
Did you say they were summoned this morning?
Yes. Is that important?
Then, let's take advantage of this.
What do you mean?
Which Government dog
lives closest to here?
Damn! That gorilla and that alligator and that lion!
I'm gonna do it again after I eat!
Going back into the forest?
Yeah! I kept getting beaten by them!
I'm gonna kick their asses this time!
I see.
Don't die.
Yeah!
Where did they go? Sleeping?
Hey! Gorilla! Alligator! Lion!
Fight me openly and squarely!
What's this smell?
It smells so good!
What's there?
Th-This must be food!
I thought so!
Can I eat this?!
Let's eat!
Luffy's here.
Yeah, he looks fine.
Oh, Luffy's there?!
Look at that reaction just by hearing about him.
She would've had a heart attack if she had landed with them.
Luffy!
He still has a big appetite!
He even ate the frilly spring outfits!
Big Sis, Luffy even ate the...
What did he eat?
Where is the Empress of Amazon Lily?
Who are you?!
My name is Byrnndi World!
I'm here to kidnap the World Government's dog,
the Warlord, Boa Hancock!
B-Byrnndi World?!
You know who that is?!
How many times do I have to tell you!
On the letter of request from the World Government,
that you tore up and threw away,
there was a name of the man who was
the reason that they summoned the Warlords.
And that was Byrnndi World!
What?!
Kidnap Princess-sama?!
Snake Princess-sama is not here!
Hey.
W-Well, I didn't say "She's here"!
I saw the Kuja's pirate ship
on the shore so I said "Maybe."
All I said was "Maybe, she's here."
What a waste of time.
Wait!
I can't just let someone who came to kidnap Big Sis, walk away...
because I'm her sister!
Her sister?
Sonia! Mari!
What's going on there?
You hear me?!
Say something!
I see! The Empress is on
the other side of the Snail!
Well then...
More-More Tenfold Shotgun!
How dare you do that to Marigold-sama!
What?
Oh, you girls!
Did you bring all this food for me?!
Luffy, run!
What's wrong?!
Did you get attacked by the beasts?!
Who is he?
Who are you?
I have no business with you all.
Go to hell!
Don't do it!
Ouch. What do you think you're doing?
Drop dead!
More-More Hundredfold Gun!
It's not gonna...
Luffy!
You're the Empress of Amazon Lily, aren't you?
How's Luffy?! Is he okay?!
She must be talking about that kid.
Come and see yourself!
I'll leave a Vivre Card here.
Pirate Empress!
If you want your sisters back,
track me down with the Card
before the break of dawn, the day after tomorrow!
What are you...
Clank.
I've heard of a kid named Luffy somewhere...
Luffy, are you all right?
Hancock.
Why are you two here?
I'm glad that you woke up finally!
Ow, ow, ow...
Don't try to get up. Stay still.
Oh yeah!
What about those girls?!
Margaret and the others
got treated and are sleeping.
Sonia and Mari are...
They got taken away, didn't they?
Uh-huh.
Damn, that bastard!
I think this World guy wants something from me.
Are you gonna go take them back?
Of course!
But if he's really the notorious World, even as strong as you are, it's too—
I'll go with her!
Hancock! You have to take me with you!
Luffy!
Luffy, don't you remember that you promised me
that you were gonna
train yourself here for two years?
No, I remember that!
And you haven't mastered Haki completely yet.
You're gonna die if you go!
I'm not gonna lose this time!
What have you been training yourself for?
If you go, you may not be able
to see your friends again!
But they came here to deliver food for me!
And they've been kidnapped!
I can't just sit still and do nothing!
Luffy...
Rayleigh, please let me take him with me!
I won't let them kill him!
No matter what I say,
I can't change your mind, can I?
Come back alive at any price!
I will!
But you have to be careful.
As you may know,
people are looking all over for you right now.
Don't cause any trouble in a place where you may attract public attention.
I got it!
"The Destroyer of the World, Byrnndi World, appeared?!"
"Island Vanishes Overnight"
This guy is like a mad dog.
The World Nobles, pirates, the Navy...
He's killing everyone he sees.
Did he do this, too?
That's what the Gov't thinks.
They made a decision
to summon the Warlords quickly
after the World Noble case.
They've already sent out Carrier Bats three days ago.
Without even telling us!
It's necessary.
Tsuru-san!
By summoning the Warlords,
they wanted not only to prepare for World's attack
but also to prevent any one
of the Warlords from allying with World
by having them close at hand.
I think that's how you should look at it.
Until that day thirty years ago,
he had been feared as the "Destroyer of the World."
The Government did what they did because they see him as a threat.
"Destroyer of the World"?
Uh-huh.
World would take out everything he saw.
He was dangerous not only for everyday people
but also for other pirates.
So the Government secretly assembled people carrying a grudge against him thirty years ago,
and executed a plan to take World down
in collaboration with the Navy.
That was when you guys were still rookies.
Do you remember it?
Yeah, I think so.
The allied forces of the Navy and the pirates were cornered
and they almost had to retreat
after an intensive battle against World.
But things had turned around thanks to the spies
that the Government had sent in,
besides our efforts.
The World Pirates were taken down.
Why has he returned now, then?
I have no idea.
I heard a rumor once that he had been locked up
at Impel Down, frozen and sleeping.
Sengoku-san told me
that there were some prisoners
who snuck out of Impel Down...
beyond the four prisoners
that Blackbeard took from Level 6.
And World was on that list.
He's the last person you want to be out of prison.
On top of that, we're relocating Navy HQ
and making the transition to the new system.
It's the worst possible time.
He's a More-More Fruit user.
He can make things 100 times bigger
and faster and channel that into an attack.
People don't call him
"Destroyer of the World" for nothing.
Based on information
about his campaign of terror,
he's ratting around this area for sure.
Get some warships ready!
There you are.
World.
Do you really want to go to Marineford?
Worried? There is nothing to be worried about.
That's why we need the Empress.
She's been summoned by the Government and if we can hold her as a hostage,
we can get to Marineford easily.
And once we get there,
we can fire the giant cannon...
right at Mary Geoise,
the capital of the World Government!
Picture it in your mind.
Mary Geoise blowing up.
The Navy soldiers will be freaked out!
It's gonna be great!
I'm opposed to this plan!
Opposed?
I thought that we wanted that cannon
and this ship so we could be free!
That's why we're gonna use it
against the Government!
Because they are taking away people's freedom!
Maybe, but...
All you guys have to do
is just shut up and do as I say!
You must follow my order! Even if you're my big brother,
I'm not gonna go easy on you
if you disobey me!
Captain! It's the Kuja's ship!
It's coming towards us!
Here they come!
Let's do it, Big Bro!
This is where the Card was leading us but...
I don't see a thing.
What's this noise?
What the hell?!
Is that an island?!
It's coming out of the water!
It's big!
Thank you for coming all the way,
Empress of Amazon Lily!
Your sisters are here!
Big Sis!
Big Sis, I'm sorry!
Sonia! Mari!
We'll get you out soon!
That kid is here, too.
He's quite tough. That's for sure.
If you want them back, come on board!
You're always welcome!
Yeah, right! Evasive maneuvers!
Hancock! Get closer already!
I know!
Do they think they can get away?
I'll take care of it!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
He is a Devil Fruit user, isn't he?
Give me some bullets!
More-More Fiftyfold Cannon!
Armament Haki!
Luffy!
Don't!
Let go of me!
I won't let him die!
Salome!
You have to calm down, Snake Princess!
You're a Devil Fruit user, too!
If you dive into the water, you'll drown as well!
Luffy!
Empress! If you don't wanna die,
give yourself up and go with them!
The audacity to do that to my beloved
and still talk to me like that!
Guys, you can just kill her!
Wait, World!
I thought we were gonna hold her hostage!
We can just nail her dead body
on a pole and head to Marineford.
Kill her!
Love-Love Beam!
What?
That's the Kuja's power to turn people to stone!
Luffy!
Oh, I'm glad that you're okay!
Yeah, sorry!
I dropped my guard!
The name "Luffy" reminds me of Straw Hat but...
Great! I guess she wants me to kill her.
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Don't bother.
I'll take care of them.
Sebastian. Can you do it in five minutes?
Two minutes is enough for me.
You ready?
Yeah!
Luffy! Let's get inside from there!
Great Water Shot!
You wanna go see our captain, don't you?
Let me lead you... to hell!
Get out of our way!
Just turn to stone!
Love-Love Beam!
Why is it not working against him?!
Am I not attractive to him?!
Apologies! I'm blind so...
your attractiveness means nothing to me!
What about this?!
Gum-Gum...
Jet Pistol!
Not bad!
He's quite tough!
Let me return the favor!
Hey, that's an island, isn't it?
Hold on... No, that's a big ship!
No way!
And something's going crazy!
Is it a Giant?
It's a Fish-Giant—a crossbreed species between a Giant and a Fishman.
Oh, it's a fight!
Let me see!
Get out of my way!
Somebody's fighting?
Today's the special day that I, Buggy-sama, will make my debut as a Warlord!
Who's fighting?!
That Jolly Roger is...
I-I-It's no good!
It's the World Pirates!
They're the reason the Warlords were summoned!
What?!
N-No way!
That's too much to be a coincidence...
What a coincidence!
On top of that, the Fish-Giant is fighting against...
Straw Hat Luffy
and the Pirate Empress—Boa Hancock!
Straw Hat?
Why is he here?!
Captain Buggy!
This is your chance!
Since our jailbreaking friend from Impel Down, Straw Hat,
and your fellow Warlord, the Snake Princess, are here,
we can bring down World
and take him with us as a present!
Yeah, if you can take out World,
the Navy and the Government will think highly of you!
You're gonna be a star!
A star?
It's not gonna be that easy.
Wait. I don't know why Straw Hat is fighting against World but...
the Navy is looking for him!
Even if he takes down World, he can't stay here for long.
What about letting them take down World
and then we take all the credit?
It's a big chance!
Wait a sec!
We don't know if those two are gonna win!
That's right!
Guys!
Let the Navy know that we, the Buggy Pirates, are fighting against the World Pirates now!
Oh! Captain Buggy is going for it!
What are you up to?
Okay, listen.
Once they know that the "Destroyer of the World"
and I, a Warlord, are engaging a war here,
people like the admirals will come!
I see! If things go wrong,
we can just run away leaving the rest to the Navy!
Right! Luckily, it's not too far from Marineford.
They're gonna be here right away!
Then, we can just sit back and watch.
Straw Hat! Good luck fighting for my credit!
Did he run?!
No!
Great Shark Arrows!
Luffy!
You bastard!
Perfume Femur!
Camouflage Air!
What?!
Whoa-whoa!
Straw Hat's gonna lose soon if nothing's done!
That's not good!
Hancock!
I'm fine!
Well done spotting me
while I was camouflaging myself!
But this is it!
Go to hell!
Spin Tornado!
Gear 3:
Gum-Gum...
Gigant Pistol!
Sebastian, you disappoint me!
Luffy!
Let's go, Hancock!
O-Okay, honey!
You've got to be kidding!
Gairam. Lead me to them.
Roger that.
Why don't you keep an eye on the hostages?
World!
Wait! I can't let you walk away!
You're kind of cute!
Why don't you work under me?
Negative Extra Big Hollow!
I-I wish I'd been born
a cross between an amoeba and a water flea...
You're gross.
Don't want you.
Luffy!
You're...
No way! Straw Hat!
Wh-Who is she?
Do you know her?!
Um... I don't remember who she is...
But thanks for helping us!
Y-You have no reason to thank me!
It was just a coincidence.
He said he was gonna go somewhere so I just came along to kill time.
So I wasn't thinking about helping you...
Where did they go?
That girl called him "Straw Hat."
I knew it!
What's wrong with this ship?!
The floor crumbled!
Luffy, who was that girl?
That flying girl!
Oh! She is... um...
I think I met her before but what was her name?
He's trying to fool me!
I-Is this what they call "cheating"?!
Which way should we go?
Who's that girl?
Where did she come from...
What?!
Hey, hey!
What is he doing here?!
How should I know?
Maybe he was summoned
by the World Government, too!
Maybe, he's up to get the credit
for taking Byrnndi World down
before anybody, like us!
That means he's gonna ruin all of our plans!
Well, he's a very faithful guy
so I'm sure that's what he's here for!
That stupid shithead!
Why does he wanna do such an unnecessary thing?!
Then, we have to leave
our traces somewhere at any cost!
Traces?
Traces!
Oh yeah!
Guys! Now we've got some strong backup!
It's time to fight!
Let's charge!
Yeah!
Hey, Straw Hat was there.
What's going on?
I have no idea.
What the hell?!
It's like a maze!
Oh, it's an open space!
But what is this place?
We don't know which way to go anyway.
Luffy, let's go this way!
Okay!
Luffy!
What happened?!
Are you okay, Luffy?!
I almost killed the Empress.
Hancock, you can just go ahead!
But...
Just go!
Okay. Please be careful, Luffy!
Yeah, I got it!
World, be careful!
You better not underestimate that kid!
He's the pirate who raided Marineford to rescue his brother Portgas D. Ace, and raised havoc!
He is Monkey D. Luffy!
Monkey D.?
Don't you remember?
He's the grandson of Garp—the Marine!
That old man with the fists?!
But Navy HQ was thrown into chaos
because of a brat like this?
And... did you get to save your brother?
I thought so!
You're not strong enough to save anybody...
Shut up!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Gear...
2!
Jet Gatling!
You're not dead yet?
S-Stop.
He is World, isn't he?
This is the weapon storage.
I'll give you a chance.
Swords.
Spears, guns, batons... Use whatever you want.
Maybe you can beat me, then.
I don't need it!
What stupid pride.
I don't need...
any weapon!
Jet Pistol!
There's Haki!
Don't push your luck!
You can't even control your Haki!
You couldn't even save your own brother
because you're too weak!
I'm gonna teach you
that you can never keep up with my speed!
More-More Tenfold Speed!
I don't know why you came along
with the Empress but...
let me tell you something.
You're not strong enough to save anybody!
That Empress is next.
Straw Hat!
He got beaten so easily!
What should we do?!
Since he lost so easily,
I don't think my plan's gonna work out...
Idiots! What are you doing?!
Treat him as best as you can and get him back on track!
You care about your friend so much!
Captain Buggy, I'm gonna follow you
for the rest of my life!
You guys! For real?
Garp's grandson, huh?
Garp! Sengoku!
Why are you guys doing this?! I'm disappointed in you two!
That fool!
We shouldn't have let him talk!
Maybe he's right.
World, what's going on?
They joined hands
with the pirate alliance to bring us down!
What?!
I'm sure that the World Government is behind it!
What're we gonna do, World?
The same as usual!
We take out everyone who stands in our way!
Right, Sebastian?!
Right!
It's not gonna be as easy as we expected.
We're taking a lot of damage.
Let me go!
I'm gonna kick his ass in a one-on-one fight!
No need for that.
What is Cipher Pol doing here?
There will be a sudden change soon.
What's going on?
Why... Why did they stop firing?!
World!
World...
What do you think you're doing?!
You can't fight the World Government!
It's impossible to win!
We can't follow you anymore!
Th-They told us they won't charge us
if we turn you over and surrender!
Who told you that?!
You've been bought off by the Gov't?!
N-Not just us!
They told us you did, too!
Don't tell me you fell for it!
World!
It has started.
Launch an all-out attack!
I thought you guys were my friends.
You're very strong, Captain.
Don't tell me you guys are Cipher Pol!
What the hell is that?
It's an intelligence agency of the Gov't!
You are right.
We have spent time with you
as your crew members
but that was our mission. And it's over.
World!
World...
Stop! Don't let him get away!
Nightin, Gairam, everybody, run!
Byojack... What are you saying?
What about the captain?!
I know.
But we're all gonna die for nothing if we stay!
I give you an order as acting captain!
Survive!
What is he saying?
Alright! I'm sorry, Captain!
Stop!
Sebastian! Please!
They've gotten away!
They're wounded.
They won't live long.
They've betrayed me.
I'm not gonna go through that again!
Where is the Empress now?
She'll get to Nightin soon.
Nightin...
What's that?
Don't you trust me?
Okay! Then, I will take her down
no matter what and bring her to you!
Hey, how is he?!
He stopped bleeding but...
He's saying something!
I don't wanna... let them go through that again!
I never wanna go through that again!
I don't know what you're talking about but if you don't wanna go through it,
pull yourself together, Straw Hat!
Wake up!
Why don't you wake up already?!
Shit Hat!
You can just go ahead!
He risked his life to...
save me!
I'm so ashamed of myself
for suspecting him of cheating!
I have to keep going for him and my sisters!
What's this place?
And what's this smell?
Welcome, Pirate Empress.
How disrespectful can one be?
To not even give me your name
and talk to me with your back turned!
I can't believe they made
such an immature girl like you a Warlord!
The World Government has made a poor judgment!
I'm the ship doctor of the World Pirates and a Kanpo Kenpo master—Nightin.
I need to go on.
Show me the way to my sister.
I know a lot about you. Byojack gave me information.
I have a strategy to ward off your Love-Love power!
I'm not interested in listening to your nonsense.
Kanpo Kenpo Secret Medicine!
Fishwort Hell!
Love-Love Beam!
It's so bitter!!
Your power didn't work for me!
In this "Fishwort Hell,"
I blended hundreds of bitter medical herbs!
So it's the bitterest kanpo medicine in the world!
It cleared the wicked desire in my heart.
That's why your Love-Love power didn't work!
Next, it's this one!
Kanpo Poison Mist!
What's going on?
It must be so embarrassing that you can't move!
And now...
Kanpo Kenpo...
Secret Medicine!
Yes!
Oh, yes!
Bouncy!
Hey!
Ginseng Newcomer!
I'm 80 years old but with rejuvenating kanpo,
I can look like this!
Get ready! Kanpo Kenpo Technique:
Kakkon Toe... Toe...
Toe, Toe, Toe... Toe-kick!
Cordyceps Soul Shot!
How do you like it?
This is the power of Kanpo Kenpo
which consists of kanpo medicine and kenpo!
Slave Arrow!
Kanpo Dome!
How about this, then?
Pistol Kiss!
No, no! It's no use!
People used to call me
the "Queen of Kanpo Kenpo"!
I'm as strong and attractive as you!
Could you do me a favor?
Please shut your bloody mouth.
It's bitter!
So damn bitteeeer!
She's like a goddess or something!
What a femme fatale!
But...
No matter how many times you try,
your power won't work on me!
Cordyceps Soul Shot...
Burst!
Th-That's not fair!
No?
Oh no! Oh no!
You look pale.
It's only natural to be fascinated by me and become tense.
You can't resist.
The whole world is gonna celebrate if you die here.
Because I'm that...
beautiful!
She's looking down on me so much that she's actually looking up!
I'm not interested in women at all in the first place!
I really love men!
Go to hell, Hancock!
I'm scared!
How sexy!
No, no, no, no!
Oops!
S-She's so beautiful!
Love-Love Beam!
You were wrong.
There's nothing in this world that can block out my beauty.
Nightin...
Hey!
Why don't you wake up
already, Straw Hat?!
You fool!
If you go, you may not be able
to see your friends again!
Luffy!
Luffy.
Luffy-san!
Come back alive at any price!
You're not strong enough to save anybody!
Hey! I thought you wanna take down World!
Wake up now!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Whether or not I can save anybody...
I'll never know until I try!
Where did he go?!
H-He went that way!
I'm gonna kick his ass at any cost!
Where are you, World?!
Are you okay?
I-It worked out as planned.
It's obvious he's lying.
This way?
Huh?
How is this possible?
That kid... He's still alive.
Byojack! Can I take care of him?
Gairam.
He's already in the trap that I made.
Count on me!
Taking advantage of this mess,
the new Warlord—Buggy the Clown—
and his crew snuck onto the ship, too!
Be very careful!
I'll finish them all!
Gairam...
Cube Break!
Wh-What's going on?!
Damn! This way, maybe?
Cube Break!
My name is Gairam.
I ate the Cube-Cube Fruit and I'm a cube man!
I can cut anything into a cube!
For example...
Straw Hat!
I'm not gonna let you get to Captain World!
Cube...
Booster!
Cube Booster!
That was easy.
Stay crushed for the rest of your life.
I guess it's about time
for Shit Hat to finish off World!
Stop!
What are you guys doing on our ship? We didn't permit you to get on board.
He doesn't look so friendly to us!
I'm gonna kill you all!
Cube Booster!
He's a Devil Fruit user!
It's obvious!
I thought I was gonna die!
Straw Hat!
What is he still doing here?!
I'm surprised!
Why are you still alive?!
Because I'm a rubber man!
Hey, why are you still wandering around here?!
It couldn't be helped!
I didn't know which way to go!
Didn't you bluster in front of me
like you're a big deal?!
Stop whining and just go fight World already!
Or my plan will be ruined!
That's my Captain!
What?
He treated him, encouraged him,
and he's now saying
"I'll take this one so you go ahead"!
You're a pirate with a heart of gold!
What?
How could they interpret it like that?
Captain Buggy!
I'm so happy to be part of your crew!
We'll commit ourselves
to making your dream come true!
Buggy!
Hey, what should we do?
Let's just go with the flow.
Buggy!
Wh-What are you gonna do?!
Yeah! When I come to think of it,
I guess he has a point!
Their bounties were higher than mine
when we were in Impel Down.
But now, they're all working under me.
That means I'm one of the great pirates now!
I'm not gonna be defeated by a small fry like this guy!
Straw Hat!
Leave this guy up to me and go beat World!
You don't have to worry at all!
Since I'm a legendary pirate now, I'm not gonna tell everyone...
that I saved your ass!
Thank me for the rest of your life!
Is that okay?
Are you trying to make a fool of me?!
I said "Go ahead," Shit Hat!
Okay! Thank you, Buggy!
Hey! The situation hasn't changed a bit!
How are you gonna settle this?!
What? Really?
Are they even strong?
Oh, well!
I gotta clear out you intruders anyway!
I'll show you the true power of a cube man!
Air Cube!
What?!
He compressed air?!
Air Cube Booster!
Candle Wall!
Just run!
I'll be counting on you!
That's nothing!
He was all talk.
Captain, which way should we go?!
It's a dead end, huh?
You have nowhere to run!
Cube Break!
What?!
Captain!
It's over!
Ha ha! Is that all you got?!
You're unbelievable, Captain!
You never give up even after you're compressed!
Then how about this?!
Cube Booster!
You idiot! It's no use!
You think so?
Totem Cube!
Wh-What are you gonna do?!
What do you think?!
This is what I'm gonna do.
How do you like being tormented to death?!
All right, one more!
Still more to go!
There you are now!
This is it!
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
I'm decompressed!
He's also a Devil Fruit user?
Come together!
My body parts!
What are you doing?!
I figured this was what I'd have to do!
What are you gonna do?!
Relax. I still have "it" up my sleeve.
"It"?
Yes. I swore that I'd never use it again.
Because it has the power
to blow up several towns at once!
You guys may get hurt, too.
Oh, you still have that kind of thing?!
That's our Captain Buggy!
Are you talking about the Buggy Ball?
Captain, he's right, isn't he?
Don't give it away!
Oh, isn't that the thing you used
on the Jailer Beast in Impel Down?
That's the Muggy Ball.
It's completely different.
But that's what I was gonna use.
Anyway, I'll use it, take back my torso
and then we'll run!
Enough with the chitchatting!
Air Cube!
Hit or miss! Blow away!
Special Muggy Ball!
Wow!
I got it!
Damn! I can't see a thing!
You shouldn't do that on my ship!
Perfume Femur!
Where did Luffy go?!
That way, ma'am.
What?
He's down on the floor!
Captain Buggy did it!
No, I think it wasn't him...
Forget it.
Let's just leave it at that.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, Long live Captain Buggy!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
All right, guys!
Let's take down World next!
Pull your shit together in a flashy way!
Yeah!
How much longer are you gonna be able to go on like this?
I can't believe this!
Byojack!
How's everything going?
How is this happening?
They got beaten.
Nightin and Gairam.
Who let Gairam fight?
What are you guys doing behind my back?!
Wait a minute!
They fought very hard...
for you!
For me?
Straw Hat wasn't dead!
But we didn't wanna give you any more trouble!
So they were all useless after all!
What were you thinking?!
Now,
the Empress is on her way here, isn't she?
She is. But...
Then I'll take care of the rest.
World, I'm sorry!
What are you apologizing for?
World.
This is not what we've ever wanted!
What we've dreamed about was...
Look, World!
This sea is connected
to so many islands and countries
that we've never seen before!
Isn't it cool?
Yeah, it is.
We gotta set out to—
Are you okay, Big Bro?
Yeah, don't worry.
Big Bro...
World, you gotta set out to sea someday.
There must be adventures beyond our imagination
waiting for you out there.
You're not gonna come with me?
I've been like this...
ever since I was a little kid so it's impossible.
Don't say that!
Do you wanna stay on this small island forever?
Travel far, learn about the world,
and live big for me!
Big Bro...
I... I wanna set out with you!
What?
To travel around the world... Are you gonna come with me?!
But I'm...
It's gonna be okay!
I'll protect you!
Let's sail out together!
World!
Don't cry!
We're brothers, right?
Several years later, we left the island.
It was supposed to be
an adventurous journey around the world.
World, that's enough!
You're gonna kill them!
We're the Byrnndi brothers! You better watch out next time!
Captain! First Mate Byojack got...
What?!
Anyone who stands in our way, whoever it is, we'll kick their ass!
We were supposed to be searching for freedom.
But we were merely pirates to everyone else.
The Navy and the Government
placed you on the wanted list eventually
and before we knew it
people started being afraid of you
and calling you the "Destroyer of the World."
A submarine?
Yes. If we can travel underwater, unless there's a need to surface,
we can avoid unnecessary battles.
Since we have so many crew members,
we need a bigger ship.
What about weapons?
I want a big cannon!
A truly massive one!
Why do we need such a thing?
If we avoid unnecessary battles, we don't need...
Big Bro, you got it backwards.
If we put on an insanely big cannon to show off,
the people who know about
my More-More power will stay away.
So we don't have to fight.
All right!
Count on me!
Our dream ship, huh?
Which means it symbolizes our freedom!
It's just a ship.
We had that idea thirty years ago.
And we were gonna build this ship,
Groseade, to pursue it!
We built this ship and were waiting for you not because we wanted
to take down the Government!
Big Bro, are you still talking about a crap like that?
You can just sit there and watch, to the end.
Because you're annoying!
I'm not gonna be fooled like that again.
I'm not the same person I used to be!
World! I told you it's a misunderstanding!
I know!
But I don't care anymore.
World!
I do still care!
Luffy!
Are you two okay?!
Wait there!
I'm gonna get you out!
You're such an undisciplined brat!
Why can't you stay out of this?
Pathetic!
They took good care of me once.
So I'm gonna save them!
And...
I can't protect my friends
if I allow myself to lose to a weakling like you!
Friends?
Protect your friends?
What are you talking about?
You couldn't even save your own brother!
But you think you can protect your friends?
What a joke!
I'm gonna finish you off in thirty seconds!
You can't beat me this time!
More-More...
Tenfold Shotgun!
Gear 2!
Luffy!
Oops, I miscalculated.
I only needed ten seconds.
What are you doing?
Even if you can move ten times faster or more,
it doesn't matter if I get ahold of you!
I see.
But...
More-More Thirtyfold Speed!
Jet Pistol!
What's wrong?
Can't hit me?!
Brat, you should realize that overwhelming speed...
can generate overwhelming power!
Fiftyfold Speed!
Furious Hammer!
Luffy!
It's not working!
Because I'm a rubber man!
Oh yeah.
Gear 3:
Gigant Pistol!
It's not working!
Then, what about... this?!
Jet Pistol!
Even if...
you can use Armament Haki...
Jet Gatling!
It doesn't mean anything...
if you can't hit the target!
Friends?
Brother?
You can't protect anybody like that!
Captain Buggy, this is...
Thank God!
We finally got out of there!
I can say goodbye to this gloomy ship now!
You're giving away your real thoughts.
Oh no!
Dammit!
I was gonna take down World with my own hands
but I went the wrong way!
Captain Buggy, that aside, look there!
I-It's a fleet of Navy ships!
What are they doing here?!
You told us to call them!
Oh, I did, didn't I?
Hey! I'm here!
The new Warlord—Buggy-sama—
who is now fighting against
"Destroyer of the World," Byrnndi World, is here!
Somebody's waving
his hands towards us from the deck.
Who cares!
All ships, start firing!
What?!
This is no good!
The Navy is gonna find Luffy!
Bring us around to the back now!
Roger that.
What's going on?!
We have a problem, World!
A fleet of Navy ships is here!
The Navy?!
Hey, don't you think
the Navy's trying to sink the ship?
Shouldn't we just leave?
Great!
World?
I didn't expect the Navy would come to us!
Hey, Byojack!
Let's fire it and destroy the Navy ships!
Prepare the cannon!
That's ridiculous!
If you fire it at that short distance,
this ship's gonna sink from the impact!
I don't care!
Hurry up!
I thought it was—
A "symbol of our freedom"?
What bullshit!
The ship and cannon are just tools!
I don't know what you guys were thinking
but my mind was already made up when I broke out of Impel Down.
Then you guys came to pick me up with this ship.
So I decided to use this ship to carry out my own purpose!
It's pretty logical, isn't it?
And that purpose is to get revenge against the World Government?!
I couldn't care less about what will happen
to this ship, let alone you guys!
Gairam, Nightin, and Sebastian are our friends, aren't they?!
Friends?
I've never trusted them nor you from the beginning!
I don't need any friends!
You're lying!
You aren't that kind of person...
You guys are the same as this ship,
you're just tools to me!
World!
If you can't follow my orders,
I don't need you!
Did you say "Friends are tools"?
"You don't need any friends"?!
Damn you!
Screw you!!
Luffy!
Hancock!
Take your sisters!
The Pirate Empress?
I'm gonna beat the hell out of this guy!
Mari! Sonia!
Are you okay?!
Big Sis!
Luffy! Come back to the ship at any cost!
I will!
I don't need the Warlord as a hostage anymore.
I'm gonna fight you as you wish!
Praying to God won't help you defeat me!
No, it will!
Why are you so sure of that?!
I'm not gonna get beaten by a guy...
who sees his friends as tools!
What's wrong with abandoning someone useless?!
You abandoned your brother, too, didn't you?!
What a pain in the ass!
You can't protect anybody after all!
Neither your brother,
your friends nor anybody else!
You're right.
I couldn't...
save Ace's life!
But I still have...
friends who are waiting for me!
Enough already!
To protect my friends...
To become the Pirate King...
World!
I have to beat you up!
He's getting stronger while we're fighting!
Gum-Gum...
Jet Gatling!
More-More Hundredfold Speed!
Gum-Gum...
Red Hawk!
It's Ace's flame!
I made a promise to Rayleigh and Hancock.
I can't die here!
It's not like the Navy didn't know
that we were there, right?!
In any case, we need to get away as far as we can!
Guys, keep swimming!
And you right there!
Don't get my legs wet!
Aye aye, sir!
It's a strategic withdrawal!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Luffy! Hurry up and come out!
What are you gonna do?!
I haven't lost yet.
Our friends were beaten and our ship is in tatters.
And you're wounded all over.
What more can you do?!
I'm not gonna be satisfied
unless I fire it at them at least once.
You're really gonna use it?!
I was gonna use it anyway.
I'm sorry that I was lying to you guys.
But you guys betrayed me once, too.
So we're even.
As I thought, you're still holding a grudge!
But that was—
I'd been sleeping in ice!
It seems like only yesterday to me!
I'll never forget.
How could I forget about it?
World...
Where is the exit?
A giant cannon emerged from the bow!
Meteor Volcano!
Now what?!
The least I can do now is...
land one hit against them!
More-More Hundredfold Cannon!
Get out of my way!
I am Byrnndi World!
E-Evacuate!
Luffy!
Luffy! He hasn't come out yet?!
Big Sis! Please calm down!
World.
This ship's gonna sink in no time.
We have lost.
Let's start over—just the two of us.
Let's go, World.
Across the sea.
Luffy!!
Luffy?
Oh no! He's gonna fall into the water!
Luffy!
Hancock!
Luffy! I'm glad you're alive!
What's so funny?
I don't know.
You're weird.
Ultimately, what is it you wanted to do?
I taught you all the basics of Haki.
There is nothing more for me to teach you.
Rayleigh.
I'm thinking about going back to Sabaody.
What are you gonna do?
I sent out the message one and a half years ago.
"3D2Y."
It means "two years later
instead of three days later," doesn't it?
We needed to get stronger to carry on our journey.
I'm sure they know it, too.
You still have six more months.
Yeah! I can't wait to see
how they changed after two years
and I have to become stronger just like they did.
I'm gonna stay here
and keep training for six more months.
I see. Then, keep improving your Haki until you can control it consistently.
I got it!
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Thank you, Rayleigh!
Six months later
It's been two years already.
All right!
Let's go!
Sunny!
We made you wait two long years.
Look at that beautiful woman over there!
Is that our super archaeologist...
Robin?!
You haven't changed a bit, Franky.
I'm going to the shore.
I wanna go fishing.
No, you can't, shithead!
The others will be here any time now,
so just shut up and follow me back to the ship!
Usopp!
Look at you! You've grown!
How have you been?
He's right!
You're so much fluffier too!
Long time no see, Chopper!
Nami?
That's right!
Thanks a lot!
You showed up just in time!
You guys!
There's a whole lot of stuff I want to talk to you about!
But never mind that!
I just want to thank you for going along
with my selfish request for the last two years!
It won't be the first time. Or the last.
Got that right!
You've always been like this!
Set sail!!
Yeah!!
You needn't say anything, I understand
It'll be alright
As long as you have someone
who is there waiting for you
When I made it here, I thought I had finally reached my goal
Yet something still seems to be missing
So we will carry on...
To the next...
(Download all the pain and struggles,
everything of your past)
Go to the next...
(Upload it all into a future that cannot be predicted)
Let's move on to the next...
(Embrace my body trembling with fear, and let us dance a dance of battle)
Go to the next, now
(Together, let us take the next step,
to the next stage)
Head for an unseen future and unlock yourself
Whatever may be waiting for you on the way
Do these days over
and unlock your heart
Don't worry if you stumble into tomorrow
The sleepless night has come to an end,
and the endless night has come to an end
Now if beyond those, there is a way forward...
We'll go to the next step & stage
FIN