Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made a raid on Navy HQ to rescue his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
But his struggle ended in vain as the war came to a close.
Ace is really dead, isn't he?!
Yes, he is dead!
Ace!!
Luffy and Ace
The Story of How the Brothers Met!
The Paramount War at Marineford left a scar in many people's mind.
10 years ago, in the East Blue,
there was a small village called Windmill Village where people lived peacefully
but not far from it was Mt. Corvo where people seldom stepped foot.
Only the strong could survive there and the weak who entered were doomed to die.
What I'm saying is, grandpa...
I'll become the Pirate King...
Cut the crap!
Let me... Let me go!
On top of eating that Devil Fruit,
you're talking nonsense!
Luffy! Both you and Ace have to become
Monkey D. Garp
Ten years ago
【              】
the strongest Navy soldiers!
Ow, ow, ow, dammit!
Monkey D. Luffy
Ten years ago
【              】
My body is rubber but why is it painful?!
Let me go, grandpa!
It was a mistake to leave you in Windmill Village!
Of all things, you like pirates?! You fool!
You can't make friends with Red-Haired Shanks!
I wanna become...
Ouch!
...a strong man like Shanks!
Hey!
What's this place?
Stop it!! Whoever you are, do you wanna get killed?!
It's me.
G-Garp-san!
Curly Dadan
Mountain Bandit Dogra
Mountain Bandit Magra
You're looking good.
Give me a break! Please, you gotta have mercy on me!
Ace is 10 years old now!
Oh yeah, already? How is he?
It's not funny!
We can't handle him anymore! You have to take him!
--Putting that aside...
--Don't put it aside!
You're annoying, kid!
Look after him, too.
Hey, Luffy, say "hi" to them.
Yo!
Who is that kid?
He is my grandson.
What?
What?!
One more?!
He's Garp's... I mean, Garp-san's grandson?!
We can't!
Alright then, Here's your choice.
Do you wanna spend all your life in prison or raise him?
There are many crimes you committed that I've overlooked.
Come on!
Well, I don't wanna get arrested but...
Sometimes I think that maybe it's better to be in prison than take care of Ace...
But you want us to look after your grandson, too? I bet he's also a monster.
Crappy shack!
You wanna fight?!
Not listening!
Boss! Are you alright?!
What is it?! Ugh, spit! Gross!
Who did it?!
Hey, you!
Say "sorry"! It's gross!
Ace!
Are you back, Ace?
Portgas D. Ace
Ten years ago
【              】
Hey, say "sorry"!
Luffy, this is Ace. He's 3 years older than you.
You're gonna live here with them from today.
What?! You can't just do that!
Be nice!
Is it decided?!
Any problem with that?
We'll take him!
That's all from me. I'll stop by when I have time.
--Um... What about some child support?
--Put it on my bill.
--This is not a bar...
--Huh?
--You're always welcome!
--Boss, we can't take care of one more kid!
--Shut up! Let's just eat first! Fix it!
--Okay!
Say "sorry"!
Wait!
I'll leave this hat with you.
Where did he go?
Who are you?
Let me go!
Give me your money or I'll kill you!
I don't have any!
Then tell your parents to bring some money here!
--Grandpa is my only...
--That's fine. What's his name?
Garp-san.
Is this kid...?!
He's gonna live here with us.
--Why did you accept?!
--This is not a day-care!
Our boss has no guts!
Shut up you all!
It's time to eat!
--Give it to me, fool!
--It's my meat!
I want some meat!
--You already ate!
--I want more!
I'm not gonna give in to young people!
--You got to share!
--It's a dog-eat-dog world.
His arm stretches!
Dog?
It's your turn to wash dishes!
Can I have some more, pops!
I'm a woman!
Do you even know where you are now?!
No.
Then I'll tell you.
This is a den of the Dadan family, mountain bandits that rule Mt. Corvo!
Mountain bandits? I hate mountain bandits!
Shut up, you little shit! We're annoyed by having a kid like you!
If you don't wanna stay here, that's fine!
Go away and die like a dog somewhere!
Easy, easy, boss.
I wanna eat more...
I wanna have that meat, too.
These are all from a bison that Ace brought.
He gave us a cut of the take so everybody can eat.
The mountain bandits' world is rough sailing.
You're gonna have to work pretty hard from tomorrow!
Cleaning, laundry, polishing shoes and weapons,
burglary, robbery, fraud, and murder!
Remember, you can't tell Garp what we make you do!
One bowl of rice and one glass of water for a day!
That's all I can guarantee you.
You gotta get everything else by yourself and grow up on your own.
Okay!
"Okay"?! Why don't you cry or something?
I'm fine because grandpa threw me into a jungle once
and there was water to drink and frogs, snakes, and mushrooms to eat in the forest!
Plus, I'll become a pirate someday so...
...I must be strong like that!
--Boss!
--Are you alright?!
What're you doing?!
Here we go!
Where is he going?!
Where are you going?!
Did you just say "pirate"?
He's not listening!
Hey!
See? He's too tough!
That's why I didn't wanna take care of Garp's grandson!
Easy, easy, boss.
Hey!
Wait for me!
My name is Luffy! I'm not mad about you spitting on me anymore!
Why are you laughing?!
He only spilled some booze on me. It's nothing worth getting mad over.
It's nothing worth getting mad over. Let's become friends!
Are you going somewhere?!
It's a dead end!
Hey! Ace is back!
Food!
Ace, did you come back alone?
Where is Luffy? I thought that you were with him.
I don't know.
That fool, where is he and what is he doing?
Maybe he's dead already.
We are dead if Garp finds out about this.
Boss must be pretty worried I bet!
--Get hold of yourself, boss!
--What did you say?!
I said it's not good that we lost him on the first day!
Who cares! if he dies, he dies!
Garp is gonna kill us.
First of all, why should we look after Garp's grandson?!
We're not nannies! He has to take care of his own grandson!
--Why don't you say it to him?
--You have a problem?!
What if Gold Roger had a child?
Of course I know what'd happen to him! He'd get his head cut off for sure!
I want to hear from him as he dies:
"I'm sorry I was born! I'm just a piece of trash!"
I'm already giving up on Ace, too!
I don't care if he dies or not. I'll just tell Garp it was an accident.
It's true that "the devil's children have the devil's luck"!
He's the devil's son!
If the Government finds out about this, what do you think they'd do to us?!
Easy, easy, boss.
You're drinking too much!
One week later
One week later...
How annoying!
Why don't you shut up?
Boss! Boss Dadan!
Who is it?
--You!
--Luffy came back!
You fool! You're alive! You...!
Easy, easy, boss.
Where were you?!
Easy, easy. Where were you and what were you doing?
I've been chased by wolves at the bottom of the valley.
What were you doing at the bottom of the valley?
--Anyway, it's nice that you're okay.
--Yeah.
It's not okay! The pest came back!
Why don't you go to bed tonight? You gotta work from tomorrow!
Already?
What's up?
Are you gonna go somewhere today, Ace?
Take me with you! Let's become friends!
Wait for me!
Boss! He's going after Ace again!
Hey! You gotta do chores around the house!
No thank you!
You little shit! You're out of control!
Easy, easy, boss.
--Bring him back right now!
--Yes, ma'am.
Hey!
Ace!
Ace! Let's become friends!
The 8th day...
Ace!
Wait for me!
Boss!
Work, you little shit!
It's no use...
--Bring him back!
--Yes, ma'am.
I'm not gonna lose you today!
I can do that!
Let's become friends!
10 days have passed...
--Luffy!
--He's gone already...
Look for him!
He kept going after Ace and losing him.
But it went on everyday.
Ace!
1 month...
2 months...
Ace!
No matter if it rained and was windy...
Luffy kept going after Ace desperately.
Luffy is chasing Ace again?!
How does he never learn after getting hurt so many times?
Damn! He has to stop making me worry!
So you're worrying.
N-No way! Stop talking nonsense!
A bee-hive fell on me.
Who are you?
Ace!
Ace! Hey!
I can't believe he's coming this far. He's so persistent.
Oh crap!
Damn! I lost him again! Ace runs so fast!
Is it Ace?!
That's the beast of Mt. Corvo! No one can beat it!
Why is he not running?! It's gonna eat him!
I-I feel weak at the knees!
That fool!
Now, Luffy had been chasing Ace for 3 months with cuts and bruises all over...
It's the end of the forest.
What is this place?
Discarded junk lies around everywhere, and smoke fills the air.
This is Gray Terminal, a town of outlaws.
Ace once took charge of the thugs here,
amassing funds in order to become a pirate someday.
Along with one other friend...
Next time, on One Piece:
"Here Comes Sabo!
The Boy From Gray Terminal"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Here Comes Sabo!
The Boy From Gray Terminal