Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
He's not here!
Which guy?
That guy!
That guy?
That tin bastard!
Ahhh! That bastard!
I'll find him right away and finish him off!
What's going on here?
What have they done... to my castle?!
Doktorin...
Hm?
He called me...
his friend...
When the Kingdom's Rule Ends!
The Flag of Faith Flies Forever
This is no time to be in bed resting!
I should get out of here
while Doktorin isn't around!
I couldn't take being stuck here for three days.
Huh?
I got lucky!
Looks like I can leave without a problem.
Wh-Who's... this guy?!
You must be one of the Straw Hats!
He definitely looks like a bad guy!
No, that's not true at all!
I don't have any idea what you're talking about!
What?! I'm wrong?! Really?!
That's right!
I'm a navigator who's just passing by here!
Oh, I see...
Well then... see ya...
Okay!
Hm?!
Liar!
– No!
– You idiot! Wait!
Don't come this way! Go away!
Did I gain some weight recently?
Then I'll do this...
Munch-Munch Factory!
I'll eat myself!
Ah! What's that?!
H... He turned into a bucket!
Miraculous bone structure
shaping technique... complete!
Slim Wapol!
I won't let you escape.
No!
I'll eat you first!
I found you!
Huh? Was he that skinny before?
Ahh!
Luffy... Why is my jacket all beaten up...?
How much do you think I paid for this jacket?!
28,800 berries!
And that's the price after I talked them down!
I'm sorry, but that guy shot a bomb at me!
I couldn't help it!
Geez... but oh well. I'll forgive you.
I didn't expect it to come back in
good shape when I let you borrow it.
As payment for the damages,
you owe triple that amount plus some.
The total is 100,000 berries.
Consider it a loan.
Ahh!
Don't tell me you expected this to happen!
That's it, you bastards!
Darn! His body sure is made tough...
Look!
Believe it or not, this is the arsenal!
I'm the only one who has the key to this room.
Naturally, there are a wide
variety of weapons in here.
When I eat them up and make them
part of my body using Munch-Munch Shock,
you'll witness a horrific human weapon!
Now, be prepared. The door will open!
It'll be scary!
The key to that horrific door is...
gone!
No, this isn't over yet.
Ah! He's running away! Wait!
I've got another trump card.
Oh, it's just the key to the arsenal.
It would've been nice if it
were a key to a treasure room.
How disappointing...
Nami-san!
Good! You're safe!
What happened?! Why're you crawling
like that, Sanji-kun? Are you all right?
Nami-san, you're that concerned about me?!
If I get enveloped in that warmth...
Don't!
Nami...-san...
Wait! Wait, wait!
Dammit!
The upper levels are full of snow, too!
I won't let them get away with this...!
I won't!
I'll make them all experience
how great the king is!
The power of Drum is my power.
I'll use the ultimate weapon of Drum Kingdom...
the Tin Titan Royal Crown Seven Barrel Cannon!
I've now cornered you! Be prepared!
Humph!
It's you who's cornered, Straw Hat!
Time to be blown away!
Huh...?
A bird's nest...!
Snow Birds!
How dare you make fun of me!
I'm surprised to see a rope connected
to the castle from a place like this...
A young man in town found it by accident.
This place used to be Dr. Kureha's house!
This is a great view!
Yeah...
Hey, isn't this a little overcrowded?
We can't let Dalton-san go alone when he's injured!
We'll fight, too!
W-Well, I get it.
But we'll never get there like this!
Paddle! Paddle harder!
Dalton-san, don't push too hard.
Wapol...
Who do you think you are, Dalton?
"There's no medicine that
can cure fools" you say...?
Did you just call me a fool?
You think you've become an emissary of
justice who saves people or something?!
Don't be so full of yourself!
You're just a retainer!
A week or so in this cell will probably
make you realize your mistake.
I'd imagine an impulsive rebellion
wouldn't last so long.
You're an excellent guard the citizens trust.
Reconsider it, Dalton.
Thanks to that idiot doctor Hiriluk,
you just got caught up in a little fantasy!
Giving up your status and destroying the country...
What good will that do you?!
I'll forgive you, if you can just say...
"I'm sorry" to me, the king, Dalton-kun.
To hell with status! To hell with the king!
I'm the king! I'm the king of Drum Kingdom! I'm the king!
This is it for you.
It doesn't matter... if you're a king or god...
It doesn't matter who's great or who's not great!
After all, I'm a pirate.
It does matter, Straw Hat!
Drum Kingdom is a member of the World Government.
Now listen. This is a world-class offense!
Like I said, that doesn't matter, either!
This is my own fight!
Y-You damn Straw Idiot...!
I'll digest you!
Try and eat me.
Not yet! Munch-Munch Shock!
Tongue Cannon!
Ah! His tongue became a cannon!
Disappear!
Ahh!
Dalton-san! Please hang in there!
What should we do?
Dalton-san! Dalton-san!
Dalton-san!
I'm... I'm all right.
Dalton-san...
I'll make sure... to end this country!
To hell with history!
Hey hey, wake up, Dalton.
Governance is about caring
for your country... you say?
Governments don't need to have a heart.
He's right. What's important is the system.
Ah!
Wh... What're you doing?!
Let me go! Stop it!
I currently have many patients to treat!
Throw him into the sea!
If he resists, you can kill him.
Hey, let me go! Please!
My patients are waiting for me.
Please!
To hell with state control!
Good... So none of them are sick?
What's wrong with wishing
the country to have a heart?!
D... Dalton-san... What're you...
Dynamite!
Listen, everyone.
When we get to the castle and once
I get inside, lay on the ground.
Are you worried about him?
I'm not worried about him at all!
He's a pirate!
What an idiot!
He let his guard down!
Actually, that's you.
Wh-What?!
One, two...
What?! What're you going to do?!
Hey, let me go!
Gum-Gum...
Bowgun!
Doktorin...
Yeah... It seems... that it's finally come...
the end of the long nightmare...
End...
This country is sick right now.
Its citizens, king, and the
government, too, are all sick.
People suffer from a sickness of the heart.
I'll definitely save this country
using medical science one day.
Get out of here, quack!
Never come back!
Run, Chopper!
Whoa!
Ahh!
You'd better be prepared if
you're gonna meddle with
someone else's skull flag!
– Gum-Gum...
– Ahh!
Doctor...
– Hold on a sec!
– Gum-Gum-Gum-Gum-Gum-Gum...
– I'll give you status and a medal!
Look! There's someone on top of the castle!
Doctor...
The kingdom is...
Drum Kingdom is...
Then... I'll make you the viceroy...!
about to fall!
...Bazooka!!
Drum Kingdom was defeated by the skull.
Alright, then! I'll go check.
Don't worry. You can come later.
Ahhh, Zoro's going ahead of me again!
Serious power, activated!
Hey, let go!
Alright! I got your back.
Hey, if you're scared, you can come later!
Hm?
I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I'm not scared!
Because I'm...
What?!
Luffy!
Ah?! Zoro! Usopp!
Ah!
What'd you do that for, you jerk?!
Oh, it's you guys!
Since I recognized the clothes you're wearing,
I thought you were one of them.
So you guys came up, too.
Usopp, didn't you say you couldn't come up?
Don't be silly!
If I see a mountain in front of me,
I climb it. I'm that kind of guy.
But coming up this cliff was quite an adventure.
We came up by ropeway. Luffy-san,
are Nami-san and Sanji-san okay?
– Yeah, they're fine now.
– Now, get it together...
– Ahh, I'm glad to hear that!
– We were also attacked by
a huge condor on our way!
Man was I surprised.
But then I was like,
– I'm glad...
– or maybe I should say,
– just what you'd expect from me...
– So,
– The moment it flew at his heart,
– what were you doing on top of the castle?
– Captain Me dodged as if dancing
– I was beating the crap out of the king.
– and quickly rode on the flying condor!
– Then as I suspected... the one who
– It was actually me!
– flew far into the sky earlier was Wapol!
– I put a rope around its neck and said,
– You beat him...?!
– Yep! Why?
– "My name is Captain Usopp!"
So what about his two top men?
The reindeer beat them up.
Those two... A reindeer did...?
– How's that? Are you guys amazed?
– Oh yeah! Usopp,
– listen! I found a new friend!
– Check me out!
Hm? What?
Reindeer...
Reindeer...?
Blue nose...
Wait!
For laughing at Hiriluk's death, I apologize!
Without enough power, you'll just die in vain...
Don't sacrifice yourselves
any longer for this country...
You are that reindeer...
I see... You've been fighting
all this time since then!
Thank you.
Drum will definitely...
definitely be reborn...
Hm?
Ah!
Wh-What's that strange creature?!
A-A reindeer? No...
That's a... m-m-m-mons...
Hey, stop it!
Ahhh! It's a monster!
Don't call him a monster!
He's the new friend I was talking about!
What?! That thing is?!
He got shocked and ran away!
Wait! Monster!
Hey!
Reindeer!
Hey, wait!
Hey! Reindeer!
You're my friend!
– You're definitely my friend!
– Doctor...
– Hey!
– This is for the best, right?
– This is...
– Wait!
Wait! Reindeer!
No way I'd wait!
Nemuranai kono machi mo Ima dake wa madoromu
Even this sleepless town has dozed off for now
Kyou kara to kinou made
From today forth,
nani ka ga kawatte yuku
something's going to change
Kitto yarinaoseru hazu
I'm sure I can start fresh,
Datte hitori janai kara
since I'm not alone
Soba ni ite kureru dake de
Just by having you by my side,
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru
I feel I can become strong
Doko made ikeru kana
I wonder how far I can go,
mirai e tsuzuku basho
towards the place that leads to the future
Tooku de kagayaite sekai o tsutsumikomu
Off in the distance it shines, encompassing the world
Yoake mae
Before dawn
Doktorin, thanks for teaching me
medical science all this time.
Although I experienced many hardships,
I love this country where I met Doctor and you.
But I'm leaving. I'm going out to sea!
I wanna see the world with my own eyes!
Don't talk so cocky.
Next time, on One Piece:
Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms!
Miracle in the Drum Rockies.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms!
Miracle in the Drum Rockies