Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue his brother, Ace, who will be executed!
He got over the barricades in order
to make it to the scaffold with Jinbe's help
and faced the 3 admirals!
The Whitebeards then made it to the plaza, too!
An all-out battle between the Navy
and the Whitebeards has begun at Oris Plaza!
Ice Block: Partisan!
Pops, move on!
I'm counting on you!
All you have is courage.
But if you're not strong enough,
you can't save him no matter how hard you try.
Why don't you just get lost?
He is nothing but a bundle of energy who just bluffs. Young and clumsy.
But I like fools like him.
If I let you wreak havoc, this island won't survive!
Then why don't you protect it?
I'm on my way, Ace!
If you wanna go further, you have to kill me first!
The Power That Will Shorten One's Life
Energy Hormone, Redux
Garp the Hero...
...took part in their protection!
He fought against Gold Roger, the Pirate King, 20 years ago
and made his name in the world—
he's a legendary Navy soldier!
I heard that it was Garp who fought
Roger's competitor—Shiki the Golden Lion...
...here in Marineford with Sengoku and imprisoned him in Impel Down!
Don't get tripped up by his name, you fools!
He's just an old soldier!
If you'd lived through that era,
you should know that...
...you should focus on the enemy in front of you!
Hound Blaze!
You gotta stop destroying the city!
I told you to protect it!
Hurry and execute Ace!
Get a substitute right away!
Yes, sir!
Make a path!
A path to rescue Ace!
We still got those pains in the ass here!
I won't let you do it, monster!
I'll show you...
...the power of the New World!
Now is the chance!
Get to the scaffold!
How is he?
Not good at all! First aid won't help him!
He needs proper treatment!
Straw-boy can't fight anymore!
But...
What's the matter, Fire Fist?
Ace...
Gol D. Roger?
You mean Gold Roger?
Did you ask me if I know him?
Don't you realize why there is so much destruction in the world caused by pirates?
It's all Roger's fault!
His fault?
I heard that right before his execution,
he bullshitted about this great treasure thing...
...causing the idiot pirates who believed him to run wild.
He should've never been born in the first place!
He was just a worthless bastard!
Even after his death,
he causes the pirates to roam the seas!
He's such a nuisance—living or dead!
He was the biggest piece of shit
the world's ever seen! Remember that!
Huh? What's wrong? What are you getting mad for?
I mean, who are you, brat?!
What have you done in the city, Ace?
They're making a fuss over some punks
who almost got killed by a kid.
Oh, I thought they were dead.
What did you say?! If you cause trouble, I'm the one who'll get chewed out!
Are you listening, Ace?!
Honestly! How could he just leave
a kid like this with me?!
You wanna know about Roger?
He was just a great liar and a murderer!
It makes me laugh
that they call him the "Pirate King!"
He was more like the King of Bullshitters!
That's right!
Roger?
Don't mention the name that makes me sick, brat!
It's ruining my drink! Go away!
What are you looking at?!
What do you think you're doing, you little shit!
Look at you! You got beaten pretty badly!
Hey, Ace? I heard that you're out of control these days.
Old man, you have a grandson, right?
Does he look happy?
Oh, you're talking about Luffy!
He's growing up in fine feather!
Old man.
Huh?
Do you think...
...that I deserved to be born?
That's something...
...you'll see as you live.
Carry Straw-boy to the ship in a hurry!
I have no choice! We gotta save Ace-boy without him...
Iva-chan...
You came around!
Could you do me a favor one last time?
We're almost there! We'll be there soon, Ace!
Clear the way!
I'm...
Dammit!
Ace-san, wait for me! I'll save you with my life!
We're almost there!
We're on our way, Ace!
Ace, we'll save you at any cost!
Wait for us, Ace!
Don't give up!
Dammit! My mind is so warped! It's not the right time for this!
Pops and brother and friends are...
...going down one by one bleeding, but...!
Don't say "one last time!" It'll bring bad luck!
Please! Can you...
I'm so happy and I can't stop crying!
At this last moment,
I'm starting to think that I wanna live!
I beg you! Iva-chan!
Are you serious about this?!
Captain Buggy!
He's awake!
He's alive!
I'm so relieved!
What happened to me?
You got frozen by Blue Pheasant and...
Captain Buggy!
Oh no! It's too late!
Damn! You said that you were gonna conquer the world!
We really believed in you!
Oh no!
Ouch!
I got it!
Captain Buggy wanted to show us
how to save our frozen mates!
With his frozen body? How great he is!
Let's carry all the other frozen guys to the water!
Yeah!
Hey, before that...
Ow! Save me first, you fools! I mean...
Please help me, I'm drowning...
Captain Buggy!
You saved our lives how many times now?!
Damn, you're great! We'll follow you
to the end of the world!
You guys! Thank me as much as you want!
Looks like I still have my luck!
By the way, where's Mr. 3?
The last time we saw Brother 3
was before the barricades came up.
That bastard! He made it out of here!
Huh? Is this the wall that you're talking about?
The Navy tried to round up the Whitebeards with this!
We're caged birds because of this!
How ridiculous!
Do they really think that they can stop me with this cheap wall?
Damn you, Navy! Be ready for it!
Don't even think that you can get away with this!
Amazing! To have such conviction after just being defrosted!
That's how I am!
But what should I do?!
Get out of my way, magma brat!
Damn!
Pops!
Even you can't win out against the onslaught of time,
Whitebeard!
That's what I was afraid of the most!
Are you telling me to draw their sympathy
by putting these on?
Pops!
If you have an unguarded moment,
you will lose the fight!
Marco!
You can't look away like that!
Jozu!
Should I be the last voice you hear before you die?
Pops!
Hey, Pops is...!
What?!
Hey! It's too late for you to go out now!
Look, Koby, there's no question! It's obviously the Navy's victory!
Red Hound-san got Whitebeard
and Yellow Monkey-san and Blue Pheasant-san got Marco
and Jozu, 1st and 3rd division commanders!
And Straw Hat can't fight anymore after getting beaten up so bad!
That was the best they can do against all the forces of the Navy!
I will be much much stronger and...
I'll become a Navy...
...ad...
...admiral someday!
Whoa! Oh, I mean...
I-I-I'm sorry! I got carried away!
It's embarrassing! I wanna crawl in a hole!
After I met you, I became emboldened a little bit...
Koby!
You wanna fight me, right?
Then, of course you have to become such a heavy hitter!
After all, it was just a pipe dream for me to become an admiral!
Even Luffy-san's strength gave out before he accomplished his goal!
It's impossible for me because all I do is run despite being a Navy soldier!
It's just impossible!
It's over already! So let's just sit back
and enjoy it from here!
Alright, Koby?
Are you asking me
to inject another shot of Energy Hormone?!
That's insane!
You gotta stop it now!
You've been fighting since Impel Down!
You got poisoned and you were almost killed!
You're pushing it too far already!
Like I said before, Energy Hormone
is nothing more than a temporary treatment!
If you just keep using it,
you will die for sure afterwards!
If I'd be able to do all I could...
I'd be happy to die!
Let me fight, Iva-chan!
Pops got beaten!
Marco! Jozu!
If I can't fight now
and if I can't rescue Ace, I...
I'd rather take my own life afterwards!!
Let me have the strength to fight for now!
I said I can't! If I let you die now, I'd be too ashamed to face Dragon!
You hardheaded fool!
Where's the other guy?! What's taking him so long?!
Since it was such short notice,
he's having trouble getting ready...
Hey, hurry up!
Alright, let's go!
A-Ace...
All right!
Do whatever you want!
Hey, what are you doing to Straw Hat?!
S-Straw Hat is...!
N-No way! I thought he received a mortal wound by getting kicked
in the teeth by Yellow Monkey-san!
H-Hey! Where are you going?! It's too dangerous!
Koby...
Luffy-san!
Luffy!
Ace!!
Using Ivankov's Energy Hormone,
Luffy works up the last
of his strength and runs forth.
But the Navy forces form a massive wall in his path.
Among them stands one young man
trying to motivate himself
to achieve the heights he once swore to reach.
Next time, on One Piece:
"To Live Up to a Promise!!
Luffy and Koby Collide!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
To Live Up to a Promise!!
Luffy and Koby Collide!