All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After landing on Punk Hazard; an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen,
the Straw Hats learned about the hideous experiments
performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
and headed off to investigate but as things got going,
Luffy was unexpectedly approached by Trafalgar Law.
We're gonna form an alliance with the Heart Pirates?!
So what we're gonna do is kidnap the Master, right?
This is the last chance for you to reconsider.
That's okay. We're with you.
How does it feel to be loose after so long,
Smiley?!
"Capture M! The Pirate Alliance's Operation Launches!"
THE MOUNTAIN BEHIND THE LABORATORY PRESENT
Maybe from when I fell? Looks like I hit my head.
Oh, maybe I did, too. I have a huge headache!
We've wasted so much time. I wonder if the samurai is okay.
You made us take this side trip.
I thought we all wanted to do this!
It's a shame that we couldn't find the Yeti.
But I'll never forget the shadows that we saw!
That wasn't it. Don't fool yourself.
You said it was an enemy attack.
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
No, I didn't!
I don't believe it exists.
I believe it exists.
I just want to talk about whether it exists or not forever.
I'm impressed a little. You're kind of mature.
I'm very old, you know.
I don't like that indecisive attitude.
Hey! Samurai-san!
Where are you?!
If only we could find traces of his wooden clogs.
So heavy!
My breasts are heavy when I run!
I thought you wanted to save that samurai!
Oh no!
How romantic!
No, fool!
I don't care if you fall down!
Hey, you two! Take a look at this!
There is a footprint!
A trace of his wooden clogs?
It's nothing like that!
Then, it must be some centaur's footprint.
No!
Th-This is...
Look at this! Doesn't this look like the legendary Yeti's footprint?!
--Hey hey, don't be ridiculous. --Hey hey, don't be ridiculous.
Wow, is this for real?! There are mysterious footprints in the snow!
They're huge, aren't they?! I can't believe it!
And they look fresh!
If we follow them, we will find...
…one of nature's greatest mysteries!
A dead end?
Oh! Look! There are huge shadows behind us!
Don't tell me they're the Yeti...
What is this gas?!
All of a zudden, I can't zpeak clearly az if I kot drunk. I'm tired.
Iz it an enemy attack?!
These KYP gas canisters
make you drunk and drowsy regardless of whether or not you're a heavy drinker.
Down below the cliff is district F-16 filled with terrible Ice Spikes!
Three, for a starter.
Spikes?!
Hey, guys!
That was close...
We left their bodies at the bottom of the cliff in district F-16.
Can you recover them?
We arrived at district F-16.
We found three of the Straw Hats as informed. We'll recover their dead bodies.
Who are you calling dead?!
What?! She's alive!
She's just a girl - she can't fight us...
It doesn't matter if there're hundreds of you!
You underlings!
I have to be careful.
Nami-san's body is delicate.
I should avoid getting even a single bruise.
Excuse me for having one, Nami-san.
Now...
Wake up, you idiots!
In any case, hunting for nature's mysteries is over.
Should the samurai be around here?
I think so. He's probably still looking for his torso around the lake.
We almost made it to the lake.
Samurai-san!
Hey, samurai!
Samurai, come on out!
Samurai!
Did you get your ass kicked already?!
Come on out! Are you alright?! Samurai!
Samurai-san! We're calling you!
I wonder how far he went.
Maybe he found his torso already and went looking for his son.
Oh?! He's here!
What?!
I can't believe it! He's frozen!
1, 2, 3!
Hey hey, are you alright?
Did someone kick your ass?
I was mysteriously paralyzed and thought I was gonna die.
You just got caught in a snowstorm and froze solid, didn't you?
No! I don't feel cold at all...
Don't be so stubborn!
Warriors don't feel cold!
He's such a pain.
Get yourself some clothes! You have an ability to do that!
T-To tell you the truth,
because of that magic, I have a weakness.
I-I became not capable of swimming...
You can't swim, right?! We know that!
Wh-What I'm trying to say is my torso is...
...p-probably soaking in the water!
The water?
I-In fact,
it feels like the upper half of my body is in the water.
I see. That's why you couldn't even move and you were frozen here.
If your body's in the water, you can't use the power.
Speaking of water, Brook, his torso may have fallen into the lake.
Maybe. I heard that lake is actually filled with seawater.
He's still alive here so I don't think it has become food for sharks yet.
But we don't know what's in that lake.
We better pull it out as soon as possible.
Yes, we have to hurry.
I-I have to ask you to... um, go under the water for me...
We know! You can't swim, right? What a crappy samurai!
I thought you people were pirates! And I'm a total stranger to you!
Why are you helping me so much?!
Because I'm responsible for you!
But when you get your whole body back,
you have to fight me! I'll kick your ass!
I...
I accept it!
Thank you!
Oh great! Now you're able to say thank you.
Maybe getting frozen makes people nicer.
What?
Hmm... What is that?
Oh! Those are...
...Brownbeard-san's subordino-centaurs that we robbed.
--Stay with me! Keep running! --Get away from the lake!
A monster appeared on the other side!
We have to tell the Master!
Where has it been hiding on the island until now?!
Just keep running! It's gonna come after us!
Huh, a monster? You guys are monsters.
They're the pirates who robbed us earlier!
Dammit! That's my coat!
Forget about them! Just run! To the lab!
They got our Boss!
You'll pay for that!
What's going on?
I don't know. What was it?
Hey, Brook. They were coming from the lake that we saw earlier, weren't they?
What?! Yes! You got it right!
I'm impressed, Zoro-san! And what about it?
Well, if in fact that is the lake,
I don't think there was a mountain there before, was there?
A mountain?
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Smiley is the embodiment of a chemical weapon explosion...
...that occurred on Punk Hazard, four years ago.
I invented the H₂S poison gas bomb.
It worked so well
and killed everything on the island in a matter of seconds!
ONE YEAR LATER
Do they believe I purified the gas all over the island?
No way! No one would do such a wasteful thing!
I compressed it and turned it into a monster.
And there he is!
Smiley!
This island was once covered with dead soil where no one could live.
People tend to forget tragedies in no time
but that one has lingered here all along.
It was always in my hand!
VEGAPUNK'S FORMER THIRD LABORATORY
THE REMAINS OF VEGAPUNK'S FORMER FIRST AND SECOND LABORATORY
I'll never let him take these children again.
I can't believe he was using them as his test subjects and drugged them.
I can't forgive the Master guy!
Okay, then let's just go and kidnap the Master!
Yeah, if we're too late, we can't work with them.
We're not gonna be late. I have an idea!
What is it?
It's a very good idea!
We got their ship!
Stop the ship!
Hurry up! Let's finish them off!
S-Smoker-san, how can I turn back?!
You're in my way! Stay still, Tashigi!
The door is not open yet?!
The enemy is in the lab!
We can't just stay out here!
It's no good! The door is as steady as a rock, Smo-san!
I feel miserable!
If I were in my body, I could easily force myself into the place!
Room.
Your power is very useful! Was it teleportation?!
Shut up and stay inside the bag.
We've almost reached the backdoor of the lab.
Caesar will probably be in the main room with that woman.
I'll try to draw them out of the room.
I want you to find out about the drug while we're gone.
But if you can reach the Master that easily
and you're so strong, why don't you capture the Master yourself?
Then we can take time to find out about the drug.
Because of a problem I have,
I can't do that and that's why I need help from you guys.
In any case, I just want you guys to kidnap Caesar.
I'll do the rest.
Hey, look at that!
Wh-What's that?!
--Something's flying toward us! --It's a big bomb!
No, it's not!
Cien Fleurs:
Wing!
Wham!
What?! He said "Wham"?! Is it a human?!
Hot damn!
That was a nice shortcut!
Master, show yourself!
We will kick your ass and kidnap you!
Luffy, that was supposed to be a secret.
Straw Hat!
It's the Straw Hats!
Go, Luffy!
That fool! Who said anything about confronting everyone?!
Where are you, Master?!
Show yourself!
A battle unfolds between Smoker's G-5 Navy men and Luffy's crew.
After the violent clash, just when it seems like the research lab will be breached...
...Caesar's deadly weapon, Smiley, rains down upon person after person...
...throwing everyone into fear and chaos.
Next time, on One Piece:
"On the Verge of Annihilation! A Deadly Monster Comes Flying In!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!