Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
Huh?
Yahoo!
A-Are you all right?!
Yeah! It's okay, it's okay!
They're new recruits who heard
all about me and came from afar...
...to join the Usopp Pirates!
No, not me!
I'm here to ask a favor!
A favor? Of me?
Yeah!
– We want a big ship...
– You, there!
What are you doing?!
Klahadore...
I don't appreciate you breaking
in here without permission!
Who's there?!
The Weirdest Guy Ever!
Jango the Hypnotist
A-Actually, Klahadore, these people are-
That can wait for now.
I can hear all about your reasons later.
Now leave, all of you!
Or do you have something to say?
Well, actually, we want a ship!
No!
Usopp-kun!
Crap!
I've heard all about you.
You're well-known in the village.
Yeah?
I hear you've been on many an adventure.
Quite impressive for someone so young.
You can call me Captain Usopp, too!
Since you admire me so much!
Captain, huh?
I've heard all about your father, as well.
What?!
Klahadore! Stop!
You're nothing but the son of a filthy pirate!
Nothing you do will surprise me,
but I ask that you stay away
from the lady of this house!
F-Filthy?!
She and you are from
completely different worlds!
Is it money you're after?
How much do you want?
That's enough, Klahadore!
Apologize to Usopp-san!
Hey, now! Be careful, Kaya!
What reason is there to apologize
to this savage man, my lady?
I am merely stating the truth.
I feel for you.
You must truly hate your
great idiot of a father...
...for abandoning his family and village
because of his lust for treasure!
Klahadore!
Don't you dare insult my father any more!
Usopp-san!
What are you getting unnecessarily riled up for?
Why not simply tell another of
your special lies at a time like this?
About how your father is
really a traveling salesman,
or how you're not really related by blood...
Shut up!
– Captain!
S-See!
You immediately resort to violence!
Like father, like son!
Shut up!
I'm proud that my father is a pirate!
I'm proud that he's a brave warrior of the sea!
You're right, I am an exaggerator!
But I'll never lie about my pride
to be related by blood to a pirate!
I'm the son of a pirate!
Captain...
A pirate, a brave warrior of the sea?
That's quite a twisted way of putting things...
But you're the undeniable
proof of his savage blood!
You run around spouting lies,
and act violent whenever you're angry!
And to top it off, you cozy
up to the lady of this house
so you can get her fortune!
What?! I only...!
The fact that your father is a pirate...
...is more than enough proof
that you'd hatch such a scheme!
Damn it, you still won't let up?!
Stop, Usopp-san!
Please, no more violence!
Klahadore isn't a bad person!
He's just...
He's just trying too hard
to do what's best for me!
Leave this place!
Never come near this mansion again!
Yeah, I get it.
I don't need you to tell me!
I'll never come back here again!
Usopp-san...
You stupid butt-ler jerk!
Our captain's not that kind of guy!
Yeah! You stupid-head!
Stupid-head!
Why're you saying it, too?!
– What's your problem?!
– Hey, now! Stop!
– Let go! You stupid butler!
– What?!
Come fight me, if you can!
You will leave at once, too!
Your meal, my lady.
No thanks. I don't want it.
The cook would be sad to hear you say that.
He works his hardest to come up
with meals that suit your needs.
Why did you talk like that?
I know I was wrong to talk with
Usopp-san without telling you.
But you didn't need to kick him out like that.
May I sit?
Go ahead.
It's been nearly three years...
...since the day I came to this mansion.
I'll never forget what happened that day...
I was kicked off the ship I worked on...
...because of a blunder I made,
and with no work or money,
I was on the verge of dying like a beggar.
Hey, you! Get out of here!
Get up!
This is no place for the likes of you!
Huh?! Sir?! But...
Understood!
Take him inside and tend to him!
In my eyes, I owe my life to your late parents...
And to you, their daughter.
I realize that it isn't my place
to interfere with your friendships.
But that Usopp lad isn't exactly
known for his upstanding character!
If... if anything should happen to you,
I would never be able to ask for
forgiveness from your kind parents!
Do you think ill of me for what I did earlier?
No, not at all!
I'm glad to have you, too, Klahadore!
But please don't misunderstand.
Usopp-san is a very nice person.
However, whether he's nice or not is irrelevant!
Klahadore! Urgh! You blockhead!
Yes, "blockhead" will do just fine!
Hey, where'd Luffy go?
Who knows?
Probably ran after that "captain."
Our captain would be at his spot!
Yeah, the shore!
He always goes there when something happens!
Wanna check it out?
Huh? Nah, that's okay.
But never mind that,
isn't one of you missing?
– Yeah, Onion!
He always just ups and disappears!
Yeah!
And then he shows up all freaked out!
Bad news!
See?
A b-backwards guy!
A weird guy is backwards-walking this way!
– Liar!
It's the truth!
Just look!
Hey! Who's calling me a weird guy?!
I am not weird!
Seem pretty weird to me.
Don't be stupid!
I'm just an ordinary, passing-by hypnotist!
H-Hypnotist?! Awesome!
Show us something!
Yeah! Do something!
What?!
Don't be dumb!
Why should I have to reveal my techniques...
...to a bunch of strangers?!
Alright. Watch this ring closely.
You're gonna do it?!
You'll feel sleepy at the
count of "one, two, Jango."
Alright, here we go!
One, two,
Jango!
Geez, what's with this guy?!
Yo!
Here you are!
Oh, it's just you!
At least say something, will ya?!
So, what, do you want something?!
Not really.
Oww...
That damn butler,
insulting my old man like that!
Yeah, I hate that guy too!
No matter what anyone says,
Yasopp was a great pirate!
Yeah, huh?!
In this day and age where
pirates are everywhere,
I'm proud of my old man for living
with his life on the line at sea!
Yet, that bastard stomped all over my pride!
He'll pay for this!
But you're not gonna
go see the girl anymore?
Y-Yeah, I dunno...
If that butler comes and apologizes
to me, I might consider it.
That butler?
Yeah, that butler...
What's that butler doing out here?!
Oww! That hurts!
Hey, Jango.
I told you to avoid doing
anything to make you stand out.
Yet you go and sleep in
the middle of the village...
Don't be stupid.
I don't stand out one bit.
I'm not weird, either.
There's someone else with him.
A weird guy...
Never seen him before. Who is he?
So, preparations for the plan are ready, I hope?
Of course.
We can start anytime...
The Rich Girl Assassination Plan!
A-Assassination?!
Don't call it assassination, Jango.
That has a bad ring to it.
Oh, right. Accident. It's an accident.
Hey, what're those guys talking about?
D-Don't look at me!
That's what I'd like to know!
We can't simply kill her.
Miss Kaya must perish
in an unfortunate accident.
Don't mess that up!
So basically, on your signal,
the men and I storm the village and kill the girl.
And then you'll get her inheritance...
You fool!
You don't understand a thing!
How would I, an outsider, inherit Kaya's estate?!
You'll work hard to?
Working hard won't amount to squat.
Listen, this is the most important thing!
Before you kill her, you'll use
hypnosis to make Kaya write her will...
...to say, "I leave my entire
fortune to my butler, Klahadore!"
Only then will I inherit her enormous fortune...
In a completely ordinary manner...
I've spent three long years gaining
the trust of everyone around me...
...so that it would be unsurprising for
her to leave her inheritance to me.
Three years as a butler for that, huh?
But you sure scared us back then...
Captain Kuro.
Three years ago, you suddenly said
you were giving up life as a pirate.
In no time flat, you set up
a subordinate to be your double,
then let the world see
Captain Kuro get executed.
So that was the very beginning of this plan.
You truly are Kuro, Man of a Thousand Plans.
Don't call me that.
I abandoned that name three years ago.
I now want to obtain great sums of money...
...without the Government on my back.
In other words, I'm a pacifist.
Some pacifist you are,
killing off an entire rich family
for this "peace" of yours.
Hold on, now.
The father's death was real.
I hadn't planned on that.
Well, whatever. It doesn't matter.
Anyways, hurry and give the signal.
We've been sitting in the waters
near here for a whole week now.
The men are starting to grow impatient.
This is bad!
We heard something really bad!
Hey, what's going on?
This sounds kind of bad.
Weren't you listening this whole time?!
This is seriously bad!
They're the real deal!
Captain Kuro is said to be the smartest...
...and most brutal pirate of all!
Word had it the Navy caught and
executed him three years ago...
...but Captain Kuro is alive!
As Klahadore, the butler!
He's been after Kaya's fortune
for these past three years straight!
They're gonna attack the village!
Kaya's in danger, too!
Bad! This is seriously bad!
Hey! Don't stand up! They'll see you!
Hey, you guys! Don't attack that girl!
Who're you?!
You idiot! They spotted you!
Hurry and hide before they kill you!
Oh... If it isn't Usopp-kun.
They spotted me, too!
Did you... hear anything?
N-No! Whatever do you mean?!
We just got here now, so of
course we didn't hear anything!
We heard everything!
Hey, you!
Oh, all right.
Hey, you guys!
Watch this ring closely!
What?
Th-This is bad!
It's a throwing weapon! Dodge it!
At the count of "one, two, Jango"
you will get sleepy.
Ready?
– One, two...
– Hide! He's gonna kill us!
...Jango!
Hey! Wake up, Jango!
Have you still not fixed that habit yet?!
H-Hey! What're you doing?!
You're gonna fall!
Head-first...
I didn't mean to kill him,
but he couldn't have survived from that height...
Damn it!
He killed him!
That bastard! Damn it!
What about the other one?
Shall I take care of him?
No need.
No matter what he does,
it won't matter.
Tomorrow morning, Jango.
Attack the village at daybreak.
Tear up the villagers' homes a good amount,
and make certain Miss Kaya's
murder looks like an accident!
Tomorrow!
You heard me, Usopp-kun.
There's nothing you can do to stop my plan.
Damn it!
You sure about him?
Of course. My plans are flawless.
This is bad, this is bad, this is bad!
Everyone in this village I grew
up in is going to be killed!
Kaya's going to be killed!
Even though I love them all!
Who are you?!
I'm Usopp!
A brave warrior of the sea!
I hear you've been unhappy lately!
I'll cheer you up with a story!
Mind your own business!
Please leave! I'll call for someone!
And then? What happened after that?!
I fought, of course! Bravely, at that!
First, for the giant cat, I used a cattail plant...
Damn it!
Usopp ran by with a really intense look.
Did something happen?
That butler is a pirate!
He told his crew to attack the village!
Now they'll know, and can run away beforehand!
That's a relief!
– Oh, no!
– What is it?!
We need to stock up on food
before the meat shop guy runs away!
That's not the issue at hand here!
Next time, on One Piece:
Expose the Plot!
Pirate Butler Captain Kuro
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Expose the Plot!
Pirate Butler Captain Kuro