Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
However, there they find the New Fishman Pirates
have been plotting to destroy Ryugu Kingdom,
arm in arm with Vander Decken, who has been
stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
and involved in an all-out war!
Now, set off the fireworks!
Okay, I cut you already.
Quinte Tierce Fantasia!
Mil Fleurs,
Gigantesco Mano:
Stomp!
Soldier Dock System!
Channel 4!
FR-U 4!
I'll take care of it!
The new number! Channel 5!
Brachio-Tank 5 is here!
Come on out, Kraken!
There are only 10 of them! Just crush them all!
Then it'll finally be over!
Oh, hey, Surume!
It's me! Surume!
The Kraken betrayed us!
Listen, Surume! Stay here and protect Wimpyhoshi!
Um, thank you for doing this, Surume-sama!
Iron Pirate!
General Franky Makes his Entrance
They're pushing their luck too far!
I'll make them pay for this!
Where am I?
You're in Conchcorde Plaza. Don't you remember?
Looks like they have some good swordsmen!
Get out of my way!
Don't cut me! Hyouzou-san!
Get away!
Run!
Oh? What's going on?
They're trying to escape from us!
I guess they're scared of us!
Let's take out their officers while they're gone!
Yeah! Advance!
There is one of them right in front of us!
Prepare to fire!
Roger! Preparing to fire!
Oh? He's gone!
Cookie Cutter!
There he is! Prepare to fire!
I'll get him this time... Oh, he's gone again!
There! Fire!
What?! Oh, he's gone again!
No, there he is!
Damn! He moves so quickly!
Hey, Commander Chopper!
It's rattling! Is there something wrong?!
What? What?! What?!
It's a sinkhole!
That serves you right! Special Attack - Daruma Drop!
Ouch!
I just dug a web of underground tunnels with my fangs!
Hey! What happened?!
Usopp! Chopper!
Now, I'm gonna take care of that stupid biker too—
Oh no!
A sink hole!
What?! Is he dumb?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey! Are you okay, guys?!
Bastard! Super I won't forgive him!
You guys, get out!
Why?!
Are they splitting up?!
Hey, what are you doing, Franky?!
How dare you kick the commander out!
Because it's gonna turn into a single-seater!
Let's get perverted!
You're already a pervert!
Black Rhino FR-U 4!
Stand by!
Oh, it perverted!
That's not it!
Brachio-Tank 5!
Head change!
Black Rhino FR-U 4!
Docking!
What?! Docking?!
Iron Pirate!
General Franky!
Awesome!
What the hell is that?!
Cool!!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
The transforming robot of our dream!
The mad genius Vegapunk who I haven't met yet.
I realized his old dream...
...after trial and error for the last 2 years.
By using the shape-memory alloy called Wapometal,
I finally did it!
D-Don't be intimidated by its looks!
Oh, so strong!!
There is more to come!
Look at this! The "Sword of the Pillager"!
Franken!
He has a sword!
General...
...Watch-Your-Step!
Striking below the belt!
It's unmanly but effective!
The cannons in these shoulders will get you while you're jumping!
What?!
What?! Cannons in its shoulders?!
Franky Cannon!
Oh, the cannons are in your shoulders!
--But... --But...
--...you're so cool! --Oh yeah!
Oh, how awesome!
Dammit!
He's so tricky!
I've got more new weapons!
Watch out!
Come on!
New weapons!
General...
...Weight!
It's so heavy!
--You're so cool, General! --Weight! Weight!
What's so cool about that?
Oh!
Here is a weak one!
How dare you say I'm weak! I'm just a chicken!
Sorcery Klimatakt!
Watch out for a gust of wind.
Gust Sword!
Do you understand now?
It's Weatheria's science of weather!
Don't underestimate it!
Oh? Huh?
Where did Chopper go?
Let's get that guy!
Damn! I got kicked out of the tank after all!
I have no other choice but to fight.
But I'm not scared!
Because I'm not the same person that I used to be!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Bamboo Javelin Grove!
Master Heracles'n!
I'll never forget those 2 years that I spent in the deadly Swindling Forest!
It begins now!
The second chapter of
"The Adventures of the Real Man Usopp"!
I'll make sink holes all over the plaza!
Doesn't matter if it's a cool robot or something else! Once it falls down, it's all over!
What is that?!
Somebody else is digging too!
Daruma-san got blown out!
Wh-Who is it?!
It's me!
Horn Point!
I'm good at digging too!
Chopper!
Cool! You can turn into a stag beetle now?!
It's not a stag beetle!
I strengthened 7 of my transformation boosts in the last 2 years!
I only need the Rumble Ball for one boost now!
So I can turn into any other forms whenever I want!
What a pain-in-the-ass coral guy!
I'll bite your flesh off!
These are not coral - they're horns!
And that's "pain-in-the-ass monster" for you!
They all seem so full of life when they're fighting!
Like they've been waiting to fight for so long!
How many of them have we killed?
N-None, sir.
Kraken!
Good job, considering it was you.
You gained their favor so slickly and caught Shirahoshi!
Now, squeeze her to death!
Your brother at the North Pole...
I know exactly where he is.
We can just go there and kill him whenever we want.
You brothers are mythical creatures.
Even dead, I can sell you for a good price.
Don't tell me that's what you want.
Kraken?
I can't believe this.
He was obeying Hody because his brother was taken as a hostage!
I'll tell you one last time!
Squeeze Shirahoshi to death!
Huh?
Surume-sama, y-you're hurting me!
Surume!
So you were doing everything he says in order to save your brother's life?
I know how you feel.
Is it your younger brother or older brother?
Let me try to save his life too!
Did you forget?
I'm your friend!
Surume-sama!
Straw Hat is coming this way!
Kill him!
You guys are no match for him-dogon!
Let us take care of him-ch!
Straw Hat!
We won't let you come any closer to our captain-ch!
Drop dead!
We won't let you guys...
...Get in his way!
Stop Straw Hat!
Gear 2!
Where did he go?!
What?!
I don't know why but I'm full of fight now!
Awesome!
How did he get there?! I couldn't see him!
That's...!
I can't believe it!
That's...
...the Ship of Promise!
"Noah"!
As Luffy and Hody begin their battle,
suddenly, directly above Conchcorde Plaza,
the massive form of Noah appears and terrifies the citizens.
As everyone begins to lose hope,
Shirahoshi places herself in front of the Noah to save Fishman Island.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Noah Approaches!
Fishman Island on the Brink!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Noah Approaches!
Fishman Island on the Brink!