Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates,
who are plotting to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom,
alongside Vander Decken, who is after
Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi, move in secret.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
--We've been waiting for you, Straw Hat! --H-He really came!
Luffy-sama, what did you just call me?
You were calling me "Wimpy" before.
Yeah, it's not like I know everything but you're not as timid as I thought you were.
So I'll call you Wimpyhoshi from now on!
All pirates will fall down on their knees before us--the New Fishman Pirates!
Look at these human pirates with confidence in their ability to fight!
You will all be like them, Straw Hat!
I'll be the one who becomes Pirate King!
The Pirate King?
We have 100,000 on our side!
Hey, Luffy!
That 400-million-berry prize is mine!
No, mine!
No way!
Kill him!
What's going on here?!
He didn't do anything but so many of us got knocked out!
You're Hody, right? I guess I have to kick your ass.
You can become king of whatever you want in any country.
But there can only be one Pirate King!
A Flurry of Deadly Attacks!
Zoro and Sanji Join the Fray!
--Oh, what... --...Extraordinary power!
So he's the Straw Hat Luffy!
He's out of our league!
Where do you think you're going?
If you run from your enemy on this historic day for the Fishmen, you deserve death.
We may have lost 50,000.
But...
...we are still 50,000 strong!
The Straw Hats always shatter our dreams. They're our...
...worst enemy!
And Jinbe!
He lives Otohime's dream and befriends humans!
But that's not the future we Fishmen want!
He's right! Straw Hat is nothing! He's just a human!
And Jinbe betrayed the Fishmen! Let's kill them both!
Luffy! I wish you left more than 50,000 of them for me.
Oh, sorry.
Don't get so excited.
Huh?
I'll go for 30,000! Okay, Mosshead?
Shut up, Mr. Nosebleed.
Huh?
You audience babies!
Okay! Let me do one song for the beginning of the battle!
They're not here to see you.
As always, Robin-san's so cool!
They weren't listening at all, were they?
That's because I whispered it!
--What?! --He has too much pride.
Kill them!
--Let's show them... --...How great Fishmen are!
Let's do it!
Gear 3:
I don't care if there're thousands of you! Just bring it on!
Gum-Gum...
--Here he comes! --What's wrong with his hand?!
...Gigant Pistol!
All right, let's join him.
That fool didn't wait for us again.
I've got to do this, after seeing tears in Shirahoshi-chan's eyes.
You must have been trying so hard to protect...
...that small "sprout" single-handedly, day after day.
But let us protect it for you this time.
Men who can't wipe away the tears from women's eyes aren't real men.
Let's wreck these guys!
When this is over, let's have a drink at the Mermaid Café, Shirahoshi-chan!
Drop dead!
Collier Shoot!
I won't let you destroy this Mermaid paradise!
They'll either give up or be wiped out.
108-...
...Pound Phoenix!
What are you looking at, woman?!
There are some important historical resources here on Fishman Island!
You can't just rampage around destroying things!
Whether it's the citizens or the kingdom or the history.
Trienta Fleurs...
What's this?!
...Clutch!
They're so excited!
It's a nice day to do a concert!
Everybody say "ho"!
Today's audience is awesome!
I got him!
Kung Fu Point!
H-He transformed himself!
I don't care how many at once - just bring it on!
Th-The raccoon dog shape-shifted!
I'm not a raccoon dog!
Sure-Kill Green Star: Devil!
It's gonna eat me!
Take this! Green Stars at random!
How's that? I'm a Pop Green master! People call me Usopp'n-sama!
Huh?
Thanks, Nami!
I thought you got stronger but some things never change!
Super it's getting pretty exciting, isn't it?!
There are 50,000 enemies. This is the perfect opportunity to unveil them!
Them?!
What are they, Franky?!
There are 2 new weapons on the Sunny!
Who wants to ride along?
What?! New weapons?!
--Super! Super! I'm super! --Hey, hey! What are they?
Can I ride it?
Is it safer to be onboard than out here?
Well, you'll see! You can set your expectations very high!
You are all amazing!
What are you guys doing?! How pathetic!
Try and save the giant Mermaid...
...in the middle of the plaza,
if you can!
Water Shot!
Oh, I didn't have to worry.
What?!
He deflected Captain Hody's destructive Water Shot...
...with his own Water Shot?!
That man is a monster, too!
I don't know how you've attained that much power
but your Fishman Karate is very unskilled!
He was the first Fishman to join the Seven Warlords!
And after he resigned, his bounty exceeded 400 million berries!
How can we fight a guy like that?!
Shut up and bring it on!
You have to kill us all in order to kill the Princess!
Why are you hesitating?!
There is nowhere for you to run!
N-No way!
How boring.
How rude.
Hold your tongue until you've beaten the formidable line of defense...
...of the New Fishman Pirates!
We'll even smash that sword you're proud of!
Go, Iron Shell Squad!
Please!
Train me as a swordsman!
They're really just copying what Hawk-Eye does!
It's a pain in the ass to fight all these weaklings!
Here we go again - just like that time!
I... I swore to become stronger, didn't I?!
I will never lose again!
Three-Sword Style...
Kalasutra: Grand Dragon Twister!
What?!
He cut through their iron shells as if they were fruit!
What was that attack?! It looked like the Grim Reaper's scythe or something!
I-It's still going on!
--It won't stop! --It's like a cyclone of blades!
--Run! Or you're gonna get cut! --Don't come after us!
It'll chase you to hell's end!
Use your brains, fools!
Use your bubbles to float!
Let's hit them from the sky!
Kill Princess Shirahoshi!
How sneaky.
Outta my way!
We'll impale you all!
Go, Harisenbon!
It's the Sea Urchin Spike Unit led by Commander Harisenbon!
Impale that kick-fighting guy!
Hari, sen, bon!
Now, you have nowhere to hide!
Sanji-san, watch out!
How can you act so relaxed?! Hey!
It's been a while already...
Sanji-kun!
I ran.
Wait, candy-chan!
No way, screw you!
I brought my favorite dress for you!
--Put it on! --You don't need to be shy!
I said I won't wear it! I'm not being shy!
In the rain, in the snow,
in the rolling thunder, I ran and ran...
Go to hell, kick-fighting guy!
You silly boy!
Do you think you can escape us forever?!
Sanji-kun!
I shouldn't have trouble dealing with these fools!
Damn you!
Stop! Sanji!
Do I forget what happened at Sabaody, already?!
Sanji-kun!
What I need to do now is to get all the Vital Recipes
from the grand masters of the New Kama Kenpo!
You fools will...
Sanji-kun!
You let your guard down, candy boy!
What?
Sanji-kun!
You're already surrounded by New Kamas!
Sanji-kun-kun!
Sanji-kun-kun-kun!
Then one day, I finally got cornered and...
I ran...
Ouch, ouch! Ow, ow, ow... Huh? Where did he go?
Sanji-kun!
And I...--
...ended up...
...flying!
He's up there!
Sky...
...Walk!
Cool! Sanji is in the air! Like those people in the past!
That's the Moon Walk of CP9's!
Hey, you guys!
--What?! --He's flying!
If you wanna talk to Shirahoshi-chan, you need to talk to me first!
I'm the notorious knight...
...here to protect you!
Sanji-chin-sama!
Don't push your luck too far!
Let's cook these small fries!
Diable Jambe,
Poêle à Frire:
...Spectre!
Hey, you!
It's gonna be over soon so just stay still!
Doesn't matter if there are 100,000 or 1,000,000!
We'll just beat them all!
Brooke and Robin use the
exquisite techniques learned in their two years
of training to defeat their opponents.
But the New Fishman Pirates' Deadly Venom Squad begin a counterattack,
things start getting dangerous
when Franky, Usopp and Chopper
bring out a wondrous new weapon!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Debut!
The Sunny's Secret Weapons!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Debut!
The Sunny's Secret Weapons!