Two years have passed since Havy HQ
and the Seven Warlords...
clashed with the Whitebeard Pirates
in the Paramount War.
On a deserted island northwest of Maiden Island—Luscaina...
Luffy!
Yeah!
I'm coming!
Time sure flew by.
It's already been two years.
Hey!
Look carefully.
She's my friend.
Luffy, the ship is ready.
We can set sail whenever you want!
Okay, thanks!
That's amazing.
He's the boss of this island now.
But now that I'm friends with these guys,
I can't eat them anymore.
And they look so tasty, too.
It's okay, Luffy.
We loaded the ship with all your favourite foods.
I think that, since I am so thoughtful, I'd make a fine wife for you.
I'm not gonna get married,
but thanks for the food!
I love that blunt side of you!
Rayleigh left half a year ago.
I'm sure he's waiting for you on Sabaody.
He finished teaching me the basics after a year and a half, after all.
Now it's time to say goodbye to you guys and this island.
Alright...
Let's go!
Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
"Shakky's Rip-Off Bar"
It's been two years.
Sure doesn't feel like it.
True.
I can't wait to see how much they've grown.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
We don't even know
if they can get back together safely.
They're infamous all over the world now, after all.
Oh my!
Oh? So you're the first.
What? None of the others are here yet?
They never change.
The Beginning of a New Chapter
The Straw Hats Reunited!
About ten days later
At a certain bar
Have you heard?
Navy HQ's been relocated.
What, really?
Yeah, they traded places with a branch called G1
that was on the other side of the Red Line.
Really goes to show how determined
the new fleet admiral replacing Sengoku is.
After all, he set up his HQ
in the territory of the Four Emperors.
Thanks to the switch,
the Navy's presence here has dropped off
and this island's become a hotbed of lawlessness.
Hmm, no wonder this town
seems rougher than it was two years ago.
Hey, did you see this?!
Yeah, I was shocked, too.
I can't believe the Straw Hats have resurfaced!
You can say that again!
No one's heard from them for two years so I thought they were gone for good.
"Crew Wanted"
And now they're recruiting new members!
Greenhorns who managed to survive
the first half of the Grand Line gather on this island.
He must be planning to expand his group here
so he can run wild in the New World!
How exciting!
I wonder if they'll let me join?
No way!
There are plenty of pirates with bounties exceeding 100 million on this island.
Do you really think they'd  take someone like you?
What's that supposed to mean?!
Hey, old geezer!
Bring me some booze!
Food, too!
Everything you have!
Y-Yes, right away!
Hey, could they be...
No doubt about it! They're...
The Straw Hats...
Grove #33
Sabaody Park
Live Concert Hall
Sabao Dome
Please, don't say that!
Can't you work something out?
The tickets are sold out!
There's no way there'd be any left!
This is the farewell concert of a superstar! Soul King Brook's final world tour concert!
The place is already packed!
Manager!
Let's make this the greatest concert ever!
Yeah, we'll be counting on it!
TD sales are at an all-time high.
We've already sold more than one million!
You really are the soul music king of the world!
Listen to those cheers!
Soul King! Soul King! Soul King! Soul King!
Manager...
Before we do this concert...
there's something important I have to tell you.
What is it?
Come on, baby!
Yeah!
Yeah! I'm all bones!
Bone!
Bone to be wild!
Bone! Bone! Bone!
Booone!
Macho, yet unpopular with the ladies.
That's the brutal truth.
Soul King, mysterious...
He's nothing but bones!
I can't believe it...
How selfish can he be?!
Hey, get me a Transponder Snail!
I won't let you get away with this, Brook!
Let's make today the best anniversary ever!
Long time no see, Sabaody.
I'm back at last.
Women! Real ones!
No doubt about it!
There are women here, real women!
Real women live on this island,
just like I've dreamed of day after day after day!
Viva Sabaody!
I need ladies!
Sanji-kyun!
Looks like we have to say goodbye.
I'll miss you! Be seeing you!
I never want to see you again!
But thanks for the ride!
Give my regards to Iva! Bye!
The manly Sanji has returned from hell!
Hey, did you know?
Boys always pretend
to hate the girls they like most.
Yeah, I know. It's happened to me.
I don't think I'll ever stop thinking about him!
Wait for me, Nami-swan! Robin-chwan!
Huh? Did I hear you right?
Your bounty's fifty-five million berries?
"Straw Hat Pirates"
Captain Monkey D. Luffy
Take another good look at the poster!
Your bounty has to be at least seventy million berries.
We're not accepting any captains below that level.
How'd you guys even get here in one piece?
Dammit!
Get lost, pest.
Don't you know I'm the son
of Dragon—the Revolutionary?!
Navigator Nami
Shipwright Franky
You'd just slow us down!
We're the chosen pirates!
We're in another league.
Sniper Sogeking
Don't think we'll accept just anyone!
Get lost!
He's so merciless.
That Straw Hat Luffy!
What can we do, though?
He's really strong.
Hey, Franky!
How many we got so far?
About 100 in all.
Three entire pirate crews have joined us.
Ten of the pirates have bounties on their head.
Sounds great.
Two of them are those infamous rookies.
"Wet-Haired" Caribou and "Blood Splatter" Coribou!
They're well known for killing marines.
Those two brothers are pirate captains with bounties of 210 million and 190 million.
They'll come in handy!
Let's keep recruiting!
Old geezer! Get us some more booze!
Y-Yes!
Hurry up!
Oh? And you there, woman!
You've been sitting there for quite a while.
Don't drink alone! Come over here!
She's a real looker.
Hey, woman!
Didn't you hear me?!
Hey, he's talking to you.
That's okay.
I'm waiting for a man.
What?
She turned him down.
Hey, hey, you'd better listen to him!
That's Straw Hat Luffy!
Remember?
He's that crazy pirate who jumped headfirst
into the Paramount War two years ago!
You know the one?!
You're waiting for a man?
He's probably a coward
who'll faint at the sound of Captain Luffy's name!
So get your ass over here!
I'll only tell you one more time.
You're not good enough for me.
I'm not gonna drink with you!
What?
Understood?
Straw... what was your name again?
Did you just ask who I am?!
I said I'm Straw Hat Luffy!
Hey, you better apologize!
This is bad!
Huh?
You've got some nerve!
Let me handle her.
Hey you!
You're an interesting woman.
You got two choices.
Accept Captain Luffy's invitation...
or die.
By the way, I have a bounty on my head too.
I'm the Cat Burglar—Nami!
Don't you forget that!
Sure-Kill Green Star...
Devil!
Huh?
Wh-What is this?!
What's going on?!
Help me, Captain!
Don't come near me, you idiot!
What's that plant?
Hey, girl.
Will you drink with me?
Usopp! It's really you!
And look at you!
You're so big and strong now!
Y-You've grown too...
In more ways than one.
What?! She was waiting for that geek?!
Did you do that?
That's right!
It's my new weapon, the Pop Green!
I did more than just
stare at the ocean for two years!
Sorry, but...
I'm not part of the weakling trio with you and Chopper anymore!
I'll never falter no matter what happens!
I've finally become a true warrior!
Hey, dude!
Don't tell me you did this?!
What?! Sogeking?! But how?!
Usopp, forget about those idiots!
Let's go somewhere else.
There's something I wanna ask you.
Hold it, you bastards!
Huh, Luffy?!
Let's go already!
Hey, ma'am!
What about your tab?
Keep the change!
Damn, they're making us look bad!
Get them back here!
Dammit!
Huh?! What are all these black bubbles?!
What the hell are they? Clouds?!
Wh-What's going on?!
So I have this new technology, but...
Seriously? You were on a sky island?
Find those two...
and fill them with lead!
A report from Sabaody Archipelago!
What? The Straw Hats?!
Yes, sir!
Word is they're recruiting new crew members.
Contact Headquarters!
If he really is alive, that's not good.
Request reinforcements immediately!
And order a search on Sabaody Archipelago!
Yes, sir!
Did I lose them?
Brook's concert?
Pirates wanted for the Straw Hats?
What's going on?
Soul King?
I don't believe it.
Not a single scratch on her.
Sorry to have kept you waiting, Sunny!
We'll set sail soon!
Grand-Buns really are delicious!
I wonder how everyone's doing?
I can't wait to see them!
Mister, please make it bigger!
Thank you!
Hey, you alright?! Hey!
How could he?!
He just shot her out of the blue!
How awful!
Hey, hang in there!
Why'd you shoot us?!
What did we ever do to you?!
I said I was sorry, didn't I?
I mistook her for someone else!
Sorry. I was looking for
two people who look like you.
A man with a long nose
and a woman with long hair.
You mistook her?!
And then you just shoot her?!
That Straw Hat Luffy's a fiend!
What? You got a problem with me?
Looks like you do.
Don't blame me, blame those two!
Hey, stay with me!
Are you alright?!
Hunt those two down, you guys!
I won't let them get away with what they did!
We'll kill them as a warning to others!
Oh, did it hit you?
My bad!
See ya!
What's he doing?
Doesn't he know that's Straw Hat Luffy?
H-He's a dead man!
Stop right there!
Huh?
The fake Luffy who appeared in front of Luffy
attempted to boost his crew's power
by calling them Straw Hats.
Facing the pistol-wielding fake,
Luffy's newly acquired powers are activated.
Next time, on One Piece:
"An Explosive Situation!
Luffy vs. Fake Luffy"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
An Explosive Situation!
Luffy vs. Fake Luffy