Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy finally made it to Marineford to rescue his brother, Ace!
There, the Whitebeard Pirates are trying to get to Ace
and the Navy is standing in their way.
The battle is heating up!
Gum-Gum...
...Gigant...
...Rifle!
Ace!
Hard Battles, One After Another!
Devil Fruit Users vs. Devil Fruit Users
He beat the Giant!
Awesome, Straw Hat!
You beat the Giant in one sweep!
I'm back!
Straw Hat, I think we caught their attention!
Don't let them advance any farther!
Don't let the rookie get the best of you!
Luffy!
Get them!
Let's launch a frontal attack
Marineford bay head
and join Pops inside the bay!
We gotta save Ace!
Drive the Navy out!
The Navy vice admirals! They're so strong!
But we can't stop!
We're gonna rescue Ace!
They're a bunch of fools!
Bazooka unit, fire at Whitebeard!
Pops!
Damn! Please don't do this!
Slash him to pieces!
Gum-Gum...
...Twin Pistol!
I'm gonna...
...rescue Ace! Don't get in my way!
Luffy! Why did you come?!
Why did any of them come?!
I deserve this!
They don't have to risk their lives for me!
We, the 2nd division of the Whitebeard Pirates,
will save our commander Ace!
Don't do this!
Everyone! Why are you doing this for a guy like me?!
I'm your brother!
How stupid you are! Luffy! Pops!
Become my son!
What's wrong?
I'm ready...
...to accept anything that's gonna happen to me.
I'll hold a helping hand.
I'll take the blade of punishment.
I won't make a scene anymore.
Because I feel sorry for them.
Start firing!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
He's suddenly standing out in this battle!
Damn Straw Hat!
Captain Buggy, we need
to make a strong showing, too!
Let's beat Whitebeard now!
Alright! Let's do it!
Having said that, this war is crazy!
There're a bunch of big-time pirates
and the Navy soldiers!
I better keep quiet here...
Hey, you red nose!
What did you just call me?!
I'm gonna kick your ass, you bastard!
Huh?
Whitebeard!
I know you. You're the brat who used to work under Roger.
It's been a while, huh? So you're alive.
Oh no! I drew his attention! He's gonna kill me!
He's dead! He better run!
W-Whitebeard! That notorious Whitebeard is...
...talking to him! How cool!
I knew that you were a living legend!
Why're they so thrilled?!
Must be nice if it's not your own problem!
You're accompanied by so many prisoners...
Are you here to challenge me?
Yes, he is!
Oh, sorry. Captain had to say it.
Give it to him straight!
Dammit! I have no choice now!
Y-Yeah, at last we meet! Prepare yourself!
He's pushing his luck a bit too far!
Oh? I don't mind if you try to beat me
but what are you gonna do next?
There are more Navy soldiers than you can handle.
In fact, they're more than I can handle, too.
Shouldn't we join ranks since we're both pirates and knock the Navy down?
Then, you can beat me after that.
Oh my god! Whitebeard recognizes you as a powerful man!
Like his equal!
No, Whitebeard called him a "brat!"
You can't fight against the Navy! You think there's a chance to win?!
Yeah, if I go all out.
He's losing his grip on reality!
You sure?!
I got goose bumps!
I'm starting to think that I can do it! I can do it!
I can see myself becoming the King of this world!
Yeah, we can beat the Navy if he and I join forces.
This is too great! I'll faint!
Alright, Whitebeard,
I'll join up with you! If you insist!
Huh? Who does he think he is?!
Well, he's our Captain Buggy!
How many more things
can they take the wrong way?!
He is unbelievably easy to trick.
The red nose aside,
the prisoners behind him are something.
It's a pain to have them as our enemies.
And now, I must...
Ships in the back,
Marineford bay head
come forward and deploy the backup!
Our forces are superior!
I have a report!
The pirates in the back are also heading this way!
It's about time.
Forward unit at the bay head,
change the formation
as Fleet Admiral Sengoku instructed
All units, keep fighting back and back up slowly!
Did they stop firing?!
They're backing up, too!
There is disarray among the Navy!
One more push!
Navy ships are coming from either side!
It's too late!
Let's charge into the bay!
Alright! It's our chance to join Pops inside the bay!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank!
This is Whitebeard.
Is Squard there?
Pops! Captain Squard... Oh?
He was in my sight a while ago but it seems like he's gone.
That bastard.
He was all fired up to strut his stuff
to make Pops proud.
It can't be helped. Then, DeCalvan Brothers...
What is it, Pops?
Pops, what is it?
Follow my lead and take command of all pirates.
Okay!
Okay! And what's your lead?
Sink the Navy ships around you first.
What?! Pops, I think we can make a frontal attack now!
Are you giving up?
I have a bad feeling about this situation.
I got it, Pops!
Pops, I got it! We'll tell the captains!
What?! Pops said that?
Alright, then I'll get the right side!
We'll take the left.
Okay, got it.
We'll take the right side.
If Pops says so.
I can head my ship in any direction.
Squard?! I haven't seen him. Really?!
I'll take the left side.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
The New World pirates changed their moves!
Yeah, they turned to the left and right.
They've started attacking Navy ships!
Good guess! Whitebeard must have sensed it.
He didn't fall for that cheap trick. Maybe it was a bit too lame.
But he can't prevent a thing just by sensing it!
Damn! There're too many enemies! It's hard to break through!
Death Wink!
Heehaw!
Iva-sama, you're alright!
Iva-chan, I wanna clear the way to Ace!
Jinbe!
Fishman Karate:
Death...
Gum-Gum...
5,000 Brick Fist!
...Wink!
...Bazooka!
Advance!
Ace!
Stop Straw Hat and the others!
Straw Hat! I won't let you get through!
Moria!
You've got to fight me, Moria!
Jinbe!
I can handle you on my own, Moria!
You wanna fight me, Jinbe?
Alright! I have to get rid of you in order to use zombie soldiers!
Go ahead, Luffy-kun! Don't waste any time!
Thanks, Jinbe!
Pffft! It's a pity to think
that I'm letting Straw Hat go!
Jinbe, you think
you can beat me on land?! Huh?!
I never thought that Jinbe would become our enemy!
The Seven Warlords are our crucial forces!
We shouldn't fight each other!
Huh?
What's wrong?
There's something wrong with my shadow.
Now, fight for me,
shadows of the damned Navy soldiers!
Did you know that I get more powerful
by taking in the shadows of other people?
You have no chance to beat me, Jinbe!
You got bigger.
But getting stronger
by taking other people's power
doesn't make you any better, Moria!
Silence! I couldn't care less about it!
All that matters is winning!
Now, I'm gonna take your shadow!
Spend the rest of your life
in the dark undersea, Jinbe!
Let me have your shadow!
You're so quick for a hulking fellow!
You're the hulking fellow here!
Fishman Karate:
Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
Shark Brick Fist!
You let go of the shadows that you've taken in!
You need to train yourself more!
Now, you need to let me through, Moria!
I have to hurry forward!
Wait, you bastard! The fight is not...
Straw Hat!
Move, Tashigi!
Ouch! You are... Smokey!
I see you finally, Straw Hat!
Straw-boy!
Kuma! You're so persistent!
Oh, no, no...!
Oh yeah, that jitte is tipped
with Sea Prism Stone! That bastard!
Gear 2!
I'm gonna take care of you!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
White Launcher!
You've got much stronger than before!
Straw Hat!
He disappeared!
That's fast! Where is he?
It seems like you became stronger than before, as well!
Your power is not enough to beat me!
Commodore Smoker pinned Straw Hat!
Amazing!
Damn! Get your jitte off of me!
Now I know why Dragon...
...helped you at Loguetown, Straw Hat!
Dragon got in my way at that time but this time I won't let you get away!
D-Damn!
You! Leave him alone!
She got me although my body is smoke!
Kicking shouldn't hurt him!
Th-That's...! The Pirate Empress saved Straw Hat!
Hancock! What are you doing?!
Are you gonna resign from the Warlords, too?!
Shut up! I'm deafened by my own anger!
How could you hit and pin down my beloved?!
I won't let you survive!
I have never felt this much anger before!
I'm gonna cut you up and feed you to beasts!
That's the Haki of Kuja!
Hancock!
Yes!
You called me Hancock again!
Kuma! Kuma, that's enough!
It's me! Did you forget my face?!
If you don't stop, I'm gonna fight back
although I'm a gentle person!
I don't know how you know him but you may as well give up!
It's no use talking to him, Emporio Ivankov,
commander of the Revolutionary Army!
You...! What do you mean?! What's wrong with him?!
You're a friend of Bartholomew Kuma I suppose.
He was once called Tyrant Kuma and now he is...
...dead.
What are you talking...
Kuma is...
...dead?!
Ivankov and Bartholomew Kuma
were once comrades,
but despite Ivankov's desperate cries,
Kuma's cruel attacks persist.
Then Doflamingo shares the shocking truth
about what happened to Kuma.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Kuma's Transformation
Iva-san's Blow of Anger"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Kuma's Transformation
Iva-san's Blow of Anger