It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement—there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail—let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag—together, we're one
One Piece
--Who are you?
--What?
Oh? Who the heck are they?
Are they also your subordinates, Captain Usopp?
Hm?! Y-Yeah, of course!
You guys lost your memories, too?
Hi, pretty ladies! Your names, please?
What the heck is that?
It's a deer.
Shut up, human! I'm a reindeer!
It talked!
Pirates this, pirates that! What a stupid era!
I hate pirates! What I like
are money and tangerines!
There's no way that I'd
be traveling with pirates!
You guys're making quite a
racket so early in the morning.
You're interrupting my morning nap.
I have to get out of here somehow.
I've got no idea what's going on,
but it seems like there's
no point in me staying here.
A Mysterious Boy with a Horn
and Robin's Deduction!
Navigator...
Now I can rest easy for a while.
I'm glad that unpleasant pirate
hunter is off the ship, but...
I have a feeling that Navigator
might set foot on the island.
Knowing her, she probably won't do too much
until she can make a level-headed decision.
I hope so.
Hey, I'm starving. I wanna eat!
You look tasty!
What?!
Geez... You have no sense of tension, do you?
Hm?
But, well, I guess we can think about
what to do after we finish eating, huh?
By the way, Miss, I didn't get your name yet.
I'm Nico Robin.
First, could you tell us about
the memories that we lost?
Sure.
No way that I'd stay in a place
like that for even a second!
Pirates cold-bloodedly steal
things that people cherish!
I have to come up with a way to
return to Cocoyashi Village quickly.
I'm glad... that you came, lady.
I welcome you.
It's awfully quiet here.
I wonder if something happened...
I wonder if I'll find something
if I go up a bit higher...
Hm?
Newspaper...
Wh-What?!
H-Hey, wait!
This is mine!
Shut up! This newspaper is
the only thing I can depend on!
I'm not gonna let you have it!
You bastard! Stop screwing with me!
Why would I give you something to go on?!
Shut up! It's mine!
I got it first!
--Who cares?!
--Hey, who are you?!
If I knew, I wouldn't be having this problem!
What's with these people?
What the heck is going on?
--Hey...
--Hm?
What's the matter, lady?
I see... So you're looking for a boat?
--Yeah.
--The boats docked at this harbor
are the only boats on this island.
What? Is that right?
They all seem to be in disrepair, as if
they haven't been used in a long time.
It seems that everyone is too busy
with other things to care about them.
If you don't believe me, go ahead
and go around the island.
It's a small island. It won't take long.
Well, take it easy and stay a while.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it here.
I can't stay too long.
--Oh, I see.
--I'm sorry.
No, don't worry about it.
I've gotten kinda sleepy. I'm going home now.
Ah... hey!
Well then, see you later!
These guys are real pirates!
So clouds are really fluffy?
Daaachshund... Horsey-Bird...
Darn it! Why can't I remember them?!
Davy Back Fight, the large Navy fortress...
Sky islands and the sand country, Alabasta...
We really had such a grand journey?
Yes, we did.
I-I can't believe it...
The captain of this ship has a
100-million-berry bounty on his head?
Hey, don't you have some
more neat adventure stories?
I joined your crew after you left Alabasta.
So, unfortunately, I don't know
what happened before that.
Darn! That sucks!
Although I have a hard time buying her story,
it is true that the seasonings and equipment
are where I would like them to be.
Robin-san, could you tell us about the
most crucial thing-- about yesterday?
Sure. Well then, let's include
the ship's doctor, too.
Hm?
Like I said, it's backwards.
Sh-Shut up, you bastard!
You're hungry, aren't you?
Come and eat with us.
Ahh! Don't be ridiculous!
I can't eat with humans!
May I ask your opinion, too?
Please, our exceptional ship's doctor?
Dummy! Praising me wouldn't
make me feel happy! You jerk!
He sure looks happy.
We were traveling this area of sea.
Nami, are you really sure
we're on the right track?
Don't worry. The Log Pose
is pointing this direction.
Usopp! Can't you see anything yet?
Err, hold on, okay?
Let's see... Ah! I see an island!
There are coral reefs scattered all over.
It's dangerous to keep heading ashore like this.
Let's drop anchor off the coast
tonight and land tomorrow morning.
What?
Are you saying you don't
wanna listen to your navigator?
Sanji-kun, Luffy won't be having dinner.
--What?!
--Okay, Nami-san!
I'm sorry.
After that, everyone went to bed except
for me, as I was doing some research,
and the swordsman, who was standing watch.
I know it's not much, but that's about it.
The rest is what you remember... probably...
Given the way the pirate hunter talked earlier,
it seems he fell asleep
partway through the night.
It would seem so.
Would you like another cup?
Yes, thank you.
In any case, I wonder why only you
didn't lose your memory, Robin-san...
If the swordsman was really asleep,
the only difference between you guys and me
is that you were sleeping and I wasn't.
Although I was asleep, I remember!
I'm certain that we're the Usopp Pirates!
In other words, sleep determined
whether we lost our memory or not?
I just stated the facts, that's all.
I can't draw any conclusions.
I've never heard of such a case.
Now, it's your turn.
Please tell me the very last thing you remember.
I thought I went to pick
medicinal herbs with Doktorin,
returned to the castle and went to bed.
And then, when I woke up, I was here.
As for me... Hey, you're ignoring me?
I fainted after being
swallowed by a big whirlpool.
And the next thing I knew, I was here.
I thought I went to bed in my room after work,
but when I woke up, I was here.
So you don't remember
anything after those points, huh?
That's right! I heard the sound
of a horn from somewhere and...
A horn... Yeah, a horn! I heard it, too.
Come to think of it...
A child suddenly appeared before my eyes!
Don't tell me... It's not that
we lost our memories...
...but in fact, that the kid
stole our memories from us?
I don't know if that's the case,
but it's certain that he
holds the key to this matter.
Isn't it possible that we'll lose more
memories each time we fall asleep?
--Ahhhh!
Don't scare me like that!
Hey, wait. It happened in my dream, right?
A supernatural thing like that
can't actually happen, right?
Then how do you explain the fact
that we all had the same dream?
Supernatural or not, it's the fact.
I don't mean to scare you,
but in the worst-case scenario,
it's possible that you will no longer
be able to tell who you are.
Whoa! That scared me!
Hey, why do you care if we
remember things or not?
Sure, it sucks that I lost all those fun memories,
but we can just start over and go on
new adventures together, right?
D-Don't be ridiculous! We may
end up losing all our memories!
I-If that happens, our past
and dreams will all be--
They won't.
My dream won't be lost. It must
be the same for you guys, too.
Wh-What a positive thinker he is...
Our captain is the same...
whether or not he has his memories.
He's kinda amazing.
Ahh! My food is gone!
Don't touch other people's food!
Sorry...
I don't know if he's crazy or what...
...but I feel like I'm an idiot for
thinking about things seriously!
Where's the town?
This is kinda exciting!
Wha...
What're you making?
A-A new medicine for regaining
memories! Don't interfere.
--Did you find something?
--Ahhh! Don't touch that without asking!
--No. It seems like an ordinary island.
--Ugh! What the heck is this? It's bitter!
All right! Done!
This is, indeed, my great invention.
What the heck is that?
Thanks for asking! Now...
...we don't have to worry
even if we lose our memories!
I name them, "My name board"!
That's a good idea.
A question mark? That's rude!
I'm not a raccoon dog or emergency food!
"Stupid Lovelyn"?!
How do you like my idea? Cool, huh?
Don't make stupid stuff!
My memories... huh...?
People are such fragile things, Zoro...
Zoro...
You're lucky, Zoro. You're a boy.
I want to be the world's
greatest swordsman, too!
You see, when girls grow up,
they get weaker than men...
It's frustrating!
If only... If only I had been born a man...!
Don't be whining like that after you beat me!
That's not fair! You're my goal!
--Zoro...
--Boy this, girl that!
Are you gonna say that stuff
too when I beat you someday?!
You act like none of it is skill!
You're insulting all the hard
training I've been doing!
So don't say that stuff! Promise me!
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
We'll compete to see who gets there!
You dummy. You're so weak...
It's a promise!
Sensei...
Let me have... that sword...
Kuina's sword?
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
I'm going to get strong enough
that my name reaches to Heaven!
I'm going to be the world's
strongest swordsman!
I promised her...
I... I...
Yes. You can have it.
I leave Kuina's spirit and dreams... with you.
After that, I trained hard every day
and set out to sea to search for that man.
Aiming to become a master swordsman...
I got on a boat and went to sleep.
I remember up to that point.
After that... I can't remember
what happened after that at all.
What's weird, in the first place, is these swords.
When on earth did I obtain these two swords?
And yet, they suit me quite well.
What's going on?!
Who's there?!
The most current date on the logbook
is the day before the newspaper.
So it's consistent... but...
I can't believe it... Is what
that woman said all true?
If it is...
I'm a member of a pirate group...
Me...?!
There's... There's no way that's the case!
But this tattoo... What on earth happened to it?
I don't know what's going on!
I don't know...
You seem to be in excellent spirits,
pathetic humans!
As of this moment,
this island is under my control!
On this memorable day, you will
all buy your lives from me!
Those who can't pay... die!
I don't want to.
Why do we have to leave?
I... want to live in this village...
Is it because we're poor that I can't
be Belle-Mère-san's kid anymore?!
Hold it!
That 100,000's for my two daughters.
I don't got enough for me.
Belle-Mère! What are you--?!
I'm sorry, Gen-san. I just can't
say I don't have a family...
Even if it costs me my life...
Yeah, maybe we're not related by blood...
...but we're a family.
I want to be their parent,
even if it's only in name.
They're... my kids.
Belle-Mère-san!
I'm sorry! I was never able to
do anything mother-like for you!
That's not true!
We don't need anything! Just don't die!
Nami...
Make your dream... come true!
Live...!
Die with your pathetic love.
Nojiko! Nami!
I love you!
I'm joining the Arlong Pirates...
...to be a surveyor and draw sea charts!
Nami...
I made an agreement with Arlong
to buy Cocoyashi Village from him.
To buy the village?
For 100 million berries. If I buy
the village, we can be free.
But, 100 million berries?
I'm not sure you can earn that
much working your entire life!
I will earn it! No matter what it takes!
If I ask for help from anyone,
more people will get hurt.
It'll hurt, you know...
Yeah...
Staying with the people who
killed Belle-Mère-san'll hurt.
If you survive, lots of fun things will happen!
I'll be fine. I'll put on a big smile,
even when I see his face!
I've decided not to cry anymore.
I've decided to fight on my own!
Belle-Mère-san...
Can't wait...
I'll steal all the rest... All the rest...
Oh, shoot.
Did I wake you up?
--No...
--You can go back to sleep.
If I notice something unusual, I'll wake you up.
It's okay. Sorry, Robin-san.
Shall I make some coffee to help us stay awake?
Thanks. That would be great.
At any rate, he's sleeping like a log,
after saying that he was gonna
stay awake no matter what.
So you two weren't asleep yet?
So it was you who stole everyone's memories?
I'm surprised that you've noticed.
But it's too late.
Wake up! Everyone, wake up now!
Oh? I see you have some mysterious technique.
--Huh?
--Hm?
Ugh! He's here!
--Ahhh!
--What? Breakfast?
That wasn't nice, lady.
To think that you woke them up...
I guess it can't be helped now.
I didn't wanna do this.
Hm? Ahhhh!
What're you doing there?!
--What?
--I'm not gonna let you take that place!
I've decided that that place is my special seat!
Don't you dare...
...sit there without asking!
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Whoa?! Wh-What's this? What's this?
Argh! What the heck is this?!
It's scary!
Wh-What was that?
Hey, isn't he in trouble?
He's not moving.
Is he still alive?
Doctor! Doctor!
Oh, right, that's me.
My memories are back!
We're setting off toward the distant orange horizon
Today's winds are blowing
across the morning sea
I can't sleep
The kind of passion I saw this very morning
cannot be stifled by anyone
Hope, frustration
and much more might come our way
but for now
we can just start from scratch
Some time ago, we had a dream
in which we followed our aspirations
so we'll raise our hands high
and embrace the shining sun in our hearts
We're going to make it to that place
All right! My memories are back!
You are all my friends!
Cook, swordsman, navigator,
doctor, scholar, and... liar.
--Hey...
--Well then, we'll go bring back Nami and Zoro!
I totally agree about Nami-san,
but we don't need that man.
--Right, we don't.
--I guess we don't. No! We do!
We can't do without even one person!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Now, Let's Get Back Our Memories!
The Pirate Crew Lands on the Island"
I'm gonna cut you jerks down!
Now, Let's Get Back Our Memories!
The Pirate Crew Lands on the Island