Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
Please, leave the ship, Sanji-san.
I don't want to kill you.
No way!
Pearl... Cymbals!
I took everything away from that damn geezer...
So that I could live...
His power...
His dream...
This restaurant is that geezer's treasure!
I... I can't repay the damn
geezer for his kindness
unless I risk my life for him, too!
Gum-Gum...
Stop it! Keep your hands off of them!
...Battle-Axe!!
Cool-headed,
Cold-hearted Demon!
Pirate Fleet Chief
Commander Ghin!
The fin's been smashed!!
How dare that brat do such a thing?
Is he trying to destroy the ship?!
Ghin! Blow Zeff's brain out!
Do it already!
B-But he saved our lives by giving us 100 meals!
Ghin, you son of a bitch!
Hey!
I didn't really attack you guys or anything...
...I only broke the fin.
Hey, chore boy!
What do you think you're doing?!
I'll sink it.
What?!
I'll sink this ship.
That ain't funny!
I was wondering how you'd explain that...
Are you crazy, you damn bastard?!
If I destroy the ship, there'll be no reason for them to attack.
What?!
What do you know?
What do you know about
the significance of the kindness I received?
What do you know about this restaurant?!
So you're gonna die for the restaurant?
Are you stupid or something?
What'd you say?!
Dying isn't...
Dying isn't something you
should do to repay kindness!!
That's not what he saved you for!
Being given life and yet dying...
is something that a weakling would do!
Then is there any other way
to settle this matter?!
Now, now, you guys... Stop fighting.
It's simply disgraceful for you to fight
among yourselves after all this.
You can't do any more reckless things
while the hostage is with us anyway.
It was unfortunate for you guys to have
the Krieg Pirates as your opponent.
Burn to death with my Fire Pearls!
Huh?
Ghin! Why...
Ghin-san?
Sorry, Pearl. Out of my way...
Ghin! Are you going to betray us?!
I'm sorry, Don Krieg.
He saved our lives.
I don't want him to die this way.
At least... At least...
...please let me bury him with my hands.
Have you lost your mind,
Pirate Fleet Chief Battle Commander?
Are you all right, Owner?
Owner! Please hang in there!
Chief Battle Commander?
Then he wasn't an underling?
To think that he cracked the shield guy's shield... How powerful...
See? It worked great...
my plan to lure him out...
Liar! You really were going to
break the ship, weren't you?!
Sanji-san!
What?!
I wanted you to leave this ship unhurt,
but it looks like that's not gonna happen.
You got that right.
I can't let you have this restaurant
even if it means risking my life.
Then, at least burying you
with my own hands is...
...my way of settling this matter.
Hmph! Thanks. To hell with you!
You too, Straw Hat.
Well... I won't lose against weaklings like you.
You bastard!
What did you just say to our Chief Commander?!
"To hell with you"? "Weaklings"?
How dare you run your mouth like that!
We're the Krieg Pirates,
the strongest pirates in the East Blue!
Wasn't it just because you had
the biggest number of pirates?
Oh, boy...
You struck at the heart of the matter...
So I was right...
You son of a bitch!!
I'm gonna kill you!!
Stop mocking us!!
Back off!!
Don Krieg!
But...
If you get upset when called weak,
that just proves that you are weak.
The result will decide if you're strong or weak.
You've got me. Don't get so worked up!
Y-Yes, sir!
Ghin!
Finishing off that cook is your responsibility.
I'll take care of that naive idiot over there...
Understood, Don Krieg.
Hey, brat!
Hm?
I'll make you fully experience the true
power that conquered the East Blue.
I'll teach you that your devil fruit
or whatever it is means nothing.
All your griping's getting annoying....
I'll kick your ass. It's as simple as that.
I'm coming over now.
You just wait there!
What impudence...
This is it for that cook.
That's right.
When Ghin-san holds that weapon
in his hands, it means he's serious.
His nickname is... Demon...
It doesn't matter if his enemy
is crying or screaming,
he tortures him to death mercilessly.
He's a demon who doesn't
have a shred of sympathy...
I'm sorry, Sanji-san, but you can't defeat me.
Just keep saying that, you small fry.
Here I come!
You son of a...
Sanji!
I warned you... that you can't defeat me...
See you...
Just accept your defeat!
Yeah!
Our Chief Commander is really incredible!
Crush him, Ghin-san!
Sanji!
Sanji! Come on!!
Die!
That cook landed a blow on Ghin-san...
Don't tell me Ghin-san is
gonna be defeated, too...
You fools...
What have you seen with
your own eyes all this time?
Ghin is a coolheaded demon
whom I put my trust in.
That's exactly why I appointed
him as the Chief Commander.
He'll show his true colors soon.
Is Sanji really okay?
Of course he isn't!
Combining the attacks from that shield guy,
he must have at least 5-6 broken ribs.
Those skewered dumplings...
aren't as good... as I thought.
Is that the best the Chief Commander can do?
Hm? What's he doing?
Is this any time to be paying attention to others?
Ah-ha!
All right!
I'll kick his ass while I have an opening!
Hm?
Don't overexert yourself.
Huh?
You bastard!!
Do you really intend to fight me?!
Intend to fight you?
I don't need to do such a thing.
What's needed is a means to kill.
That's all.
And that's the force that humans have.
Remember it, you damn monkey!
What?!
If you take a monkey lightly, it'll scratch you!
Sanji!
All right!
His bones are shattered by now!
Get him!
Dammit! If only he hadn't taken
the damage from the shield guy...
He's taken at least 10 hits
of those iron balls by now...
You really do whatever you want... you small fry!
Damn... He's really strong...
I'll finish you off now!
Don't struggle any more...
What was that?! Pity?
Don't underestimate me!
Ah! Ghin-san!
Sanji!
Ah! Sanji!
Oh, no! He can no longer bear even
the shock from his own attacks...
All right!
That's our Ghin-san!
You... damn... bastard...
I can't...
I can't... Don Krieg...
Huh?
I can't...
I can't do it, Don Krieg!!
Ghin...
I can't... kill this man...
What'd you say?!
It was... it was the first time for me...
Even when I'm down and out,
I won't take charity from others.
Take this food away now!
Stop whining and eat it already!
To me, anyone who's hungry is a customer.
Sorry, but I'm not a customer.
I can understand how a hungry
person feels more than anyone.
You can die for your pride if you want,
but if you eat and survive,
don't you think there's a future for you?
Sorry...
Sorry... Thank you... I thought I'd die.
I thought I was done...
Delicious... Delicious...
I've never eaten food so delicious.
It's damn delicious, isn't it?
Sorry... You're gonna get yelled at,
because you fed me free, right?
There's no proof, so there's no
reason for me to be yelled at.
No one had treated me so kindly before...
So I can't... kill this man!
Come back any time!
I know... I don't intend to betray you.
I don't think what we've done up until
now is wrong or anything, either...
I still respect your power
and I appreciate you as well.
I was really happy when you
put your trust in my strength
and appointed me as the Chief Commander.
So I've followed your orders
and I will from here on as well...
But... But...
I can't kill... just this one person!
Don Krieg... If circumstances allow... is there any way...
is there any way you'd let this ship...
this restaurant off the hook...
You son of a bitch!
As if defying my orders wasn't enough,
now you're giving me a lecture?!
What's the meaning of this craziness?!
How disappointing...
Morality... Sympathy...
I hate those kinds of things the most.
Didn't I always say that?!
Move away, guys...
Don! That's...
M... MH5!
That's the strongest poison gas weapon!
What?!
Poison gas?!
Ahh! Mask!
Put the mask on!
Hurry up!
We'll be killed, too!
To use a weapon like that...
That's despicable, you bastard!
Do you know what's gonna
happen when you use that?!
Stop whining about stupid stuff, you fools!
This is a battle!
Winning is the only goal.
Foul play? Dirty?
What's wrong with that?!
Might makes right.
No matter what means we take,
the result is everything.
Using poison gas or whatever...
Winning is all that matters.
That's power.
What a horrible bastard...
Throw that gas mask away!
You're no longer one of us.
Die!
I won't let you shoot poison gas!
Stop scampering about, anchor boy!
D-Dammit!
Ghin! You don't have to listen
to what that weakling says!
I'm gonna kick his ass now!
Don't mock Don Krieg!
He's the strongest man.
You can't defeat him.
Come to your senses, you idiot!
That man is trying to kill you!
I deserve it...
...since I couldn't fulfill my role,
shamelessly losing to emotion...
This is... This is a well-deserved punishment!
Ghin!
Why... Why?
Ha! So you showed your pride at the end... But it's too late.
Die together with that cook!
Deadly Poison Gas Bomb... M... H... 5!
Dive into the sea!!
Owner! Get inside the restaurant!!
Let me borrow those.
Sanji! Ghin! Use these!
Chore boy!
Now for mine!
Ahh! Everyone dived into the sea!
Oh, boy... Oh, boy... Oh, boy...
I'll show you whose graveyard this place is!
You can't stop my ambition with a silly weapon!
How come you don't flinch?!
You don't know?
Are you stupid or what?
What'd you say? Say that again!
Don't repeat it!
You're the one who told me to say that again.
How selfish you are...
Next time, on One Piece:
I Won't Die!
Fierce Battle, Luffy vs. Krieg!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
I Won't Die!
Fierce Battle, Luffy vs. Krieg!