Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
However, there they find the New Fishman Pirates
have been plotting to destroy Ryugu Kingdom,
arm in arm with Vander Decken, who has been
stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
Uh, everybody on Fishman Island.
Can you hear me?
I'm the captain of the New Fishman Pirates from the Fishman District,
Hody Jones!
A Kingdom in Shock
Orders to Execute Neptune
All right. Next!
Next!
You won't step on it?!
I'm sure Queen Otohime would forgive us.
If I refuse, they'll kill me! I have no choice!
I'm sorry, Queen Otohime!
Okay, you pass! Next!
This is boring! Surprisingly, they're all just stepping on it.
Otohime was not that well-respected after all!
Daruma-san, Captain Hody is on the air now!
Huh?
--So he is the one who is behind all of this! --He made us step on the picture!
Hey, wasn't he the one who killed the assassin of Otohime-sama?
Yes, his name is Hody Jones! I'm sure it was him!
Wasn't he a soldier of the Neptune Army?
There is something I want to tell all citizens...
Sea Forest
...of Ryugu Kingdom.
This country will soon be destroyed.
And it will be rebuilt under a new king.
Namely, me!
What is he talking about?!
Coral Hill
Who does he think he is?! Cut the crap!
--Where is he broadcasting from? --What happened to the King?
I heard the Straw Hats occupied the palace - what happened to them?
What's going on in this country?
The new Fishman Island over which I will rule is going to be strict in discipline.
Those of you who hope for friendly relations with humans,
get packing and leave this country!
Humans are weak and they don't know their place.
They don't deserve any help from us strong Fishmen.
Instead, we will have new residents from the Fishman District soon.
They hate humans and hope to change this island like us.
They're in the same camp as us.
What? New residents?
Waterwheel Town
All those outlaws will come and live with us?
I bet you all witnessed how your beloved Queen Otohime died.
She was so selfless and tried so hard to build a bridge between Fishmen and humans.
But who killed her?!
It was a human.
If you trust them and meet halfway in friendship, they'll disappoint you again!
Why can't you see it?!
That bastard!
Duped by the Neptune family, you are all heading down the path of death.
Their high-sounding dream is just unfeasible.
It's a lie that will lead you to perdition.
No!
Look at this!
Father-sama!
Father!
King-sama!
The Great Knight Neptune got old like anyone else.
There is no future for Fishman Island if the old guard remains in power.
Unfortunately the King was captured because of us...
...or Zoro.
Don't worry, Nami-san. It's all that Mosshead's fault.
What did you people do?!
B-B-But, Boss Jinbe!
Soldiers of the Neptune Army attacked Nami-chin and the others first!
The Neptune Army?
Citizens of Fishman Island!
It's time to say goodbye...
...to the old Ryugu Kingdom!
Three hours from now, at Conchcorde Plaza,
I'm going to cut this incompetent King's head off!
The Great Pirate Era began...
...when they executed a human - Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
That era saw humans grow to persecute Fishmen.
So this time, by executing Neptune, I'll start the Great Fishman Era...
...where Fishmen will dominate humans.
As you may know by now, I'm at Ryugu Palace as I speak. And we found something good.
It's the letter from the Celestial Dragons that Queen Otohime got 10 years ago,
at the risk of her life!
If I destroy that letter, it's over. You won't get another one.
And,
in this big box,
there are signatures from the majority of this country.
I couldn't believe my eyes!
There are so many fools who want to befriend humans!
Those of you who have signed your name would oppose my new kingdom.
So this is actually...
...a list of traitors!
No more stepping on her picture.
It would be easy to pretend you don't mind stepping on it.
But these signatures will tell who is my enemy and who is not.
It's hard evidence!
I will take care of those enemies one by one.
First...
Togare from Coral Hill.
No, I... I'm not... I...
Next, Gotan from Waterwheel Town.
What?
Luca from Mermaid Cove.
Garcia from Fishverly Hills.
Meverly from the Coral Apartments.
There are a lot more!
Stop!
I won't let you hurt my folk!
Well, enough for now. We don't have time anyway.
Lastly...
Straw Hat Pirates!
I'll show you something good.
I know you are somewhere on the island watching this.
You people shattered Arlong's dream - he was a symbol of Fishmen's anger.
Zoro! Usopp! Brook!
--What fools... --I can't believe they got caught!
Do it.
Yes, Boss!
--Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? --Wh-What's going on?!
Th-This is so high!
--What's this noise? --It's like a roar...
--It's water! --It's water!
That room will be filled with water by the time we finish executing the King.
You lowly creatures can't survive that, can you?
Straw Hat Luffy with a 400-million-berry bounty!
Your people's heads will serve perfectly as a lesson to humans above ground.
Now, let's start cleaning up the old Ryugu Kingdom!
Bury the embarrassing past and shift the helm towards the great future!
Fishman Island will win back its pride in three hours!
I-I can't believe it!
We won't let them do that!
Now, issue an order to Daruma and the others to assemble.
It's gonna get busy.
Yes, Boss.
I'll make your execution a big show.
So that all citizens of Fishman Island will be afraid of me.
How could you be so selfish? You can't govern a country like that!
All kings are selfish.
You were a selfish king to us.
You and Otohime's dream made me sick ever since I was a soldier in your army.
When the leader changes, a country will change, too.
I will be the "law" from now on!
Damn! The water level keeps rising!
Usopp-san, I just got dry. I don't wanna soak in sea water again!
Me neither!
Do something, Zoro-kun!
All right. Then...
...untie me.
Got it!
I feel it! I feel my psychic power! Chains, come off! Chains, come off!
Chains, come off! Come off, chains! Come off...
...or not!
It's no good. I don't have any psychic power.
Hey hey, did you see it?
The look on those Fishmen's faces when I moved.
He isn't moving. Is he dead?
I should stay dead.
What should we do with these skeletal remains?
How did they even get here?
I guess they flowed in with the water when Captain Hody broke the wall of the palace.
Let's pull them up onto the bridge.
Great!
Brook can free us later if he keeps pretending to be dead.
He was adrift at sea. I feel sorry for him.
He must've been dead for 50 years or so.
That's correct!
You got it right!
H-He's moving!
Yes, I'm a dead skeleton--Brook!
Wait!
Nice, Brook!
Touch my bones!
Here, here, here! Here!
That's enough!
Damn.
Oh, I can't stop laughing just thinking about it!
We got caught because of you!
Help! They're gonna kill me!
Oh, I'm already dead.
Well, at least Nami and the others got away.
They can bring Luffy and the others here.
What if they don't come?!
Robin would say,
"I hope Nami hasn't been eaten by a deep-sea fish."
Sounds exactly like her!
This is different from any of Poneglyphs than I've seen before.
This is like a letter... A letter of apology.
Who are you apologizing to? And who are you?
"Joyboy."
Hey.
He said I'm worth 400 million! When did they raise it?
This is no time for that!
Obviously, they want to fight us.
The Paramount War at Marineford made you infamous instantly.
When it goes over 300 million, it's not easily increased again.
But if somebody wants to fight me, I'll fight!
Hey wait, Luffy-kun!
Father-sama...
Father-sama!
Father-sama! Father-sama!
Megalo!
I have to go save him!
Wait, Princess Shirahoshi!
Stop, Megalo!
Wait!
Boss Jinbe-sama! But...
Luffy-kun, Princess-sama, both of you have to wait!
Princess, I don't think you should go either.
Hachi-sama...
What Hody is most afraid of in Ryugu Kingdom now is...
...Princess Shirahoshi's ability!
Even if he reshapes Fishman Island exactly the way he wants,
once she controls the Sea Kings to attack the island, it'll be gone.
He took the King hostage to use him as a shield.
So what they're really going for is Shirahoshi-chan.
Hody is not planning to capture her and get control of her power.
He prefers her power didn't exist at all.
That's why he teamed up with Decken who is capable of killing her.
Hody wants to get rid of everything that could stand in his way.
He is right.
Rushing to the plaza is just what Hody wants Princess-sama to do!
I have been told about my power but...
...I have never communicated with the Sea Kings-sama.
I don't even know if I really have that kind of power...
But even so, I'm sure that Hody will try to kill you.
And we shouldn't let Hody know that you can't control the power.
It's good that he is afraid of it.
Is that all? Then I'll get going.
Shark! Take me to Ryugu Palace!
Sanji, take care of Wimpy!
Yeah! Count on it.
I said "Wait," Luffy-kun!
Huh?
You people shouldn't fight Hody!
Why are you trying to stop me?
Is it because we're humans?
You two shouldn't say that! It makes things more complicated!
That's right! You humans shouldn't do that!
The surviving Fishmen will hate humans again!
You have to leave it to me.
Jinbe! They have my crew!
And I got to do something about Hody before my friends get into real trouble!
Luffy-chin...
Straw Hat.
Why can't you see it?!
--I'm going. --You're impossible!
Just shut up!
Stop me if you can!
Luffy.
I shouldn't let my guard down just because we fought together.
I almost forgot that you're that man's brother.
If you're not going to listen to me, I have no choice!
Whoa... Whoa!
You ready to do this?
Kid?
Luffy and Jinbei's emotional battle has begun!
Luffy faces the overwhelming force of Jinbe's Fishman Karate.
Their duel is interrupted, and takes an unexpected turn!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Rift Opens!
Luffy vs. Jinbe"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Rift Opens!
Luffy vs. Jinbe