Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and in order to move on
to the next stage, the New World,
they return to Sabaody Archipelago!
Oh my!
What? None of the others are here yet?
Take another good look at the poster!
Your bounty has to be
at least seventy million berries.
We're not accepting any captains below that level.
Get lost!
I'll only tell you one more time.
You're not good enough for me.
I'm not gonna drink with you!
Sure-Kill Green Star...
Devil!
Hey, girl.
Will you drink with me?
Come on, baby!
Yeah!
Yeah! I'm all bones!
Bone!
The manly Sanji...
has returned from hell!
Brook's concert?
Pirates wanted for the Straw Hats?
What is going on?
Sorry to have kept you waiting, Sunny!
We'll set sail soon!
Oh, did it hit you?
My bad!
See ya!
Stop right there!
Huh?
An Explosive Situation!
Luffy vs. Fake Luffy
This isn't good...
You can see Sabaody Archipelago there in the distance.
Luffy, this is as far as we can take you.
No one must find out about our relationship.
Okay.
Put this on...
like this!
I don't need that! That's too much!
You don't?
But you never know what might happen.
Sure.
You have to be careful.
Make sure you hide your face.
Right now, everyone thinks you're dead.
But thanks to what happened two years ago,
the whole world knows your face.
If you're discovered,
you might never make it off these islands.
Got it.
I've loaded your pack with
500 changes of clothes, 1,000 lunches,
and a five-year supply
of handkerchiefs, tissues, and towels.
There's also a three-year supply
of drinking water and snacks... and silver cutlery.
And a three-year supply of toothbrushes, soap, hand lotion and bug bite ointment.
You overdid it!
I hope you can safely meet up with your friends.
Yeah. Thanks for everything, you guys!
Good luck!
I hear Sabaody has become less safe these days.
Indeed. That's why the Navy
has been keeping a close eye on it.
Please be extra careful!
All right!
If you ever need us, the Kuja Pirates will always come to your aid!
Please remember that.
And... I have one more request.
What is it?
I'm not gonna marry you.
Not that... Go, but please don't say "goodbye."
Is that all?
I never say goodbye to nobody!
'Cause I always plan to see them again!
Now, off I go!
Take care, Luffy!
See you!
See ya!
He said he wants to see me again!
Is this what they call...
a proposal?!
No, it's not!
Hancock told me so many times to be careful...
You bumped into me on purpose, didn't you?
H-He's in serious trouble!
Grove #13
Shakky's Rip-Off Bar
W-What?!
The first one here was that idiot swordsman?!
Unbelievable...
I forsee a difficult voyage ahead.
The second one here was Franky-chan.
He came about ten days ago
and went straight to the ship.
So the Sunny is safe?
Not a scratch on her.
I finished coating her too.
That's good.
And this guy did a great job as well.
Call it a badge of honor!
I regret nothing!
Yes! A year to recover!
I didn't realize you had such a strong sense of duty.
We owe you big time, Duval.
What's that? I'm handsome?
I just wanted to pay you back, young master!
Through rain and shine, storm and snow,
I stood my ground and protected the ship
from those bloodthirsty pirates!
Day after day after day!
I was hurting all over, but I kept on fighting.
Duval-sama!
Even so, how'd you get hurt this badly?
Well, fall for me...
I mean, listen to me, young master.
After a while, even the Navy showed up—
And Nami-chan showed up third.
Nami-swan?!
Where is she?! Where?!
She got bored and went
to town to do some shopping.
What about my epic struggle?!
Nami-san's shopping! Nami-san's shopping!
Usopp-chan arrived fourth.
He got here three days ago and went to town.
Chopper-chan was fifth.
He arrived yesterday.
Brook-chan came to the island for his concert today.
Concert?
What's that?
And then you came.
So, counting you, there are already seven of you on the archipelago.
Nico Robin and Luffy are the only ones left.
It's no easy feat just getting to this island.
You really are an amazing bunch of pirates.
It looks like you might all make it back safely.
That's true.
But I didn't know you were the one training Luffy.
He must be unbelievably strong by now.
I haven't seen him for about six months.
I can't wait to see how he's grown.
Grown, huh?
And I can't wait to see how much Nami-san's grown!
Hey, you alright?
Y-Young master?
Still, I endured two years of arduous training.
I have to show off the results.
So I gotta shake off any signs of temptation.
You're just saying that!
Grove #47
Run!
Some rookies are fighting again!
I thought the pirates would settle down
after Whitebeard's death...
But it's the exact opposite!
Pirates have been coming from all over.
The whole island is pretty much
part of the Lawless Lands now!
Really?
Seems dangerous.
Do you get it now?!
Blackbeard, Kid, and Drake
are doing as they please in the New World
and we're the ones who'll follow—
No! Surpass them!
Hey, look!
Th-They are...
So the rumors are true after all.
People thought they died fighting the Navy here on Sabaody Archipelago two years ago.
But they really did come back.
No doubt about it.
The most powerful crew on the island right now is...
The Straw Hats...
Huh? Is it Nami?! Maybe Usopp?!
What?
The Straw Hats?!
"Pirate Hunter" Zoro.
He's got a bounty of 120 million berries.
"Black Leg" Sanji.
His bounty's 77 million berries.
She became a wanted criminal at the age of eight. Nico Robin.
Her bounty's 80 million berries.
And the "Cotton Candy Lover"—
Tony Tony Chopper.
With a 50-berry bounty!
It's so low!
"Straw Hat Pirates"
Zoro, Sanji, Robin, Chopper
Who is it?!
Is Luffy there, too?!
Move! Please get out of my way!
Finally some worthy opponents!
Let's do this!
Hold it!
Why're you stopping us, Captain?!
If we pick a fight with them,
Straw Hat Luffy won't keep quiet.
It's not a good idea to get into unnecessary conflict
when we're about to enter the New World!
Hey! Zoro! Sanji!
Robin! Wait up!
What's with that talking raccoon dog?
Huh? What're you talking about?
Raccoon dogs can't talk!
But...
I heard you got here first, Zoro!
Can't believe you didn't get lost.
So Sanji and Robin finally made it too!
See?
Never seen anything
like that before, that's for sure.
Sounds exhausting.
Let's just ignore it.
Huh?! Wait!
Hey, wait a minute, I said!
The target, Nico Robin, is a Devil Fruit user.
We'll be in trouble if she fights back.
We need to catch her off guard!
I better hurry.
They might all be here already.
I really want Nami-san and Robin-chan
to get a taste of my improved cooking immediately!
But before that, I better go see
if the kitchen on the Sunny is okay.
And then I'll go shopping for ingredients!
Was that Sanji?
Why don't you say something?
Did you bump into me knowing who I am?
Didn't you see?
How you made me look like a fool!
You humiliated me in public.
Me, an elite pirate with a bounty of 400 million!
Get down on your knees, fear me,
and beg for your life!
Please...
Please just apologize!
Doesn't he value his life?
Looks like he finally realized
what a huge mistake he made.
And now he can't even speak up.
He's that scared!
Just a minute ago, a man with a long nose and a woman with long hair embarrassed us.
The Captain's in a bad mood right now!
You better apologize, and quick.
On your knees!
One wrong move now and you'll be crow food.
Our captain is quick to pull the trigger, you know?
Get on the ground already!
That's Straw Hat Luffy!
Do you want to die?!
Apologize already!
I'm really sorry!
But I don't have time for this.
What's he doing?!
Okay!
You asked for it!
What?!
Hey, did he do something just now?
Hancock was right.
Guess I better put it on after all.
Hey, Zoro! Sanji! Robin!
What happened to you guys?
I haven't seen you in ages!
I never thought Zoro and Sanji
would get to be so chummy in just two years.
But why are you guys ignoring me?
Hey, he's still following us.
Are you guys feeling shy, you jerks!
That raccoon dog seems to know an awful lot
about us Straw Hats, doesn't he?
I've been thinking about that too.
You don't think... Have a look at this.
He couldn't be?!
The real Cotton Candy Lover, Chopper,
worth 50 berries!
The crew's pet?
You guys seem a little different!
But that's okay!
The crew must've dumped him on this island when they were still alive and now he's gone feral.
He thinks we're his masters.
That's why he's following us.
Then let's ditch the fox and keep the real thing.
If our pet's the one on the wanted poster,
we'll look more convincing.
We're gonna keep it? What does it eat?
Cotton candy, what else?!
But we don't have any!
We don't need you anymore! Just get lost!
Come here, Chopper.
Have a cucumber.
Scary! Robin, that's scary!
Now's our chance!
Hey, Robin!
What? Hey, Nico Robin!
W-Who were they?
This is bad!
They took Robin!
They must be kidnappers!
Hey, shouldn't we tell Captain Luffy?
What?! You've already met Luffy?!
You're right!
They must have new members by now, too!
Yeah, we better rescue Robin as quickly as possible, huh?
Take me with you!
Reporting from Sabaody Archipelago!
We've captured Nico Robin!
And we also captured... a fox?
It bit her and won't let go!
Franky's all fired up.
Guess I don't have to worry about the Sunny.
Which means I have to...
Viva Sabaody!
Hold on, I gotta focus on cooking!
I need to stock up on the best ingredients I can find first.
It's beautiful!
I need ladies!
And then I'll whip up something so good
it'll knock Nami-san and Robin-chan off their feet!
But,
this place doesn't have anything interesting.
What should I do?
Well, you might want to check out the shop
on the coastline of Grove #42.
Oh, thank you! 'Preciate it!
Hey, fisherman!
Can you sell me something cheap?
Huh? Nobody home?
Hey, are you the owner of this place?
What's wrong?
He's gone!
The green-haired guy!
Green hair?
What happened?
This is terrible! You see...
Old man, I wanna fish.
Huh?
Young man, you don't look like
a fishing type of guy.
I promised to meet up
with my friends on this island.
But I arrived first,
none of the others are here yet.
Since I'm first,
I have nothing to do.
Can you take me out to sea on your fishing boat?
Sure, I'll take you with me on that boat right there.
Get on board and wait for me.
...that's what I told him.
He had green hair and three swords?
Was he wearing a sash?
That's right!
And a big scar on his eye.
You know him?
A scar on his eye?
Is this the guy?
That's him! That's the guy!
Are you his friend?!
Well... we're acquainted.
I told him to get on my fishing boat!
I'm sure I said that.
But when I got here...
No, young man, not that ship!
That's a pirate ship!
Men! It's time to set sail for the New World!
The place of our dreams!
W-Wake up, young man!
You're on the wrong ship!
...so, he's probably on his way to Fishman Island by now.
That idiot!
I thought it was strange that he'd get here first.
I should've known he'd get into trouble right away.
But it's a pirate ship!
They'll kill him!
No, no, it's alright.
This isn't your fault.
He isn't that easy to kill.
At least I can tell the others what happened.
Anyway you got any fish for me?
Fish? You know...
Hey, what's that?!
Look in the water!
Something's surfacing!
What is that?
It's huge!
It's a galleon!
Did it break under the water pressure
because of a bad coating job?!
Did a Sea King hit it?!
It looks like it was sliced in two by a blade!
Don't be ridiculous!
How could anyone do something like that?!
You...
ruined our dreams for the New World!
Fate's a fickle thing.
You should blame your own destiny.
It brough a curse upon your ship.
Bullcrap, you're the one...
Look!
Someone's on top of the ship!
Oh, he's back!
Well, I guess that's fine.
I got on...
the wrong ship.
One by one, the Straw Hats are gathering on the Sunny, preparing to set sail.
However, the Navy catches wind of this,
and sets out for Sabaody Archipelago.
The opponent that cornered Luffy & Co. two years ago
sets their sights on the crew once again!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Navy Has Set Out
The Straw Hats in Danger"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Navy Has Set Out
The Straw Hats in Danger