Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
You can't break it!
The skull mark is a symbol of faith!
Luffy!
It's a direct hit!
Zoan-Type Devil Fruit!
Chopper's Seven-Form Transformation
He must've been blown away!
Such an idiot!
Ahh!
Ahhh...
See? It didn't break!
What?! Can't be... He's stupid!
I don't know who the heck
this pirate flag belongs to...
but since this flag is a person's
pledge to risk his life...
it's not raised as a joke!
This flag isn't something you can
just break while laughing foolishly!
Incredible...
So this is... a pirate!
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
I will save this country as a doctor!
By raising this, I'll fight just like pirates do!
What are pirates?
Pirates are incredible guys at sea.
It's cool to be a pirate!
There're tons of incredible guys at sea!
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
Hey, reindeer!
Hmm?
I'm gonna beat these guys up now.
What do you wanna do?
I...
What're you saying? You damn idiot!
If you wanna protect the flag that bad,
stay there forever to protect it!
Why don't you stop... right there!
Hmm?!
Ow!
Looks like your backbone gave out...
That's just natural.
You're moving around too much!
Stop, doctor's orders!
What're you idiots doing?!
Just stand there and watch!
I'll blow him to bits along with that flag!
Time to get blown away, Straw Hat!
Stop it!
That's the idea! Get him, reindeer!
Wapol-sama! Watch out!
The little brat is showing his guts
as if he's a fully grown man...
Sorry.
I won't let you lay your finger on Wapol-sama!
Really, there are some strange
creatures in this world.
Seems like you're that "yeti" the citizens
got worked up about at one time.
You must really have spent your
whole life disliked by everyone.
You poor monster. Why's a loner like
you trying to save this country?
Don't make me laugh!
Shut up!
Even if I don't have friends, I can still fight!
As long as Doctor's flag exists, I will...
You do have friends!
I am your friend!
Straw Hat!
Are you okay?!
I'm just fine... since I'm a rubber man.
A rubber man?!
Hey, reindeer. Can you finish that guy?
Someone like that is a piece of cake.
Then it's decided.
My opponent is the annoying mouth!
How dare you, Straw Hat,
flying around like that!
I won't hesitate any longer!
You can take me down?!
Huh, you monster?!
How dare you...
Old hag! I will fight...
Shut up and watch!
If you keep moving around, you won't
be able to walk on your own anymore.
Don't worry. When push comes to shove,
my reindeer can handle things.
My name is Tony Tony Chopper!
It's a name that the world's
greatest doctor gave me!
Even if Doctor forgave you,
I won't forgive you for laughing at how he lived!
I'm the one who'll show no forgiveness!
I'll stomp you!
Rumble Ball!
Dalton-san! Dalton-san! Wake up!
Please! Dalton-san!
Vivi...
Hey! Dalton-san! Dalton-san!
Dalton is still alive.
The Twenty MDs!
His body is frozen. That's all.
Will you leave him in our care?
Hey, there are doctors.
I thought I heard that there weren't
any doctors in this country...
These guys're called the Twenty MDs
and they exclusively work for Wapol.
In other words, they're bad doctors!
That's right! We can't trust you!
Leave Dalton-san in your care when
you gave in to Wapol... to the king?!
What're you going to do to Dalton-san?!
If you want to save him,
just do what we say!
We are still doctors.
Even though we were forced to give
in by Wapol and his men's power,
we've always worked to advance
our medical research...
for the patients in this country!
It was because a certain quack
taught us not to give up.
We can't lose any more... stupid men like him!
The effect of the Rumble Ball lasts 3 minutes.
I'll take you down in 3 minutes!
3 minutes?!
You can't defeat me at all,
much less in 3 minutes!
3 minutes? That's amazing!
We'll be able to see something interesting.
Dammit! Let me fight, too!
Rumble!
What... did you say you could do?!
Marimo's Snow Melting Arrow!
Walk Point! Leg Boost!
Whoa!
Humph! Just a transformation?!
I was expecting something more!
In other words, you have
the powers of a devil fruit.
Zoan-type, just like Dalton!
A reindeer human, huh?!
Heavy Point! Weight Boost!
I'm a human reindeer!
Same difference!
I know everything about the three-form
transformation you Zoan-types use.
Marimo's Super Surprise Quattro Hammer!
I've seen all your forms.
Looks like you're a power fighter like Dalton.
But there's no way you can...
Jumping Point! Jump Boost!
...outpower me!
He jumped! He can really jump!
Whoa!
What?! What's that form?!
Wasn't his "human-animal form" the little
reindeer from earlier?! How impudent!
Guard Point! Fur Boost!
Again?!
Whoa!
Can't be... I hit him dead on!
It won't work!
I was sure that Zoan-types
had a limit of three forms.
What the heck are you?
The Rumble Ball is a drug
that messes up the wavelength
of the devil fruit's transformations.
During my 5 years of research,
I found 4 more transformation points.
3 transformations plus 4.
Seven-form transformation?
Sev...
What's the big deal with the
number of transformations?!
A... A seven-form transforming
interesting reindeer!
What's the matter with him?
Looks like his happiness exceeded its limit
after hearing seven-phase transformation.
You bastard...
What happened to your fight against me?!
To hell with seven-phase transformation!
I won't be deceived by such a sham!
It's not a sham!
Arm Point! Arm Boost!
Let me tell you one thing.
My iron hooves can smash even rocks!
Amazing!
How impudent, you bastard!
This'll show you! Marimo's Surprise...
Quattro Axe!
Snow Splitting Blade!
Hey... The castle wall got hollowed out!
Tsk! He dodged it.
Then, how about... this?!
Omni-directional Snow Splitter!
What happened to your high spirits from earlier?!
You can't win if you just
keep dodging, you know!
Brain Point! Brain Boost!
It's not that I was just dodging.
I was looking for your weak spot.
What?!
This will finish you. Scope!
A... A beam!
He'll definitely shoot a beam!
He won't, you idiot!
Shut up! It's definitely a beam!
I don't care what anyone says, it's a beam!
– What else could it be?! It's a beam!
– How can you know?! Huh?!
– I just know! It's a beam! Beam!
– Then what kind of beam?!
I should use this chance...
You were looking for my weak spot?!
So what?!
I don't have a blind spot!
You're a transforming idiot
who can't even attack!
You're the one who'll be finished!
I found it!
His jaw!
Where'd he go?!
Hoofprint...
...Roseo!
3 minutes.
All right, reindeer!
You're pretty good, reindeer! Amazing!
Shut up!
– Dalton-san!
In any event, let's go up the mountain,
Usopp-san, Mr. Bushido!
Huh?
I can't just sit around and wait!
I'm worried what happened to Luffy-san
and the others in that big avalanche!
Nami-san has a very high fever!
If anything happened...
You're worried about Nami...
On top of that, you're worried about
Dalton-san as well as Alabasta, huh?
Vivi, calm down! You're carrying
too many burdens on your shoulders!
What?
Nami is with Luffy and Sanji.
I'm sure she's okay.
They'll be fine! I believe in them!
That's right... He's right...
Usopp-san believes in his friends.
That's why he can be so calm.
Thank you, Usopp-san. I...
For you, it's just that you're afraid
of going up the mountain, isn't it?
B... But I heard that there're things
like a yeti and bear-bunnies there!
Then say so from the start!
It'll be fine. It's Luffy we're talking about.
He'll make it work.
I can't help it if I'm scared!
Any problem with that?!
Dalton-san!
W-Wait!
Ahh! Dalton-san!
Dalton-san!
Would someone please tell me
who the heck this guy is?!
Dalton-san! You can't!
Get out of my way!
We can't let Wapol in the castle! Never!
Don't tell me you're heading to the castle!
In your condition... that's reckless!
When will I fight if I don't fight now?
If Wapol goes back to being the king,
this country will become rotten forever!
There's no way you can fight in that condition!
We're no match for them, either...
I will settle this!
No matter how dirty I have to play!
Get on my back.
I'll take you to the castle.
You don't need to be modest!
I don't wanna waste your determination.
That's all.
Usopp-san...
Hold on, okay?
I will take you... to the castle now...
Usopp-san...
Hey, Usopp-kun.
I really don't think this is going to work...
It'll work! I'll take you there!
You're gonna fight for the country, right?!
You're gonna settle this, right?!
Don't worry. I'll definitely take you there!
Geez... that moron...
We just have to go up the mountain, right?
Zoro...
– You jerk! You jerk! Usopp Punch!
– Ow! Ow! What're you doing?!
I was just about to use my serious power!
Yeah... I know.
– Serious Power!
– Whoa, amazing, amazing...
Wait!
If you're willing to go that far to get there...
...there's a ropeway to the castle.
Can't be. There's no rope
connected to the castle any more.
There's one.
Someone has reattached a white rope...
...from a big tree at the
edge of Gyasta to the castle!
Gyasta?
That's the name of the town
that Dr. Kureha headed last.
Hey, Luffy!
Huh?
Where is that guy?
That guy?
He's not here!
Which guy?
That tin bastard! He's disappeared!
Ahhh! Ahhh! Ahhh!
He came up on the haired hippo.
He wouldn't go down on his own.
When on earth did he...
While you were fascinated by
the transformations, of course!
That bastard!
I'll find him right away and finish him off!
Don't tell me he got into
the castle from somewhere...
If that's the case, Nami-san will be...
That bastard!
If he lays his hands on Nami-san,
– Hold it!
– I'll gut him 100 times!
Geez, does he want to die?
Doktorin...
Hmm?
He called me...
his friend...
Where're you, annoying mouth?!
Seems like my fever is coming down quite a bit.
At this rate, it's likely that
I can go back to the ship soon.
What am I doing?!
This is no time to be in bed resting here!
Vivi is waiting for me!
What the heck is going on here?!
Is this really my Drum Castle?
What have they done to my castle?
They won't get away with this!
I will chew up every single one of them!
Nemuranai kono machi mo Ima dake wa madoromu
Even this sleepless town has dozed off for now
Kyou kara to kinou made
From today forth,
nani ka ga kawatte yuku
something's going to change
Kitto yarinaoseru hazu
I'm sure I can start fresh,
Datte hitori janai kara
since I'm not alone
Soba ni ite kureru dake de
Just by having you by my side,
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru
I feel I can become strong
Doko made ikeru kana
I wonder how far I can go,
mirai e tsuzuku basho
towards the place that leads to the future
Tooku de kagayaite sekai o tsutsumikomu
Off in the distance it shines, encompassing the world
Yoake mae
Before dawn
I should get out of here quickly
while Doktorin isn't around!
That bastard!
I'll find him right away and finish him off!
If he lays his hands on Nami-san,
I'll gut him 100 times!
Oh no! He looks like a bad guy!
I've cornered you, annoying mouth!
Dalton-san's got dynamites!
I have no idea what's going on here.
Next time, on One Piece:
When the Kingdom's Rule Ends!
The Flag of Faith Flies Forever
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
When the Kingdom's Rule Ends!
The Flag of Faith Flies Forever