Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the Paramount War against the Navy,
Luffy was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
However, 10 years ago, in the East Blue...
What did you do?!
Ace!
Don't do it!!
Where Can Freedom Be Found?
The Boy's Sad Departure
Dadan!
Stop it, you sea cretin!
Let go of Ace!
What are you guys doing here?
Finally we found you!
These are pretty serious
wounds, Luffy! Are you okay?
Dogra...
I don't see Sabo anywhere!
Sabo went home. He's not here.
Ace!
You're the boss monkey from Mt. Corvo!
I'm the mountain bandit - Dadan!
I don't know why but I'm registered
as their foster parent.
I won't stand by and watch someone
try to take my boys' lives...
...even if I'm not their real parent!
I'll just let you go if you back away.
If you don't, I'll have
to resort to violence!
Try it!
Oh yeah? Alright then...
Run!
Yes, boss!
Hey, what're you doing?!
Ace, hurry up!
Ace!
I...
...won't run!
What're you saying, Ace?!
Don't try to fight him!
Bluejam is a real villain!
He's not a guy that a kid like you can beat!
--L-Let me fight, too!
--No, Luffy!
You all, why don't you
take Luffy and go ahead!
B-Boss!
I'll take responsibility
for bringing Ace home!
Boss!
Go!
--Y-Yes, ma'am!
--Ace!
Boss! Come home safely!
A woman and a child.
If you overestimate your
ability, you'll only get hurt!
Only the strong and the
cowardly survive in wars!
The brave always die.
Is that so?
What a fool!
Damn!
I'm a dead man! The fire
is all over the place!
How could this happen all of the sudden?!
--It's hot! It's hot!
--There's no way out!
We have to give up!
What just happened?
There's a path!
The explosion left a path!
I don't know what's going
on but this is great!
Hey look, there is a ship!
I see a ship!
This path leads up to the shore!
We can get away by following it!
Let's go before the fire returns!
How awful they are to burn
the area and the residents there!
By the way,
how did you know the situation in such
an outlying country in the East Blue?
Is there something special
about this country?
This country is an example of how
the world will be in the future.
There can be no happiness in a world
where the undesirables are thrown away.
Someday, I will change the world!
If I stay here... I'll never be free!
Even in a country like
this, there are children.
Those of you who are willing to
fight for freedom, come aboard!
Goa Kingdom, Royal Palace
High Town
Did they find Sabo?
I just called in the military.
They'll find him soon.
I see. Sabo is giving us
a hard time, isn't he?
Yeah...
Is this town really safe?
It looks like the fire will
engulf the town any minute!
Isn't there any way to enter High Town?
No, there isn't.
They don't even allow a bug
to enter - nobles only!
--Boss!
Ace!
Boss!
Ace and Dadan didn't return
from the burning Gray Terminal.
Easy, easy, wait, Luffy. You're not
recovered - where're you going?
I gotta go and look for Ace and Dadan!
You can't do that!
Ouch!
See? That's what I told you.
You're seriously wounded. You
have to rest nice and easy.
There are a lot of troops in Gray Terminal now
to take care of the mess after the fire.
It's not just burned junk
that they're throing out,
but survivors, too.
They're gonna kill you if you go there.
But...!
I wanna see Ace!
I know that Sabo is worrying about us, too!
The former site of Gray Terminal
What a great view!
How can you be so happy?
It's a pain in the butt
to clean up this mess!
If we find a survivor, we're
to shoot them on sight.
There aren't any.
But there aren't as many dead
bodies as I thought there'd be.
It was a big fire. It could've
burned out the bones.
I was nervous yesterday,
thinking that the
fire might get to this side of the wall.
They say that Bluejam's
ship was on fire, too.
It's nice to know that
those villains got burned!
It's morning!
Hi! it's a nice day, isn't it?
Yes, it is a lovely morning!
There are still so many of them!
Enough with this game of tag, okay boy?
No matter how many times you
run, you can't get away, Sabo!
All the police and troops
have a picture of you now!
You will never get out of High Town...
or even out of this house!
You two, change your uniforms and
start working here as guards.
But we have our duties...
There is nothing that a nobleman can't do.
I'll get the approval of your superiors.
Sabo, you must barricade
yourself in your room
and educate yourself in your role as a noble!
No!
As you know, I can make things
happen just by giving the word.
So I can take care of
you or those two easily.
Am I understood?
Dad...
Ace... Luffy...
So why don't you mend your ways
and study hard like Stelly.
And...
...study so that you can make your parents,
who brought you into the world, happy!
Because that will make you happy, too!
Don't you think so?
Father!
Don't worry! I'm here for you!
You're so dependable, Stelly!
Okay, Let me buy you some luxurious clothes
for the ceremony the day after tomorrow.
There, we'll see the
Celestial Dragon in person!
I'm... helpless!
Okay, that's it for today.
I'll check your homework tomorrow.
Okay, have a nice day!
Ace... Luffy...
I don't think that you died in the fire.
You guys are okay, aren't you?
I wish I could see you.
But I know I'll put you guys in
danger if I try to see you now.
This place is like a birdcage!
I don't think I can stand living in
this country filled with stale air.
What is freedom?
Where can I find it?
Your shift is over.
Is it the time already?
You shouldn't be sleeping on the job.
Sorry. By the way, how
are things in the town?
The ceremony is just a day away, right?
It's crazy. People are going
wild getting ready for it.
What bad luck!
It's a once-in-a-lifetime
thing but I got to be here.
This boy and I will be the only
two in this house tomorrow.
I wanted to see the Celestial Dragon.
It depends on your attitude.
All the citizens will be
at the harbor tomorrow.
It'll be such a pain to stand guard there,
compared with this baby-sitting gig!
Then, why don't you take my place?
No way!
Alright, we're leaving now.
Take good care of Sabo.
Yes, sir.
The day of the World Noble
from the Grand Line's visit
to the Goa Kingdom has arrived.
A lavish ceremony is prepared
for the arrival of the ship.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
Hello, this is A-team on the coast.
The Celestial Dragon's ship
will arrive in a few minutes.
Roger that. It's all quiet here.
We'll continue to stand guard.
Clank!
Hey, look! There is a ship leaving port!
--What?
--Is it a fishing boat?
Hey! Come back here! Don't get
in the way of the ceremony!
It's a child! There's a child on the ship!
A child? I wonder which family he's from.
A child?
Honey, could it be...?!
No, that's impossible! The
guard is looking after him!
What a nice day! It's
perfect for setting sail!
Oh no! That's mine! Somebody
stole my fish boat!
Look! He has a black flag on it!
Does he think that he's a pirate?!
No way! A kid can't just become a pirate!
--Where is he heading?
--He's disrupting the ceremony.
The Government's ship will arrive soon!
Hurry up and do something!
Y-Yes, sir!
Hey!
Kid, come back here now!
The scariest fate for me is to
lose myself in this country and...
turn into someone else!
I'm not gonna go back!
Is it Sabo on that ship?
The Government's ship is here!
The ship is huge!
I'll die if I crash into it.
Let's avoid that.
Good. He's turning away.
It seems like the commoners are welcoming us.
Yes.
They're so blessed that
it's rare to even see them!
I can't believe that a real
Celestial Dragon is on that ship!
By the way, what is that?
That looks like a fish boat.
It'd be nice to be captain
of a ship like that someday!
Commoner!
How rude is that!
The fishing boat has been hit!
Ace and Dadan return to their hideout.
As everyone is rejoicing
over their safe return,
they learn of the tragedy
that struck Sabo at the port.
Realizing with sympathy
what Sabo had tried to do,
Luffy and Ace are befallen
by regret and grief.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Take Care of Him for Me!
A Letter From a Brother!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Take Care of Him for Me!
A Letter From a Brother!