Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
The Straw Hats have left the
Fishman Island and finally reached the New World.
But not before entering the treacherous Maubeugemour Sea.
Arriving there, they met a Giant girl who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit.
My name is Lily Enstomach.
People call me "Lily the Glutton"!
I eat a lot for a woman, right?
The ship carrying Dad will pass through here!
You mean the Navy is coming?!
If they see us, it's not gonna be pretty!
Yeah. But I have to save Dad at any cost!
Before they take him to Impel Down,
this is my last chance to save him!
Lily.
Let me help you!
I wanna try that heavenly food that only your dad can make!
They decided to help Lily save her father
- Panz Fry from the Navy's ship. However...
...a mysterious group called the Neo Navy is trying to kill him.
I heard a ship carrying Panz Fry, that big-shot pirate,
will pass through the Maubeugemour Sea soon.
It's the Navy!
--Dad! --Is that him?
"Z's Ambition! A Dark and Powerful Army!"
SIN
They deployed 4 ships just to transport a pirate?
I guess Lily's dad is really a big-shot.
Dad...
Is that the only reason?
That security is a strange choice
but I wonder why they chose to pass through
this dangerous area on their way to Impel Down.
Alright! Let's raid them already!
No way! Don't be ridiculous!
Listen. Our priority is to save Lily's father!
If we make a raid without any plan, he could get hurt!
She's right, Luffy!
If anything happens to her father,
we wouldn't be able to eat that heavenly volcano food!
Then what should we do?
Can I take charge of this operation?
What do you say?
Yes, I want you to do it, Nami-sa!
Uh-huh, all right!
First, we need a diversion team.
You take the Mini-Merry and divert their attention from a distance...
...to set up the infiltration team.
The members of the team are Chopper as boat operator,
Luffy, Robin, and Brook.
A diversion? That means I can kick their asses?!
No, you can't!
Robin and Brook will create a diversion!
You just have to wait in case something really goes wrong!
Don't do anything before!
Now, the infiltration team.
You take the Shark Submerge and sneak
onto the raft without being seen by the Navy soldiers.
Then cut the chain and release Lily's father.
The members are Zoro, Sanji-kun...
Count on me!
...Usopp, and Lily - can you do it?
Uh-huh!
That sounds like more fun.
All right?
The point is how to bring such a giant man back safely.
You're right. It'll draw their attention since he's so big.
It'd be nice if we could steal one of their ships
but it'd take too much time and energy.
So what we're gonna do instead is detach
the raft from the ship and whisk it away with Coup de Burst.
Franky, you stay on the Sunny and wait somewhere they can't see you.
Prepare for Coup de Burst.
I got it!
What about you, Nami?
Me? I'll spy on their movements with the White Hobby Horse
and take command of this mission.
Don't forget that we're in the Maubeugemour Sea.
Watch out for a sudden change in weather.
Now let's do it!
Okay!
Come to think of it, we are all Devil Fruit users in this team.
You're right.
So if we fall into the sea, we're pretty much finished.
What?!
I hope we don't drown and get eaten by sharks.
No! You're making us scared, Robin!
Since we're deploying on the open sea,
I placed all Devil Fruit users except for Lily
in the diversion team to be safe.
See you!
Where is Luffy?
I told him to get on board the Mini-Merry!
He took the Shark Submerge instead and left earlier.
What?
Well, he came with us saying that the diversion sounded boring.
Lily, I can't wait to see your dad!
Uh-huh!
How selfish!
Hey, Luffy, are you listening?!
Don't you dare sneak onto the raft!
It will screw up the whole plan!
Alright!
By the way, both you and your dad came from Elbaf like other Giants, right?
Usopp-sa, you know Elbaf?
Do I know it? Yes, of course!
The brave warriors of the sea - Dorry and Broggy...
...are our close friends!
What?! Have you met those legendary pirate bosses?!
Yeah, we have!
I can't believe it! I've never even met them!
My dad has been friends with them since they were kids.
Really?!
Yeah. He told me about them all the time.
Sounds like they're having fun!
Let's have fun here too!
Yeah!
The song is "Let's Go to the Rescue"!
Yeehaw!
Go, go, let's go! To the Ill-Tempered Sea!
Shut up!
You got us in trouble, Brook!
Sorry! I'm really sorry!
Don't get in my way!
Move out of my way!
I've never heard of a pirate who
so brazenly boarded a Government-owned cargo ship before.
Why did you do it?
I just wanted to take back what you took from them!
Since you Navy people killed Whitebeard, the New World is in disorder.
That island where the Government's ship was
moored was not an exception.
The islanders were on the brink of starvation.
But the crew on that ship took away all food that they had stored,
to provide for the World Nobles' nightly feasts!
I'm a cook!
I have to provide food for hungry people!
So you boarded the ship to steal food for them?
The islands are in disorder because of you pirates.
Don't shift the blame!
After all, we remain as far apart as ever.
We'll never be of the same mind!
You're right.
Somebody is raiding pirates these days.
Since we have a pirate on our ship, we are possible targets.
Be on the look-out and shoot anything that moves on the sea!
Yes, sir!
Guys, are you ready?
Anytime.
We're in position. We're ready too!
Thank you all!
I couldn't even sneak onto their ship if I were all by myself!
Don't thank us yet.
We haven't saved anybody yet.
He's right!
Ready?
Roger.
Cien Fleurs:
Okay, my turn.
Clutch!
What happened?!
I-It's a ghost!
I am not a ghost! I am a soul!
What's going on?
Now! Sneak in!
Roger! Go!
Oh, Sanji-san, good job.
It's going well! We finished the initial phase!
Huh?!
I can't see his face like that.
You're...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
Hey, frying pan pops!
D-Dad!
Lily?
Hey, Luffy, we cut the chains off!
"Pirate Hunter" Zoro?!
Not just Straw Hat! And that's...
Who is that?!
I'm Sanji! Sanji from the Straw Hats!
What?!
Where did they come from?!
Look what he's done.
But I assumed something like this
would happen once I heard Luffy was on the Shark Submerge.
Franky, get over here now!
There's been a change in plan!
Forget about the raft!
We'll put a rope around her father and split!
Roger!
Lily, go!
Uh-huh!
Straw Hat!
I won't let you get away this time!
That was close!
He's a vice admiral?
Yeah, he's pretty strong!
Oh yeah?
Looks like we can't avoid an all-out battle, huh?
Dad!
Lily! Are you all right?!
Uh-huh! Dad, I missed you so much!
Dad!
You must be kidding! What's going on?!
Are you okay?!
What?!
Damage report!
Consider that our greeting.
Surface and finish them off at once!
Yes, sir!
It broke the hull and we're taking on water!
--Where is the enemy ship?! --We can't find it yet!
Estimate their location from the track of the torpedoes and
concentrate fire there!
Yes, sir!
Prepare to fire! Go, Alpacacino!
Are they the pirate raiders?
Why are they firing at us Navy?!
Hey, pops! Are you alright?!
I'm okay! Where's Lily?!
Dad! I'm here!
Another bomb?!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Move!
A man?!
Outta my way!
Luffy-sa!
Damn!
Usopp! Luffy, fell into the sea!
What?! I got it!
That was unexpected.
Who is that?
You're... Shuzo!
Oh, it's you! It's been quite a while!
I didn't know you were on board, Momonga...
You're a vice admiral now, aren't you?
Don't tell me...
...you're responsible for all the raids on pirates!
Yes, I am! I'm gonna cut this guy's head off too!
I won't let you do that!
Take a look around!
Just give him over to us. If you don't...
Why?!
You were a great Navy soldier. Why are you doing this?
Do you wanna know?
I'll tell you then.
We're the Neo Navy, concerned about today's New World.
We banded together to kill all pirates in the New World!
How absurd to take a villain to Impel Down and let him continue to live!
In the name of Master Z, I'm gonna kill the pirate - Panz Fry, right here!
Did you say Z?!
You should not tell him that, Shuzo-san!
I forgot about that.
Well, I don't care!
It doesn't matter that you know our secret now
because all of you Navy people are gonna die here among those pirates!
How could you do that to Dad and Luffy-sa!
Lily-chan!
What are Luffy and the silly swordsman doing?
Who are you now?
Me?! I'm Panz Fry's daughter - Lily Enstomach!
So you're a pirate?! Then you die, too!
Iron Body!
Three-Section Lariat!
Lily-chan!
Another disturbance? I'm sick of this!
How dare you try to hit a lady!
You worthless piece of crap!
You...
--Who the hell are you?! --Who the hell are you?!
Shuzo-san, I think he's "Black Leg" Sanji of the Straw Hats!
He looks very different from the wanted poster!
I assume he's had cosmetic surgery!
No, I haven't!
He's a pirate? What is his bounty?
It's 77 million berries!
--Humph! He's a nobody. --What did you say?!
But he's a pirate too. Sink them all into the sea!
Roger!
Augh! We're in big trouble!
Now, Lily-chan, shrink down!
Uh-huh!
I don't want to fight for pirates but...
...I won't let you do whatever you like on this ship
while it's under the control of the Navy!
You're very sensible for a Navy soldier.
Praised by a pirate?
That is why I'd say today's Navy is useless.
Shame on you!
Shut up, you backstabber!
Pirate blah-blah... Navy blah-blah...
Enough with this bullshit!
Straw Hat!
Pops' heavenly food is...
...all mine!
He's a pirate with a 400-million-berry bounty - Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh, 400 million, huh?
Great! I'll kill you all at once!
The Straw Hats have begun fighting the Marines
as well as the mysterious Neo Marines.
They fight each other to a draw.
Then, as Maubeugemour reveals its unimaginable wrath
and rescuing Panz Fry seems impossible...
The Straw Hats pull off something incredible!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Z's Ambition! A Great and Desperate Escape Plan!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!