Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Yuba
Erumalu
Nanohana
Katorea
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
Erumalu
Yuba
Nanohana
Katorea
and a mighty swell.
The once-green city of Erumalu now lies in ruins.
To stop the rebel army, Luffy and
company now head into the desert
for Yuba, the oasis town.
Adventure in the
Country of Sand!
The Monsters that Live
in the Scorching Land
Burning up...
Sweat won't even come out...
Quit moaning so much, Luffy.
You'll only tire yourself out.
Guess he's not listening.
I can't go on...
I can't take hot weather...
I'm fine in cold weather, though...
It's 'cause of all that fur...
You should take off that animal suit...
What was that, you jerk?!
Don't make fun of reindeer!
Monster!
Chopper! Don't turn big!
Or else I won't pull ya!
Who're you calling a monster, Humongo-Nose?!
D-Don't be stupid!
I-I'll have you know this nose—
Just turn back already!
You don't seem to be having
a hard time, Vivi-chan.
I was born and raised here,
so it doesn't bother me much.
But what's with all these hills?
I figured a desert would be more flat.
This is a very old desert,
so some sand dunes here
are over 300 meters high.
Th-Three hundred meters?
No wonder this is like climbing mountains...
It's too much... It's so hot...
Just one drink, Luffy.
Just one mouthful.
Don't drink so much!
Let me have some, too!
That was 13 mouthfuls just now!
Hold on! You just had some! I'm next!
Stop fighting!
You'll only waste strength!
– But she started it!
– It's your fault!
Yeah! This is because of you!
So hungry...
Don't be so greedy!
It's still raw! Don't eat that!
Nami-san!
Just a minute, it'll be ready soon!
– Oh, looks pretty good!
– Get away, you!
Oh, come on!
Cheapskate! Let us eat!
Get away!
It was so hot during the day!
What's going on?!
With nothing to block out the temperature,
the desert scorches during the day
but falls below freezing at night.
The desert is fraught with unpredictable dangers.
Oh! Look at all those stars!
Didn't you see stars on your winter island?
Winter island skies are always
covered with thick snow clouds,
so I've never seen so many stars before!
I don't have the luxury of
looking at stars right now...
Cold weather doesn't bother me!
That's because you wear such a warm suit!
Hey, you! Get away!
I can't help that you're so fluffy...
Quit making fun of reindeer!
Monster!
Chopper. Don't turn big.
We need your warmth.
Yahoo!
So warm!
Come closer!
See? Warm, isn't it?
Yeah!
It must be a real surprise for you.
I mean Luffy-san.
I was surprised too, at first.
Maybe it's that he isn't captain-like,
or that normal pirate captains are
respected by their crewmates...
But just this afternoon, a simple
drink of water caused that big fight.
But...
But, you know...
The longer I've been with them,
the more I've come to understand.
That's how Luffy does things.
Eh?
He hasn't changed a bit since he was a kid.
Despite how he seems,
people always gather around him.
Even though he's my little brother,
he has a mysterious charm to him.
Oh. You already knew.
He and I do go way back.
But thanks.
Eh?
You were worried that I was concerned, right?
Yes. But it looks like I didn't
need to worry after all.
Whoa! I found a shrimp!
So this is a shrimp?! Wow!
– Shrimp don't live in the desert!
– See?!
Oh, you're right!
Is it a "desert shrimp"?
– It looks yummy!
– Hey, now! Are they edible?!
Probably! Crawfish are edible, after all!
I've never seen a real shrimp before!
Stop, Luffy-san! Throw that away!
No! That'd be a waste!
That's a scorpion!
It's small but it's very poisonous!
You'll die if it stings you!
Oh. It's not edible? How boring.
– You can have it.
– Don't give it to me!
Then I'll throw it away.
I'm sorry.
I should've mentioned it earlier.
That's for sure!
What is it, Chopper?
Something's... coming.
Something? What?
Oh? Is the wind picking up?
Everyone!
Hide behind the rocks!
What?
A storm! A sandstorm is coming!
Oh?
Whoa! Cool!
Again?! Deserts are nothing but storms!
I forgot to mention it, but sandstorms
are one of the desert's dangers!
Mention these things sooner!
What the hell was that?!
Can't people get some rest?!
Hey! Sanji! Let's have a lunch!
A Pirate Boxed Lunch!
Not yet. Not until Vivi-chan says so.
Come on, Vivi! Let's eat!
I'm out of strength!
But we're only one-tenth of
the way to Yuba, Luffy-san.
You're so dumb!
Haven't you heard of this proverb?
"If you're hungry, eat!"
You liar! Quit making stuff up!
All right.
Then what do you say we take a
break at the next rocks we find?
Alright! Rocks!
Guys! Let's hurry to the next rocks!
Whoever wins rock-paper-scissors
has to carry everyone's stuff!
Quit deciding things!
Shouldn't the loser carry the stuff?
Alright, here goes!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Hold on, now!
– Hey! You went after!
– Woohoo! I win!
Idiot.
H-Heavy... So heavy... And hot...
I won rock-paper-scissors, so why me?
It's because you won.
Now shut up and haul.
Don't drop it, now!
Rocks spotted a small ways ahead!
For reals?!
Break time! Food!
Whoa! He's fast!
Shade! Feels so good!
Hey! Say something!
I'll go get you a doctor!
Bad news!
Huh? He's coming back!
There's lots of hurt birds that can't move!
Chopper!
Right!
– Alright! Let's go, Chopper!
– Yeah!
We gotta help the birds!
Birds?!
Wait, Luffy-san!
Don't tell me these birds are...!
Eh?
All our stuff is gone!
We've been had...
It's the truth!
There really were dying birds here!
I'm sorry.
I should've mentioned it earlier.
Warusagi birds are "desert bandits" that trick travelers
and steal their belongings.
What?!
Birds playing dead?!
That's dishonest!
Yes, that's how they are.
They tricked me?!
Luffy!
Is that all you can say for yourself?!
There were three days of provisions in there!
And you just had to let some
damn birds steal everyone's stuff
smack in the middle of this desert?!
How're we supposed to cross the
desert without food or water now?!
It's not my fault. They tricked me.
Is your brain less than a bird's?!
Say what?!
Stop it, you two!
There's no use.
At times like this, it's best to let them have it out.
Yeah, huh?
Let's take a short break.
This heat is what has them fuming.
I'm sure we'll manage food-wise.
It's nothing that'll kill us.
Let's just put it out of our minds.
Yeah. Just thinking makes me thirstier.
Give us our stuff back!
Luffy-san! Don't chase them!
That idiot.
Hey, you!
Will you be able to come back?!
Come back, Luffy!
Stop! You can't get away from me!
Get back here!
What are these?!
What is this thing?
A mystery desert plant?
Neat!
What are you doing?
That's funny!
Huh? You want me to help you?
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Good thing you didn't get eaten!
The birds got away while
I was beating these guys up!
The desert sure is full of strange creatures!
Hey, camel.
What're you doing out here all by yourself?
What is it?
Did you find something?
What the...?!
What's taking Luffy so long?!
Yeah. Do you think he got lost?
He has a horrible sense of
direction but always has to run off!
And there are so many desert
dangers he doesn't know about...
Y'know, isn't he hungry
from not eating anything?
He's such a lost cause.
You can say that again.
Sorry.
For my little brother's ineptness.
I apologize for the trouble.
Good luck finding him!
Yeah.
What's that?!
What's this rumbling?!
Another sandstorm?!
No, wait! That's...!
Luffy?!
No... it couldn't be!
Why is he on a camel?!
So?! What's that chasing him?!
I can't really see!
But it seems more like something's in the sand!
It's huge!
What is that?!
A Sandora Dragon!
A what now?!
They're the largest of the
reptiles living in the desert
and they wait under the sand for their prey!
They have sharp claws and fangs,
but they hardly ever use them!
The reason being that they tend
to swallow their prey whole
because they're so large!
He really does have a gift for attracting trouble.
Setting aside the camel for the moment...
...what star was he born under to be
able to attract trouble like this?!
Hey! Camel! Stop!
– Luffy! Is it too much for you?!
– We'll lend a hand!
Yeah! I brought some meat!
Here goes, lizard!
Gum-Gum...
– Dragon...
– êpaule...
...Whip!
– ...Twister!
– ...Shoot!
Y-You didn't have to go that far...
When they're fighting,
you almost pity the monsters...
There's more?!
I forgot to mention it,
but Sandora Dragons hunt in pairs!
Mention these things!
– Ace!
– Look out!
What a nuisance.
You wanna play?
Oh, okay. If that's what you want.
Check it out!
These rocks are natural frying pans!
So, what's with the camel?
I dunno.
It was getting eaten by a mystery
plant when I was chasing the birds.
It doesn't seem to be a wild camel.
No. It even has a saddle...
I knew it!
Oh! Good for you!
Huh? You know each other?
Yeah! He gave me a ride
when I escaped from Katorea!
That's great! We can ride it?!
That'll make things easier!
Yeah, that'll be a real help!
Looks like it could carry two people!
Camels do go hand-in-hand with deserts!
Then I'll be the first one!
What was that for?!
"I am a freedom-loving, hard-boiled, compassionate camel!
Thanks for helping me out of that pinch.
I can give you a lift, but no men allowed!"
This guy's a punk!
Yeah! You let Chopper ride you!
"I'm manly!"
– Quit being stupid!
– Why, you...!
I'm so sorry!
My crewmates are so ill-bred!
You're a good boy!
What should we call you?
– Idiot!
– Moron!
Doofus!
"Lashes" it is, then!
Uhh, that's the weirdest one of all.
Okay! Get on, Vivi!
No, I can still walk!
Just get on.
Pervy camel! Pervy camel!
Now we should make a little better time!
We need to get to Yuba as fast as
we can to talk to the rebel army!
Giddyup, Lashes!
Hold on!
Hurry, guys! If you get separated,
you'll never leave the desert alive!
Quit being stupid!
I like this side of Nami-san, too!
After them! Hurry!
– Get on, Chopper!
– Yeah!
Wait for us!
Kodomo no koro yume mita boukenka mitai de
Like the adventurers I dreamed of when I was a child
Omoi no hate ni tsurenatte yuku yo
I continue on to the ends of emotion
Sukuiageta tenohira kara
I scoop up my hands,
koboreochiru suna to jikan
and the sand and time that spills from them
Kono tame ni umarete kita to oshiete kureru
show me that this is what I was born to do
Korogeochisou na supido de
Let's continue swimming
Bokura oyogitsuzukeyou
at a near-tumbling speed
Soshite dare mo
Until we wash up someday
shiranai shirahama he itsuka
on a white sandy beach
Uchiagerareru made
no one knows about
– So hot...
– Nami-san! How far did you go?!
We're completely separated now!
Come to think of it, I don't see Ace, either.
– Do you think he got separated?
– What a troublesome big brother!
– Huh?! What's that?!
– Do you see Nami's group?!
A ship! A pirate ship in the sand!
Next time, on One Piece:
Enter the Desert Pirates!
The Men Who Live Freely
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Enter the Desert Pirates!
The Men Who Live Freely