It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement—there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail—let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag—together, we're one
One
Piece
In the right corner, hailing from East Blue!
The leader of a miniscule pirate band
with a 100-million-berry bounty...
..."Straw Hat" Monkey D. Luffy!
Wow! The afroed Luffy is all
fired up in the right corner!
Lookin' sharp, Luffy!
Are you kidding me?
There's the starting bell!
--Let's do it!
--Yeah!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Only my fist is slow!
Nine-Tails Rush!
Oh...! I wouldn't ride that one if I were you...
Oh, or that one.
Told you so!
Luffy...
Oh, no...!
Full-Blast Slow-Slow Onslaught
vs. Invulnerable Luffy
E-Explosions suddenly rock our ship...
...which just happens to be the battlefield...
Caused by Foxy Face Bombs that
also happened to be loaded...!
Making their ship the battlefield
is such a dirty trick!
--Hey! Luffy! What's going on?!
--Simmer down!
Using this to his advantage, our boss succeeded
in blowing up Straw Hat Luffy
with a cannon attack!
No way! Is Luffy...?!
Is it all over for him?! He's nowhere to be seen!
Whew, that was close!
Indeed, it was a--!
What?!
Quit it! You're annoying!
Straw Hat Luffy is... alive!
--Y-You serious?!
--He's mind-boggling!
He somehow evaded the
close-range cannon barrage!
What speed! I-Is this the true power
of a man worth 100 million?!
--Of course it is!
--Just finish 'im already!
Oh! But it looks like our boss's
next attack is already underway!
From out of the resulting smoke screen
comes our boss's disturbing laughter!
But where exactly is he?!
What does "Silver Fox" Foxy
have up his sleeve this time?!
--Oh!
--There he is!
Okay, I hope you're ready!
You got blown up?!
I did not! Don't be stupid!
Liar!
Don't assume for one minute
you'll leave this battlefield alive!
--Slow-Slow Beam--!
--Gum Hook!
No more beams for you!
I'm gonna smash your arms!
He disappeared into the smoke again!
Huh?! There you are!
--A board?!
--Slow-Slow Beam!
Now, then! Which one is me?
Where will the beam come from?!
Darn it! How should I know?!
They all look like stupid-heads!
Stupid-heads...
There!
And you call yourself a
warm-hearted individual?!
You're in for it now! Look up!
Huh?
Crap! A trap door!
That's what you get for being distracted!
You're the one who told me to look up!
You might wanna pay more attention!
Huh?
Wh-What the...?! Whoa! The floor's moving!
It's dragging me away!
--There's Luffy!
--Why'd he come out of there?!
Oh, no! He'll lose if he falls into the water!
I ain't gonna fall in...!
So close!
Nah, it'd be no fun if it ended so soon!
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
Geez! What's with this ship?!
Where'd you go, fox?!
What's this?!
A Foxy pin eerily taunts Straw Hat
Luffy after his narrow escape!
In there!
The inside of the ship is our boss's
playground! Will Luffy be lured in?!
No, Luffy! It's totally a trap!
He obviously has a bunch of booby traps set!
That jerk! I'm gonna beat his brains out!
Straw Hat Luffy rushes right in!
The battle has moved inside, but I
can't enter to give the play-by-play!
This is the true essence of this round:
a solitary battle between two combatants!
Get up! Get up, Luffy!
Remember your painful training!
Quit playin' around and sit down. I can't see.
Oh, a gun deck!
Man, it's big! I bet Usopp would love this!
Now where is he?!
There he is!
All right! He's coming after me...!
Now he'll bust through
the door at breakneck speed!
Little does he know...
...that this room is filled with spikes!
Now rush in and get--
Oh. There he is.
Whoa, what's with that room?
Who fires cannons inside other
people's ships?! Seriously!
Oh. It's coming back.
You have some nerve!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Dammit!
I'll show you!
Oh! He's running away!
"Infirmary"
Get back here!
Does this brat have any common sense?!
That's it! Foxy Face Transformation!
Stop right there, fox!
--A person?
--Dear me!
Whatever's the matter? Do you feel sick?
Where are you sick? The head?
Are you sick in the head?
H-Huh?! Did anyone just come in here?
No, I didn't see anyone. But never mind that...
What's wrong with you? Your face?
That's weird... I'm sure I saw him--
Hold on! That woman looked like him!
Could it be?!
Hey, you! You're that guy's sister, aren't you?!
Counter Fox Blow!
Fool!
What is this thing?!
That's weird! He really was in this room!
Is he even trying to fight?!
Oh! The kitchen!
Fish, fish! Cut it up, sour it up! Carpaccio!
Grill up a sole, fa-mi-re-do!
Oh? Can I help you?
Have you seen a fox with its head split
in two who looks like a real moron?!
That's going too far...!
It's you!
I was the lady in the infirmary, too!
That thing, too?!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Oh... no...
Nine-Tails Rush!
Don't think I lured you
in here without a reason.
Go check out what's waiting
for you when you get sent flying!
It ain't a living creature.
That'd be against the rules, after all.
While a Slow-Slow Beam
is in effect, any impacts given
are stored up and then go off all at once.
Go on, now! Your life's final stop lies ahead!
30 seconds are up.
Huh? Where is he?
I'm... right here!
Feh-feh-feh-feh-feh!
And another feh!
What's with that outfit?!
I am Pilot Foxy! And...
...let me introduce you
to the Gorilla Puncher 13!
A gorilla-like punching machine
that's had every single flaw ironed
out through constant improvement!
Is the gorilla face really necessary?!
Excellent point!
I mean, shut up! Who asked you?!
Go, Gorilla Puncher 13!
How is it moving on its own?
It's a secret...!
You're sure sweatin' a lot...
Shut up!
You think you can dodge these
measly punches, don'tcha?
Slow-Slow Beam!
What? Where are you aiming--?
Take a look behind you!
Huh? Who's that?! A mirror?!
Yes! Mirrors reflect Slowmo Photons!
Got ya!
Ouch! Ouch!
Oh, that hurt? Too hot for you?
I forgot to mention that this
thing's punches are flaming hot!
Better watch out! Not even Sea Kings
can withstand a beating from this!
Mirror Racket!
We're just getting started!
Slowpoke Ball Demon Coach! A two-sided
attack with bouncing beams and punches!
Oh! So that's why the beams
didn't work on that Fishman!
Man, this is irritating!
If I can just get close to him...!
Keep running! You'll end up squished
between the gorilla and the mirror!
That's it!
I never thought of that!
What?!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Got him!
Slow-Slow Beam! Beam! Beam!
Fool!
Gorilla Punch Golden Hits!
Round #3 of this second Davy Back Fight--
the combat round-- is underway!
What's happening now is
anyone's guess, but there's no doubt
a truly epic battle is
taking place inside the ship!
Boss! Boss! Boss!...
Despite not being able to see him,
the crowd cheers for our boss!
He ain't gonna lose!
Of course not! He's Luffy! And he has a 'fro!
Being Luffy is more than enough.
That damn fox...
What's so special about an afro?
Does it power you up or something?!
This is taking longer than usual...
Well, the guy is made of rubber.
He's made of rubber and has a 'fro!
Seriously, what's that
have to do with anything?!
Luffy will win us back...!
Yes. He does have that afro and all.
Not you too, Robin...!
Oh, my! There's activity on the deck!
Who has the upper hand?!
Or could the fight be over now?!
I see two figures!
Our boss is the one still standing!
Boss!
Meanwhile, Straw Hat is charred black!
He seems to have taken some
seriously heavy punches!
Luffy!
That's impossible...
How could some simple punches
burn him?! What did he do?!
Luffy!
Look!
Straw Hat Luffy is up!
Just when it seemed he was down
for the count, he got back up!
Looks like you barely
pulled through, Straw Hat...
It's the brotherly soul! Afro power!
Kick his butt, Boss!
Take this!
This is the Slow-Slow Beam Sword!
I've restrained your arms and legs!
But feel free to move anything else!
Not that you can, though.
Megaton Nine-Tails Rush!
Rush! Rush!
Rush!
30 seconds.
He's down for sure this time-- No, wait!
Luffy!
Straw Hat Luffy is up!
Whoa! Who is this guy?!
It's gotta be the 'fro! Is it the afro's wildness?!
Stubborn little...!
Take this! Slow-Slow Beam!
Megaton Nine-Tails Rush!
Dammit, that's not fair!
That beam's against the rules!
Usopp!
Whoa! This looks like the end...!
Dealing the punches ain't so easy, either!
He's beating him to death out there!
Oh?! Again...?!
A-Again...?!
Luffy...!
I won't...
...let you have...
...a single member of my crew...
...even if it costs me my life!
Luffy...
Straw... Straw Hat Luffy
is on his feet once again!
We're setting off toward the distant orange horizon
Today's winds are blowing
across the morning sea
I can't sleep
The kind of passion I saw this very morning
cannot be stifled by anyone
Hope, frustration
and much more might come our way
but for now
we can just start from scratch
Some time ago, we had a dream
in which we followed our aspirations
so we'll raise our hands high
and embrace the shining sun in our hearts
We're going to make it to that place
He's unsteady and out of breath,
yet he stands with a glimmer in his eye!
Now this is a Davy Back Fight!
I'm so teary-eyed I can't see straight!
--Luffy!
--Luffy! Luffy!
Don't cheer on the enemy!
Boss! Boss!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Epic, Heated Combat!
The Fateful Final Conclusion"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Epic, Heated Combat!
The Fateful Final Conclusion