Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
Finger Pistol!
After all, your ridiculous attacks wouldn't...
I-I got stuck!
This is bad!
Sorry, but die in that stupid state, Straw Hat!
Finger Pistol! Spots!
Go back to normal, body!
Hurry! Hurry! I'm gonna be killed!
The damage I took earlier is affecting my legs!
Oh? I'm going back...!
I'm going back to normal!
See? My attacks...
...did a number on you after all.
We have to do something...! Or we'll all drown!
When we still haven't really
gotten Robin-chan back yet...!
I can't breathe...! Everything's going dark!
Help!
You'll be fine. Get ahold of yourselves!
I'm not gonna let you die!
What?! What's going on?!
My body is being pulled by something!
Oh... Am I dreaming?
I must be...!
Several sailors are drowning in the sea...
As their consciousness fades away,
they see an elegant tail fin...
When they look up, they see
long hair swaying in the sea...
She's so beautiful.
This is the Mermaid legend...
It's like we're seeing a fantasy...
If I'm dreaming... please don't let me...
...wake...
I'm gonna go super express!
Make sure you hold your breath tight!
Du...
--Du...
Du... A dugong?!
Cannon Fire Sinks the Island!
Franky's Lamentation
Sorry, marines! We're gonna
use this ship to escape.
Now, we've finished cleaning out our
escape ship, the former escort ship.
Yes.
All we have to do now is wait
for Straw Hat and the others.
What's that?
Don't...
...die!
Battleships 6, 7, and 8 identified
pirates in front of the main gate.
Okay.
Hey, you guys! Wake up!
Hey!
This can only be described as a miracle.
They must've... They must've
received a tremendous shock.
They all stopped breathing,
so they didn't swallow much water.
Good thing they're all okay... but...
...what on earth could have shocked them
enough to make them stop breathing?
It was you.
Hm?
You must be the friend that
pirate king kid came to rescue.
I saw you at the Shift
Station, right? I remember.
Back then...
...I never thought that you guys
would pull something like this.
Put some clothes on, you damn old hag!
I laughed when I heard him say he
was gonna be Pirate King...
Our friends are waiting!
Don't stand in our way!
...but who knows? It might actually happen.
Is Nami-san okay?
You guys are as tough as ever.
I'm glad you're alive!
Ahhh! So it was real!
Mermaids really don't exist!
So the tales were true about
people seeing a Mermaid
then realizing it was actually a dugong!
You morons! She still hasn't
said she's a Mermaid yet!
Don't give up on the dream yet!
I'm an icefish Mermaid.
Stop it! Don't say "icefish"!
But I've never heard of a Mermaid with legs.
I have an objection, too!
Mermaids should be more...
Mermaids should be more like...
A well-proportioned sexy body...
Smooth white skin and flowing hair
that's beaming and beautiful...!
Stop it!
When Mermaids are around 30,
their tail fins fork into two
and they become able to live on land.
They're a mysterious species.
If you go to Fishman Island one day, you'll see.
Hm? Fork into two...? Oh, I see!
They say when a cat lives 100 years, its tail
splits into two and it becomes a monster.
Oh, a goblin cat, huh?!
Don't lump me in with monsters!
Couldn't you at least say
thank you for what I did?!
Thank you very much, Kokoro-san!
No problem.
Robin-chaaan!
Huh? Where am I?
Robin!
I'm so glad we made it in time,
Robin! So you're okay!
Robin!
Yes, all thanks to you guys.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it!
Grandma! That's amazing!
So you were a Mermaid all this time?!
I was thinking you were different,
since you have fins and scales!
You should've noticed, grandkid!
Chopper?!
Are you okay?
Oh...?
I can't move my body.
It's not surprising. We'll tell you
what happened when this is all over.
Zoro!
Zoro! I mean, Zoro-kun!
Hey, look at that.
It's hard to believe that's the island
we were on up until just a bit ago.
What's with this attack?
It's already a sea of flames!
It seems like they've been ordered
not to kill Nico Robin in their attacks.
So that's why this bridge
isn't being targeted right now.
Their trying not to kill her must mean
they still intend to get her back.
After completely destroying Enies Lobby,
they'll probably engage in some
close combat to get her back.
H-Hey, isn't that bad?
We're all physically wrecked,
and on top of that, there are lots of crazy
powerful guys on those battleships, right?
Where's Luffy right now?
I see the dust of combat still coming up
from the top of this bridge's first column.
His opponent is, of course,
that pigeon guy, Rob Lucci.
It's not far from here! If we give him a hand...
Don't bother.
The pigeon guy is no ordinary man.
What's the point if we get dragged
into the fight and get separated again?
To make sure we still have an escape route
regardless of when that group
of battleships turns this way,
we'll wait for Luffy right here.
That's all we need to do.
The storm is just beginning.
Understood.
Your legs are being affected after all.
I see. Looks like your ridiculous way
of fighting isn't just playing around.
But don't underestimate the inner
strength of a Six Powers Master.
In order to master the ultimate techniques,
you need the ultimate inner strength!
So what?!
Tempest Kick! Victory Bird!
Franky... your guys are...
You damn idiot!
They've got the luck of the devil!
They're fine. I'm sure they've escaped okay!
Dammit!
Prepare to fire cannons.
Hm? That's...
Hey, Paulie! Come back!
You're picking up a transponder snail?!
What're you gonna do with that?!
We can find out how the Straw Hats are doing!
Dammit! It's a cannon attack!
Bro!
We can depart anytime!
Once Luffy gets here,
we can set sail right away!
Okay.
But, simply put, there are about as
many battleships as there are of us.
Even if we could set sail, it's virtually
impossible to get through here.
This is a report from the
front gate in the northwest.
We've completed retrieval of
Enies Lobby's marines and officials.
Also, at the front gate,
we identified about fifty pirates,
including the Giants, escaping the main island.
Those guys...!
That's Zambai and the others!
See, I told you! They escaped the island okay!
I wasn't worried about them at all!
Really, they wouldn't die
even if you killed them!
The other day, too...
We have finished eliminating them
with a barrage of cannon fire.
All are dead.
Under the circumstances, no one could
possibly survive on the main island.
Hence, the number of survivors on
Enies Lobby's main island is zero!
This is a report from Battleship 2.
The courthouse and the Tower of Law
in the southeast of the island...
...as well as the underground passage
connected to the bridge...
...have all been destroyed.
The only target left to attack
is the Bridge of Hesitation.
Franky...
Those guys have been...
All right, you guys go straight to
the courthouse and join Straw Hat.
We're gonna split into two
and bring the drawbridge down.
Galley-La's shipwrights, too...
When you see... those guys, tell them...
"You guys're fired."
Oimo... Kashii...!
How...
...dare you...
...deceive us?!
I guess Yokozuna was with them, too.
Do you wanna come along?
Ribbit... Ribbit!
Sodom and Gomorrah, too...! They all...
He says, "I'll be faithful to
Big Bro Franky for the rest of my life!"
His pectoral muscle got hurt by a trench mortar!
Move over now before he falls!
No one's gonna be saved
unless you guys move forward!
Is it really okay...
...for people to die so easily like this?
You can't see people on the map.
They just erase a small island from the
world map, without a shred of emotion.
That's what Buster Call is.
Bro! We came to rescue you!
Bro! Let's go back together!
Hurry up! Straw Hat!
Your friends are waiting for you here!
Don't you dare die on us!
Franky...
This will be the last time!
Until I bring you down, I won't stop it.
Are you gonna try to use up
all your power and die?
I don't know what's gonna happen.
Gear... 2!
Two hundred Captains
from Navy Headquarters?!
Just how many strong guys
do they have to send in?!
That proves just how scared they are of us.
Listen up! Hold strong until Luffy comes!
We'll all make it through this
and leave this place!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Wait for Luffy!
Mortal Combat on the Bridge of Hesitation!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Wait for Luffy!
Mortal Combat on the Bridge of Hesitation!