Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
rashinban nante jyuutai no moto
compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
delirious with fever, i take the helm
hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
if the dusty treasure map has been verified,
tashikameta no nara densetsu janai
it's not a legend!
kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
when it comes to personal storms,
biorizumu nokkatte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
omoi sugoseba ii
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
poketto no koin
a coin in my pocket,
soreto You Wanna Be My Friend
and do you wanna be my friend?
We Are
we are!
Terrible news, everyone!
Pirates are attacking!
Pirates! Pirates!
Run for your lives!
Pirates! Run for your lives!
Liar of Justice?
Captain Usopp
It'd be reckless to go straight
into the Grand Line now!
Yeah, some meat would be nice to have first.
Eating nothing but fruit everyday is no good...
Need some booze, too!
What're you talking about?!
That's not what I mean!
The Grand Line is the most
dangerous place in the world!
On top of that, it's crawling with
strong pirates after the One Piece!
And they're all on powerful ships, of course!
We need more people, too.
The number of crew members,
the lack of equipment on this ship...
There's no way we could survive like this!
Yeah, we need a cook. And a musician.
A musician?!
You're so stupid...
A little to the south of here is
an island with people living on it.
It'd be best if we can get
ahold of a real ship there...
Alright! Time to eat some meat!
Don't forget the booze!
You guys!
Pirates are here!
Pirates!
Everyone run away!
Pirates are here!
Pirates!
Terrible news!
Pi... rates...
The pirates...
...are just a lie!
Oww...
You exaggeration-spewing kid!
I'm gonna get you today for sure!
Stay right where you are!
I'll show you a thing or two!
Here they come!
Here they come! Here they come!
Get back here, you damn kid!
Just try and catch me!
Come and get me!
Dammit! He got away again!
He's one hell of a troublemaker!
He's in trouble if I find him!
Where the hell'd he go?!
Another job well done today!
I sent the wind of excitement
into this boring village!
There he is!
Oh, it's you guys!
Good morning, Captain Usopp!
The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
Pepper! Carrot!
Is it just you two? Where's Onion?
Terrible news! Terrible news!
Oww!
Terrible news!
Onion...
What's he freaking out about?
Terrible news! Terrible news!
Terrible news! Pirates are here!
There's a boat with a skull
mark at the north shore!
Yeah, right!
It's the truth!
T-The truth?
It's true! This is bad!
Oops! It's time for my snack!
Don't run away!
Actually, I have "I'll Die if
I Don't Eat My Snacks-iosis"!
Liar!
Don't you want to be a real pirate, Captain?!
What good is a pirate who's afraid of pirates?!
If I recall correctly,
it was Buggy the Clown's mark!
B-B-Buggy the Clown?!
I think I'll just...
But it was two small boats!
And three people or so...
Alright! Let's go, Usopp Pirates!
To protect this village's peace!
Alright, let's go! Follow me!
R-Right!
Finally on dry land again...
There's a village past here?!
Yeah. It looks like it's a small one, though...
Oh! In that case, meat, meat!
Meat, meat, meat!
There's a place to eat in this village, right?!
Forget about meat for a minute, will you?!
Huh?!
Careful!
I sense people!
Where?! Where?! Where?!
Look out!
So cool!
Is this the time to be impressed?!
I am Usopp, leader of the great
pirates who reign over this village!
People praise me-
and then praise me more-
as "Captain Usopp"!
Huh?
If you're thinking of attacking
this village, then forget it!
My 80 million subordinates won't sit by quietly!
Awesome!
You're lying, aren't you?
Yikes! She saw through it!
See, you admitted it.
I admitted it to her!
What?! He was lying?!
Curse you, you crafty tactician!
80 million may have been an exaggeration,
but I do have great men under my command!
Like maybe three people?
She saw through it!
R-Run!
H-Hey, you guys! Don't run away!
I've never heard of pirates
using slingshots before!
You're neat!
Hey, you! Don't insult me!
I'm a very proud man!
Because of my great pride, people call me...
"Proud Usopp"!
You saw it yourself just now!
My slingshot skills are far
greater than your average pistol!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
Huh?!
I'm saying those aren't for threatening people.
What you're looking at now are real pirates!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
Huh?!
I'm saying those aren't for threatening people.
R-Real pirates definitely have way
more punch behind their words...
Awesome...
We stole those lines!
Eh?
From Shanks, a pirate I respect!
S-Shanks?!
You know Red-Haired Shanks,
the great pirate?!
Yeah.
Your dad's Yasopp, right?
Eh?
Yeah, Yasopp is my old man...
But how do you know that?
"Food"
Good, huh?!
I met him when I was a kid!
So my old man's on Shanks' ship?
Yep! You guys look the same,
so when I first saw you, I wondered...
Really?!
My old man's on such an awesome ship?!
I dunno about now,
but I bet he's still with him.
After all, your dad was a good sharpshooter!
Awesome!
That's nothing. I could even shoot
an ant right between the eyes!
Y'know, Luffy,
I got a kid named Usopp,
just about your age!
You've already told me lots of times!
I'm sick of it!
What?!
Well, I'm gonna keep on
tellin' you more about him!
It was sad to say goodbye,
but there was no other choice!
There was but one reason:
the pirate flag was calling me!
Stuck! Stuck!
Usopp. I heard enough about
you to make my ears sore.
Yasopp was a great pirate!
Yeah, huh?!
I'm proud of my old man, who leapt
onto these possibly endless seas...
...to live with his life on the line!
Then that makes this easier!
Do you have any friends in this
village who know how to sail...
...and anyone who can supply a big ship?!
As you can see, it's just a tiny village...
Sorry, but we can't live up to your hopes.
On the top of the hill...
There was a huge mansion.
Say! Do you know them, Usopp?!
Think you could ask them to help pay for one?
You can't go there!
I-I just remembered something I hafta do!
I have lots of influence here!
Eat and drink as much as you want!
Alright! Later!
Why was he in such a rush?
You wish to see Usopp?
Not this again...
May I? I want to talk to him.
That will not do.
That man is the village's biggest exaggerator!
For someone in your weakened state,
Usopp's exaggerations would be too much to handle!
But...
Your late parents firmly
instructed me to protect you...
...to the fullest of my abilities, Miss Kaya.
Now then, I'll leave your medicine here.
Please be sure to take it.
Cheapskate.
"Cheapskate" will do just fine.
What's bad is bad.
Pardon the intrusion-
Usopp-san!
Heya! You seem as down as ever!
I'm sorry!
I'd really like to invite you in as a real guest...
...but Klahadore refuses to allow it...
He's not a bad person, though.
Don't sweat it!
After all, I am a brave warrior of the sea!
I'd only feel cramped inside a house!
So what adventure are you
going to tell me today?
Hmm, let's see...
Alright!
The story of when I fought the
giant goldfish at the South Pole...
...when I was five!
Goldfish?
Yeah! What first shocked me...
...was the immense size of its poop!
It was so big that I landed on it,
thinking it was solid ground!
Is this really the place?!
Yeah, the pirates dragged him inside!
We gotta save him!
But they're real pirates!
They might've grilled and eaten him!
You idiot!
It's old hags who eat people!
Alright! Get ready, you guys!
This will be the most epic battle
since the Usopp Pirates' formation!
Yeah!
The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
What're they?
The captain is gone!
You don't think he...
H-Hey, pirates!
What'd you do with our Captain Usopp?!
– What'd you do with him?!
That meat was yummy!
Meat?!
Don't tell me the captain...
W-What?! What did you do?!
If you're lookin' for your captain...
...we ate him.
Old hag!
What're you looking at me for?!
You just had to say something stupid!
Whew, it was just a joke?
Huge!
If our captain ran off at this hour, he'd be here.
Oh? What's he come here for?
To lie!
That's a bad thing!
He's not bad! He's great! Right?!
Yeah! He's great!
How does that work?
– Kaya, the girl who lives here,
is weak, and she's had depression...
– There was a ship stopped near the goldfish,
– and on it was a pirate bigger than even a mountain!
– ...ever since her parents died
from an illness a year ago.
– His face was hilarious!
– Even though she has lots of money, she's so sad.
So our captain tells his special
made-up stories to make her laugh!
'Cause our captain's the best at telling lies!
Never heard of a pirate with
a face like that, have you?
Oh, so he's great!
Yeah!
I like the captain's meddling side!
I like his bossy side!
I like his exaggerating side!
So that's helped her feel a little better?
Yeah, a lot better!
Great! Let's ask her for a ship after all!
It's thanks to Usopp that she's gotten better.
Just getting in is impossible!
There are way strong guards at the gate!
– Huh?
– Where'd Luffy go?
I'll go ask!
Wait, you're not gonna...?!
Gum-Gum...
H-His arms stretched!
He's a monster!
...Pardon...
– Hey!
– Wait, Luffy!
...the Intrusion!
...And so we escaped into the sky
atop a gigantic slingshot ball!
Huh?
Yahoo!
That worked great!
Did not!
A-Are you all right?!
Yeah! It's okay, it's okay!
They're new recruits who heard
all about me and came from afar...
...to join the Usopp Pirates!
No, not me!
I'm here to ask a favor!
A favor? Of me?
Yeah!
– We want a big ship...
– You, there!
What are you doing?!
Klahadore...
I don't appreciate you breaking
in here without permission!
Who's he?
Chisana koro ni wa takara no chizu ga
When I was little,
Atama no naka ni ukandeite
I had a vision of a treasure map
Itsudemo sagashita kiseki no basho o
and I always searched for that miraculous place
Shiranai dareka ni makenai you ni
before someone else could beat me to it
Yume sae tsukamenai mama
If the world is going to change
Moshi mo sekai ga kawaru no nara
before I can even attain my dream
Nanimo shiranai koro no watashi ni
then take me to the time when I knew nothing
Tsurete itte omoide ga iro asenai you ni
so that my memories won't fade
Who does that butler think he is,
treating people like thieves?!
Yeah!
We only came inside to get a ship!
That has "thief" written all over it.
That weird guy's way more suspicious!
What's that ring?
Hey, look! That butler is with him!
What's going on?!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Weirdest Guy Ever!
Jango the Hypnotist
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Weirdest Guy Ever!
Jango the Hypnotist