Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can become Pirate King!
Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
BON VOYAGE!  hito kakera no yuuki hirogete
BON VOYAGE!      Let that shred of courage grow
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
saisho wa minna BARABARA ni egaite ita chiheisen
The horizons everyone dreamed of were separate at first
ima nara hitotsu no bouenkyou de nozokeru
but now they can be seen through a single telescope
kimi no KOKORO madowasu unmei no shoppai KONPASU
A bitter compass of destiny is leading your heart astray
saka te ni kajitoru yo
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
BON VOYAGE!
SHIGARAMI mo kako mo sutete
Toss aside your bonds and your past
bokura nara sore demo waraeteru hazu
We can surely smile despite that
yume o kanaeru tame no namida naraba oshikuwanai
Tears shed trying to achieve your dreams aren't for naught
PRECIOUS IN MY LIFE
precious in my life
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Nami?
We've been had...
Our treasure is gone!
The Pirate Ship Disappears!
Fortress Battle, Round #2
What?!
They're getting away! After them!
But Lt. Commander!
These are shallow waters, and we
have to go through the shore reef,
so all this smoke is dangerous!
I'm aware of that! And I don't care!
But...!
What if they make it onto the ocean outside?!
We'll wind up the laughingstock
and shame of the entire Navy!
We... the Navarone Fortress... will?!
That's right!
Those damn Navy bigwigs'll start arguing again
about destroying some useless hedgehog of a fortress
that can't even capture a
single bug that snuck inside!
You! As a marine of the Navarone Fortress,
can you tolerate that?!
No, sir!
Attention, all warships!
Full speed ahead! Pass through the Sea Gate!
It's the outside ocean!
We can get out if we go straight ahead!
No, we can't leave!
Eh?
Take the ship back! Turn it around! Hurry!
We're going back into the fortress!
The Navy stole all our gold!
Say what?!
A-Are you insane, Nami?!
We almost died trying to get this far!
I'm very sane!
Even if we do make it out,
there's no point without the gold!
When money is involved,
she can be strangely persuasive...
I love that side of Nami-san, too!
But we made that huge hole!
Why can't we just leave now?!
Aren't we pirates, Luffy?!
Yeah.
Don't you think pirates leaving gold behind is shameful?!
Oh, right!
Good! Then it's decided!
Right rudder, full! Make a U-turn
and take us back into the fortress!
Right! Got it!
Yes! As you wish, Nami-san!
Right rudder, full!
U-turn!
Hold on, you guys!
What're you doing?!
Don't be reckless!
That's it, that's it! Keep it up!
Sound the alarm bell! Louder!
Can't see a thing in this smoke!
Be sure not to hit any fellow ships!
Something happen?
Quiet, Luffy!
Wind chimes?
These are alarm bells for signaling
your location to other ships in fog!
Oh, no! One's coming straight at us!
How's that? Is that good enough, Nami-san?!
No! Left rudder, full!
Eh?!
We have to change course or we'll crash!
Whatever you want, Nami-san!
We're gonna crash!
We almost wound up in pieces
without ever seeing the gold again...
How are things up ahead?
Not again...
There are lots more wind chimes than before!
There's one... two... no, even more warships coming from the smoke!
What?!
Nami-san! What'll it be?
Left or right rudder?
More left!
We gotta get out of this smoke!
What the heck's going on?!
Just do what she says!
She's the best navigator in the world!
We're gonna crash for sure this time!
Please, God...!
We made it...
Keep going straight now!
We have to get out of this dangerous
smoke as quickly as possible!
They're gonna spot us, you know!
Yeah!
We'll be sitting ducks once we leave the smoke!
We'll get blasted and wind up at the bottom of the ocean!
We'll just have to play it by ear!
Navigator...
Eh?
I did some research in the reference room...
this fortress actually used to house many more people and warships.
Hey now, Robin!
This is no time for old stories!
It was military downsizing.
They've really fallen into decline since.
So it seems there are many unused docks in this port.
Unused docks...
I see! That's some nice info, Robin!
Guys! We're gonna hide the
Going Merry in an old dock!
Eh?! And where exactly is that?!
Just follow my orders!
W-What?!
Call the cannoneers at the waterway!
Ask if the Straw Hat ship passed through!
Y-Yes, sir!
Attention, cannoneers!
This is Drake's flagship!
Have you seen the Straw Hats' ship?!
What?!
Apparently, no other ships have
passed through the Sea Gate yet!
What?!
Where did you disappear to, pirates?!
Don't tell me you managed to
sneak past the cannoneers
and vanish beyond the horizon in that short period of time?!
I'm very sorry!
We lost sight of the pirate ship
once it entered the outer waters!
It's almost as if they magically turned invisible!
Just as I thought.
Sir?!
No, good work. Come on back for now.
We can talk leisurely about our forthcoming plan.
They won't try to escape.
Not with their dreams still in this fortress...
Unhand me!
Do you wanna be court-martialed for insulting a superior officer?!
Hear that? He's gonna court-martial us!
Go ahead! Be our guest!
You two! Let that man go!
I'm so sorry, Major!
I told you so!
I am Major Shepherd, special inspector for Navy Command!
I'd say the Straw Hats are right around here...
I'd like to use them a little more.
I guess I'll wait for them to come out on their own.
Those Straw Hat pirates
have us working like crazy...
Time for some good, energizing grub,
then it's back to searching.
What is this?!
This isn't like this morning's food!
Yeah! I'd never had anything like it before!
Hey! Don't be skimpin'!
Give us some grub like this morning's!
Give us good food! Give us good food!
Jessica-san!
The soldiers are complaining about their meals!
Give us good food! Give us good food!
Please, let us use those recipes!
Where has your pride as
cooks of Navarone gone?!
Jessica-san!
It's true that he was a pirate,
but he was still an excellent cook
who made food for the famished
soldiers who came here to eat!
Yeah! All these men want to be revitalized by eating his food!
Please make a decision! Please!
Please, Jessica-san!
Please!
We will make our own cooking
that's every bit as delicious and replenishing as his!
But for today, we'll abandon our
cheap pride and borrow his recipes!
It's true that he wasn't a pirate
in the kitchen... he was a cook.
What's most important of all is
satisfying the people eating!
Jessica-san!
What're you standing around for?!
Those men are waiting!
Right!
What do we do now, Nami?!
It's not too late yet.
We should go back to the
gate and get onto the ocean.
Yeah! These guys mean business!
It's a shame about the gold,
but our lives are more important!
What do you think, Luffy?
We need the gold!
But I'm hungry! Sanji! Food!
I'll look for some food and make you somethin'.
The storeroom is empty.
There's gotta be something left somewhere.
Do you really think it's okay to
escape without getting the gold?!
Yes! Yes!
Well, that's a pity.
Pirate treasure is always divided up!
And given all that gold, we'd each have gotten so much money!
Divided up?!
Naturally.
I've been waiting for this!
I'm gonna buy me a bronze statue!
Yeah! Can we buy books?!
I want the latest medical books!
I want to study all sorts of medical techniques I don't know about!
New pots and frying pans,
plus silverware and giant mousetraps...
That leaves a crapload left over!
I could drink all I want!
Right?!
Yeah! Yeah!
First, my stash will be 80%!
Hold on a second!
Just kidding.
Obviously!
You can't just openly have a secret stash!
By "stash," I mean money
saved up to repair the ship!
The ship? You mean Merry?
That's right. The Going Merry is what
brought us where we are now.
Come to think of it,
it has given us a ride on the seas
ever since my East Blue village...
It's a slightly older model,
but I personally designed it!
A carvel-make caravel, with lateen
sails and a central stern rudder...
The Going Merry!
Get on already.
Eh?!
We're friends now, aren't we?
I...
I get to be captain, right?!
Don't be dumb! I'm the captain!
We've made so many memories with this ship...
I'm thinking of leaving this island!
I'm... going now.
I'll be back someday!
And it was with us when we crossed Reverse Mountain
and burst onto the Grand Line...
This can't be real!
The ocean really is flowing up it!
We made it!
We're going into the clouds!
I see it! This is the greatest sea in the world!
The Grand Line!
The One Piece is up ahead, somewhere!
Go!
And then the sky islands...
Who's this ship's navigator?!
You are, Nami-san!
All right, men! Do what Nami-san says!
Right!
We're flying!
Awesome! The ship is flying!
Nami-san! You're wonderful!
And I like you!
And I even risked my life to protect it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Please don't harm the ship!
Dammit!
And then someone fixed the ship for us...
I really saw it!
When you think about it,
this ship's been through a lot!
It's done so much for us, but now it's all beat up.
Good idea! The Going Merry's Great Repair!
I'm all for it!
Okay, then.
Since we don't know how much it'll cost,
we'll hold off on dividing up the
treasure when we get it back.
They took most of the food,
but not the stuff in the fridge.
Dig in.
Yeah. Usopp's cheap repairs are just about at their limit.
I'll have you know that I'm a sniper!
But yeah, Mechao-san said the same thing...
that it needs real repairs.
Yeah.
We should go to a real shipbuilding dock
and have real shipwrights fix it for us.
There are people better than you at fixing ships, Usopp?
Sometimes you gotta take extra good care,
or you'll wind up paying for it later!
All right, it's decided!
Let's get a shipwright in our crew!
Our journey is far from over!
Yes!
We need those skills anyway...
Yes, yes!
And Merry is our home! Our life!
Let's find a shipwright who can keep it safe!
There he goes again...
Yeah, on rare occasion,
he gets straight to the point.
That's the best way! Let's do it!
Okay, then that's the plan!
I hope we find someone good!
And we need a musician, too!
No, just forget about that.
It's nice to be all excited, but have you forgotten what comes first?
What's that?
We have to get our gold back!
Oh, right.
Question is, where's it hidden?
In a vault, most likely.
We know that!
The problem is, we don't know where it is!
You don't hafta yell at me!
Wouldn't it be here?
It's only a guess, but if I were to hide gold in this fortress,
this multi-lock storage vault
seems like the only place to do it.
Eh?!
You're so smart, Robin-chan!
Yeah, that does seem the most likely!
All right, guys!
Let's go there and get our gold back!
But are we just gonna leave the
Going Merry here? It'll get spotted!
"Hide a tree in a forest! Hide a ship in ships!"
What, that's it?
You shouldn't try to get too serious that often.
These are the remains of a dock
where ships were built and repaired.
When we came in just now,
I saw plenty of abandoned materials.
Aha! I have a great idea!
Whisper, whisper, whisper!
All right?! Help me out, guys!
Yeah!
Whadya think?!
At least now we don't have to
worry about it being stolen again!
Gluing paper all over the
Going Merry was a great idea.
But I dunno how long it'll fool people,
given how crappily it's been done...
Yep! This is definitely a Navy warship,
no doubt about it!
Yeah!
You serious?!
All right, then! Now to get our gold back!
Everyone! We commence tonight at midnight!
Got that?!
Yeah!
But why don't we go now?
'Cause the mood'll be better at night, obviously!
Oh! Mood! I see!
No, I don't think that's quite why.
Mirai ni mukatte, saki o isoge! Ima sugu ni
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Yume to iu mono oikakete ikou
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
Afure dashi teru subete no kotae ga kokoni
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Hashire, hashire, hiraka reta michi wo
Rush forth, rush forth, on the road opened before us
Tomaru koto naku susumou, bokura wa dekiru
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
Makenai, makenai, ookina kabe demo
We won't give in, we won't give in, even if the obstacle is big
Kowagaru koto nante nai sa, norikoerareru
It's nothing to be scared of, we can overcome it
Now we don't have to worry about Merry,
but hold on, you guys!
Are you just gonna go like this?!
Geez! Seven people running
around will stand out too much!
Here! I'll give you my super secret plan!
On the next One Piece!
I do this part!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Gold and Waver Recovery Operations!
I'm gonna be a brave warrior of the sea!
The Gold and
Waver Recovery Operations!
You too?!