Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue his brother, Ace, who will be executed!
He and the Whitebeards finally got over
the barricades to make it to the scaffold!
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught, Luffy runs toward Ace with the Whitebeards' assistance!
Finally... finally...
I made it!
Luffy!
You're so...!
Fire! Blow them away!
There's a tunnel of fire in the smoke!
You never change!
Luffy!
You never do as I tell you...
...and always get yourself in big trouble!
Ace!!
Ace Rescued!
Whitebeard's Final Order!
F-Fire Fist Ace is...
...now free!
Great! You did it, Straw Hat!
He rescued Ace!
He has been relentless
since Impel Down! That guy is really...
...Something else!
I'm relieved!
You finally accomplished your mission, Luffy!
If we can escape here in one piece...
we'll be married!
Look, Koby! Damn Straw Hat finally did it!
Luffy-san, you're awesome!
Don't lose your cool! Be ready to fire!
Shoot them as they land!
Yes, sir!
Stay alert, Luffy! Let's split up for now!
Okay!
Oh no!
Flame Commandment!
Fire Pillar!
He's so strong! Be careful!
Can you fight, Luffy?
Of course!
Ace-san! Luffy-kun!
Don't forget! Fire Fist Ace is made of fire—he's a Logia type!
I never thought that I'd be saved by you one day!
Thanks, Luffy!
Whitebeard and the others helped me do it!
Don't think that you're safe now!
This is now your execution ground!
Now is the chance!
I'll cut you into pieces!
He's my brother! Leave him alone!
Fire Fist!
Gear 2!
Shave!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
Fire Gun!
Die!
Let's hurry, Luffy! We gotta get out of this place!
Alright!
They make a perfect pair!
Make room for them to run!
Don't let them get away at any cost!
Firefly!
Fiery Doll!
Execute Fire Fist and Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
You got stronger, Luffy!
I'll become stronger than you someday!
Then, let me protect you for now!
"Someday?" There's no tomorrow for you.
You think that you can escape?
Admiral Kuzan!
That bastard!
Ice Block!
Back up, Luffy.
Pheasant Beak!
Flame Mirror!
Blue Pheasant-san's ice was instantly vaporized!
He's our 2nd division commander! Of course, he's capable of that!
Cool!
What brothers!
Stop being impressed, you boneheads!
Fix the Transponder Snail already!
Y-Yes, sir!
And now, I wonder how far he can run... The important part begins here, Straw Hat!
At any rate, if I can finish off Whitebeard who's already dying in this confusion...
...then I'll join the Four Emperors!
Wow! He's relaxing during a situation like this!
That's our Captain Buggy!
Mr. 2...
Somehow, I managed to grant your wish.
And now, I gotta hurry and escape...
To whom does this traitor owe allegiance?!
No, he's a prisoner impersonating a guard!
Oh no!
Fleet Admiral-dono!
I can't believe this blunder! Even I couldn't stop it!
Let them go! That way,
things will be more interesting!
Cut the crap!
Even an admiral's power is useless against them!
How can we fight them?!
Don't lose your head!
Admiral Sakazuki!
We won't let them get away from here!
Don't be afraid! Let's beat them!
W-What now?!
Heads up, everyone! Their ship is moving!
Don't get close!
It's running on the ground with its paddles!
Hey, who is on board?!
Squard!
The Whirl Spider Pirates!
Pops, everyone, run!
Leave the war to us!
Those fools!
Don't be silly, Squard!
You don't wanna die, do you?
Of course I do.
What I did to Pops was horrible.
Even if this doesn't make amends for it,
I can't let things go like this!
I'm sorry, guys.
I shouldn't have dragged you into this.
It's okay, Captain! Don't worry!
We followed you because we wanted to!
We'll choose where to die on our own!
Captain! We'll follow you to the end!
I'm sorry...
Everybody, take Ace and run!
St. Elmo's Fire!
Squard!
Fool!
Damn Squard! That's not the smart way to do it!
Hey! Hurry up and uncuff me!
You guys! Are you all ready?!
Advance!
Pops!
What happened?!
The ship has stopped!
Pops!
W-With just one hand...
He stopped the ship!
Can't you understand
how ungrateful it is for a child...
...to die before his parent, Squard?!
Don't get too confident!
That little stab wound that you created doesn't really jeopardize my life!
Everybody has his own duration of life!
We accomplished our goal here!
There's no need to stay here anymore!
Old chap!
Pops!
Listen carefully, Whitebeard Pirates!
I'm gonna give you an order from the Captain one last time!
What do you mean "last?!"
Wait, Pops, don't say something so ominous!
I don't wanna hear something like that!
Let's go back to the New World together!
Cross Fire!
Pops!
You and I will split up from here!
Everyone, survive at any cost
and get back to the New World safely!
P-Pops! Are you planning to die here?!
I'm a remnant from the old times!
There is no ship that can carry me in this new era!
Go, you guys!!
Whitebeard!
No, Pops!
It's an order! We gotta go!
Old man!
Pops!
Don't look back!
Because the era is changing!
Everything started on that sea...
This is unbelievable!
Hey, why do you look so dispirited?
Join us! There's more than enough treasure!
Never mind him.
Huh? What do you mean?
We got all this treasure thanks to him...
Just leave him! He's not interested in treasure.
That's odd! What kind of a pirate is he?
What is it you want?
Hey, Newgate!
I've been traveling a very long time.
Let's get this over with!
Navy!
Following Whitebeard's last order,
the pirates swallow their sadness and retreat.
But Red Hound's cruel words directed at Whitebeard
stop Ace in his tracks.
Ace shakes off his friends' protests
and leaps forward—to be met by Red Hound's fist!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Power That Can Burn Even Fire
Red Hound's Ruthless Pursuit"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Power That Can Burn Even Fire
Red Hound's Ruthless Pursuit