Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
--Sogeking!
--There's no time to lose!
Jump down from there!
Hm?
Usopp!
Hey... He couldn't have... right?
Hey! Usopp!
Ahhh!!
You called?!
Hey, you're alive!
Hey! Don't you guys have
the kindness to catch a hero
making a desperate jump
off of the rooftop?! Morons!
There's an escort ship on the
other side of the bridge, huh?
Don't you think that is the key to our escape?
Looks like stealing that ship
is our only chance of surviving.
Franky...
...Convert!
Franky Centaur!
Hold it, you bastards!
Although your physical ability
indeed spikes, exceeding its limits,
your physical strength itself just can't
keep up with that intensification.
That's not really smart.
You're shortening your life, you know that?
It's better than losing all sorts
of things right before my eyes!
I'll do whatever I can do!
You're too ambitious!
Tempest Kick!
That naive idea of yours that you
can save everyone and escape...
Let's see how far it gets you.
What're you doing, you jerk?!
Ahh!
Behind the fog...
...we can see the outline of the ships!
H-Hey, don't run away! Wait!
Oh, no...
This serves you right!
They're here! They're finally here!
A fleet of battleships!
The Buster Call has begun!
I Can't Protect Anyone Unless I Win!
Gear 3 Activated
I repeat. Our targets are Straw Hat Luffy
and his gang of about sixty pirates!
Completely destroy Enies Lobby!
Ah... H-Hey!
Hey, look at that, you guys! Don't run!
See? The battleships are ignoring
the bridge--they aren't attacking us!
That's because I'm here!
That's right. My old man said it, too.
Even the indiscriminate cannon fire avoided him!
However, the bridge the criminal
Nico Robin is on is an exception for now.
Hey! Look at this! This bridge is safe!
That's because I'm the Chief of CP9!
What a crazy sight...
Hm? Hey, are you...
I can't stop trembling.
I'm exercising a Buster Call.
Commence concerted fire!
We're targeting everything on Ohara,
the island of archaeology.
Annihilate the devils living in Ohara!
In the name of justice!
Buster Call...
Merciless, indiscriminate cannon fire...
It destroys anything and everything.
It's hellfire.
That tragedy is... That grisly event is...
...happening again...
Let's hurry, you guys! Be quick!
Stop bossing us around, you jerk!
If I may say one more thing,
this is affecting my wounds.
Could you carry me a little more softly?
Don't ask too much! Besides,
you're contradicting yourself.
As the price I paid for my great work,
it's no exaggeration to say that
I have wounds all over my body!
Ahh! All my ribs got broken! All six of them!
There are more than that, so don't worry.
Seriously, you're such a pain!
By the way, would you like to know
the secret of my new weapon, Kabuto?
I shall explain it for you. Kabuto,
the weapon that belongs to Sogeking, is...
--Sparkle!
--Shut up, you jerk! Or we'll make you run!
Please! Spare me! My ribs
got broken! A-All ten of them...
--There are more than that.
--What?
Then 20... 30?
How about 100?!
There are more than that!
No way that's true!
Is that cannon fire?
The Navy sure does put on a big show.
Amazing! Amazing! Cannon fire! Cannon fire!
Hey, they aren't festival fireworks, you know.
Anyway, where's Luffy right now?
You know, pirate lady, that iron
door we came through...
The pirate guy broke it.
Luffy did?
It was amazing... though he became small.
S-Small? Luffy did?!
Yep!
So these are the ones, huh?
Gear 3!
They opened...
All right! I'm heading there now!
What?! How come you're small now?!
Gear 3?
He opened the iron doors and
became small? What the heck?
That must've been fun!
Yep, Grandma! That pirate guy is fun!
She's not making any sense!
Anyway, let's hurry and...
Oh? Grandma, I can hear something down there.
Now that you mention it, yeah.
We don't have time to stop here right now.
No matter what it is,
we just have to keep on going!
Now, let's go resolutely!
Grandma! You're cool!
Th-That's...
Water!
What the heck is going on?!
Why is there water?! What?!
Why?! We have no way out!
Help!
Whether there's someone in the passage or not,
no one can now reach this place.
You bastard!
Soon this room will be submerged in the sea.
Coo coo!
You son of a bitch!
This place is located above the sea.
The seawater won't reach here.
Coo coo!
You can hear the sounds of the
battleships' cannon fire, right?
What happened to your pirate crew...
What happened to Nico Robin...
You must be worried.
If you wanna go rescue them, go right ahead.
I won't take my focus off of you.
No matter what they're going through
right now, they'll survive for sure!
But if I let you get away now,
you'll go kill my friends!
I won't take my focus off of you!
The cannon attack has begun.
By the way, I can hear a
strange sound ahead of here.
Shut your mouth!
Hurry!
Ah... Ow, ow, ow...
Hm?
As I thought, I sense something odd...
I hate to say this, but unlike you two,
I'm delicate and cautious.
And my sense is telling me...
...this sound is probably...
Ah...
Hey!
Wait up!
Whoa!
My ribs got broken again! Wait up, you guys!
I'm severely injured with
broken bones all over my body!
Nooo!
Grandma! What's going on?!
Who cares?! Hurry up and run!
You have a high caliber, befitting a boss.
I'd like for a certain idiot to hear that.
But I wonder... if your abilities are
good enough to back up that decision!
The result will be the same if you die!
Hey! Capture Nico Robin already!
Once this is all over, I'll be able
to become the world's hero!
The Buster Call sounds like a gun salute for me!
Razor!
Finger Pistol!
Tempest Kick! Leopard Tail!
Can you really defeat me?!
I can't protect anyone unless I win!
Gum-Gum...
...Rifle!
Iron Body. Empty Tree.
Razor!
I'll give you credit for having the guts to
pick a fight with the World Government.
But in the end, you're just like any other pirate.
It seems your level is nowhere
near enough to put up a good fight.
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Flying Finger Pistol...
Pick!
Three Picks!
Flying Finger Pistol...
Fire Pick!
I thought I was able to meet a man
with some backbone. How disappointing.
Did you run out of strength from
your doping earlier after all?
If it's backbone you want, I'll show you...
...another tactic!
Gear... 3:
Bone Balloon!
Bone?
The power that moves
from one bone to another...
Take a look! My left arm is...
...the arm of a Giant!
If it's all show, don't even bother!
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
...Gigant Pistol!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Justice would never surrender to evil.
For example, if there's a soldier
who can't protect what he should,
that alone is a crime.
Everything I do is in the name of justice!
In the past... and in the future, too!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Shivering Past!
Dark Justice and Rob Lucci"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Shivering Past!
Dark Justice and Rob Lucci