Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can become Pirate King!
Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
BON VOYAGE!  hito kakera no yuuki hirogete
BON VOYAGE!      Let that shred of courage grow
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
saisho wa minna BARABARA ni egaite ita chiheisen
The horizons everyone dreamed of were separate at first
ima nara hitotsu no bouenkyou de nozokeru
but now they can be seen through a single telescope
kimi no KOKORO madowasu unmei no shoppai KONPASU
A bitter compass of destiny is leading your heart astray
saka te ni kajitoru yo
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
BON VOYAGE!
SHIGARAMI mo kako mo sutete
Toss aside your bonds and your past
bokura nara sore demo waraeteru hazu
We can surely smile despite that
yume o kanaeru tame no namida naraba oshikuwanai
Tears shed trying to achieve your dreams aren't for naught
PRECIOUS IN MY LIFE
precious in my life
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
Whadya think, old fortress guy?!
I rescued my crew!
♪ We are the Navarone Marines! ♪
♪ We'll show you our fiery spirit! ♪
The special capture operation at Dock 88 is ready!
We can now capture the Straw Hats!
Don't let your guard down.
What do we do, Nami? Do we go there?
Yeah!
Let's rely on Dr. Kobato to lead the way!
Breaking Through the Siege!
The Going Merry Is Recovered
Is this really the right way, Usopp?!
Don't worry! This is definitely it! Keep moving!
Y-Yeah!
Merry's dock was just around the corner there!
But this seems too easy. I don't like it...
All right! Let's steal our ship back!
Now this is somethin'...
So we were being ambushed!
Sniper Team #7, to the front!
Take aim!
Just like that?!
Gum-Gum...
Fire!
...Balloon!
What are you doing?!
Cannon Team #12, to the front!
Bazookas?!
Fire!
Duds?
Damn, what is this?! My eyes!
I can't see! My eyes are all irritated!
Those were flash bombs!
Sword Team, to the front!
Charge!
Bastards!
I'm fine!
Oh, that's some nice equipment there.
You can borrow these!
Thanks.
Dragon Twister!
Blinders don't work on me,
unlike a certain lovesick moron!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
And...
...Whip!
What a cinch!
Huh? Where's Sanji and Zoro?
You took care of 'em!
Oh, sorry.
You dumbass!
Oww...
All right, you dimwitted moron!
What was that you said earlier?!
What the heck are you guys fighting for?!
Fire!
What the...? Crap! I can't get this off!
Luffy!
Stay right where you are!
Your wanted posters say "dead or alive,"
but here at G8, we prefer alive.
But if you resist any further,
I can't guarantee that.
H-Hey, Luffy! Can't you get that net off?!
I can't! It won't come off at all!
Plus I'm suddenly out of strength...
Sea Prism Stone?!
What?!
That's right! That was a Prison Bomb,
meant for use against those with Devil Fruit powers!
What do you think, Straw Hat?!
I knew he'd come...
What're you doing?!
It's dangerous here! Return to your station!
Don't be such a stick in the mud!
Not good!
Dammit! There's still this many left,
even after all the ones we beat?!
Just give yourselves up.
Escape is absolutely impossible!
All hands, take aim!
Got no choice!
Attack!
What is this?!
Huh? Was that...?
I'm on the verge of death...
Usopp!
What terrible injuries! He's badly wounded!
The marines did this?!
Damn them!
No, no, no...
Kobato?!
U-Umm, Lt. Commander?
Who are you?!
What's the big idea?!
We've been taken hostage! Please save us!
We were forced here against our will!
Kobato-san?
This giant is one of the pirates!
Eh?!
W-Wait! When did I do that?!
What is this?!
Who's that other girl?
How should I know?!
Seriously! Huh?! What're you talking about?!
We can't act carelessly with the hostages there!
Damn that coward! This is why I hate pirates!
That giant was the fake doctor, then?
He has to be! He's carrying his crewmate!
That's right! I'm a rough and tough member of the Straw Hats!
Even crying babies shut up around me!
Better do as I say, or these hostages are dead meat!
All right!
Have your men stand down and let us through!
Now I get it.
Interesting.
Hurry up, or I'll snap these girls' necks like twigs!
He'll do it, too!
He's so crazy not even we can stop him!
Are you upholders of justice
gonna let two helpless ladies die?
正義 = Justice
Chopper! That's cowardly! I misjudged you!
You shut up!
He's gonna kill us!
Please, do what he says!
No! No, no!
How many times do I have to say it?!
We have 1,000 mouths to feed!
We have to be efficient to make it in time!
You're too slow!
Oww...
You didn't need to hit us...
What's that? You got a problem?
I'll tell you right now... save your big talk
until after you've proven yourself to me.
Now come here and help prepare!
Doesn't Jessica-san seem a bit wound up?
I guess the fact that that cook was a pirate hit her hard...
Not to mention that the real new guys are losers who're all talk...
That's enough talking there!
Yes! We're sorry!
Here, Billy! Try out my special sauce!
Pretty good, huh?!
Or not...
No, it's good...
But it's our usual flavor, isn't it?
Yes! Exactly!
Ever since I tasted his cooking,
I've felt like we're lacking something.
It's not bad or anything. It's just...
He had flair, I'm sad to say...
Damn it! What did he do differently?!
Jessica-sama.
What?
Could this be of use somehow?
Seems he left some recipe notes before he left...
That pirate did?!
Recipes for his cooking?!
Oh, come to think of it, he...
I'll write down my recipes for you, then.
What about it?
Eh? Oh, I was hoping...
since he did leave it and all...
that we could maybe use it...
Don't be stupid!
Can you really proudly call
yourselves cooks of Navarone
if you accept help from a pirate?!
Who do you think our marines are fighting as we speak?!
Don't you have any sense of pride?!
Umm...
Sorry to interrupt, but...
What the hell is this?!
Can't you even peel potatoes right?!
Our men always did it...
And it was always like this...
Listen! This is a battlefield!
Even a single potato is a vital resource!
Even shreds of potato skins are...
U-Uhh...
You two need to start all over with dishwashing for a while!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
L-Lt. Commander...
I'll pull my men back.
All hands, lower your weapons and withdraw!
Stand down!
All sniper squads, lower your guns!
Lt. Commander...
We have no choice.
Wow, that worked well.
I hope so...
Huh?
I owe you one, Zoro...
H-Hey! Was that Kobato-san's voice just now?!
Y-You think so too?!
Mechao-san! What's going on?!
Kobato's being held hostage.
Eh?! Isn't that bad?!
Nah, don't worry about it.
I can see whether my daughter's
crying for real or not!
But my main worry...
...is them!
As you can see, we've opened the way!
Now release them!
Yes! It worked!
Hey! Chopper!
No!
I'm not letting them go until we can escape!
Damn you!
I've contacted Squadron #17,
as you ordered, sir.
Good. Have them standby for my signal.
I give in to your demands!
Get onto your ship!
He's a good sport.
But is he telling the truth?
Hey, hold on, you!
Nami. Chopper. Love cook.
Huh?!
Run to the ship on my signal.
Luffy, stretch your arms and get
everyone on board. Can you do that?
No problem...
I see...
Lt. Commander...
It doesn't matter.
If anything happens, I'll take responsibility.
If we let them escape now,
all of G8 will be shamed!
Whoops. Silly me.
What the...?! Don't scare us like that!
N-No!
You fool! He's on your side!
Crap! Nami-san!
Get to the ship somehow!
Let's do it, Captain!
I have no choice! All hands! Attack at once!
I knew that dunderhead would do this!
We have no choice!
Go, long-nose!
Hey, guys! We're gettin' on!
Are they alive?
And now for you and me!
What?!
Damn them! Don't let them escape!
All squadrons, open fire!
B-But there's still a hostage!
Warning shots are fine!
We did it, Merry!
Why can't you ever rescue us normally?!
That takes its toll on regular people!
All right, everyone! Get up!
Is that the pirate ship?!
What's the deal?
Why won't they order us to attack?!
I hear they have a hostage.
Some nurse they captured.
Pirates sure are nasty!
Oh, is that her?
Whoa, the hostage is giving orders!
This is one hell of a fiasco!
Are the ships ready yet?!
I'm having them hurry!
Dad!
Oh, Kobato.
You've had quite the unusual day!
You released the ship, didn't you?
You've caused a real mess.
You'll be punished for this, you know!
What father can sit idly by when
his daughter is about to get hurt?!
Kobato-san had been rescued!
The plan was underway!
What about the other one?!
You completely ignored her!
Officers have to learn not to view people too lightly!
You could learn a thing or two from Commander Jonathan!
Lt. Commander! About that hostage!
All sections believe that she's part of the Straw Hat crew!
What?!
Stop right there, Inspector.
Where are you going?
I don't believe I'm required to report my actions.
We are.
I see. Then please tell the commander this.
"I had a lot of fun."
Screw you!
I guess there's no point in disguising myself now.
Why're we going along the edge of this cliff?!
We'd have cannons on both sides if we went through the middle!
This way, we only have to worry about one side!
Where am I?!
Oh, he's awake!
Huh? When did I get on Merry?
After a bunch of this and that.
I see! Nami as a hostage! Nice!
Isn't it, though?!
You are good at tricking people.
But why'd the ship start moving on its own?
Oh, I bet it was the old maintenance guy.
Why's that?
I just get that feeling.
Nami-san dressed as a nurse is really nice!
We managed to get out, but what do
we do without maps or charts?
This is why I wanted to look around the place first, you morons!
Robin-chan!
So cool!
So Major Shepherd was a fake?
I'm sorry, sir. She got away.
You're not at fault.
I just have a bad habit of being weak around pretty women.
Huh?
Anyway, that makes six.
We're currently searching for the last one!
Oh, there's no need for that now.
I just found her.
Sir?
I contacted the medical room.
They said they aren't missing any nurses.
A map of this fortress!
I thought we might need it to escape.
You know the score!
You're the only one who's on my side, Sis!
A-Am I?
They're shooting at us!
I thought we were okay cause we had a hostage!
They were bound to realize the truth eventually!
Warships are coming after us!
There is no hostage!
Everyone on board is a Straw Hat member!
I repeat, all cannons,
commence firing consecutively!
That's this fortress' gateway: the "Sea Gate."
Usopp, prepare the bow cannon!
Chopper! Don't get my orders wrong!
Got it!
If that's the only exit, our only
choice is to break through by force.
But I don't like that there are more shallows than this chart shows.
That's unsuitable for a port, so why is it here?
Something doesn't seem right...
It's all-clear on your end?
That's fine, then. Keep watch.
Reporting, sir. The pirate ship appears
to have reached the Sea Gate.
That makes it checkmate...
But it's a real shame.
You weren't careful enough, Straw Hat-kun.
Say what?! We don't have a single cannonball?!
Nope!
We don't even have a box to hold explosives!
That does seem only natural,
given that the Navy confiscated the ship.
What're we gonna do?!
We can't bust through that gate like this!
Just means we gotta fight our way through.
All we gotta do is gain control of the
device that raises and lowers it.
Don't talk like it's easy!
Don't worry! I have a nice idea!
Target the enemy pirate ship!
Fire!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Yes!
I see! I hadn't thought of that!
Nice, Luffy!
Now let's get...
We have no cannonballs or explosives?
Nami?!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Nami?
We've been had...
The treasure is gone!
Mirai ni mukatte, saki o isoge! Ima sugu ni
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Yume to iu mono oikakete ikou
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
Afure dashi teru subete no kotae ga kokoni
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Hashire, hashire, hiraka reta michi wo
Rush forth, rush forth, on the road opened before us
Tomaru koto naku susumou, bokura wa dekiru
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
Makenai, makenai, ookina kabe demo
We won't give in, we won't give in, even if the obstacle is big
Kowagaru koto nante nai sa, norikoerareru
It's nothing to be scared of, we can overcome it
Where'd you disappear to, you damn pirates?!
Don't tell me you managed to
sneak past the cannoneers
and vanish beyond the
horizon in that short period?!
They won't try to escape.
There's no point without the gold!
Pirates leaving treasure behind is shameful!
Right rudder, full!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Pirate Ship Disappears!
Fortress Battle, Round #2
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Pirate Ship Disappears!
Fortress Battle, Round #2