Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war against the New Fishman Pirates,
who were holding a grudge against humans and looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom.
Luffy finally defeated Hody, the captain of the New Fishman Pirates, in a fierce fight
and thwarted his plot.
2 years ago at a Sky Island,
I read a Poneglyph indicating where one of the ancient weapons is.
The Mermaid Princess who lived around the same time as Joyboy...
...was known by a specific name, wasn't she?
The ancient weapon...
...Poseidon!
"The Straw Hats Stunned! The New Fleet Admiral of the Navy!"
I do not know their purpose
but a long time ago, there were powerful entities that could destroy the world.
They were 3 Ancient Weapons given the names of gods.
Pluton, Uranus, and Poseidon.
And she is one of them.
Indeed.
We can't let anyone know about this.
Every powerful group in the world would want Princess Shirahoshi's power.
The Government--even pirates.
The Ancient Weapons?
They could destroy the world?!
I got all their treasure and I was about to leave
but this is even bigger news!
I see. So that Mermaid Princess is...
Whew, I want seconds!
You already ate it all?!
It's so good--I could eat this forever!
Especially this candy!
It's as good as meat. I want hundreds of them!
I-I'm afraid we are running out of that one.
We can bring other things if you want!
All right!
Let me ask you, Luffy.
What do you know about the state of the world now?
Huh? What are you asking all of a sudden?
Looks like you know nothing. You're out of the loop--that's not good.
Yeah?
Here's the food!
Let's go somewhere else to talk.
Okay. One sec.
I'll take a light snack.
Oh, you guys are here too!
I drank too much! I'm trying to sober up!
I ate too much!
Sanji Mermaid-ed too much.
It's like heaven! The Mermaid Island!
What?! Red Hound and Blue Pheasant had a big fight?!
That's what I thought.
You didn't even know about that, did you?
I didn't hear about anything during my training.
Rayleigh is terrible.
I knew about it! I knew!
Are you serious?!
Right after the war 2 years ago, Fleet Admiral Sengoku resigned.
Sengoku recommended Blue Pheasant
to be his successor since he was very popular among his own men
but a lot of people at the highest level favored Red Hound
and so he became a major contender.
Normally, Blue Pheasant doesn't show his passion
but he hated the idea of Red Hound becoming a Fleet Admiral.
They stood against each other and the first-ever feud between the Admirals...
...erupted into a battle on an island somewhere.
Like the saying "Dead men tell no tales,"
whoever lost had to withdraw his candidacy.
The winner would lead the Navy.
As all the world now knows, their deadly struggle lasted for 10 days.
They were comparable in their strength but it came to an end.
Red Hound won!
Sakazuki is the new Fleet Admiral.
Red Hound!
I got you!
Did Blue Pheasant die?
They were both severely wounded
and though Red Hound is pitiless, he showed mercy
to his former comrade who couldn't even stand.
But Blue Pheasant refused to work for Red Hound
so he left the Navy.
He's not a Navy soldier now, is he?
No, he is not. I wonder where he is and what he is thinking now.
It was a big loss for the Government, too.
Of course. The Admirals were the Navy's greatest powers.
But what the Government did to cover their loss...
...gave the Navy unexpected power.
Listen. You all need to know the two biggest changes...
...which have occurred in the New World.
First, Navy Headquarters led by Sakazuki...
...has become an even more powerful force for justice.
And second,
the Blackbeard Pirates have advanced.
Blackbeard?
We met them in Mock Town.
They destroyed my hometown once.
The new era they're talking about is crap!
The era where pirates have dreams will be over, they say?! Huh?!
What's going on?
People's dreams... have no end!!
Isn't that right?!
So you're...
...Blackbeard?!
Oh yeah, I never gave you my name.
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
He was once a long-time member of the Whitebeard Pirates.
He knows their territory very well
and he conquered it in an instant after the old chap died.
Using the Tremor-Tremor Fruit power that he got from the old chap.
The world already counts him among...
...Red-Haired, Kaido,
and Big Mom,
and considers him as one of the Four Emperors.
So he took Whitebeard's place successfully.
What a dirty rat!
Yes, he is annoying.
Rumor has it that they are on the hunt for Devil Fruit users.
They can somehow acquire a Devil Fruit user's power after killing them.
They keep looking for stronger Devil Fruit powers.
Be careful!
They'll get me!
No one wants your Human-Human Fruit power.
What?!
Especially you, Luffy-kun.
There is a lot of bad blood between you and Blackbeard--Teach.
So take extra care...
Luffy! Are you even listening?!
I thought you were the captain!
You have to know a little bit of information at least!
Don't worry, Jinbe.
We were listening.
I thought captains normally don't listen to other people!
Captains are responsible for their crew's safety, aren't they, Luffy?!
Hey Jinbe, take it easy! I like taking chances anyway!
It must be hard to work for him.
Yeah...
Luffy-chin!
There you are!
You shouldn't be here. You're the life of the banquet.
Camie!
I haven't seen Wimpyhoshi.
Princess-sama said she's tired and she wanted to rest
so she went to her room.
Hey, Zoro!
Sanji!
I think there is a wild animal or something in this palace.
You're right.
I feel it, too.
THE HARD SHELL TOWER
I did not know it's such fun to party with everybody!
Help!
Shhh!
Please stop! Who are you?!
Somebody! Help!
Don't look so resentful, Princess-san!
Don't worry! I'm not gonna hurt you or make you suffer!
I was content with taking the treasure.
It became a pain to sell those Mermaids
but you're an exception!
I just need you to be unconscious for a while!
I just got word from my brother and the others
they've arrived at a port on this island!
Come to the New World with us!
Hey.
Come on! Why don't you laugh?
Nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah, boo!
Hey!
What do you want, Straw Hat? I'm having fun here so go away!
Nyah, nyah!
Nyah, nyah, nyah! Nyah, nyah, nyah... Nya...
What?
Straw Hat?!
Luffy-sama!
I didn't know he was still around.
It was scary!
You're so lucky, Luffy! I should have kicked him!
He was the pirate that we captured in the sea.
I haven't seen him since we entered Fishman Island.
I forgot about him.
That was close! Thank you again!
Don't mention it!
I can't believe the treasure thief was still here.
We usually don't even let a tiny fish into the palace
but the gate was left open in the confusion of the battles.
Look! That tower on the right has been sliced clean through.
I assume the thief did it while we were not here.
No, this guy cut the tower.
When they escaped from the cage, he cut bars, walls... everything!
Why did you have to tell him that, you stupid starfish?!
What?! As they say, lying and stealing are next-door neighbors!
Wait a minute, Minister of the Right-chan!
Chan?
Did you say "treasure thief"?
Yes, he stole all the treasures in the palace.
What?! He did?!
I have a bad feeling!
Aren't they national treasures? You're not gonna go after him?
After seeing my people's lives be saved, treasures mean nothing to me.
No, they're worth something!
What if we get them back?!
You can keep them all.
It would be wonderful if people who saved the country had them-jamon.
Are you sure?!
You fools! Why did you kick him out?!
Why didn't you just punch him and tie him up here!
I love it even when you...
Go find him now!
K-King-sama!
Something wrong with Hody and the others! Their cuffs came off!
What?!
THE PRISON TOWER
Damn humans! Our grudge against you will never go away...
Our time to avenge will come again...
Bring Straw Hat here! I'll kill him!
Am I drunk?
I feel pain in my joints!
I got old on purpose.
I'll get back at the Straw Hats-fosun...
We are the ones who will punish humans.
What is going on here?
Is that Hody and his clan?
Don't think that you can keep me in jail, you stupid royal family!
Th-These bars are nothing...
Captain Hody!
What is going on here?!
I knew it! The Energy Steroid that you guys were taking...
...was the legendary pill that was kept in the Tamate Box!
Tamate Box?
It was national treasure that had been passed down for generations-jamon.
10 years ago, somebody stole the contents of the Tamate Box.
We couldn't find who did it and by the King's decision,
we closed the case before it became a scandal.
Come to think of it, that was when you left the army, Hody.
That's right! I stole it!
You idiots!
The legendary pill had unclear effects.
One explanation says it gives you tremendous power.
Another explanation says it just makes you old.
It is an odd national treasure.
I assumed they guarded the power drug closely
in order to seal off its dangerous effect.
You folk opened the box that should not be opened
and dreamed a foolish dream of gaining some power-jamon.
Shut up, Neptune!
Seems like they no longer get their revenge.
Shut up!
We're chosen avengers!
We will kill all humans...
...and you!!
I feel sorry for them now.
I will consider giving them clemency.
Wait, Neptune!
Fukaboshi, you're a dishonor to our race!
Fishman Island will change.
You killed my mother but I will not hold a grudge against you.
So please. Just shut your mouth!
I don't want the children on the island to hear you.
Minister of the Left!
Mr. Pekoms and Baron Tamago arrived at the Candy Factory!
They were sent by Big Mom. This is not a good time!
Where are our sweets? Grr!
Mama is waiting for them-soir!
We don't have any sweets to pay them for this month.
Hody and the others destroyed the factory
and the undamaged sweets have
been sent to the banquet since everybody wanted the
Straw Hats to have them!
I wonder if we can explain the situation.
She is like a monster who would destroy a whole country for sweets!
One of the Four Emperors...
Big Mom!
Luffy and the others are caught up trying to reclaim the treasure of Fishman Island.
The crew of Big Mom, one of the Four Emperors, shows up.
Just as Fishman Island faces destruction yet again...
...at the hands of one of the overwhelmingly powerful Four Emperors...
...Luffy takes a stand!
Next time, on One Piece:
"She Loves Sweets! Big Mom of the Four Emperors!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!