Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
While Buggy and Mr. 3 ascended to Level 4 in order to break out,
the moribund Luffy was injected with a Healing Hormone by Ivankov,
which will cure him, but rob him of 10 years of life!
Food!
I'm...
...recovered!
Luffy Returns!
Iva-san's Escape Plan Set in Motion!!
Wow! He absorbed all the energy!
What a guy! You must be superhuman!
He has overcome Magellan's poison! I can't believe it!
He recovered after only 20 hours!
This must be a miracle!
Miracle? It's something far greater than that!
You did it! You did it! You did it! You did it!
You did it! You did it!
I'm so glad!
Oh, Bon-chan! I'm so happy you survived!
What?! Are you kidding?! Gimme a break!
You're the one that made me worry....
Bon-chan! Hey!
You alright?! Hey!
What happened to you? Hey!
He's just exhausted! But it's not because of his wounds!
Oh, Iva-chan!
Iva-chan?!
I made it! Thank you for helping both of us!
If you wanna thank someone, you better thank Mr. 2 Bon-boy, not me!
I only nudged you along with my powers.
But him,
he was struggling alongside you for hours and hours and hours here!
He lost his voice and spewed up blood but he didn't stop!
He kept shouting "Hang in there!" "You have to live!" to you!
I think it somehow affected your recovery!
I see.
--What's wrong with him?
--Is he naked?!
Straw-chan, I come to rescue you!
In the name of friendship!
Who the hell is this guy all covered in blood?!
Earlier, I was...
I'm sorry that I ran!
How do you know this guy?
I'm his friend!
Straw-chan! I'm not gonna let you die!
Bon-chan, thank you! I'm really grateful!
Here are your hat and clothes. But you're not ready yet.
You need to rest for several days to be fully recovered.
I don't have time! I've already wasted too much!
Sorry, but can you look after Bon-chan? I'll be back for him later!
--Hey, hey!
--See? You're not completely well yet!
The paper is still pointing down! Ace must be downstairs!
By the way, where am I now?
What's that?
It's a Vivre Card, isn't it?
You're on a floor between Level 5 and 6.
I bet that since you've recovered,
you wanna go to rescue your brother no matter what.
Well, it's your life! You can do whatever you want!
What about you, Iva-chan? Are you gonna break out?
Bon-chan thought he'd help your butt get out of here.
Your butt?!
Can you guide me to Ace on your way out?
What did you just say? Bon-boy came here to save me?
Oh, I didn't know that. That's really sweet of him.
But I don't need to be saved.
It's not time to break out yet!
I know what's going on in the world now.
The world is about to change with the Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates as major players!
But he's not gonna make a move yet!
He's the mastermind of all revolutionaries in the world and my comrade!
The Revolutionary--Dragon!
Oh, you're talking about my dad.
Yes. When your father makes a move with his army,
then I'll reappear and enter the world again!
If I escaped now, I'd just end up on countless wanted lists around the world!
D-D-D-D... Dad?!
Did he say "my dad?!"
What?!
Dragon is...
...your dad?!
D-D-D-Don't be ridiculous!
You're a son of Dragon?! He has a son?!
Oh! I shouldn't have said anything.
I guess it's okay. Grandpa didn't keep it a secret.
Your father's name is...
...Monkey D. Dragon! He's a revolutionary!
I don't really know about him. I've never even seen his face.
What?!
This seems legitimate!
He doesn't seem to be the kind to lie and he's a new star in the world of pirates!
And I've just seen his extraordinary vital force!
He's not a normal man! So it's believable!
Where did you come from?!
I'm from the East Blue!
Dragon.
Whenever you go for some air,
you always face towards the same direction no matter where you are!
Do I? Why would you be so curious about such a thing?
I've never noticed.
Then, it must be a homing instinct like animals have.
Is your home in that direction?
You're thinking about your family in the east,
aren't you?
Don't be so inquisitive about my past, Iva!
I'm sorry.
Oh no! If Straw-boy is a son of Dragon for real, that means...
Inazuma, check to see when they'll take Ace-boy away!
Yes, right away!
There isn't much time!
But the Vivre Card was pointing down which means that he's still here!
I'm gonna go to Level 6 with Straw-boy now!
What? Are you gonna show me the way?!
But, did you just say "Level 6?" Isn't it 5?
It can't be! You're on Level 5.5!
Whatever. Alright, let's go!
I wasn't paying attention! It didn't even occur to me!
If Straw-boy is Dragon's son, so is Ace!
Is this why the Navy captured Ace?!
No, it can't be! There would be no point in it!
They don't wanna fight Whitebeard and Dragon at the same time!
What does the government truly want?!
In any case, it's time to make a move!
Okay, Bon-chan! I'll be back!
Straw-boy!
Don't tell anyone casually about your birth!
Yeah, that's what I thought.
I'm a friend of your dad and one of the commanders of the Revolutionary Army!
That's why I was arrested!
So it's my duty to support you whether you like it or not!
I can't let my friend's son die before my eyes!
Tell all the people in the New Kama Land!
We're going to rescue Ace-boy and try to break out of the prison!
--What are you saying all of the sudden?
--Isn't this a bit hasty?
Decisions must always be sudden!
If you wanna come with me, get ready to die,
prepare for action and wait for us here!
Alright! Let's do it!
I'll follow you, Iva-sama, to the end!
It's a new beginning for New Kama!
Alright! Wait for me, Ace!
I'm coming for you!
What?!
His pulse...
...is fine!
That was a joke?!
Because the treatment has just shortened his life,
he must be exhausted still on some level!
Emporio...
...Energy Hormone!
It's a matter of adrenaline!
Now you have enough energy for a day!
You'll feel the after effects in several days but I guess it won't matter much at that point!
Vice Warden! Warden won't like it if he hears that you've been sitting there!
We'll be sure to tell him later!
You guys are so mean!
Mr. 2, Mr. 3, Buggy the Clown...
Are you sure that they got onto Level 5?
Yes, his disguise was perfect!
But the only thing that they found on Level 5 was the headdress covered in blood.
We assume that they took Straw Hat out of the cell
but ended up being eaten by the wolves.
I see.
I never thought that I'd wear this special order thing before I became the warden.
I still haven't brought down Magellan!
Don't say it so plainly!
If we get duped or beaten again,
both yours and the Warden's jobs are on the line!
My position, too?!
--Of course!
The Staircase to Level 3 must be close!
Level 4 is a breeze!
I haven't seen any jailers at all! They're totally gone!
Let's make a game of it! It's the Buggy and 3 Adventures!
Don't stop suddenly!
Wait a minute!
It's a Surveillance Transponder Snail!
If it finds us, all our efforts will go to waste!
Thank you for noticing it, partner!
Let's go carefully from now on!
What is this?!
M-My eyes are itchy!
This must be Magellan's poison!
That poison that he used against Straw Hat is still in the air here!
Oh no!
The guards will see us through it!
--That was close.
Elevator to Level 6
You were too late!
You're so strict, Domino.
You need to do your business quickly from now on!
That's impossible!
Here it comes again!
Just hold it!
No way!
We need to hand them the prisoner at 9 a.m. sharp by the front gate!
That's our mission!
If we can't make it, we'll ruin the honor of Impel Down!
Front Gate of Impel Down
Listen! We'll take Portgas D. Ace from here and go to Marineford--Navy Headquarters.
Until the very moment that we hand over the prisoner,
--I need you to pay full attention!
--Yes, sir!
To be prepared for any possibility, we'll convey him strictly with 5 ships...
...under the direction of 5 vice admirals! Do not fail!
Yes, sir!
I dunno why but I'm full of energy!
We gotta hurry! We don't wanna waste even a second!
There's no security here! So we can just run out in the open!
Nothing can stop us now!
What's that?!
Who are they?!
T-That looks like Ivankov! I thought that he was dead!
No way!
Outta my way!
Don't mess with me!
Death...
...Wink!
Inazuma, open it!
Okay!
They'll be monitoring us from now on!
Come and get me if you want!
We have an intruder!
They're at the staircase between Level 5 and 6!
Oh! I know this big guy!
He was the Queen of Queers--Ivankov--who went missing years ago!
How could this be possible?!
How did he survive all these years?!
And this is the invader from yesterday
I thought that he was killed by the Warden!
And he's another missing prisoner!
A revolutionary from South Blue--Inazuma!
What's going on here?!
They're heading straight to Level 6!
They want to save Fire Fist Ace!
Domino-san and Warden Magellan are also heading to Level 6 now!
They'll bump into each other!
They are all alive?!
Vice Warden!
Activate passageway traps now!
Call jailers on Level 6 and have them clear for action!
They need to hold on until Sadie-chan and the Jailer Beasts get there!
And report this to Warden Magellan and all floors!
--That's all! Hurry up!
--Yes, sir!
I've never seen Vice Warden getting so serious!
Maybe it's an imposter again!
We have to get them!
My job is on the line!
No, he's the real one!
We can make it! We can make it!
I'll be there right away, Ace!
Alright, Portgas D. Ace!
We will take you to Marineford...
...where the execution ground is!
Time until Ace's execution:
hours!
6 hours!
Luffy finally makes it to the
lowest level of Impel Down, Level 6.
However, Ace has already been taken away,
and the cell is empty.
Luffy tries to follow Ace but he's held up by Hannyabal's traps!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Ace's Convoy Starts Moving
Battle on the Lowest Floor, Level 6!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Ace's Convoy Starts Moving
Battle on the Lowest Floor, Level 6!