A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
And So, the Legend Begins!
To the Other Side
of the Rainbow
Father, it's an even bigger
harvest than we anticipated.
Take it! Take every last bit of treasure in here!
Charge!
Guys!
Don't do anything crazy!
This is the Pumpkin Pirates' territory!
Until Rapa Nui gets back,
it's up to us to defend it!
Professor!
I'm one of the Pumpkin Pirates, too!
I'll fight alongside you!
I'll help you out, Pops!
Professor!
They got me!
How come you guys are having
trouble against those kids?!
W-Wetton...!
He's still his same, young self!
No, you see, I'm Grandpa
Wetton's grandson, Lake.
Do I really look like him?
Yeah, a dead ringer.
I am, huh?
My grandpa was as handsome as I am, was he?
What's with him?
He's a weirdo.
You guys hand over your treasure, nice and easy!
If you refuse, I'll burn you to a
crisp with this electroshock suit!
Watch out! He uses electricity!
Heh! Electricity, huh?
And here I was just itching
to wreak a little havoc, too!
I'll take your electricity, and cut
it clean in half with my sword!
No, electricity doesn't work that way.
This will be interesting. Just try it.
I was hoping you'd say that.
It's quiet, huh?
Yeah. Quiet.
Do you think everyone's all right?
Who knows?
"Who knows?" You can't say that!
Aren't you concerned about everyone?!
They don't need our concern.
Instead, I'm concerned about that
damn mayor coming back alive.
Huh?
If Luffy and the others take
care of that damn mayor,
then I won't be able to get him back.
Oh. I guess there is that.
Coming?
Yeah. Let's go.
Gum-Gum... Rocket!!
What was that?
Whoo, we stopped.
C-Captain!
Y-You've got some nerve,
coming into the Rainbow Mist
without my permission!
You have to pay the 50 million-Berry
"entering on your own" tax!
No way.
What?!
Are you saying you won't
follow Wetton-sama's orders?!
Wetton? That's you?!
That's right. I am the grand,
puffed-up mayor of all of Luluka, Wetton!
What? You, who were once a pirate,
are now the mayor?!
What, is that so wrong?
C-Captain! That's him!
He's the one who stole our ship!
What?
Y-You're that kid from back then?
You, the one who burned down the town,
are now the mayor?!
I don't accept it! No way do I accept this!
You shut your mouth!
Rapa Nui!
Kid, being the mayor is nice.
I'm able to stay at my desk,
and rake in the money I swindle
from all the foolish citizens.
I don't have to wander the seas in search of my prey,
or get hunted down by the Navy!
Every day is a carefree paradise.
There's no other trade as easy as this!
Once you are reborn, you too
will obtain power, as I did.
There's no use going on being a petty pirate!
Shut up!
Captain!
Father!
Why, you...! What are you doing?!
You don't know what a real pirate is.
What?
Luffy...
We don't need power.
We pirates have a dream, after all.
A-A dream, you say?
My electroshock suit is invincible!
You cannot escape from it!
Escape? Who, me?
I told you, I'm gonna cut that
electricity of yours in half!
Like I said, where's the sense
in trying to cut electricity?!
Shall I cut it?
Take this! Rolling Thunder!!
Huh? What's going on here?!
That suit he's so proud of
doesn't seem to be of much use
once the plug is pulled.
Damn it! How can this happen?!
Put it back! Put it back, you bastard!
You jackass! That's no fair!
Help me! I'm sinking! I'm sinking!
Ah, I can't open the top!
Let me cut something...!
A dream, you say? What is it? Tell me!
Everyone knows what your dream is.
You just want to obtain riches of gold and silver.
That will come falling into your lap
on its own, if you have power.
A pirate's dream is to be the greatest man on the seas.
I'm the man who will become Pirate King!
Luffy...
Damn...
No one has ever defied me and lived!
I'll blow you away, right down to your bones!
Wait, Captain!
Father, what about me?!
What do I care?!
Captain!
What is that? What's going on?
Rainbow Tower...!
It's collapsing...
Damn it, what's going on?
He's abandoned us!
Wetton, you bastard!
You're not the captain anymore, dammit!
Luffy!
Rapa Nui!
It's Rapa Nui!
He came back!
Thank goodness! Rapa Nui!
He had me so worried!
Man, how big a pain can one guy be?
W-What's that?
It can't be...!
Professor?
Ape's Concert was maintained in
a delicate balance to begin with.
If you set off a large
explosion in a place like this,
there's no telling what might happen!
What is that?!
The warping of space is expanding quickly!
At this rate, we'll be caught in it,
and all of us will croak!
What?!
How could this happen? Rainbow Tower...
...has completely sunk.
Damn, as unfinished as it was,
it wasn't reinforced enough.
But no matter.
Now, my men won't be coming after me.
The treasure is all mine!
The sky is falling in!
There's not much time. An hour, maybe.
This is bad! We have to get out of here!
But how?
The author of this book
once visited Ape's Concert.
The way out must be written
in here somewhere, too.
What's wrong?
"Continued in the last volume."
And where is that?
You don't have it?!
What's that?
Huh? What's the matter?
Luffy, that light!
That's the light of the sun...
the light of the setting sun!
Setting sun?
Yeah. The light of the sun is
shining in through a crack in space!
We followed that light, and got outside.
R-Really?!
Hurry! That light could disappear at any time!
Unfurl the sails!
Everyone, man the oars as hard as you can!
Hey, you guys come on, too! Give us a hand!
We're getting out of here!
Y-Yeah...
Hey, what are you doing?! Row right!
We are, you know!
Ah, they broke!
What are you doing?!
Damn, not good!
Hey, this is bad!
The light is starting to disappear!
So, this is the end...
You guys get off and push us from behind!
Don't be crazy!
No, if we all flutter kick, then maybe we...
We will not!
If only we could get a tailwind to blow us...
You just need the wind to blow, right?
Hold on! What are you gonna do?!
Blow up our ship!
It was originally a Navy ship, after all.
It's fully loaded with cannonballs.
If we light those,
it should give you a fairly powerful tailwind.
You can't!
Wait, Rapa Nui! If you do that, what...
...what will happen to you?!
This is my treasure! Mine!
This is why I can't give up being mayor!
Hey, our friends were
supposedly inside that mist.
What happened?
Don't tell me you're the only one who came back.
How about it?!
Hey, hold it!
Rapa Nui!
Hey, guys! Where are you going?! Come back!
We are the Pumpkin Pirates!
We're friends, who swore we'd
stay together until we died!
Guys...
Rapa Nui dove in to save you guys!
Don't let what he's done be for nothing!
Are you all trying to get killed together?!
We're not going to die!
Henzo, I promise, we're coming back!
No matter how many years it takes,
we're coming back to Luluka!
Isoka...
D-Don't you go thinking that you
won't answer for striking the mayor!
You'll have to pay the "hitting the
mayor" tax of 90 million Berries!
Are you okay with that?
It doesn't matter to me.
I'll just skip out on it, after all.
What? Paying taxes is a citizen's duty!
How is a pirate obligated to pay taxes?
Er, well...
Sanji!
The Rainbow Mist is disappearing!
What?
What will happen to Luffy and everyone else?
Now, none of them can come back! Not ever!
No matter how hard you guys try,
my power is unshakable!
Hm? What's that?!
What?!
What the...?!
The Merry!
Are those guys all right?
Aah! My mansion!
All of my possessions are being carried away!
Guys!
Nami-san!
Damn, how can this happen?!
My precious ship...!
Oh, Sanji, long time no see!
Nami-san!
What was that for?!
Oh, man, am I annoyed!
Why, Nami-san?
All of the treasure she left
on deck got blown away.
Best not to get too close to her right now.
That's far enough, pirates!
– The Navy!
– They're the same ones that were chasing us!
Help us! These guys are terrible criminals,
who have taken every last bit
of the mayor's property!
This is the ring of Princess Illusia,
a treasure which was stolen
by pirates a hundred years ago,
and has been missing ever since.
Why do you have this?
W-Well, you see...
You didn't steal it, did you?
No, of course not! This was a treasure
that was resting in Ape's Concert!
Yes, yes, we just pulled it out of a shipwreck!
I see. What you're saying is,
it doesn't belong to anyone.
What?!
Major, we've discovered a large pile of treasure
that we believe was carried out of there.
All right, the Navy will be confiscating all of it.
Hold it!
You're not laying a finger on that treasure!
That treasure is mine!
Any treasure without an owner
belongs to the World Government.
If it has been embezzled,
it will be considered an act of piracy!
Fine with me! I'm a pirate to begin with!
Whatever I want, I take by force!
Watch out!
I will take that as your confession.
Is that okay with you, Wetton the pirate?
What?!
You couldn't be...
Rapa Nui...
正義 = Justice
You're kidding!
I promised that we'd come back, didn't I?
Isoka?!
Take all of Wetton's gang into custody.
Yes, sir.
You guys are all alive? B-But how?
At the moment of the explosion,
we were thrown into the outside world, too.
However, it was the world 50 years ago.
Sure enough, that mist warped
the axis of time, as well.
Then why didn't you come here sooner?
In order to defeat Wetton,
who abused the mantle of his authority,
I thought we would need to use another authority... the power of the Navy.
But in order to gain that high a rank,
it took me a little time.
So that's it.
I may be wearing the uniform
of the Navy, but in my heart,
I'm still a Pumpkin Pirate,
and Henzo, I'm your friend.
For now, and forever.
Rapa Nui...
Also, I forgot to mention this, Luffy Pirates,
but you're under arrest, too.
What?!
You're heartless!
Have you forgotten how you owe
me for feeding you, you jerk?!
As a member of the Navy,
charged with upholding justice,
I can't just let a pirate who has
a bounty get away. However...
How can this be?! Right now, we have
to escort Wetton and his gang
back to Navy Headquarters! But if we do that,
the Luffy Pirates are going to
end up slipping away from us!
But they're just too much for us to handle!
Request assistance from the naval base at once!
No, it won't be until tomorrow or
the next day that they'll arrive!
If they escape during that time,
that's the end of it!
Aah, I give up! I can't do anything about it!
That sure sounded like a put-on.
We can't do any full-fledged repairs right away.
Those emergency measures should
at least keep the water out, though.
Thank you, Luffy, and all of your friends.
Now, the research that I carried
on all these years is at an end.
We can't have that.
There's no telling when the Rainbow
Mist is going to appear, right?
With that thing out there,
we can't go out to sea in peace.
We want you to make us some gear,
to help us avoid the Rainbow Mist.
That will be an easy task.
The Rainbow Mist is a land of eternity.
It has neither daytime, nor nighttime.
One never gets sick, or grows old.
The sea shines emerald, and the sky
envelops us deeply, like milk.
The countless ships that
become captives of this land
had immeasurable treasures resting within them.
It was indeed the last
paradise remaining on earth.
We were the kings of that land of eternity.
We routed the pirates that came invading,
and kept the peace in paradise.
Our name was the Pumpkin Pirates.
I would like to write down
the many unusual adventures
we went through inside the mist...
...for the sake of the adventurers
who will visit this land hereafter.
The name of the adventurers belongs to those
whose debt we are in for leading us back out into the world...
the Luffy Pirates.
Anyway, that sure was an interesting place.
Really? I've had enough of that ship graveyard!
Well, it's not like I wanna live there,
but I wanna visit from time to time.
Was it really that nice?
Hm? Rain?
It's... not rain...
Hail?
No... something's fall...
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
Aa hateshinaku tsuzuiteru sora no mukou ni
Itsuka mita asu o ima egakihajimete iru
The future that I once saw is now starting to take shape
Jibun ni makesou ni naru hi mo aru
There are days where I almost lose to myself
Sonna toki wa
When that happened,
atataka na basho ga atta
there was someplace warm I could go
Hokoreru mono itsumo kitto
The friends I took pride in always, without fail,
Boku no senaka oshite kureta yo ne?
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Aa hoshi-tachi ga furisosogu kono sora no shita
Ah, the stars are pouring down underneath the sky
Nido to nai ima o hora
This unique moment...
What's wrong?!
Our Log Pose is broken!
It's stuck pointing upwards.
What?!
That's not it.
It was updated by an island
with stronger magnetism.
If it's pointing up, it's a sky island.
Sky island?
Then, that ship fell from there?
Next time, on One Piece:
Caught Log!
The King of Salvagers, Masira!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Caught Log!
The King of Salvagers,
Masira!