Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has broken out of the
great prison - Impel Down
in order to rescue his brother, Ace!--
No! I know that you guys know about the
war between Whitebeard and the Navy!
--What'd you say?
--Navy HQ?
We passed through the Gate of Justice.
That means our destination must be
either Navy HQ or Enies Lobby.
The Tub Current that we're on
is exclusive to the Government.
It's a giant whirlpool that connects
the Government's 3 major facilities
We didn't know about this!
Buggy! Buggy!
Be quiet, you flashy fools!
You guys are all full of whim and fancy!
If you guys are real men, why don't
you live out a dream with me?!
Today...
I'll beat Whitebeard which means
that I'll conquer the world!
--I will follow you!
--I don't want a peaceful life!
That's right!
Let's go, guys! To Navy Headquarters!
Looks like it's over.
I hope they are having fun.
The Crew's Whereabouts
Weatheria Report and Cyborg Animals
I know that you are worried about Ace-san
but you need to take some rest.
The war that we are about to get involved in
is literally the decisive battle of our times!
Just as Impel Down is the
greatest prison in the world,
Navy Headquarters is the
greatest fortress in the world!
Meanwhile, a short time ago at
the small Sky Island - Weatheria,
home to scientists who study the weather.
Hey, hey, hey, young girl!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey! Hey, young girl!
Hey! Hey!
Alright! What do you want?!
H-Hey, what's this?!
Do you like the taste of my cloud
candy? I've been working on it.
It was so hard to make it
taste like cotton candy.
What do you think?
Are you trying to kill me?!
Wait a minute, young girl! Violence won't do!
Honestly!
Oh, it's sweet! It does
taste like cotton candy!
That's what I thought!
Hm... So I guess that this island
is really full of wonder!
Oh, by the way, are you sure that we're
heading to Sabaody Archipelago?!
Yes, I'm doing it for you as a special favor!
But it's been a while since I asked you.
When are we gonna get there?
What do you mean?
Huh?
Wasn't I clear enough?!
Weatheria travels on the wind.
If a
typhoon comes, it's gonna be really fast.
How far did we get yesterday?
Probably about 200 meters.
Honestly, if this weren't a Sky
Island, I would've left already!
But we're still too far away from
Sabaody if you were to go down on the ground now.
If you stay here, we'll get there someday.
Look, I don't have that much time to spare.
Then, shall we go down?
I'm running out of research funds anyway.
Huh?
What do you mean "go down?"
I mean, on the ground.
Is that possible?!
You know, it takes a lot of
money to do this research.
So I go down from time to time to do some
business with my knowledge of the weather.
What is this?!
Young girl!
It's this way!
A ship?!
Wow, this ship... floats in the sky?!
No!
Let's go!
What?!
That's just the island
that I was looking for!
This island is...
...terrible!
Did you say that you can save this island?!
Yes.
It seems like you people are
in need of blessed rain.
I can make it rain with my
knowledge of the weather!
What did you just say?!
I can do this now for a special price...
...of 100 million berries!
100 million?!
I'm afraid we don't have that much money.
Is it too much?!
That's way too much!
No one can afford that!
Well...
--Then, 100 berries!
--Huh?!
What a deal!
You came down too much! You
have no sense for business!
Relax!
That aside, can you really do it?
Weren't you being too optimistic?
Believe in my knowledge of
the weather! Okay, ready?
Those are..
...soap bubbles!
There's something inside.
Young girl, could you generate
some wind with this?!
Oh, this is...
Do you want it full power?!
Yes!
Oh my god! I can't believe this!
--It's raining!
--Yeah!
We did it!
They're so pleased!
Yeah! Now, don't you think the
science of weather is useful?
Okay. So I guess this is
goodbye, right? Young girl.
I already asked the mayor
so he'll provide
you with what you need for your journey.
--I'm not going!
--What?
I'll stay with you.
I've become interested
in the science of weather a bit.
Really?
Can you teach me about it on our
way to Sabaody Archipelago?
Of course!
You sure? Thank you!
Anyone who loves the weather is welcomed!
Is this from before? This is perfect!
Let me tell you about this soap
bubble with the thundercloud inside.
Oh no, this is not good!
Huh?
You...
What're you doing?!
S-S-Science exacts a price!
Am I the price?!
Help... Help me!
Meanwhile, on the Island of Machines,
Future Land Baldimore,
the birthplace of the Genius.
It makes me super relaxed!
Oh no!
He was way funnier before!
Oh! What do you think we can
do to turn Franky back?!
The cola hasn't arrived yet so
we can't conduct an operation.
He has to take back his perversion...
I mean, wildness, in order to
get back to being himself again.
Wildness?
It's cold!
How did I get here?
Here is a scarf!
Oh?
What is going on here?!
"Keep Out"?
"This is an enclosed forest
of mechanical animals."?
Mission: The surprising
wake-up in the jungle!
Take back your wildness
through surviving, old man!
Don't try this at home, kids!
Hey guys, you better relax!
You all seem very frustrated.
Have you eaten breakfast?
It is not good for your mental health
if you don't eat it every day!
Oh I see! This is breakfast time!
What was I thinking?
Delicious! There is nothing like the
first cup of tea in the morning!
Do you guys want some?
It feels great to be alive!
It's not working!
Help us!
Good morning, boys!
Old man!
I'm not an old man! Call me Mr. Frank!
Violence is not...
I know you are at an age
when you want to be naughty...
If you let me talk...
You'll see...
Let's sort this out...
...in a gentlemanly manner!
Stop... Nothing good... comes... from war!
Mr. Frank!
Oh no, it's not working at all!
Relax...
Listen to what I say... Listen to what...
Listen to... Listen...
Lis...
To...
Listen... Lis... L...
Lis...
Super!
Who do you think I am?!
I am Franky-sama!
Yeah! You're back, old man!
Per... vert!
What's the matter?
I got cooled down a little
so I'm running out of steam!
Oh, geek! I mean, god!
Um... Um...
Oh yeah! We gotta go there!
Where are we going?
The house of Dr. Vegapunk!
Maybe we can find a machine
to make some cola!
Dr. Vegapunk?!
He's the standout genius
of Future Land
Baldimore known for its advanced technology!
The mechanical animals that you just
saw are all cyborgs that he created!
I heard that he was a weirdo and he
left the island with cyborgs running wild
but that he was also amazing!
Grandpa told me to keep away from here
because there are a lot of
dangerous creations inside!
Alright!
What the hell is this?!
Sanji is on the run from countless
pursuers of ambiguous gender.
After running and running to escape them,
he's met by a mysterious
queen, and a frilly dress.
Around that time,
a huge, round creature falls
to the ground behind Chopper!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Crew's Whereabouts
A Giant Chick and the Peachy Showdown"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Crew's Whereabouts
A Giant Chick and the Peachy Showdown