We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for... ONE PIECE
Compasses and stuff'll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Blast through the stingy night!
We've no interest in treasure chests
Pockets bulging with dreams, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
To reach Fishman Island,
Luffy and company found themselves
looking for a coating craftsman
on Sabaody Archipelago.
However, also on the archipelago
are the Celestial Dragons,
world nobles powerful enough
to hold sway over Navy Headquarters,
and formidable rookies
headed for the New World!
But I'm worried about
the old craftsman guy,
if he's in such a rough town.
My husband will be fine.
After all, he's 100 times
stronger than you kids...
The Target is Camie!!
The Looming Clutches of a Pro Kidnapper
Are you in?
Yeah!
Well, take care.
Just so you know,
the Navy is obviously aware
that big-name rookies
have made landfall here.
Th-That's not good!
Then, does that mean there's
no telling when they might strike?
But don't worry.
Perhaps this is another
case of rookie's luck,
but I believe Navy HQ
probably has its hands full
with something else right now.
Unless something especially
problematic happens,
they won't waste major military
resources on things here.
So, to be more precise,
"Take care not to cause
any trouble." Okay?
Oh, okay!
Got it! Thanks!
We're gonna go find the
old coating craftsman now!
Here's hoping you do find him.
We're here! Sabaody Park!
Yay!
It looks so fun!
Are you even trying
to find the old guy?!
But that lady did say
he likes this place!
Only if we couldn't find him
in the Lawless Lands!
Wow! The Ferris wheel!
I've never seen it from
this close before!
Alright, guys! Let's have fun!
See, you're not trying to find him!
Yay!
Camie! You are forbidden to go in!
I absolutely forbid it!
Oh, it's moving at quite
a leisurely pace indeed!
Oh, what a truly wonderful view!
Yahoo!
Awesome!
Let's do it again!
Were you scared, Camie?
Yeah!
It was really scary, but really fun!
My heart's still beating so fast!
That's nothing! I was in the very front!
We went so fast my head
almost wound up behind my back!
I-I thought my heart
was going to stop...
Though I don't have a heart.
Yes.
Gentle rides like this
are more my style.
Oh, what a delightful view...
Wow! Look!
Don't spin too much, now!
Spin! Spin! Spin! Spin!
Spin!
Spin! Spin! Spin!
What the heck's your problem?!
You idiots spun too much!
Wow! We're so high up!
Oh! They're selling
ice cream, Luffy-chin!
For reals?!
Wow! Everyone's so tiny!
It's the ocean! The ocean, Luffy-chin!
Yeah!
Wow! Wow!
So this is how it looks!
It makes you happy enough to cry?
Yeah, I've always dreamed of this,
ever since I was a little girl!
I've never been so high up before!
I'll cherish this memory forever!
Thank you!
Hatchin and Pappagu
only let me come here
because you guys are strong!
My dreams as a kid
have come back to life too!
Merfolk and Fishmen always dream
of coming here when growing up!
So high up!
That one next!
Gondola!
Let's go in!
I-I never thought they'd
be that strong...
Sounds like you had it rough.
So, what's this proposition of yours?
Right, Peterman-san.
I think the girl that was with
Straw Hat Luffy might be a Mermaid.
When I think back...
Oh no! Camie! Pappagu!
When her shoe came off,
I saw a tail fin instead of a foot!
I see.
But these strong companions of hers
sound like trouble.
Even so, a Mermaid on land
is a golden opportunity.
They're impossible to catch
in the water, after all.
Thanks for telling me, boys.
S-Sure thing...
For the info, you can have
10% of her selling price.
Agreed?
A-Actually, we were
hoping more like 20%...
No, 10% is plenty!
Wait here a minute, Camie!
Okay! Choose something yummy for me too!
High Priest Urouge. Look...
Oh!
A Celestial Dragon, huh?
To think they'd swagger about
the Lawless Lands with nary a care...
This is bad.
Our only choice is to kneel
and let him pass.
Where on earth could Shalria
and Father have gone,
leaving me behind like this?!
We do know their final destination,
so please rest easy.
Hey, you!
It's all because you walk like a turtle!
You also sway too much and
make for a horrible ride!
You irritate me to no end!
Hey! Wait, you!
And why are you moving?! You're humans!
I-I'm sorry! Please overlook this!
He's losing blood and needs urgent care!
It's a race against time!
The hospital is just ahead!
Yes, this is very bad, indeed!
In that case, you must be swift...
...and be out of your misery!
Be out of your misery!
Please stop!
Oh no!
Talk about utterly selfish.
Which is more important,
courtesy toward me,
or a commoner's life?
Commoners owe their existence
to the Celestial Dragons.
Okay! I'm making you my wife!
Then I shall arrange to send her
to the Holy Land as your 13th wife.
Oh, and I'm tired of
wives #1 through #5 now,
so I'm sending them back
to the commoners.
As you wish, sir.
Wait! I'm...!
Stop! Please!
She's my fiancée!
Stand up in front of me, will you?!
Marie...
No!
You murderer! How could you?!
Someone!
Someone please help him!
They're even more screwed up
than the rumors say...
What was that?
Are you telling me off?
Let go of me!
Please!
Take her on ahead to the harbor.
Yes, sir!
Who's he?!
Captain Apoo!
He's an East Blue pirate hunter!
Why's he walkin'
in the middle of the street?!
Doesn't he know anything?!
He's gonna cause trouble!
What?
You need directions or somethin'?
Whoa! What is he doing?!
A kid?!
Brother!
Why did you have to die, Brother?!
Just stay still, guy.
Brother!
You stood up to a Celestial Dragon?!
Then it's only natural that you died!
I hit him?
I could've sworn he managed
to dodge my shots...
It must've been my imagination.
Well, as long as he's dead.
Why'd you get in the way?!
Huh?!
Don't gimme that, you idiot!
What the hell were you thinking?!
Are you trying to attract
an admiral to these islands?!
Tomato juice...
If you're a pirate, you must know
some of the unwritten pirate rules!
Don't get us caught up in your trouble!
Trouble?
Who are...?
Huh? Wasn't there a kid?
Are you even listenin' to me?!
You alright in the head?!
Oh, yeah, I'm not hurt.
You idiot!
I'm talking about on the inside!
You're a dumbass!
A genuine dumbass!
We managed to avoid the worst-case
scenario thanks to Jewelry Bonney...
That man is Pirate Hunter Zoro,
a member of the Straw Hat Pirates.
I heard their crew's crazy,
but attacking a Celestial Dragon?
That really is insane.
It's only natural he was saved.
I don't see the shadow of death
upon him at this time.
That bastard unleashed an absurd
amount of bloodlust for a moment.
He's a beast...
Worth 120 million,
yet only #2 on his ship...
He doesn't seem like the type
to play second fiddle to anyone,
but I guess that goes to show
the caliber of his captain.
Hey. Where's the hospital?
Hospital?
I gotta take him there.
He's been shot.
Huh?!
Forget about 'im! He's a total stranger!
What the hell?
A pirate that helps people?
Ain't ever heard of that before!
When I looked into town earlier,
I saw some bubble bicycle
things flying around!
Yeah, I saw! They're so cool!
Let's buy some!
We'll need to see how nice they ride.
Oh?
Could that be Nami-san?
Hello, Nami-sa--!
Hello?! It's me!
Me, Chopper!
Basically, they have so
many kinds of ice cream
and we got so caught up in it all...!
Hey, why are you freaking out?!
Sanji?! It's really bad!
What do we do?!
I'm not following you!
Calm down first! What happened?
I-It's Camie!
What's going on, Sanji?
Camie's been kidnapped!
What?!
A kidnapping team probably did it!
I dunno why, but they let people
sell Merfolk and Fishmen
even if they aren't bad guys!
Camie's gonna get sold!
She's gonna be a slave forever
and it's all our fault!
There are lots of Human Shops
on these islands,
so there's no telling
when or where she'll be sold!
We don't even know who kidnapped her!
The archipelago is too big,
but for now let's all split up and...!
Tell us exactly where you are
and then wait there.
Eh?! But...!
There are pros
when it comes to this sort of thing.
I'm calling the Flying Fish Riders!
--Eh?!
--Huh?!
A young Mermaid!
This one will go for quite a price!
Let me go!
She's quite lively, too!
Alright, let's welcome our
customers and start the auction!
We're sure to get a lot of high bids!
Save me, Hatchin!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Rescue Camie
The Archipelago's Lingering Dark History"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Rescue Camie
The Archipelago's Lingering Dark History