Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I won't take my focus off of you.
No matter what they're going through
right now, they'll survive for sure!
But if I let you get away now,
you'll go kill my friends!
I won't take my focus off of you!
Can you really defeat me?!
I can't protect anyone unless I win!
Gum-Gum...
...Rifle!
Iron Body. Empty Tree.
I thought I was able to meet a man
with some backbone. How disappointing.
Did you run out of strength from
your doping earlier after all?
If it's backbone you want, I'll show you...
...another tactic!
Gear... 3:
Bone Balloon!
Bone?
The power that moves
from one bone to another...
Take a look! My left arm is...
...the arm of a Giant!
If it's all show, don't even bother!
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
...Gigant Pistol!
Shivering Past!
Dark Justice and Rob Lucci
I feel like I'm about to pass out.
I can't fall into the sea like this...!
Oops...!
What was that?
Hurry up and help the injured!
Who are you?!
--A beast?!
--No, he's a power holder!
So I landed on the deck of
a battleship. That was close...
He flew from the direction of the bridge.
Is he a pirate?
I saw a huge hand, too!
Stop! Stop! I said stop!
It's dangerous ahead of here!
Water is rushing towards us!
C-Can't you guys hear the sound of water?!
Listen, if the water flows into
an underground passage like this,
we'll have no choice but to drown.
Zoro-kun, can't you hear the sound of water?!
Hmm, it's true that
something doesn't feel right.
Then let's stop, you guys!
There's no other passage. We have
no choice but to keep on this path!
I knew it!
Granny and the others
are being chased by water!
Ah! Pirate guys!
Guys! Do something about this water!
Do something?! What're we supposed to do?!
See, I told you! This passage is
gonna be flooded with water!
N-Nami-san is...
...rushing into my arms!
How positive!
This is bad! We're gonna be shut in here!
I can't cut it! So this isn't iron or stone?!
This is an undersea passage.
It must be made of some damn thick steel
that can bear the water pressure!
Then there's nowhere to escape!
Ahh! It's here!
It isn't safe here! We're gonna die!
Hurry!
This is no good! The sea train won't start!
Aren't there any engineers?!
The attacks will reach here soon! Hurry up!
Vice Admiral!
What do we do about capturing
Nico Robin on the Bridge of Hesitation?!
--Leave her alone.
--But...
As long as that man is on this island
and is given the mission
of escorting Nico Robin,
we don't have to get involved.
We'll just burn everything down
except the Bridge of Hesitation.
Yes, sir!
Vice Admiral...
Could this man you mentioned be...
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9?
As we suspected, he's a power holder!
Who the hell are you?!
We're asking who you are! Answer us!
Stop it, you idiots!
Captain?!
Put down your guns!
Who do you think you're talking to?!
He is... Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9!
R-Rob Lucci-san...
Wha... That...
We're sorry! Please spare our lives!
Shut your mouths. Your whining hurts my ears.
I've heard a lot about Mr. Rob Lucci,
so he is really that good?
It was fifteen years ago...
In some kingdom,
there was an incident where 500
soldiers got captured by pirates.
"Fifteen Years Ago"
Guys! Don't hold back! Go wild!
Kill anyone who resists! Show no mercy!
Don't flinch! Protect this
country from the pirates!
The kingdom put up unrelenting
resistance against the pirates.
However...
Those damn pirates...!
Trench mortars...?!
This is it for you! If you don't wanna die,
just give up and surrender!
If you resist, we'll blow you away
with these trench mortars!
They're all our hostages!
Throw them all in a warehouse!
In exchange for the hostages' lives,
the pirate captain demanded the throne.
Your Majesty. For the sake of the citizens,
you should firmly refuse the
pirates' despicable demand!
He's right!
With the power of the kingdom's
main military and the Imperial Guards,
we don't have to fear those pirates!
Your Majesty!
But those soldiers who fought risking their lives
and ended up being taken
hostage are also my people.
I can't just sit back and let them die.
But...
Even if this throne is taken away,
it's possible to take it back.
But you can't take back people's lives!
Your Majesty...
But even if we accepted the pirates' demands,
I find it hard to believe that they'd
release the hostages as they promised!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! An emissary from the
World Government has just arrived!
Is that right?! From the World Government...
Show him in immediately.
Yes, your Majesty!
To the kingdom that was about
to surrender with its hands tied
over its concern for the hostages,
the World Government sent a boy.
A-A child?
Dammit! That blasted World
Government! How insulting!
Where's the prey?
Prey? You mean the pirates?
They're occupying the western
harbor and making it their hideout.
Okay.
Well then, I'd like you to leave the rest to me.
Wait!
Please give the highest priority
to the hostages' lives.
Are you trying to tell the
World Government what to do?
Wh-Why does this boy make me so intimidated?
The World Government...
Good work, guys!
Eat and drink to your heart's content
and have a good time tonight!
Yahoo!
A kingdom ain't actually a big deal!
No, it ain't!
Now the kingdom will be all ours!
Hooray for the boss!
Idiot! He's the new king!
Oh, that's right!
Booze! We're running out of booze!
Us, too! Someone, bring some more!
Today's booze is especially tasty!
--You guys...
--Huh?
Who's your captain?
Who are you?
In the name of the World Government,
I've come to arrest you all.
Arrest?! Me?! A brat like you will arrest me?
It seems like the Government
is really hard up for people.
Seriously, don't make me laugh!
What can one little brat do?
If you wanna pretend to be some
Government big shot, do it somewhere else!
Beat it! We got no time
to play games with a brat.
Beat it already!
Before you get hurt!
You're in my way. Move.
It's you who's gonna move!
Iron Body.
What's with him?!
He used a weird technique!
I see. Not too bad.
It might not be a total lie that
you're from the World Government.
But if you do any more weird stuff,
we can't guarantee the hostages' lives!
So long as you obey us,
we'll keep you alive for a while
as a hostage for the World Government.
Now no one can defeat us!
Throw that brat in the same
lockup where the others are!
Get in there!
We'll have you stay in here, too.
Wh-Who's that boy?
He's a "Great Emissary"
from the World Government.
He said he came to rescue you.
Now the Government will
do whatever we tell them to.
No one can defeat us!
Well, you guys are all hostages.
Try and get along in there!
I'd like to verify one thing.
Hm? What is it?
Are all of the hostages here?
Yeah.
I see.
Shave!
Tempest Kick!
Once the boy infiltrated the
pirates' hideout, right then and there,
he killed all 500 of the kingdom's
soldiers who were taken hostage.
K-Killed all of them?
Can't be...! Is something like that permissible?!
Even if it's the World Government...
Even if it's for justice...
P-Pardon me!
"Justice"
Listen up. Justice isn't all warm and fuzzy!
You guys, too, remember it!
Yes, sir!
Naturally, the pirates got
angry and rained bullets
upon the boy who was standing on the
mountain of bodies with his back turned.
But the boy stood up in the flame of explosions,
killed the boss of the pirates,
and settled that incident all by himself.
Boss!
Boss! Boss! Boss!...
Pipe down! What's the problem?!
Boss...!
That brat is going on a rampage in the lockup!
What?!
Wh-What the hell is this?!
How dare you... kill our important hostages...?!
They committed a crime.
So I executed them in the name of justice.
A crime?
As soldiers of the kingdom,
being weak is a crime.
They surrendered to evil and
plunged the kingdom into a crisis.
Soldiers like that don't have the right to live.
They deserve to die.
You bastard! And you call yourself
an official of the World Government?!
Justice would never surrender to evil.
Guys! Bring him down!
That serves you right, you damn brat.
Don't treat us like fools!
Dammit! After all the trouble we
went through, our plan got ruined!
H... How could he have survived that?!
Shave!
Finger Pistol.
Boss...
H-He's a monster!
Help!
The boy, who had several
bullet marks on his back,
was a CP9 intelligence agent at the age of 13.
People call him the strongest
and cruelest mass killing machine
in the history of CP9,
whose mission is dark justice.
To think that he was capable of
all that when he was only 13...
That's exactly why all we have
to do is fulfill our own duty.
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!
What is it this time?!
Something came out!
That's Straw Hat Luffy, whose
bounty is 100 million berries!
I didn't think he'd be that fat.
There you are! Pigeon guy!
Shoot him down!
That won't work! The Bone Balloon is tough!
Gum-Gum... Gigant Axe!
Ahhh!
What the hell?! Is it a Giant?!
Gum-Gum... Gigant Whip!
Whoa! Watch out!
The masts got broken!
They're falling down!
The fight between those two is just crazy!
Finger Pistol...! Pick!
It seems that as your power increases,
your speed decreases.
Tempest Kick... Victory Bird!
The iron outer shell got cracked...!
This ship won't last long!
That was close. I almost got split in two.
Did you see that, Cutty Flam?!
It's all over for you guys! Or rather,
it was all over from the start!
It's a bit early to say that
when the fight isn't over yet!
The one who is fighting Straw Hat is Lucci.
He's the strongest man in the history of CP9!
You might've been able to
get rid of the others okay,
but Lucci's another story entirely!
Once Straw Hat is taken out,
you're next, Cutty Flam!
I'm counting on you, Straw Hat!
What's going on? Give me a report.
Yes, sir, Vice Admiral!
We heard that Straw Hat Luffy and
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 are currently fighting.
As a result, the #4 ship got wrecked!
Rob Lucci isn't gonna die.
To the gunners on all ships, aim at the #4 ship!
Fire all cannons together in five seconds!
Wha... Vice Admiral, you must be kidding.
One thousand of our men are onboard!
A moment's indecision can allow
vicious criminals to slip away.
Can you protect our future from them?
Fire!
We were finally able to free Robin-chan,
but if we don't do anything, we'll drown!
I-I can't breathe... I can't hold my breath!
Oh... Am I dreaming?
How beautiful... you are...!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Mystical Mermaid Appears?
As Consciousness Fades Away..."
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Mystical Mermaid Appears?
As Consciousness Fades Away...