We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for... ONE PIECE
Compasses and stuff'll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Blast through the stingy night!
We've no interest in treasure chests
Pockets bulging with dreams, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
As Luffy and his friends continued their
voyage in search of Fishman Island,
they made it halfway to the Grand Line.
Chopper!
Coup de Burst!
I can't see the top...
It's huge!
They finally reached the Red Line.
There, they met the Mermaid Camie
and the starfish Pappagu, and became friends.
Thanks for saving me.
Camie, you're okay?
Camie asked them to save her
imprisoned friend, "Hatchin,"
so they headed toward the hideout of the
kidnapping gang, the Flying Fish Riders.
What? What's going on?
There they are! The Flying Fish Riders!
Hey! Did you see?
Yeah! There's no mistake!
It's the Straw Hats!
I've been waiting. I've been waiting so long.
That pirate ship is the
one I've been waiting for.
I'll kill him.
I'll kill the man who ruined my life!
The Fated Reunion!
Save the Imprisoned Fishman
The flying fish left.
They were obviously taking
the offensive, though.
It looked like they received
some kind of message.
Maybe they were ordered to retreat?
Though I don't know why...
I wanna ride one!
Those flying fish can fly for five whole minutes?!
That's so cool!
Anyway, those flying fish will be at
the place we're heading for, right?
Then we'll need to be prepared to fight.
I never expected them to
come from the sky, though...
Why don't we bring the cannons up on deck?
Then I can shoot 'em out of the sky!
All right!
I hope Hatchin is okay...
You're the one Macro is really after.
You should be careful yourself.
You're right.
Duval-sama! The three Riders have returned!
Duval-sama, why did you order us back?
Yeah!
If you'd left it to us, we could've
nabbed the Mermaid and the pirates!
Fools!
You guys...
Yes, sir!
Do you know how I have felt
as I waited for those pirates?
I'm sure you know the story.
Duval
When I think about that man,
the huge wound on my back throbs terribly.
Uh-oh... The Head is mad!
Day after day, I have continued
to loathe that man...
Head, please calm down...
Shall I kill him here today?
What do you think?
That is the biggest question in my life!
Do you realize that?!
Y-Yes! In that case, you
should not let him live!
That's exactly why I must be careful
and thorough in eliminating him.
So do as I tell you!
Yes, Head!
Hey, Macro Pirates.
Yeah? You called?
What is it, Duva?
Gyaro, how could you call him Duva?!
And Tansui, "Yeah?" isn't right!
You're both being rude!
Ha, ha. "Duva" sounds funny.
Gyaro
Macro
Tansui
Oh, damn it!
Hey, Master Duval! Hey, hey, you called for us?
Boss, he's too worked up.
Quiet! Shut your mouth!
I'm so sorry, Master.
They truly are idiots. They don't
know how to speak properly.
That's fine, boys.
To me, you're like messengers from
heaven who bring me happiness.
I'm so grateful, I can't
find the words to thank you.
S'okay.
I told you to shut up, Tansui!
Thanks to you boys, I'll
finally... finally... meet them.
I'll finally meet the Straw Hats!
Straw Hats? Huh? Who are they?
The Straw Hats... So I
didn't hear that wrong.
The man...
...I have been praying...
...for a chance to kill is on that ship!
I will never forgive him!
Head, please calm down!
That's quite a grudge you're carrying.
I never expected to hear the
Straw Hats spoken of here...
Hey, you! Big guy!
Gah! This is Duval-sama, you damn octopus!
Was Camie captured by the Straw Hats?
This is bad... Of all people, why them?
Are they coming here?
That's right. They're headed here.
Hey, does that mean your Mermaid
went to pirates for help?
I don't know the details, but
she didn't seem like a prisoner.
Well, no matter who she brings,
as long as we're here, they'll all be
captured and sold at the human shop.
As if that's possible! Those
guys are crazy strong!
Man, this is a problem... Nami's
probably with them, too...
She's probably holding a grudge against me.
Of course she would.
I did awful things to her
with Arlong and the boys.
I've gotta get out of
here before they arrive,
or they're sure to pulverize me.
This is a huge problem!
That's...
Duval-sama!
It's the Straw Hats!
Finally... they're here...
Hey, Macro.
Huh? What do you want?
I'll give you takoyaki, so please let me go.
I'm not letting you go, idiot! You
think I'm that obsessed with food?!
Are you sure he's on the ship?
Yes! He's definitely there!
It's curtains for you
now. I hope you're ready!
Hey, Gyaro, I'll give you
takoyaki, so please let me go.
Who do you think is gonna fall for—
Hey! Just how obsessed with food are you?!
All of you, get in position!
Yes, sir!
Hey, Tansui, I'll give you— Huh?
Shut up! You come with us!
Hey, I see something!
Looks like that's the Flying
Fish Riders' hideout.
So that's where this
Hatchin guy is imprisoned?
Hatchin...
Hey! Let's hurry up and save the takoyaki!
We know! Just hold on!
We'll save him in a flash, Camie-chan!
Thanks, Sanji-chin!
Oh, but be careful, everyone!
The Macro Pirates alone
have captured me 30 times!
You get captured too much!
Well...
And eaten too much, too!
Looks like we've entered their territory.
Ugh, there's that "we shouldn't go
to this island" syndrome again...
This isn't an island.
It's more like a living
complex built on the sea.
My "we shouldn't go to this living
complex built on the sea" syndrome!
Why would they go to the
trouble to live here?
Who knows?
Sure is quiet, though.
I have a bad feeling...
Luffy! We should...
...go forward!
Hey! Come up with a plan or something!
Hey! Hatchin! Are you okay?!
Get out here, Macro!
Give Hachi back!
Oh, no! It really is the Straw Hats' ship!
Damn!
Nope, I can't get out...
Then I'll have to..
Takohachi Black!
There's someone in that cage.
What is that black thing?
What?! Let me see!
Could that be Hatchin?
We've got this, Camie! There
are no enemies around!
It must be their snack time!
Yeah!
Are you being serious?!
No matter how you look at it, that's a trap!
They're all hiding nearby
and keeping an eye on us.
What incredible insight!
I-I never thought of that!
That's why you keep getting caught!
I'm right here! Camie, I'm
all right, so don't worry!
I knew it! Hatchin!
You're all black! What happened?!
Well... I had my own reasons.
More importantly, this is a
trap! You have to turn back!
You know I'm strong, right?
I'll be fine, so go!
That same voice, and that
unusual silhouette...
What do you think, Nami?
I suspect... In fact, I'm almost sure...
Sure of what?
We could always ask him and find out.
Hey! How's Arlong doing?
Oh, Arlong-san?
Well, he and Chew and Kuroobi
were all captured by the Navy!
I was the only one to break out,
and now I'm running a takoyaki shop
like I always dreamed of doing.
Arlong?
I knew it...
It's you, octopus?!
Crap!
C-Crap!
You're that octopus from Arlong's crew!
So you're the takoyaki maker called Hatchin?!
What?
Well, some stuff happened...
Nami's hometown was controlled by a Fishman
pirate gang called the Arlong Pirates.
They put Nami through all
kinds of terrible stuff.
That octopus used to be
an officer in their gang.
Nami, are you thinking of running away?
If you do that, everyone in Cocoyashi
Village will be killed on your account.
Which one of you is Arlong?
Huh... So he's a known enemy?
Well, naturally, I took Luffy
and the others there to
bust some heads, and the
whole gang was annihilated!
Wow! You're amazing, Usopp!
Y-Yeah, well...
I thought all of those Fishmen
were dragged off by the Navy...
But it looks like he escaped by himself.
I see. Every man has a history.
Hey, you octopus!
Now that we know it's you,
there's no way we're saving you!
B-But...
I-I-Is...
Is your takoyaki really that good?!
Don't waver between your
reason and your appetite.
This is stupid.
You mean...
You know Hatchin?
Were you friends with him before?
We were not friends!
Turn the ship around!
Nami-chin...
I'm sorry, Camie.
I wasn't expecting your friend to be him.
No...
Then you won't help me rescue him?
Hatchin!
Camie, that's fine! You should
leave! This is a trap!
No way!
I will save you!
You always save us, Hachi!
Pappagu!
Right!
I had no idea these people were so heartless!
Stupid! Stupid!
Shut up!
Just wait, Hatchin!
I'll never abandon you, Hatchin!
Here we go!
Camie-chan!
That idiot.
Will they be okay?
Given all that stuff they said,
they must have some kind of plan.
I've got you, Camie!
You guys are the definition of "all talk"!
Now we're gonna be rich!
Look what happened to Hachi after
he always came to save you!
You're not gonna get away, Camie!
I told you!
Camie! Pappagu!
Bastards!
Camie-chan did nothing wrong!
Wait, Sanji-kun!
I'm coming to save you, Camie!
It's okay. We'll set Hachi free, too.
What?
Hachi's all right. He's actually harmless.
Besides...
This isn't what we promised Camie.
N-Nami-san...
That strong-willed attitude
of yours is beautiful!
Hey, Nami!
You sure?
Yeah.
Luffy!
If it's okay with you, we have no choice.
We'll save the octopus, too.
Hey! Your eyes are takoyaki!
Are you ready,
Flying Fish Riders?
Of course! Anytime!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
And one more!
He has powers?!
A Straw Hat?!
That bastard!
Luffy-chin!
You did it!
All right! I got 'em back!
Thank you, Straw Hat! I owe you one!
Zoro! Cut the rope holding up the cage!
Got it!
Straw Hat! Be careful!
You're right in their trap!
The Flying Fish Riders have
you surrounded from the air!
Get them!
Yes, sir!
Luffy-chin!
Whether it's from the sea
or the sky, bring it on!
I'll go nuts on 'em!
Boys!
It's battle time!
Yeah!
Damn it! We'll have to move while we can!
Get Camie back!
Yeah!
Camie! Pappagu! It's dangerous, so stay back!
Huh?
Stretch! You can do it, Luffy-chin!
Go! Go!
Come on, flying fish!
They're coming!
Right!
I found you, "Black Leg" Sanji!
Does he know you, Sanji?
That man ruined my life!
He really has it in for you.
Go to hell!
What did you do, Sanji?!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Tragedy!
The Truth Hidden Behind Duval's Mask"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Tragedy!
The Truth Hidden Behind Duval's Mask