Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil.
Boss!
"The Sun Pirates Split! Jinbe vs. Arlong!"
And so that was how the captain of the Sun Pirates - Fisher Tiger died.
The captain's death.
I think you all must know how painful it was...
...for the crew who were left behind.
What are you going?!
"Don't kill humans"?!
See what happens when you show mercy to them?!
Brother Tai was a fool!
Arlong-san!
Arlong-san!!
I won't forgive them at any cost!
Get ready, you bastards!
You're the Fishman...
So noisy!
You're Arlong, aren't you?
What brought you here? Why did you come back so...
NAVY HQ VICE ADMIRAL BORSALINO (FUTURE ADMIRAL YELLOW MONKEY)
...nonchalantly?
I'm gonna kill all the people who betrayed Big Brother Tai!
I'm gonna go to that island too!
So you're seeking revenge?
That's right! Fisher Tiger is dead!
You lowly creatures killed him!
Oh I see, he's dead.
But you need to come with me now.
Enraged by Fisher Tiger's death,
Arlong lashed out against humans and he was imprisoned.
He could've survived if he hadn't been refused a transfusion.
Fisher Tiger didn't have to die if there was Fishman's blood.
You humans killed him!
"Fisher Tiger, the Captain of the Sun Pirates,
Dies After Being Denied a Transfusion of Human Blood."
Not too far from the truth.
The cause of his death was related to humans.
Arlong told the Navy a lie...
The truth was far more tragic.
Tiger was betrayed by humans so he refused their blood because he had
hard feelings against them.
Plus, he was a slave.
If that became public, it would have stained Boss' honor.
That's why Arlong told a lie.
Captain Jinbe! There is an enemy ship!
Even without the Boss, there is no turning back now!
Prepare for action!
Don't kill anybody!
Yeah!
I start identifying myself as "First Son of the Sea" Jinbe
and as the captain of the Sun Pirates,
I did nothing but fight, day in and day out.
FISHMAN ISLAND - THE RYUGU PALACE
"I am writing this because..."
"...I thought that you two deserved to know the whole truth."
"The Sun Pirates captain - Jinbe."
My mind is set.
I guess Tiger had no choice but to live the way he did-jamon.
Now I understand what was going through his mind that day.
I'll be alright! I will not give in!
We shall live under the sun!
The day that humans and we understand each other will come!
Sign here to show that you want to relocate!
That's impossible, Otohime-sama! We just can't!
Humans refused to help Tiger-san who saved slaves
of all races without discrimination!
How could we understand them?!
Another day without any signature.
Mother-sama!
My sweet babies!
Mother-sama, are you okay?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
You look very tired.
You're my consolation!
But I'm fine!
Mother-sama!
I promise you...
...a great future!
Queen Otohime was working so hard day after day.
Rescuing humans from shipwrecks...
--Are you alright?! --It was pirates again.
--Help me... --Of course, we will help you.
Let's take them to the island!
Teaching the island children about the world above...
Like I taught you yesterday, this is an area with many trees called forest.
Forest? The Sea Forest?
Collecting signatures...
Wait!
It'll only take a minute!
However...
Queen Otohime!
Oh, you folk are the ones who signed it, aren't you?
We need to ask you a favor.
How many signatures have you got so far?
I have been doing this for 5 years
but on about 100 sheets of paper there are 10 signatures each.
Which means there are 1000 supporters.
The population of Fishman Island is 5 million so, to be honest, I'd prefer more...
Now, here is what we have to ask you.
We're afraid we want to withdraw our signatures - which amount to
about half of what you have.
What?
You haven't heard yet? The pirates who arrived the other day...
...committed a robbery in this town and got away from the island.
Queen Otohime...
Queen Otohime!
Oh kids! Do you want to hear about the world above?
Um... My mom wants the paper that I signed the other day!
My mom wants it!
What do you want?
I listened to you because you're the Queen...
But we have problems with humans...
We don't wanna...
...Hear your speech anymore.
We are tired of it.
Welcome home, Mother-sama!
I worked so hard today! I'm home, my angels!
I think I overdid it... Could you leave me alone for today?
You are all liars!!
Otohime-sama! You're on the air - the whole country heard it!
Shurrup!
Minister of the Left!
A-Are you drunk?!
I'm alright!
Shurrup! I'm not... I'm not drunk!
Yes, you are!
--What is that? --Is that Otohime-sama?
Everybody, listen!
We... We are capable of staying in the water forever if we want!
But in the ocean so broad,
and on the seafloor so dark,
we chose to live in this limited area... Do you know why?!
Otohime-sama...
Isn't it because there is some light and air?
But there is more light above ground, and the sky is higher!
Why do our children sneak out to see Sabaody Park?
There are more beautiful places than we can imagine in the world!
There is no place that we should not go...
You are just making convenient excuses to convince yourself
and giving everything up!
Have courage!
And go for what you truly want!
Your Majesty...
If humans stand in your way, let's face them together!
Then maybe we can make a difference for the future of the children on this island,
even just a small one!
I left my family behind on Fishman Island.
My kid and wife... I wonder how they are doing.
But you can go home someday.
We former slaves will get killed if they find us.
So whether we want it or not, we have to keep sailing for the rest of our lives.
I'm sorry! I didn't mean it.
NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Are you alright now?
It was awful.
I can't believe that you got beaten so bad.
Arlong, who was locked up in Impel down the other day, is nothing.
The most violent one is Jinbe!
He was unbelievably strong.
It's too dangerous to have him at large.
Hmm...
UNCLEAR JUSTICE
They want me to join the Seven Warlords?!
Your bounty was raised to 250 million berries!
They figured that you're gonna be an even bigger threat to the Government.
They finally got it!
Let's turn them down and gain more notoriety, Captain Jinbe!
No, I think I'm gonna take the offer.
What?!
Welcome back, Jinbe! I heard about the Seven Warlords.
If I join the Warlords, Aladdin and the others who don't want to be pirates...
...can live in this country without being chased under the amnesty of the Government.
More importantly, if I become a Warlord,
the Fishmen can get closer to the World Government.
For the good of the Queen who we've caused so much trouble.
Thank you.
She's not feeling well now.
And it could make the late Tiger's dream come true -
liberation and freedom for the Fishmen!
But at the same time, I think the amnesty would cause us some trouble too...
IMPEL DOWN
--Arlong-san! --Arlong!
Arlong-san!
--Arlong-san! --Arlong-san is back! He's back!
If you've got something to say, just say it!
You're gonna join the Warlords, huh? Brother Jinbe.
You're gonna be the Government's dog, aren't you?!
Don't you remember what Brother Tai said?
Don't let resentment and anger get the better of you!
You've gotten soft, Brother.
I know I'd be safe if I just followed you, but I refuse!
Big Brother is dead!
I'll lead the Arlong Pirates again!
I'll take my men with me.
So this is it.
Arlong, you fool...
If you really wanna stop me, you better kill me...
...right now!
A-Arlong-san!
If you can't do it, I'm free to go.
I represent the anger of the Fishmen!
How arrogant you are!
Jinbe-san!
That's great!
Stop it!
Just take him away now!
Arlong-san!
Don't worry, Jinbe.
You two grew up together and he's like a brother to you.
No wonder you couldn't just kill him even though you were justified.
Why can't that fool understand...
...what Brother Tai truly meant?!
Wherever he goes, as long as he engages in violence, the Navy won't leave him alone.
Or if that doesn't work, let's go and stop him ourselves...
...at any cost!
Well, well, we'll go our own way, just like we used to, Captain Jinbe!
Macro, you...
Let them go!
Bye!
Damn, he's like a monster...
Hachi, let's go.
The Sun Pirates split into three groups
and went separate ways.
Because of Jinbe's status as one of the Seven Warlords,
he is able to safely bring the former slave Fishmen home.
Just as Otohime's ideal future had seemed one step closer,
a drifting ship arrived.
On board is a Celestial Dragon who thinks of Fishmen as
nothing more than slaves!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Shaking Fishman Island! A Celestial Dragon Drifts In!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!