Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war against the New Fishman Pirates.
Luffy finally defeated Hody in a fierce fight
and thwarted his plot.
There's the Sunny!
Franky's there!
Looks like he's ready to go!
Here we go finally!
Setting Sail at Last!
Farewell, Fishman Island
Fishman Island, Coral Hill's Mermaid Cafe
Madame Sharley,
Luffy-chin and his friends are leaving the island.
Oh yeah? Why don't you go and send them off?
Okay!
Madame! Can we go, too?!
What? We'd need to close the cafe then.
Tourists will start coming back since that stupid Hody is gone.
So I need you to give your best for the cafe like before, girls.
You can count on us, Madame!
What? The crystal ball?
Don't worry. I won't need it again.
I will never again try to see the future.
Straw Hat destroying Fishman Island...
I never wanted to see such a horrible future.
I'll be so happy if my prevision is not accurate this time.
She is more afraid than anybody because she knows it was always accurate.
The future she saw may not happen soon.
It could be a year from now or more.
There is no reason to believe it wasn't accurate.
But, Madame, Luffy-chin and his friends would never do such...
Camie!
Forgive me for suspecting your friends.
I know what you want to say. I can trust the Straw Hat boy, right?
Uh-huh!
These are some gifts! Take them!
Yeah, thanks!
Luffy-sama and everybody, are you really going to leave now?!
We just became friends! Stay here at least one more day!
No! A week!
No! Just one more year!
You've been crying since the first time we met, Wimpyhoshi!
I-I am sorry!
I will stop being a crybaby!
I never thought the day like this would come!
The Mermaid Princess of Fishman Island
who I've dreamed about is crying as we're leaving!
Sanji-kun!
I wanna live here for a year or two!
Yes, me too!
I sing about a dream life on Fishman Island on my latest single!
When you wake up in the morning you say "Good mor-ningyo (Mermaid)!"
--In the cafe at the night, you say "Good eve-ningyo!" --Oh, my Mermaids!
That's a good idea!
Why don't you stay here, Nosebleed-kun?
What did you just call me, Mosshead?!
Who are you calling Mosshead, you fool?!
Your Majesty.
We have to tell them.
About the Tamate Box that they gave to Big Mom.
When someone opens it, there will be a huge explosion!
But, look at that!
We're doomed! One of the Four Emperors wants to kill us!
We're gonna go to the New World just to die!
Do you think she'll forgive us
if we send all the treasures that we get from now on?!
We cannot tell them that they already sent her a bomb!
But those explosives are 10 years old.
Maybe they won't explode, Minister of the Right.
Your Majesty, you are so positive!
Yes, the Ryugu Palace is very humid
and we don't even know if Big Mom is going to open it herself!
Then let's just hope for their safety!
What are you two whispering about?
What is this?
It's a Log Pose for the New World. Take it with you.
I cannot believe you were going to go there with a single-needle one!
Oh, what's that?
A new Log Pose? Wow, that's cool!
There are 3 needles. Why?
Look at the Log Pose that you have been using.
It's still moving a little bit! I thought it gathered enough logs already.
It did. And from now on, it would take only half a day to record logs.
On the first half of the Grand Line,
you let the Log Pose record the magnetic waves of the next island
and navigated your ship as it told you.
But on the second half of
the Grand Line, on top of the sea current and the climate,
there are some islands that change their
magnetic waves, the only thing you can normally count on.
And for some islands, the magnetic waves just disappear.
What?! Then we can't reach those islands!
If you only have one needle, you will get lost.
But what if you have 3 needles?
One of them is moving just like the old one but...
...the other two look settled.
They each record the magnetic waves from different islands.
That means you can choose whichever your gut tells you and advance.
Whether you live or die hangs on that point.
A good navigator can tell
which way is safer to go
by looking at slight movements of the needles.
What it basically tells you is the wilder the needle moves,
the more dangerous the island is!
Something is happening on the island
that is causing the change in its magnetic waves.
What?! I don't like this! I'd rather not know about it!
You'll see if it's dangerous?!
No way! Break that Log Pose!
Why? You have to navigate safely in order to stay alive.
Let's see.
D-Dammit!
No!
The one in the middle is wobbling a lot! That must be where the party is!
H-H-He was listening!
Luffy! You stay quiet!
I'll choose which way to go from now on!
No way! I'm the captain!
Please Captain! Listen to what the navigator has to say!
Nami-san's so cute when she gets frightened!
So cute! So cute...
The B-side of the single is "The Requiem for Us"!
All right, guys!
We're ready to go!
Den-san taught me how to ascend too!
Shall we go?
Okay!
Let's go!
Luffy-chin!
Straw!
I'm gonna help with repairing the factory! Are you gonna be okay without a guide?
We're fine! We had a lot of fun on our way here!
Yeah, he's right! We don't need a guide!
Man's journey always ends up in hell!
Yeah, yeah! We want a war, you bastard!
How desperate.
Everybody! Come visit someday!
I'll come back!
You're the "All Blue" of my heart!
What a cheap dream.
All I want to say is "Thank you"!
I will pray for your safe trip!
Uh-huh!
Next time we see you, we will lead the strongest army on the seafloor!
Ooh mambo!
He's right!
We will become greater than the Great Knight Neptune-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do!
Can't wait!
Um, where is he?
There you are!
Jinbe!
All right! Spread the sail!
Let's set sail!
Straw Hat!
See you, Fishman Island!
Alright, here we go!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
Come to eat sweets and meat anytime!
I like humans now!
Raccoon dogs and robots too!
Like I give a damn, you jerk!
Huh? Oh? What about bones?
Take care, Luffy-chin and everybody!
Come to eat octopus balls again!
You guys! I love you all!
1, 2, 3!
We like bones too!
Thank you for your concern!
Princess-sama!
Luffy-sama!
Wimpyhoshi!
Shirahoshi-chan!
If I can see you again someday,
I promise I won't be a crybaby!
Take me out for a fun stroll again!
A stroll? Do you wanna go to your mother's grave again?
No. I want to go somewhere further next time!
I want to go to a real forest above ground!
Oh yeah, you've never been out of the sea, have you?
Okay, fine!
I'll take you there next time!
Will you promise?
Yeah, trust me!
I promise!
Hey, Luffy! We have to help you keep that promise.
Luffy-san, a promise is something you have to keep at any cost.
Then, Shirahoshi, I promise you too!
Nami-chin-sama!
Me too!
Okay, me too!
Me too, of course!
We all promise her so...
...We won't let her down!
We promise!
E-Everybody!
So don't cry anymore!
Okay!
Do not ever forget their kindness.
Of course!
Hey, Dad, Dad!
Buy me a straw hat! I wanna pretend I'm the hero!
What? They only sell it above ground!
Buy one above ground then!
No way!
There are horrible humans who hate Fishmen above...
What?
Oh, I mean, I heard some of them are like that...
Of course, there are good and strong humans like Straw Hat, too.
Oh, Boss Jinbe! You came at the right time!
I heard what you were talking about.
I will tell a merchant to get his hands on some of those.
Really?!
Yes, what you want is that hero's hat, right?
Uh-huh!
I had a wonderful time!
The Mermaid Paradise!
Now everybody, pull yourself together!
There is no safe place once we sail out!
We have to pass though the dark water again.
What is that, Franky?
I'm gonna make the ship float with buoyant square logs of hollow Banyan.
I can adjust the speed by how many I put out.
What's the matter, Luffy?
If we ascend here,
we'll be at the sea where Shanks is!
I wanna see him!
In that case...
...I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Come bring it back to me someday!
Once you've become a great pirate!
There is one thing that makes me wanna stay.
That is my desire to see you fulfill your dream.
But I'm sure that you can do it!
Because you're my brother!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
Rise to the top!
Luffy-san! Do you know what they call the second half of the Grand Line?
People call the final sea beyond the Red Line by another name.
"The New World."
It's the sea where pirates who will open the way to the next generation gather.
The pirate who conquers the sea will become the Pirate King!
Once we pass through this deep sea,
we'll get to the ultimate sea!
Finally! I'll cut everything away!
Wait for me, Laboon! One more half to go!
Count on me! I'll navigate you anywhere you want!
That's right! The Sunny can do it!
I'll heal you no matter how wounded you are!
You'll never go hungry while I'm here!
You've got the warrior of the sea here too!
Let's go!
Guys!
To the New World!
Yeah!
The Straw Hats depart Fishman Island and rise up out of the sea.
But it's the harshest ocean of the Grand Line.
On the voyage up to the New World...
...they come across hardship after hardship.
As the crew is tossed about...
...by a killer underwater whirlpool...
...an unimaginable sight appears before them.
Next time, on One Piece:
"To the New World!
Heading for the Ultimate Sea"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
To the New World!
Heading for the Ultimate Sea