Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and in order to move on to the next stage,
the New World, they boarded the newly coated Sunny,
setting sail for Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
Okay, that's good!
That's the extra-vehicular Flutter Kick Coating!
An extra-vehicular diving suit!
Wait! You have to attach the safety rope!
Rocket Launcher!
Another arm!
Guard Point!
Are you guys okay?
Mil Fleurs:
Gigantesco Mano!
They did great.
Alright, it's my turn!
Lost in the Deep Sea
The Straw Hats Get Separated
Gear 3,
Armament: Hardening!
What is that?!
It wasn't like that before!
I feel weak because of the sea!
Damn that octopus!
Is it trying to stop him?
Blue Walk!
Whoa, Sanji-san got out of the bubble!
That's really fast! He's like a Fishman! That's so cool!
I've been running and running
in order to get away from those hideous people for two years.
Compared to them,
this monster is nothing.
It actually looks rather cute to me.
Diable Jambe,
Bien Cuit:
Grill Shoot!
I need to breathe!
Three-Sword Style Secret Art:
Crossing the Six Paths!
The demon that rules the realm of water? So weak!
I feel grateful when I think about it.
I got to fight every single day
for the past two years.
To top him...
I'm still gonna get stronger!
That was great...
I-I couldn't see his movement!
He shouldn't have done it!
Did you say something, No. 7?
I'll kill you!
Bring it on!
Hey hey, Zoro! Sanji!
You can't cut his arms!
Gum-Gum...
Elephant Gun!
He blew it away!
He's gotten so much stronger!
Even while he's in the sea...
Hey! Something is in there!
A shark?
Isn't that shark wearing something?
It's fairly big.
What is it?
Maybe it's thanking us for the help?
What a polite shark.
What?
We're being drawn into the sea current!
Luffy, let's go back to Sunny!
Yeah!
They've been swept away by the downward current!
Oh no! Follow them!
We have to stay together!
Okay!
I don't wanna die here!
You've got to be kidding me!
You're still here?
You're too calm!
My eyes are spinning!
But I don't have eyes!
Keep the yard level! Hard to port!
We're gonna crash into the continental shelf!
I got it!
Don't lose your concentration, or the ship will wreck!
What?!
Don't get thrown off!
Stay in the center of the current!
Alright!
It's really fast!
This is fun!
Usopp!
Oh, ow, ow, ow!
I'm alive!
What? Why are you all so glum?
Oh I know! You guys
can't do anything without me...
It's so cold here!
We can't find Luffy and the other two.
We got separated.
What?!
I hope they haven't been shredded to pieces by the monster.
Your imagination is terrifying...
It's too dark—I wanna look for them
but I can't see anything!
I'm no good with darkness. I feel something, don't you?
We probably submerged around 7,000 meters.
Even the Shark Submerge
can't take the pressure this deep.
Are we near Fishman Island?
Maybe they got there already!
Camie-chan said it's located
at 10,000 meters below sea level.
We have to submerge 3,000 meters more?!
All they have is a small bubble.
Even if they're alive,
there isn't enough air so it's dangerous!
That's why I told them to attach the safety rope!
We won't accomplish anything standing around like this.
Let's look for them.
I now have a search light.
What?!
Is it your eyes?!
Franky...
Nipple Lights!
Why there?!
Oh?
Th-That's huge!
Terrifying!
No way...
That's...
Let's get away!
Just look all around.
They must be looking for us too.
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Where did you go?
Come back!
Luffy-san! Zoro-san! Sanji-san!
Dammit!
In this vast, submerged expanse,
the Sunny Eyes don't help that much.
We're stuck...
The darkness is stirring up our anxiety.
In fact, we're not getting anywhere.
What should we do?
We can't stop the ship
so try not to overlook anything.
There should be some trace of them.
Let's find them.
Yeah.
Oh, it's a jellyfish!
There's a massive jellyfish above us!
That's huge! You're right!
They're twinkling!
Like stars in the night!
How beautiful!
Oh, a tentacle!
D-Do you wanna be my friend?
Don't touch it, Chopper!
It's probably venomous!
Oh no! A little...
Coup de Burst!
Wh-What?!
The jellyfish got eaten!
Oh, we lost some air.
Better than getting eaten!
Coup de Burst is a weapon
that shoots a fair amount of air.
But since we're in the water,
we only have a limited amount of air.
So when we shoot the air out, the bubble shrinks!
I see. But it makes me nervous to see the bubble shrinking.
That fish that got bitten turned upside down!
So they contain a neurotoxin as I thought.
The deep sea's scary! It's dark too...
There are a lot of fish
with white eyes... It's creepy here!
Since the deep sea is always dark,
there are many creatures with rudimentary eyes.
So they can't see well.
Fools! See this? Come here!
But there are some with developed eyes too.
What's that?
How can I see things without eyes?
Do you people wanna know why?
The answer is... Tum, tum, tum, tum, tum...
a secret!
Are you talking to yourself?
No problem.
I'm used to being lonely.
Hey! Stop fooling around and look for them!
Why did I get hit?
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji! Where are you?!
Oh?
This rope must be...
Everyone.
Have you seen that pirate guy?
Oh yeah, he's still here!
I totally forgot about him.
Where did he go?
I haven't seen him since we got this deep.
Maybe he got thrown off during the downward pull.
That could be it!
His hands and legs were tied up
so he couldn't hold on to anything.
Well but...
he untied himself. See?
Th-Then, he's somewhere on the ship? Where is he?
He's got to be hiding somewhere...
What?!
Oh no...
I'll sneak into the girls' room—
if that's what you want, honey.
Damn! We have enough problems already
but now we have to look out for him too.
Who cares!
He's not that strong anyway.
This is great.
Those formidable three who were fighting
against the Kraken went missing.
There's no way they could have
survived after getting lost
with just those bubbles to protect them.
It's a shame that I couldn't kill Straw Hat
but I can prove that he's dead
by killing his crewmates and taking their heads.
But don't rush, Caribou!
You can't rush!
If I kill them here,
there's no one else to sail the ship.
They navigate the ship pretty well.
As soon as you get to Fishman Island,
you all will be dead!
Here he is!
Oh no! Shoot! Dammit!
Now he can't get away.
How did he get in there?
We weren't paying attention.
If he wasn't so stupid, we could be in danger now.
His body wasn't taking form.
It has melted like mud.
Like mud?
Yeah, I'm sure it's a Devil Fruit power.
He must've eaten a Logia-type fruit.
He was only pretending to be caught.
Hey, get me out of here, mister!
Mister in swimshorts!
I'll become your servant!
What's the matter, Chopper?
I don't know.
I feel hot all of the sudden.
I can't stand the heat.
It's hot! What happened?
Wh-What's this? Smoke?
It's blocking our view forward!
Smoke from the sea floor? Why?
It's...
It could be...
Hydrothermal deposits!
A volcanic area in the sea!
What?!
Look, you can see that
there were volcanic eruptions here!
Let's get away from here!
If it erupts, we're gonna die!
It's hot... It's hot...
Something's after us!
Carnivorous Tubeworms!
We have no choice.
A little Coup de Burst!
Faceless Crabs!
I don't even know what they are!
A little Coup de Burst!
The deep sea's scary!
Luffy and the others can't survive here.
I'm starting to get sad.
I finally got to see him after two years...
Cut it out!
They're not gonna die so easily!
I used Coup de Burst little by little
but we lost so much air.
What is that?! It's so bright!
Is that Fishman Island?
Do you think Luffy and the others are there?
We haven't submerged another 3,000 meters yet.
"WHO-ARE-YOU?"
Hey! What are you sending the flashing signals with?!
Do you see anything?
No, it's still too bright.
Oh no!
It's an angler! He tricked us!
We were fooled by the deep-sea hunter!
That was close!
We're totally trapped!
Can we get away?
What is it this time?!
I-Is it a human?
What the hell is it?!
A monster in the sea that looks like a man...
It's a Sea Spirit!
It's gonna capsize the ship!
That?!
Hey, Ankoro! You can't do that!
Don't eat ships!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Captain Vander Decken-sama won't like this!
D-Did it help us?
Let's go! We have to get away anyway!
It's a monster too!
What the hell is that?!
The infamous ghost ship,
the Flying Dutchman, emerges from the dark.
But suddenly, a submarine volcano erupts,
creating yet more danger.
Evading falling rocks,
they make it to the ocean floor,
where a scenery not expected in the deep sea awaits them.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Undersea Volcanic Eruption!
Drifting to Fishman Island"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Undersea Volcanic Eruption!
Drifting to Fishman Island