This is a battle
to claim the One Piece,
the one great treasure left behind by
the legendary Pirate King, Gol D. Roger.
Countless pirates have raised their flags
and set sail for the Grand Line.
This is the Great Pirate Era.
From these intrepid crews have risen
pirates with immense power,
the most feared of whom are those
with the supernatural powers...
...granted by eating
a Devil Fruit:
The Devil Fruit users.
Among them is the boy who ate the Gum-Gum fruit
and aspires to be the next Pirate King: Monkey D. Luffy.
He is the captain
of the Straw Hat Pirates.
An absolutely essential member
of a crew like this is a doctor.
At the moment, however,
this ship does not have one.
Why?
Because this is
the story of an encounter...
Daily... training...
This is the best way
to become a great swordsman.
Well then...
All right! Lemme try catching a Sea King
or something with this!
What?! Hey, Luffy,
where’d you find that thing?!
It was just lying
over there.
Hey, hey, Captain!
I can make you whatever you want,
if you just ask me.
I’m the shipwright
after all.
Franky!
No, no matter how you look at it,
you can’t catch a Sea King...
If you need to catch something,
shouldn’t you leave it to me, the great sniper, Usopp-sama?
Hey, you guys! Do you know
what happened to my weights?
Hey, those
are mine, dammit!
Oh, crap! Zoro’s mad!
Straw Hat!
Hurry up and throw it away!
Destroy the evidence!
Good idea! Here, catch!
You’re too slow!
Give it back, dammit!
They sure are noisy.
Nami-swan!
Robin-chwan!
Would you like to taste this
afternoon’s relaxing snack, petits fours?
Thank you.
My pride as the ship’s cook,
as well as my heart and soul, went into making this.
Please enjoy...
Faint, blushing cheeks...
wavering eyes...
This is the look
of a maiden in love!
Who could those eyes be
looking at? Could it be...
me?!
The air has changed...
A huge gust
of wind is coming.
Hurry, haul in the sails!
Shift our heading southward!
Franky! Prepare the cola barrels!
We’ll blast away with a Burst!
Sure! Leave it to me!
Everyone ready?!
Yeah!
Let’s go!
Coup de Burst!
The power of the Burst
is as awesome as always!
But what’s going on?
Look, I’m not questioning
Nami’s navigation skills, but...
Why’d we change our
course all of a sudden?
What is that?!
A cyclone!
It’s right where our ship
was headed a minute ago!
If we’d stayed on course
we’d have run straight into it!
They say that cyclones in the Grand Line
are impossible to predict...
that they come
without warning...
I’d expect no less
from you, Nami.
Everyone, this is bad!
Come quickly!
Nami-chan has
a terrible fever!
What?! A fever?
That’s bad!
Ith Nami-than
going to be awlight?
Ith thhe, Wobin-tan?
She’ll recover if she
eats some meat! Meat! Meat!
You idiot! In times like this,
you need some refreshing cola!
Can’t you two be
a little more concerned?!
Be quiet!
Sorry...
So high... Her
temperature’s 41 degrees!
Is that bad?
Dunno... I’ve never
been sick before.
Me neither.
What’s going on, Robin?
Well, archeology
is my specialty, not medicine...
But I know that this kind of
temperature isn’t normal.
We should get her
to a doctor as soon as possible.
A doctor?
We don’t have one on this ship.
Yeah, a ship doctor
would be useful.
This could be
a fatal disease!
Nami’s gonna die?!
Nami-dan, pweade do’t die!
Be quiet!
Full speed toward
the nearest doctor!
We’re gonna save Nami!
Episode of Chopper +
The Miraculous Cherry Blossoms, Blooming in Winter
A pirate ship?
Get lost, damn pirates!
This ain’t no place for you!
Hurry up and get out of here!
One of our crewmates is sick.
We’re looking for a doctor.
Please let us come on land.
Think we’d fall for that?!
You’re just a bunch
of dirty pirates!
What’s going on here?
What do we care
if you die or not?
Dalton-san. It’s pirates.
Then can you bring
the doctor here? Please!
She’s suffering from
a serious illness! Please help her!
Quit screwing around!
Why, you...
Don’t you dare...
Straw Hat!
Hey! What if you’d killed him?!
He was unarmed!
Well, I just...
I’m begging you.
Luffy, you...!
Please call a doctor.
Please, help my friend!
I’ll take you
to our village.
Follow me.
Thank you.
This place sure is cold!
The climate on the Grand Line varies
from island to island.
This must be a Winter Island.
A Winter Island?
So that’s why there’s so much snow.
I love the white snow!
We do have summers on this island,
but the snow never melts.
Living in a kingdom
of snow is harsh,
but we can’t just
leave our homeland.
I might be a bit late in introducing myself,
but my name is Dalton.
I’m the island’s protector.
I apologize
for the hostile welcome.
Don’t worry about it.
We’re pirates;
we’re used to it.
But, you there. I’m sure I saw you
get hit by that bullet earlier...
Oh, guns don’t work on me.
This guy ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
He’s a rubber-man.
I see. You, too,
have eaten a Devil Fruit.
But despite the abilities
you might gain by doing so,
you must never let yourself
become an actual Devil!
What?
Oh, no. I wasn’t referring
to you people.
This island had—
Oh, a reindeer!
A reindeer?!
A raccoon dog?
A mole?
A cuckoo?
Wrong!
Oh, now that I look at it,
that’s gotta be a stuffed deer!
Yeah, now that
you mention it...
If it were anything else,
it’d be a monster!
Monster?!
It talked!
I’m dead.
That’s the Hiking Bear.
It’s harmless.
Just mind your manners.
I’m freezing...
I guess I’ll go take a bath.
This is our village, Bighorn.
First, why don’t you come
to my house?
Are you sure, Dalton-san?
They’re pirates, you know!
They mean us no harm.
They just happened to drift by here.
We can trust them.
Oh, okay.
I’ll leave it to you.
Her temperature is 42 degrees?!
Yes... Please hurry and call a doctor!
This village has one, right?!
We’ve only got one doctor
on this island. A witch.
Witch?
You see the mountains outside
the window, right?
Yeah... Umm...
Hey!
This is Hyper Snowman-san!
This is the Snow Monster Shirora!
Yeah, yeah, yay!
I’m gonna kick
the crap out of you two!
What’s wrong?
It’s the Hiking Bear!
Deep bow.
Hey.
At the top of the highest mountain
lies a castle.
Right now, it’s a castle
without a king.
A castle?
The only doctor on this island,
whom people call a witch,
Doctor Kureha,
lives there alone.
What? Then please
call her down here now!
I’d like to, but we have
no way to contact her.
Huh?
There used to be a ropeway to the castle,
but it was taken down.
Yet she still calls
herself a doctor?!
What kind of person is she?
She’s definitely skilled,
but she is a rather eccentric old lady.
She’s close to
one hundred forty years old.
Really? Is she all right?
How do people around here
deal with diseases and injuries?
She comes down from
the mountain every now and then.
She looks for patients,
treats them,
and takes whatever she wants
from their houses as payment.
She doesn’t sound like
a very nice lady.
Hey, hey.
She’s almost like a pirate.
But how does that old lady get down
from the mountain?
This is just a rumor,
but people say they’ve seen her silhouetted by the moon,
flying down in a sleigh.
That’s why they
call her a witch.
A... A witch
who flies through the sky?
Other people claim they’ve seen her
with a strange creature unlike anything they’ve seen before.
The... The Abominable Snow Man?!
I knew he existed...
It’s the Abominable Snow Man!
Damn it.
It’s bizarre for this island
to have just one doctor.
She must be dangerous to be
with the Abominable Snow Man.
Aah! I’ve got the
”I-Shouldn’t-Go-To-The-Mountain” sickness!
And an old
lady at that!
Hey! What
are you doing?!
Hey, Nami! Nami!
Can you hear me?
Oh, she’s awake!
We’ve gotta climb the mountain to get to the doctor,
so we’re climbing the mountain.
Don’t be so reckless!
What’re you gonna do with Nami-san?!
It’s fine. I’ll carry her.
No, that’s gonna
be too dangerous!
Why? It’s best to get her there
as soon as possible, right?
We don’t know when that doctor
will be coming down anyway...
Nami-san’s condition
is too serious!
Nami-san?
Nami?
I’m counting on you!
That’s what
I wanted to hear!
Leave it to me!
You guys are crazy.
Right! I’ll go too!
Then so will I.
No, we’ve gotta hurry.
It’s better if just
a few of us go.
Right!
Off you go, you two!
I’ll wait here with Robin!
I won’t stop you
if you’re serious about this,
but you might run into
a Lapin herd on the way.
They’re brutal,
flesh-eating rabbits.
If you get attacked by a herd of them,
you won’t survive it.
Rabbits?
That’s no problem, right?
Sure.
I’ll just kick ‘em!
Then let’s get going!
Before Nami dies!
Don’t say such ominous things,
you damn bastard!
Will they be all right?
As long as it’s those two.
I hope they can get Nami
all the way there...
There’s no point standing
out here and worrying.
Please, come inside.
Nah. I want to stay outside.
As do I.
I see.
In that case,
I will keep you company.
We had them once,
you know.
Huh?
Doctors.
There was a time when our country was renowned
for its medical knowledge.
But half a year ago,
the country fell...
because of a pirate attack.
We were attacked
by Blackbeard and his crew.
Against their terrifying power,
the kingdom was crushed.
So that’s why you
were so hostile toward us.
But many think it made
the country a better place.
There’s no way
that could be! How?!
Because the kingdom
was under tyranny!
We were known as a country
of advanced medical science,
but only twenty doctors
were allowed to stay in the country.
The rest had been culled in the Doctor Hunt
and banished from the country.
Why would they do that?
To give the king complete control
over the country’s medical facilities!
With no other doctors, the citizens
were forced to plead the king for help.
Holding every sick person
in the kingdom hostage...
It was criminal!
The king’s name
was Wapol.
He had eaten the Chomp-Chomp Fruit
and gained the power to devour anything.
He was absolutely
the worst kind of king!
But that guy was killed
by the pirates, wasn’t he?
In that case...
Once Wapol realized
the strength of the pirates,
he took the doctors
and was the first to flee the kingdom!
He didn’t even try
to fight back.
He simply abandoned
the entire kingdom!
How awful.
Then the “witch”
who lives in that castle...
Doctor Kureha is the only doctor
who escaped the Doctor Hunt.
Doktorin!
Pirates have landed!
They might come here, too...
Indeed. The ports are crawling
with pirate ships.
Seems like this is gonna be
a busy day, Chopper.
Crawling with them?
H-How can this be?!
We’ve gotta warn the village!
Right!
Don’t let them set foot on land!
We’ve gotta stop them
any way we can!
What?
Awesome!
I can’t just sit around here!
We’ve reached
the Drum Kingdom, Bro-chan!
Covered in snow,
as always!
It’s gotten colder...
The wind picked up.
Why’re you barefoot anyway?
It hurts just
to look at you.
This is just
my stylus!
What do you mean “stylus”?
Don’t you mean “style”?
Doesn’t really matter, does it?
Yes it does!
They mean completely different things.
What’s “stylus” then?
You’re the one who said it!
Besides...
these things are
really starting to annoy me!
What was
with that guy?
What was that ship?
We’re real lucky here!
I’m in super
condition this week!
Why’d I have to
come along?
That’s only because
you fell asleep in here!
Besides, didn’t you say you
were gonna take a bath?
I got lost.
On the ship?!
I don’t know how
to find anything on that ship.
Why, you! You got a problem
with my design?!
What’s going on?!
Are they picking
a fight with us?!
White bears?
Nah, they’re rabbits.
But there sure are
a lot of ‘em...
Listen up, Luffy.
You mustn’t attack these guys, no matter what!
Why?
The shock from your punches
will hurt Nami-san too!
If you do that,
she really will die!
I-I got it!
I won’t fight!
It jumped at us!
How’d it move so fast?!
Flanc Shot!
I can’t kick properly
in all this snow...
What?
They’re all coming at once!
Run into the forest!
All these trees
ought to slow ‘em down!
Or not...
Why, you...!
Stop!
Shot!
Moron!
Just leave this to me!
Sorry!
We’ve gotta shake ‘em off!
If we try to fight all these guys,
we’ll be here all day!
Why, you...!
You bastard!
You guys! You have a long way to go
before you can really give us a fight!
Three-Sword Style:
Dragon Twister!
Coup de Vent!
Strong Right!
A-Amazing...
Who are these guys?
Hey!
You all right?
P-Pretty much...
You guys saved us...
Who are they?
They’re causing quite a lot of trouble.
Still, it’s okay.
They’re nothing compared
to Wapol-sama.
Besides, we’ve got a powerful ally.
We’ve got Wapol-sama’s older brother,
Mushroo-sama.
This is quite
an impressive ship.
I gotta fix it later.
Hey. What’re you doing?
I found a rather interesting
vehicle here...
What’re those?
How do you use them?
As always, you eat
some pretty awful stuff.
Don’t say that, Bro-chan...
You damn maroon!
I told you to call me “Big Brother”!
Sorry, Bro-chan,
but you know...
What?
Even though I finally
freed you and all,
are we really gonna
rebuild the kingdom?
Who the hell do
you think I am?
There’s nothing the great
Mushroo-sama can’t do!
Just as I’d expect
from you, Bro-chan!
Still, I gotta say, it’s a shame that Blackbeard guy left.
I wanted to beat him myself.
I want to have a bit of fun
for myself too...
Wapol-sama! This is awful!
What’s up?
Doctor Kureha has taken up residence
in Drum Castle!
What’s that?!
That ancient hag
is living in my castle?!
In that case, how ‘bout we shoot her down
to teach her a lesson?
Using these.
But the castle
is too far away...
Just as I’d expect
from you, Bro-chan!
That’s perfect for striking
a bit of fear into the citizens!
Very well!
Let’s chomp on!
Yes, Sir!
You damn maroon!
I told you to call me
”Big Brother”!
After all this time?
Sorry, Bro-chan!
As long as you get it, it’s fine.
It’s terrible! Everybody! Run!
He’s... They’ve returned!
They’re coming
here right now!
Him?!
You can’t mean...?!
It’s Wapol!
Everybody! Run away!
Wapol?!
They’re not chasing us...
No way...
We’ve gotta
get away, Luffy!
G-Get away? Where to?
Anywhere will do!
Just somewhere far away!
It’s an avalanche!
Is this...?
Everyone! We’ve got
to get out of the village! Hurry!
The village
is gonna be buried!
Hey! You two...
Huh?
Listen up, Luffy! Your first priority is Nami-san!
Your second is Nami-san!
Third and fourth: Nami-san!
Fifth is also Nami-san!
Protect her even if
it kills you!
Understood!
But how?
Over there!
Get on top of that cliff!
We gotta get as high as possible!
Right!
Here it comes!
We made it!
We’re not high enough!
That was close!
We’re safe...
But if this keeps up,
we’ll end up at the bottom of the mountain!
You’re kidding!
After getting all the way up here...
Oh, crap!
It’s a boulder!
We’re gonna crash!
No way!
Ladies must be treated
with delicate care.
Sanji!
We’re done for!
Over here!
What a sight to behold!
Right, let’s march on!
Yes, Sir!
All troops, advance!
I’ll definitely get you there!
Don’t die, you two!
Damn...
That was a little too close.
What kind of guy drives straight
into an avalanche?!
The coastline is
in that direction, right?
What? We’ve been climbing higher
into the mountains!
None of this would have happened
if you hadn’t suggested we “take this for a little ride”!
That doesn’t mean that you
had to drive it so carelessly!
We’ve completely lost track
of where we are!
Whatever. Let’s just look for the village
that Luffy and the others went to.
It’ll be easy to get to
the ship from there.
Guess you’re right.
Looks like I was carried
a fair distance.
Where am I?
Here...
I can’t...
see the top.
Julie! Rosario!
Where are you?!
Please, answer!
How could he?!
Delicious!
The houses in this village
taste absolutely fantastic!
Ah, this is boring!
Oh! What’s up, Bro-chan?
You damn maroon!
I keep telling you to call me “Big Brother”!
Sorry.
I won’t call you that any more.
This is such a letdown.
I thought that something more impressive would happen.
We only buried one village!
In that case, Bro-chan...
How about we try using it?
We’ll take that device we were gonna use on Blackbeard
and launch it at the citizens!
Oh no! They’re gonna turn it
on the citizens?!
Just look at
those hateful eyes.
It’d be better to wipe out everyone who might defy
the king of this country!
Not a bad idea at all.
Launching the bomb I’ve been carrying in here
might be pretty fun too.
Right, Bro-chan?
But how’re we gonna launch it?
We’ve only got one shot.
And I doubt those
cannons will do the job...
Well... Ah, I know!
There’s a huge cannon
up in the castle.
And while we’re at it,
the old hag is up there too. So it’s perfect!
I got you.
Right, men! We’re gonna resume
our advance on the castle!
Yeah!
Everyone, prepare yourselves!
Man, you saved me!
I’m so glad to be alive!
Thanks, Robin.
Is it just me,
or is my face swollen?
It’s frostbite.
Really?
Yes.
So, you’re safe?
Oh, Dalton.
I see you’re safe too.
You’re...
Oh, Usopp-kun.
Hey, what’s
with the long pause?!
It’s the village!
Yay!
Mom!
Thank goodness!
What’s going on?
There sure are a lot
of people gathered here...
Hey, what’s happening?
The Twenty Doctors
have appeared!
Huh? Who’re they?
The doctors who surrendered
to Wapol’s authority.
But what are they
doing here?
Please! We’ve come to tell you
something important!
Don’t mess with us!
That’s right!
No way we’d trust you guys!
Just hurry back
to that damn Wapol!
We have no place
to return to.
We escaped from Wapol.
We were prepared to die trying!
We are doctors,
after all!
Even though we had to
bow to his might,
we only continued our work
for the sake of the people!
It was because a certain quack doctor
told us to never give up.
This foolish man told us...
that all was not lost.
Everyone, please let us speak.
We have no time to waste.
Wapol intends to launch Mushroo’s
Spore Bomb from the castle...
and cover the entire island
in poison gas!
What?!
Did you say Mushroo?!
Poison?!
Oh, no! Luffy and the others
are in trouble!
Wait, so are we!
We’ve gotta do something!
We’ve no choice but to run!
This island is done for!
No! We’re gonna stop them,
one way or another!
Even if it costs us our lives!
Dalton-san...
But we don’t have
any decent weapons...
Besides, how are we gonna
get to the castle?
What are you doing here,
Twenty Doctors?
You betrayed us,
didn’t you?!
Can we climb
the mountain with that?
Yeah.
Why, you...
Sure-Kill Gunpowder Star!
Clutch!
Please wait, you three!
If you must go,
then take this with you!
I’m sure it’ll
be useful!
What’s that?
It’s an antidote.
It’s made from ingredients that are unavailable on this island,
so there’s only a small amount...
but you may have it.
It’s the result of our
continued research and hard work.
I understand.
Thank you.
Doctor... Doctor... Doctor!
Sanji!
That was close!
Hang in there...
We’re almost there!
Wapol-sama,
is this really okay?
If you use
the Spore Bomb—
You don’t get it,
do you?
Why do you think I went out of my way
to save my brother?
Wasn’t it to stop Blackbeard?
Well, that too, but this country needs
to be ruled by striking fear into the people.
For that, my brother
is the perfect choice.
Can’t this damn hippo
run any faster?!
That’s it! Get going!
Go, go!
I’m glad we have
that stupid brother of mine...
He’s acting exactly the way
I hoped he would.
If I make everyone beg for the antidote,
I can easily control the population.
Whether they opposed me
or supported me before.
What?!
They’re not here anymore?
That’s right. Two of them left,
carrying the sick one with them,
and then the other two left,
just a little while ago.
Where were they going?
Up there.
The mountain?
Will they really
be all right up there?
Hey.
Yeah.
Oh, that’s right! You two had better
run away as soon as possible!
Something terrible
is about to— Huh?
Don’t you die, now!
Hang on for just
a little longer!
What a beautiful... castle.
D-Doctor...
This guy’s got
frostbite all over.
This one’s
covered in blood.
Six broken ribs
and a damaged spine...
Mind if I treat him?
Sure, do whatever you want,
Chopper.
Anyway, the worst
case is this girl...
She’s on the verge of death.
What?
You got something to say?
They’re my friends...
Friends?
What... is that?
Ya happy?
Your fever’s starting
to go down, girl.
38 degrees...
We’re getting there...
Who are you?
I’m a doctor.
Name’s Doctor Kureha.
Call me Doktorin.
Doctor?
Then, were you the one who...
You wanna know the secret
behind my youth?
No, I wasn’t asking
about that...
I just treated you, ‘s all.
It was that youngster
who carried you all the way here.
Oh, how are
the two of them doing?
They’re sleeping in the next room.
They sure are a tough pair.
I see.
You sleep, too.
You’re not completely healed yet.
Thank you.
But my fever’s gone, so...
Take a look.
What’s this?
This is the culprit.
You were bitten by a Keschia bug.
They call it
the Five-Day Illness.
Once its saliva
enters your body,
you’re subjected to hellish suffering
for five days.
Judging by the rash,
I’d say you were bitten
about three days ago.
Of course, after five days,
you wouldn’t have suffered any more.
Huh?
If those five days had passed
without treatment,
you’d be dead.
You understand now?
If you do, then you should
get back to sleep.
At the very least, you have to
stay here for two more days.
Um, can I ask you
one more question?
How long does it take
for a Log to set on this island?
A Log?
Oh, that thing
sailors use?
Why do you want to know?
We weren’t planning
to come to this island,
so I’d rather not lose our way
to the next one.
I see. I’d guess it takes
about a day.
What?! Then we’ve got
to set sail at once!
The only time I release
a patient of mine...
is when they’ve recovered,
or when they die.
I won’t let you leave.
No way...
Wait up, meat!
Don’t eat him yet, Luffy!
I’ll cook him up!
Cut it out, humans!
I said don’t eat him!
Wait up, you!
The deer from earlier is talking!
What a surprise.
They can move around already?
They were just
on the brink of death.
What is that?
That walking stuffed animal thing?
Oh, him?
His name’s Chopper.
Chopper?
He’s just a blue-nosed reindeer who ate
the Human-Human Fruit and gained human abilities.
A reindeer?
He’s a doctor, too.
I’ve taught Chopper
everything I know about medicine.
Gotcha!
Right!
You two, that’s...
Oh, Nami!
You’re all better, huh?
What a relief, Nami-san!
I’m just about to cook
some revitalizing food for you.
I’m...
not food!
He took human form!
Hey... He’s...
A monster.
He’s a talking reindeer...
And he was so small,
then he turned huge...
He’s a monster.
Awesome!
Damn kids!
You plannin’ to make a mess
of this entire room?!
Granny?
I’m still a healthy
139-year-old!
Die, ya damn brats!
Wait! I ain’t lettin’ ya get away!
Sanji! H-Hey, Sanji!
Yeah?
I’ve decided!
On what?
That reindeer is a cool guy!
Let’s have him join our crew!
Chopper.
Um... I think you have it backwards.
Too late.
And I can still see you.
Shut up, pirate!
Oh, and is your fever all right?
Huh? Yeah, it’s pretty much gone.
Still, you have to stay in bed.
Doktorin’s medicine works really well,
so the fever goes down quickly,
but the infection
is still in your body.
You have to take
the antibiotics and relax, or...
Thank you.
You’ve been taking
care of me, right?
Shut up!
I don’t want gratitude
from a stinking human, you jerk!
Are you kidding me?!
You really can’t hide
your emotions at all, huh?
You people are pirates, right?
Yes.
Real pirates?
Yes, we’re real.
You’ve been out
on adventures and stuff?
Pretty much.
Y-You’re strong?
Are you interested
in pirates?
I’m not!
I’m not, you idiot!
All right,
I get it. Sorry!
Still...
Then...
Wanna come with us?
To the sea!
Won’t you come with us?
If you became our ship’s doctor,
it’d really help me, too.
I’d like to get out of here
before the Log changes direction...
Don’t be ridiculous!
I’m a reindeer, you know!
Think I can go with you humans?!
Because you’re a reindeer?
Besides, doesn’t looking at me...
scare you?
I’m a reindeer,
yet I’m standing on two legs...
I can talk, too...
You want to scare me?
and I’ve got a blue nose.
So that’s where
you were, reindeer!
Wait! Join our crew, monster!
Monster!
I wish they’d just calm down
for a little while.
You’re not very grateful,
are you, little girl?
You planning to steal my reindeer
while I’m not around?
Oh? I need permission
to seduce the little guy?
Ya don’t say...
Nah, ya don’t
need my permission.
If ya wanna take him along,
then go ahead.
But it won’t be easy
to convince him.
He has a wound
in his heart.
A grievous wound
that even I can’t heal.
From the moment he was
born into this world,
his parents told him
that he was a disgrace...
Huh?
It was because
of his blue nose.
He always had to walk by himself
at the very back of the herd.
And he was just
a newborn baby, too...
Then, one day, he ate the Human-Human Fruit
and everyone treated him like a monster.
The other reindeer
drove him away by force.
Still, he wanted friends,
so he went down
to the village in human form...
W-What is that creature?!
It creeps me out!
It’s gotta be the Abominable Snow Man!
Get your guns!
Shoot it down!
It’s working!
Damn monster!
Shoot! Kill it!
He didn’t know what
he’d done wrong.
Nor did he know
who was to blame.
He simply wanted friends,
yet they only called him a monster.
He was neither a reindeer
nor a human.
He just lived on by himself like that.
Can you heal his heart?
There was one person, though.
Huh?
He opened his heart
to one man, long ago.
His name was
Doctor Hiriluk...
The quack doctor who gave him the name “Chopper”
and treated him like his own son.
Hey! He ran this way!
That Doctor Hiriluk is
completely insane!
Can you believe that guy?!
Just barging into the patient’s house
and forcing him to take some weird injection!
We were gonna have the Twenty Doctors
take a look at him, too!
Found him!
He’s over here!
Wait, Hiriluk!
Capture him!
Ya happy, young one?
Ya gonna put me to sleep?
How’s that gonna help ya?
That’s a sedation gun, ain’t it?
There’s nothing scarier
than an incompetent doctor.
How many people are afraid of the common cold
because of you callin’ yourself a doctor?
Hmph! I don’t wanna hear that from
some heartless doctor who barely looks at her patients,
before snatching
away their money...
That’s just my style.
Oh, and did you hear?
Apparently this country has no doctors left
except you, me, and the Twenty Doctors.
I won’t be caught
by the Doctor Hunt.
Just watch, my medical research
will save this country!
Oh, really? Sure you don’t actually mean
that it’ll destroy the country?
There’s someone
on the bridge!
Did the Abominable Snow Man
from earlier come back?!
Shoot it down
right now!
There’s nobody here...
Where’d it go? Find it!
Who’re you?
Were you shot with a pistol?
If we don’t stop your bleeding soon,
you’re gonna die.
Don’t look at me like that.
It’s all right, I’ll help you.
Still, what are you?
You don’t look human...
Oh, I see. You’re that Abominable Snow Man
they were talking about.
Monster!
Shoot! Kill it!
I got it!
Not yet! It’s still breathing!
Damn bastard...
Don’t mess with me!
Who the hell do
you think I am?!
Hey! Wait!
I would...
never shoot you!
My name is
Doctor Hiriluk!
I’m a doctor!
Y-You can talk?!
Why’d you stay silent
for three whole days?
I thought you’d hate me if I spoke.
When I try to talk to people,
they shoot at me.
So what if you can talk?!
Don’t brag about
something like that!
I can talk too, you know!
A lot better than you, too!
Run away, Chopper!
Chopper?
It’s gonna explode!
That was close!
I failed again, huh?
Hey, Chopper!
Are you all right?
Why are you
calling me Chopper?
Tony Tony Chopper.
You’re a reindeer, and those horns
of yours look like they can chop down trees.
It’s a nice name, right?
That’s what I’m gonna call you.
Chopper...
Well then, I want to start the experiment again,
but I suppose we gotta clean up first!
Give me a hand, Chopper!
Sure!
Still, what can I say?
You’re an outcast, just like I am.
But you shouldn’t
hate humans.
This kingdom is sick.
The hearts
of the people are ailing.
Society might claim that there’s
no such thing as a sick country,
but they’re wrong.
Listen up, Chopper!
There’s a tale
that goes like this...
In a kingdom far off to the west,
there was a great burglar!
He was suffering
from a terrible heart condition.
He used his stolen money to be treated
by the best doctors, but even so...
not a single one could cure him.
It was one of those
incurable diseases.
The man believed that he would soon die
and wandered off in turmoil...
After a long while, he reached a mountain
where he beheld a wondrous sight.
What do you think he saw?
Cherry blossoms!
He saw an entire mountain
of brilliant cherry blossoms.
Three months later, he went to see
the doctors, and they were shocked.
This is what they told him:
“You’re the very picture of health!”
That’s right!
He’d been healed!
He had recovered
from an incurable disease!
It was a miracle...
No, that’s not all!
There’s no doubt
that it was a miracle,
but seeing the cherry blossoms must have triggered
a sort of change in the man’s heart!
This is bona fide medical science!
It cured a supposedly
incurable disease!
Amazing, right?
That means there’s no such thing
in this world as an incurable disease!
I will save this kingdom
with my medicine!
That’s why I’ve raised this skull
against every disease there is!
Skull?
That’s right!
This is a symbol of conviction
that defies the impossible!
With this flag raised,
I will fight like a pirate!
Pirate?
That’s right! A pirate!
Chopper, you should
rest back in the house.
You’re still injured.
Don’t blame me
if your wounds reopen.
They won’t reopen!
The wounds will decide for themselves
whether they’re gonna reopen or not.
I’m all right!
I’m not so sure...
Dad!
Get lost, quack!
Damn, another failure!
I thought for sure that lizard eyes would work!
I’ll be taking these!
Hiriluk stole my money!
Don’t be so greedy,
damn snob!
It’s the soldiers!
Chopper, we’re gonna use
a decoy strategy!
What do you mean?
There!
Take care!
Get real!
I told you that you
couldn’t come with me!
What kind of doctor would kick
his own patient, you jerk?!
I could’ve died!
Go ahead and die,
you damn blue-nosed freak!
Don’t insult my nose!
Shut up!
You were just going to die
before anyway!
What kind of
doctor are you?!
Doktor...
That was the first
time I’ve fought anyone.
I suppose so.
You’d never had anyone to fight before.
Then I guess it’ll be your
first time for this, too.
A present...
to make it up to you.
What, you’re gonna cry again,
reindeer freak?
No way I’d cry!
No turning big! That’s not fair!
Take a look, Chopper!
A magnificent sea!
It’s huge!
That’s right!
This vast sea is filled with
the pirates worthy of traversing it!
You should go out
to sea someday, too!
If you go out to sea, you’ll realize just how insignificant
your own troubles are!
Really?
Yeah, it’s true!
Compared to the rest of the world,
the island you were born on is as small as this!
Really?!
No, smaller! This one country
is as small as this !
Really?!
Really!
What a wonderful story.
I don’t know
about that...
Huh?
It’s taken a year, but your treatment
is finally complete.
Yeah. Thanks, Doktor!
Then, stay well.
Congratulations on your recovery.
Your wounds have healed.
I don’t have to look out
for you anymore.
From now on, you should
just go wherever you want.
Now, get out!
I’ve got research to do.
Doktor!
I definitely won’t cause any
more trouble, so let me in!
I’ll make you tea every day,
and I’ll take care of the cleaning, so please let me stay!
I don’t have any friends!
I don’t have anywhere to go!
Doktor... Doktor!
Look, Doktor! I’m hurt!
Why, Doktor?
Your wounds have healed!
Get going!
Go out to sea or something!
Never come back here!
Please forgive me, Chopper!
I’m gonna die,
aren’t I?
Yeah, you’re gonna die.
Is there nothing you can do
to delay my death?
You still have worldly regrets?
Why don’t you just accept the inevitable?
It’d be easier for you.
I still have work
that needs to be done.
I only need a little more time.
I want to finish my thirty years of research.
If ya wanna live that badly,
why don’tcha go to that kingdom far off in the west?
Just go see those so-called “miraculous cherry blossoms”
that saved you back when you were a burglar.
There’s no need.
I’m gonna make cherry
blossoms bloom in this country.
What a fool.
This is a Winter Island,
you know.
There’s no way you can
make cherry blossoms bloom.
They will bloom!
The medicine I’ve developed at great cost to my life...
will prove that things like that do exist in this world!
Then I should be able to
save every human living in this world!
I want to do it here,
in the land where I was born.
I’m almost done!
I just need a little more time.
You just don’t know
when to give up.
By the way, what’s with
that weird monster following you around?
What? He followed me?
Yeah. I think he was trying
to hide over there.
I’m the one and only friend
he’s ever met.
How do you think he’d take it
if I died right in front of him?
Do you want him
to endure more despair?
So you drove him away all of a sudden,
after being with him for a full year?
We’re alike.
That’s why I’ll be sure
to tell him in the end,
“There’s nothing you can’t do!”
I’ll tell him by making
the cherry blossoms bloom!
Listen up. I don’t have
a miracle cure; I can’t heal you...
But I can probably trick your body so that
it stays alive for another ten days or so.
But unfortunately for you...
you’d have to pay me
a fortune for it.
Just hurry up and treat me!
Think you’re gonna trick me
with this tranquilizer gun?
It’s true, you two
are just like each other.
You’re both so clumsy.
Fine. I’ll treat you.
Then you can show me exactly what kind of change
you’re gonna bring this country as a doctor.
What happened
to the rest of the guards?
Well, they were asked
by the Twenty Doctors to look for a mushroom.
A mushroom?
Yeah. Apparently it’s a mushroom
that can cure any disease in the world.
Mushroom?
What’s that?
Is that...
Yeah, it’s the monster who was
with the quack doctor.
Get going! Go out to sea
or something!
Never come back here!
Hey! Wait!
I would never
shoot you!
I’ve done something
terrible, huh?
Chopper...
You should at least
see my cherry blossoms!
My final work!
Damn you! I don’t
have any more time!
Nothing is impossible to a man who flies
the skull and crossbones!
That’s what I taught you,
right, Chopper?
There it is! Amiudake!
That’s it!
But...
How am I gonna
get to it?
It’s been six days...
Damn it all...
Nothing’s come close
to the reaction I was hoping for!
Chopper! You...
What happened
to your body?!
Mushroom...
That’s an Amiudake, isn’t it?!
Please survive, Doktor...
I wanna become
a doctor...
Did you...
get that for me?
Teach me how
to become one...
I’m a reindeer,
but do you think I can do it?
Of course you can, Chopper!
You’re so kind, after all!
Hey! What’s going on?!
You’re telling me every single
one of the Twenty Doctors is sick?!
Please! My kid
has a fever!
Don’t complain to us!
Even doctors get sick, you know!
At least hand out some medicine!
You’re gonna ignore the patients?!
Don’t be a fool.
Give us the Twenty Doctors!
Is the Amiudake soup good?
Awful!
Medicine is supposed to taste bad!
It’s the proof that it’s working!
I can feel my
strength coming back!
Thank you, Chopper!
Doktor...
Listen up. I’m going out for a while,
you should just stay here and sleep.
You’re in worse condition
than I am right now, after all.
Got it.
Well, see you later. I’m off.
Doktor was happy.
I cured a sick person.
Hey, Chopper.
You’re gonna make
a fine doctor.
I guarantee it!
I’m gonna make a fine doctor!
Did you hear, Kureha?
The entire country is in an uproar.
Yeah. That whole thing about
the Twenty Doctors all being sick,
and no one around
to treat them, right?
How ridiculous.
Just ignore it,
and it’ll all calm down.
So what did you
come for today?
Actually, I wanted to
ask you a favor.
What’s this?
That’s...
This is it!
I’ve been waiting
for this reaction!
I waited for thirty years!
I did it, Chopper!
My research is a success!
That’s thirty years of my life.
It’s the research that
I finally managed to complete!
A miracle cure that can heal
the ailing hearts of the people!
So you’ve wasted thirty
years of your life.
Why are you giving this to me?
It’s not enough,
and I’m out of time.
I want you to make the cherry blossoms
bloom in my place.
Don’t be ridiculous!
Why would I do that?!
And one more thing!
Please teach medicine
to Chopper!
He wants to be a doctor!
Get real!
There’s a limit to
how insolent one can get!
He’ll definitely become
a great doctor!
He’s a good guy,
and he’s got a kind heart!
He risked his life
to make medicine for me!
I’m begging you!
Pass your skills on to him
and make him a doctor!
You want me to take over your stupid research
and that bizarre pet of yours?!
So what if you’re
about to die?
You should know I’m not about
to start feeling sorry for you over that!
Get out!
Yeah, I know.
We’ve known each other
for a long time.
I know perfectly well...
that doctors are all nice people
who save people’s lives.
Please take care of Chopper.
My medical research will
eventually save this country!
You seemed so desperate...
That isn’t like you.
For you to give up...
I’m out of time.
Did you hear, Kureha?
The entire country is in an uproar.
That idiot!
Don’t tell me...
Where’s Hiriluk?
You don’t have to run away.
I already know about you.
Where’s Hiriluk?
Doktor left a while ago.
He got better,
so he’s probably headed to town...
He got better?!
There’s no medicine that can cure
that disease of his!
You heard that back
at my house too, right?!
But...
Look! He drank this,
so he’s all right now!
Is that... Don’t tell me
that’s Amiudake?!
Yeah, it’s a miracle cure!
Doktor’s going to teach me
about medicine!
He’ll definitely become
a great doctor!
He’s a good guy,
and he’s got a kind heart!
You stupid reindeer!
Listen, reindeer, that mushroom...
It’s a deadly poison!
If you eat it,
you won’t even last half a day!
That can’t be true.
I checked the books.
This is a symbol of conviction
that defies the impossible!
That’s why I’ve raised this skull
against every disease there is!
I mean...
There was a skull drawn
next to this mushroom!
Doktor said it himself.
He’d gotten better!
There’s no way he’d die...
You’re a liar!
He was happy about
the way you felt...
But that skull...
is a symbol of poison!
That’s a lie!
It’s not.
There’s no medicine in this world
that can cure all diseases.
That’s why we need doctors!
Do you understand?
Kindness alone isn’t enough to save someone!
If you want to save someone,
you’ve got to acquire the proper knowledge and medical skill!
You can’t save anyone
if you don’t know how!
Did you...
get that for me?
Thank you, Chopper!
What a fool
you are.
Hey!
Doctor Hiriluk!
Now, prepare the ropeway!
Take me to the castle!
I don’t have much time,
so hurry!
Every second counts. Hurry!
Hiriluk will never come back here.
He’s decided to
make the castle his grave.
I’ll continue trying to relieve
people’s suffering until I die!
Because I’m a doctor!
Wapol-sama! Hiriluk is coming!
So he fell for the trap?
What a hippo!
That can’t be... Why?!
Why would he?!
There he is!
It’s Doctor Hiriluk!
Take me to the patients!
I’ve come to save the Twenty Doctors!
Wh—
What’s going on here?!
You hippo!
This is a trap!
As you can see,
the Twenty Doctors are doing just fine!
You just came here to die!
You’ve eluded the Doctor Hunt
for long enough!
Defying the king
is a horrible sin!
I hereby sentence you to death!
Guards, take aim!
What?!
What a relief...
So nobody’s sick?
I really thought
the country was in danger.
But you were
just deceiving me?
If the country really was in danger,
I wouldn’t want help from someone like you, you damn hippo!
Shoot the rebel!
Drop it.
You people can’t kill me.
What?
When do you
think people die?
When they’re shot through
the heart with a pistol?
No...
When they are struck
by an incurable disease?
No.
When they drink soup made
from a poisonous mushroom?
No!
People die...
when they are forgotten.
Even after I’m gone,
my dream will come true.
The ailing hearts of the people
will definitely be cured.
Why are you crying,
Dalton-kun?
Do you think that works
for a kingdom as well?
Sure, as long as someone
inherits your will.
A monster will be
coming here soon.
He’s my son.
Don’t hurt him!
Don’t worry, Chopper.
Your mushroom
won’t kill me.
This has truly been
a great life!
So long, quack doctor.
Thank you, Chopper.
You’re gonna
make a fine doc—
That hippo!
He went and blew himself up!
What a crazy guy!
Wapol-sama! It’s a monster!
Kill it!
Wait!
Get him, Dalton-san!
Kill it!
Leave this place!
If you’re mad because he laughed
at Hiriluk’s death, then I apologize!
But you’re not strong enough.
You’d be wasting your life!
Please...
Don’t become another sacrifice
for the country! I’m begging you!
Why so courteous, Dalton?
If you disobey the king’s orders...
Silence!
You still don’t get it?!
The one and only person who tried
to save this messed-up country just died!
So what if that wannabe-doctor
just killed himself?
I’ve realized the path this country
ought to go down!
The path to destruction!
What?!
No matter how far our
medical research progresses...
Even if we keep researching
medicine forever...
There is no medicine
that can cure stupidity!
You’ve said too much,
you damned hippo!
You know what happens
if you make me angry!
Don’t you, Dalton?
Please...
make me a doctor!
I’m gonna become
the miracle cure!
I’ll become a doctor
who can cure any disease!
Because...
Because there’s...
no disease in this world
that can’t be cured!
Please...
Please make me a doctor!
Call me Doktorin.
Hey! Reindeer!
Not in here either, huh?
Where’d that guy go?
A pirate flag?
Doktorin! Wapol has returned!
I know. Like I said,
today’ll be a busy day.
Well, we’re here!
This is the first step in rebuilding the Drum Kingdom!
What happened
to my servants?
The way up to the castle
is tough to travel.
They probably couldn’t
keep up with us.
I’m sure they’ll be here soon.
Wapol-sama! There’s a weird flag flying
on the roof of the castle!
What is that? What happened
to the Drum Kingdom’s emblem?
I burned that thing.
So, you’re here?! Doctor Kureha,
the last survivor of the Doctor Hunt!
You’ve got a lot of nerve,
moving into my castle during my absence!
Absence? You abandoned
the kingdom and ran away!
What was that?!
You see, I’ve made this castle
into Hiriluk’s grave.
Get out of this country!
The Drum Kingdom has fallen!
That dumbass doctor’s
grave, you say?
Don’t make me laugh!
Hey! Hurry up and dispose
of this half-dead old hag!
Yes, Sir!
Not happening!
Take this!
Static Moss Ball!
Doktorin!
Hey, hey, hey, Afroman!
Launching your afro at a lady...
What kind of soul brother are you?
Who the hell’re you?!
Just an ordinary pirate.
What the...
I can’t get it off!
What’s with this afro?
Static electricity?
Exactly. And there’s more
where that came from!
Statis Moss Ball!
Hey, reindeer!
Don’t just stand there and watch! Help me!
Uh, all right!
Ugh, this is gross.
It’s stuck to me!
You can
have it back.
No, don’t give
it back, dammit!
You could
at least take one!
No way!
What’re you guys doing?
I should mention that those static
moss balls are highly flammable!
Oh, crap!
He’s gonna ignite the afros!
We’re gonna use
a decoy strategy!
Oh, I see, a decoy...
Wait, I’m the decoy?!
Checkmate!
Why, you!
Chopper!
Wapol-sama!
Dammit!
Oh, Sanji! Did you find
the reindeer?
Luffy! Grab on to my leg from there!
Leg? Right!
Like this?
Don’t you let go now!
Arme de L’air Rubber Shot!
I’ll try adding some spins, too!
Nasty, nasty...
And there goes his spine.
What else did he expect?
Thank you.
You people sure are incredible.
Man, he’s tough!
Wapol-sama, are you all right?
Those damn pirates
have really done it now!
Huh? There’s some
weird guy there...
Hey, Wapol.
Should I lend you a hand?
No... I can’t rely on you
all the time, Bro-chan.
I’ll kill those
damn hippos!
I’ll show them the true power
of the Chomp-Chomp Fruit!
He’s up to something!
Don’t let your
guard down.
If those guys were that weak,
the people would have stopped them from
doing something as ridiculous as banishing the doctors.
Besides, that guy...
Wapol’s older brother Mushroo...
He’s got the power of the Shroom-Shroom Fruit.
He’s dangerous.
Shroom-Shroom?
Mushrooms?!
Twenty years ago,
when Mushroo
was 13 years old,
while the king had left the country
to attend a World Council conference,
He detonated a bomb from the castle,
just like he’s planning to do now,
and killed a lot of people.
He wanted to test his powers
because he was bored.
That was
the only reason.
When the king returned, he apologized to the people
and had Mushroo banished from the kingdom.
After that, Drum established itself
as a country of advanced medical science.
But how could one
explosion cause all that?
Because of the Shroom-Shroom Fruit.
A horrible power.
A Fatal Bomb.
He’s able to release the poison spores
stored in his stomach once every 10 years...
And he fired that?
I suppose we
were lucky...
The wind was strong that day,
causing the poison to disperse quickly.
But it’s been twenty years
since that day.
If he uses his power now...
the explosion will probably be
even bigger than the last one.
But he does have one weakness.
I asked the king
where he had sent him.
The king told me:
“We couldn’t allow him
to cause trouble in another country,
“so I sent him to the Kingdom of Fire,
where his power would be halved,
“and asked the king there
to restrain him.”
The Kingdom of Fire?
Everything I eat
becomes part of my body.
Chomp-Chomp Shock!
Wapol House!
Awesome!
First law of the Drum Kingdom:
Anyone who defies
the king’s will, dies.
That law means everything
to this country.
After all, this country
is my country.
This castle is my castle!
And then...
you had to go and place
that wannabe doctor’s flag up there!
It’s defiling my castle!
The pirate flag...
Hey, reindeer.
Is that flag...
Doktor...
Serves you right! What’s wrong?
You got a problem with that?
What are you doing
to the skull mark?!
What’s that
supposed to mean?
Hey! Hippo-face!
You understand what it means
to shoot a flag, don’t you?
What?
He’s...
Think I give a damn about
such a stupid decoration?
Didn’t I tell you?
This is my country!
I’ll shoot that thing
as many times as I want!
Watch out! It’s dangerous!
Someone like you can’t
destroy this flag!
The skull mark...
is a symbol
of conviction!
That was a direct hit!
You hippo!
See? It’s still whole.
Impossible! He’s crazy!
I dunno who you are,
or whose pirate flag this is...
But this is a flag
that you pledge your life to!
You don’t raise
it as decoration!
It’s not a flag that someone like
you can just laugh at or destroy!
So this is a pirate?
Amazing!
Chess!
Eliminate these guys!
Yes, Sir!
Now, just wait a minute.
Wapol. Go ahead
and get things ready.
I’m gonna have myself
a bit of fun.
Spin Drill!
Shade Dance!
Luffy!
Are you all right,
Straw Hat?!
I’m fine.
‘Cause I’m made of rubber.
Rubber?
What’s that supposed to mean?
To put it simply...
He’s a monster.
Look out!
Go!
Get him!
Rot Sting!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Gum-Gum Bullet!
Too bad.
Spin Drill!
Running Spore Hypha!
You can’t move!
What’s this?!
Snow Spore!
You guys...
Those are...
Poison spores.
You’re kidding!
Luffy!
Sheesh. As soon as we launch that bomb,
this’ll all be over...
It sure is noisy here...
What’s going on?
Chopper!
Too easy.
You’re late,
you damn maroons!
Mushroo-sama, that’s...
You know what it is?
A monster who once
scared the villagers.
We’ve got ourselves
a pretty weird creature here.
I know how you feel.
Seems you’re the same as I am.
Rejected no matter where we went,
we’ve both led lonely, pitiful lives!
What?
You still plannin’ to fight?
What’re you gonna do,
all on your own?
I’m a doctor.
I’ve sworn on Doktor’s flag...
that I’d save the people...
Save this country...
Even though I don’t
have any friends...
You do have friends!
I’m your friend!
You...
I’m impressed that you can still move
after inhaling my poison.
It’d be easier for you to just fall
over like these morons.
Chess-sama!
Even Kuromarimo-sama...
What’re you goin’
to do in that state?
I’m sure it takes everything you got just
to stand up right now.
Guess there’s no choice.
I’ll just put you out of your misery!
Stop it!
Go to Hell!
Flame Star!
Robin-chwan!
Don’t ignore me!
Wait!
Dalton!
Dalton-san...
You still don’t get it, do you?
What do you think you should do
for this country right now?
There once was a man who only thought of what was best
for the kingdom and then died, right here!
You saw it too, right?!
The time of oppression is over!
We can’t allow Wapol
and the others to stay in this country!
Damn!
How could he do that to me?!
Good thing the snow
softened my fall.
You damn maroons!
Gear 2!
All right!
Seems the antidote worked.
Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
Gum-Gum...
Cross Shade!
Jet Whip!
Amazing!
Great!
Get him!
W-What?
Nami-san!
That came from inside
the castle...
Damn! Wapol’s gone!
Nami-san!
Nami, you all right?
Yes, I’m fine.
I was just surprised.
Thank goodness!
You’ve gotten better?
Where is he?
That weird guy
went up there...
He said something
about a cannon.
What’s he planning to do?
It can’t be!
Spin Drill!
You’ve still got some
poison left in you, right?!
Gum-Gum...
Jet Bazooka!
Bro-chan!
We’re finally here!
You sure they’re here?
Beats me. Anyway,
let’s head toward that building.
Such a pretty castle.
What’s that damage up there?
I wanna fix it!
What’re you talking about?
Behold!
A miraculous three-in-one fusion!
Mushroo Wapol Cannon!
Thought so!
What’re you gonna do
with that thing?
I’ll tell you. I’m gonna cause a poison explosion
like the one twenty years ago...
No, even stronger than that one!
I’m launching a Fatal Bomb!
A Fatal Bomb?!
Drop the ridiculous act!
If you do that—
Yeah, that’s right!
I’ll kill every single citizen and purify the country!
What?!
Don’t act like the death of those people
is such a huge deal.
All that matters is that
the country will be mine again!
As long as we have our advanced medical system,
sick people will always come here,
so replacing the citizens will be easy!
Stop it!
Too late!
Rumble!
Such insolence.
Walk Point!
Jumping Point!
Arm Point!
Hoofprint Roseo!
So that’s it, huh?!
It’s released!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
Fresh Fire!
They did it!
Right! Everything went
according to my plan!
As if.
Someone like you,
without any resolve...
has no right to touch
someone else’s skull mark!
Gear 3:
Gum-Gum...
No, wait! I'll give you a title!
Medals, even!
Oh, crap! Everyone, run!
Gum-Gum...
I'll make you underking, then!
Gigant Pistol!
Doktorin... The Drum Kingdom...
This country fell to
the skull and crossbones.
Reindeer!
Hey! Reindeer!
Where’d you go?
Don’t be ridiculous!
Please! The Log will reset
if we don’t leave this island soon!
No can do. You’ve gotta rest here
for another two days.
As a doctor,
I simply can’t let you leave.
Can’t we work this out?
What’s this?
The antidote
for the Fatal Bomb.
As a doctor, you couldn’t just let someone
take it away from here, am I right?
Listen up, girl.
There’s a coat hanging in my room,
and I fixed up that youngster’s spine.
He’s lying in the next room.
Don’t you dare run away!
So she’s telling me to take
the coat and run away now?
Hey! Reindeer!
Let’s be pirates together!
So it’s a full moon tonight...
Reindeer!
Come out!
I wonder what Doktor
would say about this?
Reindeer!
Hey, Luffy,
just give up already.
Yell and look all you want.
He’s not coming.
He doesn’t want to
be a pirate.
That’s wrong!
I wanna take him along!
That’s just
what you want!
Reindeer!
Oh, reindeer! Hey!
Let’s be pirates together!
I can’t.
Sure you can!
It’ll be fun!
You don’t get it, do you?
I’m... grateful to you guys.
But I’m a reindeer.
I’ve got horns and hooves...
And a blue nose...
Can you heal his heart?
Sure, I do want to
be a pirate, but...
I can’t join
a crew of humans!
I’m a monster!
I can’t join your crew!
So I’ve just come
to thank you...
Thank you...
for inviting me...
I’m staying here, but...
If you ever feel like it...
then feel free
to come visit us...
Shut up!
Let’s go!
Hey, could you give me a hand?
I need some strong arms.
We’re gonna carry
the cannons out from the armory.
Don’t just stand there.
Hurry up!
Oh, right...
Doktorin!
I need to talk to you.
Chopper, where’d you go?
Go help carry out
the cannons.
Listen, Doktorin!
I’m gonna be a pirate!
I’m gonna go out to sea with those guys
and see the world!
Don’t be ridiculous!
Who taught you how
to be a doctor?
Are you saying
you’re not grateful to me at all?!
That’s not true!
I’m really grateful!
I love this place,
where I met you and Doktor!
Then why don’t you stay here?!
Being a pirate ain’t all fun
and games, you know!
You could end up dead
at any moment!
I don’t mind!
Don’t be ridiculous!
Who’s ever heard of a reindeer sailing the seas?!
Yeah, I’m a reindeer!
But I’m a man, too!
Good for you...
but I’ll never allow it!
If you leave, it’ll be
over my dead body!
Doktorin...
Please understand...
A crybaby like you,
calling himself a man?!
I won’t let you just
do whatever you want!
I won’t let
you get away!
What the...?
I’m sorry, Doktorin.
But I want to see the world!
What would someone like you do,
if you did go to sea?!
You gonna live
in a fantasy world like Hiriluk did?!
You’re wrong!
It wasn’t just a fantasy!
Doktor completed his research!
Everyone, get in the sleigh!
We’re getting off this mountain!
Hold it!
Hurry! Everyone, get on!
What’s wrong?
Look!
The witch’s sleigh?
That was great!
There was a rope here?
I guess we couldn’t see it
because it’s white.
Where are we?
Finally awake, huh?
You’re annoying.
Go back to sleep.
What was that,
damn you?!
Calm down! I’ll fall off!
This is it!
I’ve been waiting
for this reaction!
I waited for thirty years!
Doktor...
It wasn’t just a fantasy, was it?
Your research was
complete, right?
Or was that just another lie?
I did it, Chopper!
My research is a success!
Did you just say that because I’d be sad
if you died without saying it?
Nothing is impossible for a man who flies
the skull and crossbones...
Say it again, Doktor!
A pet I was caring for
was taken in by someone else.  That's all.
I hate long goodbyes.
We’re gonna send him off in style!
Ya ready, youngsters?!
Yes!
Fire!
Whazzat?
Did the old lady snap?
It’s coming from the castle.
No way!
Did Wapol win?!
Is he bombing us?!
No, wait. This is...
Doctor Kureha!
We’ve launched them all!
Light up!
Listen, Kureha! This dust is the miracle cure
that will heal the ailing hearts of the people!
I figured this was the right time to use it.
Ya got a problem with that?
Doktor...
Doktorin...
Amazing.
Yeah...
Beautiful.
This is the result of
my thirty years of research!
You just can’t comprehend
the thought process of a fool.
Listen, this red powder
isn’t just ordinary powder!
Once this mixes with
the white snow in the atmosphere,
it will cause brilliant...
pink snow to fall!
Now, off you go,
my stupid son!
I see, you're going, after all. You've made up your mind
Guess we won't be able to meet every day anymore
I see, well, I guess you had been saying for a long time
that this had always been your dream
This time, I can tell you to do your best,
never give up, and take care,
and that's enough, isn't it?
This time I'll promise you,
if anything happens, you can come right back,
and I'll always be waiting for you
That'll be enough, won't it?
Ah, but the void in my heart
caught even me off-guard,
and so I just repeated myself over and over, like a fool
I see, I see, I see... See you later. See you later
Why did I never realize
just how precious were the passing days
when I was together with you?
"See you later"; This simple phrase
represents such a plethora of emotions
that I'm not sure I'll ever be able to say it
Aah, I feel like I can't beg you, saying things like
"I'll be lonely" or "Please stay with me,"
when I see your face gazing at the path ahead
And so...
See you later. See you later. For sure, I'll see you later