Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has broken out of the
great prison Impel Down
and is headed to Navy Headquarters
in order to rescue his brother, Ace!
Meanwhile, the rest of the Straw Hats...
...who had been ejected from Sabaody Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma are...
The Crew's Whereabouts
A Giant Chick and the Peachy Showdown
I see.
Sounds like Navy HQ is harder
to break into than Impel Down.
They are expecting a fight
with good old Whitebeard now.
So the place must be filled with
the most formidable forces...
...that you can think of in the world today!
We want to avoid an all-out war but
I don't think that it's possible.
Meanwhile, a short time ago...
on Peachy Island in the Grand Line,
Grand Line
Peachy Island, Kamabakka Queendom
Kamabakka Queendom...
Dammit! All the queers on this island are...
You are one of us, aren't you?!
Wait!
Dammit!
Stay away from me!
What?!
Those queers...
Why are they so strong?!
They are...
...not ordinary queers!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
When can I see them again?!
I see.
There've been some candies
who have had trouble
accepting themselves after coming to this island.
It's about time for us to put
out a helping hand to him!
By the way, is he strong?
Not that much--but his kicks aren't too bad!
Then, let's use the traditional
method of Kamabakka Queendom...
...for first time in a long while!
You guys are so persistent! Why?!
Why are you...
...chasing me?!
Wait!
Why should I?! Stupid!
What's this building?!
But before that...
What's wrong with them?!
Damn!
I've been waiting for you!
W-W-Who are you, you bastard?!
It's so rude to call her
"bastard!" Call her Caro-sama!
Are you queen of this country?
Queen?! Please!
To be exact,
I'm the queen...
...stand-in!
Caroline!
"Stand-in"
Caro-sama!
A stand-in?!
Kamabakka Queendom is ruled
by the legendary queen -
Iva-sama!
It'd be presumptuous of
me to call myself queen!
I don't care if you're a sub or
not, let me get this straight now!
I'm sick of this island!
Get me out of this place!
--Alright, I got it!
--Huh?
However, you need to fight the
strongest one of us and win!
How's that sound?
It's a deal! I'll take it!
Okay!
Then you need to change into our
traditional fighting costume!
W-What?! Fighting... costume?
Is this the fighting costume...
...that you were talking about?!
Cute!
Quit it! Shut up!
I can't stand this much longer!
I'll finish this with a
single blow in a jiffy!
And I'll finally leave this stupid island!
Gorgeous!
What?!
I'm gonna fight you?!
I'm the stand-in queen of Kamabakka Queendom
and at the same time, the grand master
of the Kamabakka style—New Kama Kenpo!
--...Stand-in!
--Are you standing in for everything?!
Alright! Let's just do this!
I'll show you my technique!
I don't intend to give you a chance!
Because I'm gonna finish
you with this attack!
Concasse!
It's over!
Where is he?
I'm here, candy-chan!
Damn you!
How odd! Why can't I land a single blow?!
And what's up with his eyes?
And that weird movement?
Augh! Don't tell me that he's...
You look good!
Hey, hey, don't look at it!
I mean, why should I be embarrassed
by showing my underwear?!
That's your maiden-like modesty
that you can't disguise!
Shut up! That's so stupid! I'm a man!
I don't care if you see my underwear!
Oh no!
Your kicks are lower than before!
You're embarrassed as I thought!
See?
Don't measure it!
That's because you have doubt in your heart!
That can't be it!
Are you sure?!
N-No, don't!
It looks like you're deceiving
yourself just as I thought!
What?!
Be true to yourself!
So, why did you stop kicking?!
Do you want me to attack you now?
New Kama Kenpo Secret Art:
Awakening of the Inner Maiden!
Why? Why? It's just my underwear! But yet...
...it's so embarrassing!
Whoa! No!
Huh? Did I just scream like a girl?
N-No way!
But what is this feeling?!
I don't understand!
I'm...
...about lose myself...
...myself...
...and become somebody else!
"Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan,
how are you both doing?"
"I'm looking forward to seeing you two!"
"When the time comes, I'm sure
that we'll become good friends!"
This is Birdie Kingdom in the South Blue
South Blue
Birdie Kingdom
where birds reign supreme.
I really wanna get off this island.
This place is the worst.
Birds treating me like a toy.
And humans trying to eat me in a hot pot.
And the birds and the humans are...
...always fighting.
What should I do?
Here, I got you something to eat!
How are your legs?
Did they get any better? Let me see.
Stay still!
Oh! They look okay now!
Here, go ahead and eat these.
You were lucky.
I was just searching for various
kinds of herbs at the time...
This is for stomach trouble.
What was that?!
The humans are after me again?!
Oh no! They're gonna eat me in a hot pot!
A cheeper of the birds?
She must have fallen out of the nest.
I don't understand what she's
saying since she's a baby
but sounds like she's been hurt.
You are injured!
No wonder! She fell from such a height!
Don't move! Stop, it's gonna get worse!
Calm down!
I'm a doctor!
You really eat a lot!
You know, it takes a lot of energy
just to get enough food for you!
But she will grow up someday
and be able to fly!
Then she can fly back to the nest. Oh yeah!
When you learn how to fly,
you gotta take me to Sabaody Archipelago!
Luffy!
Everybody!
Yeah! Then I can see Luffy and the others!
Promise me! And don't forget about it!
Hey! Stop! That tickles, you little monster!
No!
So you're gonna treat me like a toy too?!
It's warm!
It's great to see you guys again finally!
But I wasn't sad at all!
Oh? Where did she go?
Oh okay, since she can walk now,
she must be walking around a bit...
What?!
Something's wrong! From the
looks of her footsteps,
she must be somewhere around here.
I'm hungry!
That raccoon dog that we tried to cook in
a hot pot must still be here somewhere!
That was not a raccoon dog, that was a reindeer!
Let's catch it again and
cook reindeer hot pot!
--Yeah, let's do it!
--Let's do it!
Th-This is bad!
Really bad!
Oh, it's you!
I'm glad that you're okay!
It's not over here!
Let's go somewhere else!
Yeah, good idea!
They didn't see us! So you were lost?
You're fully recovered!
But you gotta be quiet!
If you're
not, they're gonna find us!
Oh no! Be quiet!
Oh, dammit!
--There it is! Right there!
--There's a bird, too!
We're gonna have a big feast today!
Chicken hot pot and reindeer hot pot!
Damn! We're on a cliff!
You can't run anymore!
Give up now!
The birds are coming!
Let's shoo them away!
Are you guys here to save us?!
I've been taking care of your baby but...
...you don't need to thank me, you bastard!
Huh?
I saw this coming!
Guard Point!
So they're fighting again...
I didn't know that she was her baby!
I'm happy for you!
Hey, don't forget the promise!
When you grow up and learn how to fly,
you gotta take me to Sabaody Archipelago!
I'm counting on you!
But when it will be?!
I can't wait that long!
I'm sick of this place!
Why can't the humans and the
birds on this island get along?!
Luffy! Everybody!
Help me!
Robin is held prisoner in Tequila Wolf.
Despite the tight security,
the young girl Soran takes action to save
Robin without concern for
the danger it puts her in.
Meanwhile, Usopp chows down to
become the hero of the forest!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Crew's Whereabouts
Revolutionaries and a Gorging Forest's Trap!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Crew's Whereabouts
Revolutionaries and a Gorging Forest's Trap!