Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats reach the New World at long last,
the harshest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
Responding to an emergency signal, Luffy and crew
land on the burning island, Punk Hazard, when...
Bu! It's strange but it's cool here!
You're not gonna believe this!
Somebody's stuck in the dragon's back!
One-Sword Style...
...Draw:
Lion Song!
Meanwhile, Nami and the others...
Tie them all up!
Alright!
It's good that they're pirates.
No one will care if they go missing.
Let's take them to "Master"!
The Straw Hats Astonished!
Enter the Puzzling Samurai's Head!
Punk Hazard
Burning Lands
Now, what should we do about him?
Let's pull him out!
Hey, who are you?!
Get your hands off of me-bu!
Hey! I'm helping you! Stay calm!
Here we go!
Wow, he's completely stuck in the dragon's body.
How is that possible?
His upper body is stuck but he's talking normally.
Why isn't he suffocating?
Who the hell is he?
I-I-It's missing!
What's missing?
He's torn in half! I'm sorry!
You fool! Sorry isn't enough! You killed him!
Oh, I'm finally separated from it-bu!
What?!
The lower body just talked! What's going on?!
A zombie! A monster!
Wait a minute.
This is strange.
There is no upper half here.
What do you mean?
He didn't have an upper body from the very start?
Oh, this is too freaky!
He's kind of big.
Who is there and what are you doing?
I sense your presence but I don't have eyes or ears.
You're bizarre!
I don't know who you are but get out of my way-bu!
What?
I cannot die here!
Oh, he took off!
I'm not going to let them get away!
That goddamn Warlord!
Hey, wait! Why don't you join my...
No, Luffy!
I'm gonna go catch him!
Can you grill the dragon for me?!
Wait, legs!
Luffy is so whimsical.
Why does he like that monster so much?
It troubles me that he mentioned the Seven Warlords.
Does it mean one of the Seven Warlords is here on this island too?
Oh no! That's too much trouble!
We don't wanna face the Warlords!
It's not too late!
Can we go back?
Hey!
Wait, legs!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
What is he doing?
Hey!
There's a wall!
Who is it?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Why did you do it-bu?
Who is it?
I know someone's after me.
But for some reason,
I don't feel any hostile intent.
He's fast.
Bu! I don't know who you are but what do you want from me-bu?
If you stand in my way, I'll fight you!
Stand in your way?
What are you talking about?
Cut that crap and join my crew!
Bu! What are you doing-bu?!
Gotcha!
Let me go-bu!
Now, why don't you join...
...my crew?!
Sorry!
Oh, that was surprising!
Hey legs, are you alright?
What the...?!
And you ended up like that?
Yep, that's right.
Oh, this dragon meat is yummy!
What do you call someone like this, Usopp?
Huh?
Um...
I think it's called...
...a centaur, maybe?
A centaur?
How funny!
First, he was stuck to the dragon's body and now Luffy's?
What's wrong with him?
How do you like it?
Damn! I'm stuck in something again-bu!
Let me go-bu!
That's vulgar, Luffy.
Is it?
What's this?!
See? He's not gonna just go along with you.
There's no such creature!
I bet his upper half is looking for him.
Give him back to his owner!
Where's your sense of adventure, Usopp?
He was born like this. Right?
Oh, so he's naturally a half-body... No, I don't buy it!
What's your name?
Hey, I know you're gonna eat most
of this dragon meat so why don't you carry it?!
Hey, guys! Come and take a look at this.
Oh, Zoro! Is the samurai and the guy who got cut?
Look.
What is it?
What?! S-Snowcapped mountains?!
No, are those mountains of ice?
There is a big lake in the middle and there are snowcapped
mountains on the other side!
But on this side, there is an active volcano and it's burning hot!
What kind of island is this?!
So one of the mysteries is solved.
Huh? Oh yeah, the man on the Snail said he was cold!
Help me!
What happened?
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
My colleagues are getting cut one after another!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
It means the killer samurai and the victims are on the other side!
This island is so interesting!
There is snow on those mountains, huh?
It's so hot here - I wanna eat a snowcone!
We're not gonna go there! It's too cold!
And it's a long way. Let's go back to the ship for now.
Oh no, it's gonna be cold this time.
If there are animals, we could make coats from pelts.
But it's gonna be okay.
No, it's not gonna be okay!
How can you guys go along with this?!
Snowcone!
Hey, I said "Wait"! Luffy!
Oh, you two are going too?!
I'm not going at any cost!
There's no immediate threat to my life here but over there,
I'll freeze to death.
I'm not gonna...
A monster!
No!!!
Ouch! What're you...
I saw... I saw a monster! A bird! No, a human!
A bird or a human, which was it?!
Huh? What are you talking about? Nobody's there!
Huh?
Gee! Hey, let's go!
No, believe me! There was somebody just a minute ago!
Believe me!
I'm here to report, Master.
We seized intruders.
I assume they are pirates.
Oh, that is perfect.
We were running low on guinea pigs.
Well, well... They all look unique and interesting.
They're gonna be good test subjects.
Yes, I thought you would especially like this cyborg.
Oh, what a rare find!
He is worth testing. You're right. I can't wait.
Will this be all?
It seems there was another man who looked like one of them but...
I assume they had a falling out and he was murdered.
All that remained was his skeleton.
Such brutality is not so unusual for pirates.
I see. All right.
I want you to lock them in a room and make sure they can't escape.
Let's see what they have here.
Look for food or something usable.
Yes, sir.
Oh? What was I doing?
Where are Nami-san and the others?
Who are those people?
It was very hot before
but it became extremely cold while I was sleeping.
Who is it?!
Are you one of those pirates?!
It's bone-chillingly cold, isn't it?
Oh, I'm a skeleton - that's why.
Th-The skeletonized body said something!
I don't know who you are but do you know
where Nami-san and the others went?
S-Shoot! Shoot!
Huh? No, wait, you guys! Don't be so rash!
Sanji, what are you messing around with?
Oh, you're up.
Can't you see?
Oh no, Franky! We are locked up!
Hey, what's this place?! Where are we?!
I was eating a Giant Shellfish dessert on the deck and...
I can't remember anything after that!
I assume that somebody used sleeping gas
and seized us once we fell asleep.
What?
The ship was, in fact, filled with gas.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could've noticed it a little sooner.
What should we do?
Are they gonna sell us?! Are they abducting humans?!
But if they took all of us on the ship, where's Brook?
I don't know.
There are only four of us in here.
If they're abducting humans, they wouldn't need a skeleton.
You're not a human either.
Neither are you! That's enough!
You guys.
Did anybody say something?
No, it wasn't us.
Do you guys like hanjimono?
That means "puzzles" in a foreign language.
Was it this thing that just talked?
What is it?
Don't call me an "it"!
It's...
What? A bug?
A new kind of Transponder Snail?
There are eight of them! I hadn't noticed!
I'm not a bug!
You guys don't seem like bad people.
These are all parts of my face.
Could I ask you to put them back together?
Your face?
Oh yeah, this is a mouth.
And this is an eye.
Like this?
--How is it?! --Yeah, looks like a face now!
No no, you left out some parts!
I think it's like this!
How about this?
It's completely wrong!
No no, this is better.
Alright, that's fine.
No! No!
I wanna try it too!
You guys! Stop playing with my face!
It's done!
Looks like a human face now!
I think there is something wrong with the chin
and the top part but it's okay.
Thank you!
A severed-head just talked!
You just noticed?
How can you live like that?! Are you possessed?!
I don't know. I didn't wish to become like this.
That bastard... He used some kind of weird magic!
I thought I was dead when he cut me but I ended up like this.
To be kept alive after being sliced apart is...
...a dishonor to a warrior!
It seems like crossing the lake
is the only way to get to the other side.
But how do we cross the lake?
I don't know if we can live long enough to get to the lake in the first place.
It's hot!
Snowcone!
I wonder how Luffy can be so high-spirited.
Snowcone! Snowcone! Snowcone!
Who goes there?!
There you are, intruders!
Huh?!
You have...
...those...
...legs!
They are so cool!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I was looking for intruders and I saw some unfamiliar faces so...
Oh, okay! You surprised me!
By the way, your legs are cool too!
Yeah! Your hind legs are a little different.
You think so?
Where am I-bu!
Hey, calm down!
Your hind legs can talk?!
Yeah!
Awesome! None of my friends have legs like that!
--I've never seen it before! --Yeah?
So, Luffy made an odd friend again.
A panther centaur?
One, two...
...three...
...and four.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Hello? Did you find them?
Yes, we found them. We were about to kill them.
There are four intruders.
I see.
That's exciting.
Please be careful!
Roger.
Clank.
Luffy and the crew face a new crisis while they cross the Burning Lands.
After Sanji and the others hear what the bodiless samurai has to say,
they escape together from their cell.
While being pursued, they wander into a room,
and discover a terrifying secret hidden on the island!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Shocking!
The Island's Secret is Finally Revealed"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Shocking!
The Island's Secret is Finally Revealed