Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
While breaking out, Luffy and others
ran into the Warlord--Blackbeard...
...at the staircase in Level 4!
I'm gonna save Ace at any cost!
Yeah, I'm not gonna say that it's a waste!
Anything is possible in this world!
I told you that the Sky Island exists!
And so does the One Piece!
It certainly exists!
You all should look forward to this!
In a few hours, we're going to...
...put on a show that's
gonna shake the whole world!
Don't stop, Luffy-kun!
Keep going!
To Level 3!
Are you Magellan?!
So you're Blackbeard?!
Yes, indeed!
Hydra!
Ouch! What is this?!
Straw Hat! How did you survive
after I poisoned you?!
He's probably the one who
caused this situation!
I must take his life for sure this time!
Straw Hat!
That poison bastard!
I will never let you get out of this prison!
Stop Magellan!
Iva-san Unleashes His Secret Art
Straw-chan! Don't look back! Keep running!
I won't let you get away!
Hurry up!
Hurry! Magellan's right there!
Let's go all the way to Level 2!
This is the last group!
Behind these ones, no one is...
left standing!
Inazuma!
Alright!
Great Scissors!
Inazuma-san!
Why did you cut the staircase?!
Iva-sama hasn't come up yet!
Don't worry! Just keep moving!
Iva-san!
Please be safe!
What are you trying to do here?
What am Vi trying to do?
If you really can't tell what Vi'm trying to do...
you must be very...
stupid!
Death Wink!
Heehaw!
Now things are getting serious!
Even if you buy yourself some time,
Straw Hat and others can't get out of here!
"Buy some time?"
So you think that you can beat me?
Kamabakka style, New Kama Kenpo!
Feast your eyes on this!
Kama!
Heehaw!
Hey hey! Come on now!
Long underpants!
Chemise!
It's odd! The poison bastard
was right behind us while ago!
I saw Iva-san and Inazuma
stopped in the lower level!
What?!
So they're fighting the poison
bastard! Let's go back!
Gimme a break!
If they're fighting, we gotta keep moving!
You have to believe in the
power of the miracle worker!
Spin, spin!
What's wrong with this floor?
They can't be this lax.
It's strange! I don't see
any prisoners in the cells!
And all the doors are open!
I wonder who released them!
Come on, get out! Let's
get back on the street!
Thank you, Captain Buggy!
Yes! I'm so glad!
I'm out!
You gotta do your part!
--Here you go!
--Thanks!
Take this!
Shoot! Shoot!
Keep going! Keep it up!
Come on, get out! Let's
get back on the street!
Thank you, Captain Buggy!
Yes! I'm so glad!
I'm out!
You gotta do your part!
--Here you go!
--Thanks!
Take this!
Keep going! Keep it up!
Luckily getting out of Level 2
blocked by Magellan's poison,
Captain Buggy and merry prisoners
are heading to the main entrance.
They're on Level 1.
Running through Level 4--the Inferno Hell and Level 3--the Starving Hell,
the mob of New Kamas led by Straw Hat
Luffy and the assembled freed prisoners...
...are now running through
Level 2 - the Beast Hell.
And Warden Magellan who was on their tail...
...is fighting with the Queen of Queers Ivankov in Level 3!
M-My spine has... mmm... got hurt!
D-Damn Ivankov!
Heehaw!
That's unforgivable!
Get them right now!
How long... mmm... are
you gonna keep sleeping?!
And the 4 Jailer Beasts who have been
beaten but come back repeatedly...
...are heading to Level 1 by elevator.
Jail Manager Shiryu who switched
sides cut all communication lines
so no one would find out the
situation inside the prison.
Those unprecedented dramatic events keep
expanding literally behind closed doors.
Navy ships and prison ships are
anchored around the prison!
If we're able to steal one of them, we can
get to Marineford before Ace-san's execution!
Great! Wait for me, Ace!
Ace's execution draws near:
4.5 hours remain!
My face... My face is gonna melt!
My face... My face...
My face... My face... My face is...
gonna melt... melt... melt...
Or not! Because Vi've got so much make up on!
"It's not gonna melt?!" Heehaw!
"You got me there!" Heehaw!
Heehaw!
Death Wink!
Wink! Wink!
Death Wink! Wink! Wink!
Wink! Wink! Wink!
Wink! Wink!
Venom Blowfish!
The lace... My bootlace...
came loose... loose...
loose... loose... loose...
Or not! Because they're laceless!
Heehaw!
"There's no lace?!" Heehaw!
"You got me there!" Heehaw!
This is foolish.
What?
It's foolish of you trying to gain some time!
You think so? Vi'm having so much fun!
Alright then, let's get this over with.
Between you...
and me!
New Kama Kenpo, 44 Aesthetic Arts:
Hair Removal Fist!
Iva-san!
Venom Road!
Oh no...
Keep Out!
Are you here to stall me, too?
Here they are!
The 4 Jailer Beasts all
together after all this time!
Run!
It's over! Let's go back!
We can't fight them!
Let's just forget about breaking out!
What?!
Hey, are you okay?
You bastard! What are you...
...dile?!
B-B-B-B-Boss!
Huh?
Oh, it's you, Mr. 3.
What are you doing here, you useless trash?
W-Who released this pain in the butt?!
C-Captain Buggy!
They KO'd the Jailer Beasts!
What?!
S-S-Straw Hat?!
Th-That's the Warlord Jinbe!
Good! You guys are okay!
"Good! You guys are okay!"
It breaks...
...My heart!
Captain Buggy!
A bunch of prisoners and perverts
are coming up one after another from Level 2!
Perverts, too?! What the hell?!
Who are you calling perverts?!
You two! This is for walking
out on us back there!
You're here, too, Mr. 2!
What're you doing to Captain Buggy?!
This is no good!
These Level 4 prisoners
came all the way up here at last!
They managed to get away
from Warden Magellan?!
Jeez! We allowed two riots at the same time!
Where's Warden now?!
Hydra!
Magellan's here, too!
What's going on on this floor?!
What?! Then Iva-chan and Crab-chan are...
Finally, Magellan catches up to Luffy and the others.
Luffy, in order to help the others off Level 1,
holds Magellan at bay with the aid of Mr. 3.
Meanwhile, Jinbei makes it to the entrance with the prisoners,
but Magellan has one more thing up his sleeve!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Magellan's Clever Scheme!
The Escape Plan Thwarted"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Magellan's Clever Scheme!
The Escape Plan Thwarted