Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and on their way
to the next stage, the New World,
they reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
However, there they found
the New Fishman Pirates disturbing the peace.
What's wrong with you?
Who are you, sir?!
Woah?! You're a huge lady... I mean, Mermaid!
Somebody! Father-sama! Brother-sama!
Whoa, whoa! I didn't do anything to you, did I?!
Oh, damn! What's with you?!
A Weakling and a Crybaby!
The Princess in Hard Shell Tower
Hey! Keep lighting the way!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Crewmate of the Flying Pirates
"Great Monk" Wadatsumi
It's no time for playing!
A snack!
Wadatsumi!
Didn't you get a reply yet?
A reply from Princess Shirahoshi?
No, not yet, Captain Decken.
How long have I been waiting for it?
For ten years or so.
And it hasn't come yet.
It's all because of that hateful Neptune!
He wants to force Princess Shirahoshi
into a political marriage!
I suspect!
The fact is, the Princess has been locked up
in the steel tower for ten whole years!
Oh, how painful this is!
Because we love each other!
I suspect!
Captain of the Flying Pirates
Vander Decken IX
Princess Shirahoshi! I love you!
I love you! I love you!
I love you!!!
No matter how much I roam this vast seafloor,
I can't find someone who is as great
and beautiful as you are!
If we end up together, then all is well.
However, I cannot allow you to live with another man!
I'd rather see you dead
than with somebody else, Shirahoshi!
It's either "Death or Marriage" for you!
As always, let me present you with a rose-emblazoned axe.
Accept it, Shirahoshi!
As proof of our marriage!
Captain? It's way off target.
Don't be silly! I don't miss!
I suspect.
It's coming back!
It's heading towards Ryugu Palace!
Ryugu Palace
Royal Palace of Ryugu Kingdom
Hey, hey, whoa! What's going on?
I'm just a pirate who came here looking for food!
Listen to me!
Hey!
She's loud! What should I do?
Princess Shirahoshi-sama's crying!
It's coming from Hard Shell Tower!
What are the tower guards doing?!
What?! Why is nobody with her?!
I'm sorry! The guard shifts were changing!
In any case, get to the tower now!
A human is... here in the room... trying to kill me!
Huh? No! Hey! That's not true!
I was hungry and I didn't know the food was yours!
What's that axe?!
Where'd it come from?!
Ryugu Palace, Main Entrance
Oh, boy!
When's the banquet happening? How long do we have to wait?
My stomach is growling...
But I don't have a stomach that could growl!
Hey!
Yes?
It doesn't look like we're having a banquet any time soon!
Does this mean that we've landed ourselves in trouble?
What should we do?!
I'm sorry that you came all the way here
but we've just received a call!
You Straw Hat people!
You are suspects in two ongoing investigations.
S-Suspects?! What do you mean?!
First, for multiple counts of Mermaid kidnapping!
We didn't do—
Second, you people are suspected
of being potential risks to Fishman Island...
according to Madame Sharley's future vision!
Huh? Future vision?
You don't even know if that'll happen for real!
Shut up!
What's wrong with them?!
Is this the right thing to do?
Therefore, we're here
to take you people into custody!
Catch them at any cost!
We have to protect Fishman Island!
Yeah!
Go!
Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
Somebody's coming!
I'm sorry to do this!
Are you alright?
Did you get hurt?
N-No!
You were crying louder
than usual—we were worried!
What are you—
Who opened this door?!
Was it an intruder?
I-I'm sorry to make you worry!
I think I had a bad dream...
H-Hey!
No, I heard somebody for sure!
No, that's... Um... Well...
My stomach made a noise!
A-Are you sure?
Who is it?!
Megalo! Welcome home!
Oh yes! There is something I must tell you.
It's about Straw Hat Luffy, the pirate who saved Megalo.
He is a suspect in the kidnapping of some missing Mermaid girls.
And due to Madame Sharley's prediction,
all of the Straw Hats are considered an unconfirmed but potential risk,
so we've decided to lock them
in the palace prison.
We took the swordsman, who arrived first,
into custody after he fell asleep from drinking.
The three members who just arrived are probably in custody by now, too.
But their captain—Straw Hat—who was with them,
might have noticed our intentions and ran away.
He is probably hiding somewhere in the palace so please be careful.
We'll catch the rest that're on the island and defend this country at any cost.
I just heard something.
Did you? Wasn't it just your imagination?
No, I'm sure I...
No, just your imagination!
If you say so.
Well, in any case...
I feel bad we have to arrest
the people who saved Megalo's life!
Princess-sama, you're acting strangely.
Are you hiding—
Minister of the Right, we have to go.
Oh, it's been five minutes already.
We're gonna go now.
Lock the doors tightly!
Thank you very much!
I was being very rude to you earlier.
Please forgive me!
I didn't know that you were the one
who saved Megalo's life.
May I call you Luffy-sama?
Sure.
Luffy-sama, you're a pirate;
does that mean you're also a bad person?
I don't know. You decide.
Okay.
Oh, they said that our soldiers took your friends into custody...
Yeah, but that's fine.
You guys can't keep them under control anyway.
Is that so?
Don't worry about it.
Now tell me, what's with that axe?
Who threw it? From where?
I know who did it...
His name is Vander Decken-sama.
He holds a grudge against me for refusing to marry him.
That man has attained the Devil's power
through the Mark-Mark curse.
He can strike me anytime, anywhere, since he's designated me as his mark.
That's why it's too dangerous for me
to leave Hard Shell Tower...
I'm hungry!
Yum-yum! Can I eat this?
Go ahead.
Yummy!
He wants to marry you but he's trying to kill you?
It doesn't make sense, does it?
It's been ten years already.
Ten years?! You must be bored!
On top of that, my father made a rule
that soldiers can't stay here more than five minutes.
Hmmm.
That's why Megalo is the only one I can talk to.
He's my dear friend.
So that's why they wanted to hold a banquet for us.
I'm sure it's canceled now.
I wonder why they want to put Megalo's liberators in prison.
I heard that Madame Sharley-sama's future visions
are unbelievably accurate.
That explains why everyone's afraid, but...
Anyway, you humans eat a lot
even though you're so small!
That hairy old man...
said we were gonna have a banquet...
but he kept getting scolded...
so I couldn't wait any longer...
and I followed the smell.
By the way, did they call you Princess?
Yes.
Are you the Mermaid Princess?
Yes. I am King Neptune's daughter.
My name is Shirahoshi.
Shirasu?
Shirahoshi.
Hmmm. That's hard to pronounce.
Oh, I wanna eat that too!
I don't think you're such a bad person.
Do you seek adventures since you're a pirate?
Uh-huh.
Oh yeah! Have you ever seen the sun?
There are stars in the night sky, aren't there?
And there are different kinds of flowers and hairy animals!
Have you ever been
to a green place called a "forest"?
Wait, wait! That's too many questions! Wait a moment!
Okay!
Oh, that's a big cheek pouch!
Push!
Stop it! What are you doing?!
P-P-Please...
Don't yell at me like that!
Luffy-sama is a scary man just as I thought...
Whoa, whoa! I didn't do anything
to make you cry! Stop!
I have never been yelled at by anyone before...
You may be big but you're a coward and a crybaby!
I don't like you!
What?!
No one ever said such a horrible thing to me...
How awful you are!
Please leave now!
I can't take it anymore!
I'm full! Thank you for the food!
So you've been here for ten years, huh?
That would probably make me sick!
Luffy-sama, please leave now!
Hey, isn't there anywhere you wanna go?
Huh?
Of course...
there are a lot of places I want to go to...
That's what I thought.
Then let's get you out of here!
What?
Let's go for a walk!
No... No, I'm not supposed to do that!
Why? Let's go!
You're gonna be okay!
Huh?
If something's thrown at you again, I'll deflect it!
Boy! How can he sleep under these circumstances?
He did drink like crazy, after all.
Hurry up!
Yes, sir!
Things sure are getting busy in the palace.
Did something happen?
Usopp-chin! Nami-chin! Brook-chin!
Catch them!
They're just three humans!
What're you gonna do?!
Guys! If you resist any more,
you're really gonna become criminals!
But there is no reason for us
to obey them, Camie-san.
I was looking forward to a banquet at Ryugu Palace.
They'll just arrest us if we don't resist!
They made unthinkable accusations against us first!
We will take on as many of you
as you like, if you so desire!
They're so strong even without the captain!
I can't believe it!
I don't know what we might do in the future.
But you can't arrest us now
for things we haven't even done!
The nose guy wasn't ever
that dependable, was he?!
Brook-chin and Nami-chin have gotten a lot tougher
than they were two years ago, too!
See? That's the prologue to the future
that has been predicted.
Yeah, right! If you guys didn't start this,
we wouldn't have to fight back in the first place!
He's right.
But this is nothing compared to the giant insects'
all-out attack on Bowin Islands!
Witness the power of my new weapon—Black Kabuto!
Bring it on!
Neptune-sama, we need your help!
I wonder if it's fair to arrest somebody
based on a prediction.
I need some time to think-jamon!
Thus,
you need to be in custody for now!
He's formidable!
Take this!
Zoro!
I thought you'd been captured!
I heard the sounds of a festival...
so I let myself out!
Captain Decken, we're here!
Wait there, Wadatsumi!
Fishman District, Noah
Uh-huh, okay!
This way, sir.
Thank you for waiting!
Vander Decken-sama is here!
Please!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We ran into a volcanic eruption.
So you're the notorious Hody?
I suspect?
You're notorious, too.
Nutty Vander Decken.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, a handshake?
That's no good.
Just a second.
I'm all set!
Never mind!
The pleasure is mine.
Nice to meet you, Hody Jones!
We're unbeatable on the seafloor now.
The worst of the worst coming together!
Decken! Decken!
Hody! Hody!
Neptune is a nuisance for both of us.
We have the same goal.
Beat the Neptune Army who take no pride
in being Fishmen or Mermaids...
And kill Neptune, the God of the Sea!
And...
We will destroy...
Ryugu Kingdom completely!
The Straw Hats are facing
the God of the Sea, Neptune's, army.
Neptune's soldiers attempt to break the bubbles
protecting Zoro's group to turn the tables of the battle.
Meanwhile, unidentified pirates continue attacking Hard Shell Tower where Luffy and Shirahoshi are.
The tensions inside Ryugu Palace continues to rise!
Next time, on One Piece:
"An Emergency Breaks Out
Ryugu Place Under Siege"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
An Emergency Breaks Out
Ryugu Place Under Siege