Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Welcome to the Grand Line!
Welcome to our town!
To the welcoming town, Whisky Peak!
Pirates! Welcome to our town!
This is delicious!
You're hopeless!
What fun!
Looks like there're about
100 bounty hunters here.
I'll fight you all...
...Baroque Works!
Humph...! Was it a secret?
If you know our secrets,
then we have no other choice but to kill you.
Another gravestone...
...will be added to the Cactus Rocks...
Kill him!
H... He disappeared...!
Explosion!
The Three-Sword Style!
Zoro vs. Baroque Works!
H-He's gone!
Wh-Where the heck did he disappear to?!
– Ahh!
– What?!
All right then.
Shall we?
How dare you mock us?!
Fire!
Idiots! They shot each other!
H-He disappeared again!
Darn! Kill him already!
It's just a single swordsman!
Let me ask you a question.
Are you sure that you need
to add only one gravestone?
There he is!
I-Idiots! Don't!
Are you gonna shoot me, too?!
Stop! Igarappa!
Where did that man disappear to?
Phew.
So that's a shotgun?
That thing sure is dangerous.
It seems he's good enough
that even we must be cautious.
Does he seriously think that
he can fight all of us by himself?
It's hard to believe that he challenged us
even after knowing we're with Baroque Works.
Ladies, please come closer...
I'm gonna sing Usopp Cheer #721!
So the welcoming town, Whisky Peak,
is the bounty hunters' nest, huh?
I thought it might be something like that.
Where did he go?! Find him!
The new recruits that I got in Loguetown,
Yubashiri and Kitetsu III...
This is a good chance to try you guys out in earnest.
I'm going to go all-out!
There you are!
Die!
Tsk! Dammit!
First, I'll try Yubashiri.
It's light! This is a good sword!
There he is! This way!
Hold it!
Looks like they found me!
He went up!
Welcome!
Whoa! That thing's dangerous!
This is it for you.
Miss Monday!
Ahh... That was an expensive drink.
What a waste!
What was that feeling in my hand just now?!
How sharp this Kitetsu III is!
A legendary sword cuts only
when its master wishes it,
but this one is a problem child.
So this is what a cursed sword is like.
Huh?
Lord have mercy!
I beg you for mercy.
Lord have mercy! Please save us!
Merciful Lord Blinding Powder!
You should use such a cheap trick
on someone with a pure heart.
I used the back of the blade, so forgive me.
He went further up!
Corner him!
He's over there!
Cut him off!
Go around to the back!
Okay!
Did someone step on me?
Mademoiselle, would you care to dance with me?
Darn... Is this all the treasure they have?
Some bounty hunters' nest this is!
Whisky Peak sure is a crappy town.
There's nowhere to escape up there!
S-Stop it!
Help me! Help me!
The ladder's falling!
Ahh! He's jumping over here!
Shoot him!
Two-Sword Style:
Hawk Wave!
Watch out. That place is unstable.
What?
That was close! It grazed me!
Don't try our patience.
There's no man who can best my strength.
This is the end of you.
Superhuman...
Brass Knuckles!
We've wast...
Ma-ma...
We've wasted time, but we finally settled it. The End!
What?!
M... Miss Monday!
What's the matter, muscle woman?
Didn't you want to have a contest of strength?
Well?!
Shall we continue, Baroque Works?
Fighting isn't a joke.
M-Miss Monday was overpowered...!
I-Impossible! This can't be true...!
I-I got it!
The Navy made a mistake on that wanted poster.
I see. It makes sense if this guy has
a 30 million-Berry bounty on his head.
He is the real captain.
Right. I thought it was strange
that such a namby-pamby guy
was worth 30 million Berries.
But, even so, how disgraceful...
If we lose against one pirate swordsman,
we'll be held responsible since the
boss put us in charge of this town.
It seems that it's finally our turn to fight.
You may know this, but with members of Baroque Works,
the smaller his number, the higher
his level and destructive power are.
The three of us, Mr. 9,
Mr. 8 and Miss Wednesday
are agents with a single digit number,
which means we're powerful people
who are beyond comparison
to those you just beat.
Humph.
Aren't titles useless when it comes to fighting?
The stronger one wins. That's all.
Igarappa!
Let's go, Miss Wednesday!
Okay, Mr. 9!
Come, Karoo!
I didn't say "give me your hand"!
Come over here!
Now, show him your quick speed
that leaves leopards in the dust!
Who said "sit"?!
What the hell is that?
Can you afford to let your guard down?
Follow my acrobatics, if you can!!
Hot-blooded...
...Bat of Guts!
These're metallic bats.
Be careful not to chip your blades on them.
What's the matter?
Are you so frightened you can't move?
What happened to your proud acrobatics?
If you wanna see it that bad, watch carefully!
Ahh...
Don't they have anyone better?
Anyone better? That would be me!
Be prepared... Mr. Bushido!
Now, take in my allure to your heart's content!!
Charming Perfume Dance!
Good boy...
I'll finish you off with... Peacock Slasher!
Go, Karoo!
You went too far!
Fighting these guys is starting to get embarrassing...
He escaped below using that hole.
That's useless...
Get a good taste of how frightening I really am!
That shotgun of his is a pain...
How should I close the distance?
Ka-boom!
How dare you beat me like that earlier?!
You won't get away with it!
You fell on your own!
Home Run Sneaky Bat!
I tied up one of your arms!
It's an iron chain...
You caught him.
Mr. 8, do it now!
I won't let you escape!
That's right. Don't move.
If you make a stupid move,
I'll have to take your precious friend's life as well.
Good job, Miss Wednesday.
You can't escape or attack now.
That idiot! At least wake up
when you're being held hostage!
Prepare to open fire!
Preparations completed!
What?!
Igarappappa!
Is he a toy?!
Igarappappa! Igarappappa!
Luffy! Let me use your belly!
What?!
Okay! Done!
It's finally become a quiet, nice night.
Huh? Why am I outside?
Oh, well. I'm sleepy. I'm gonna sleep.
I never thought that four agents
with numbers under 12 would lose!
But where are you planning to escape to?!
In any case, we'll hide somewhere
until they leave this island and...
Ahh! The Unluckies!!
H-Hold on a sec!
We're not running away!
It's not that...
Please! Don't report to the boss!
Hold it!
This town is quite lively despite how late it is.
Ha! What a boring job he gave us...
...sending us all the way to the front lines...
Hm?
I can't fall in a place like this.
I've got an important mission...
How pitiful...
...losing against just one swordsman...
Hm?!
Mr. 5! Miss Valentine!
Are you guys kidding around? Huh?
After all, this is the difference
between our rank and yours, isn't it?
Did you come to laugh at us?
That, too, but...
Of course, we're here under our mission.
Thank goodness.
If you help us, that man is no match for us!
That's right.
Please beat that swordsman right away.
Huh? Enough with the bad jokes.
Us help you?
Did you really think that we'd come all the way
to the end of the Grand Line for that?
What? Then what mission
did you come here for?
You really have no idea?
There're criminals here that
are big enough for the boss
to send us here to deal with.
These're the boss' words:
"They've found out my secrets."
Of course, I don't even know what
kind of secrets they are, but...
...our company's motto is "mystery."
No matter whose identity it is,
the rule is that you never nose around.
If someone finds out the boss' secrets,
that's, of course, a sin worthy of death.
So, when we very carefully
investigated who learned his secrets...
Oh boy, we found out that a VIP
from a certain kingdom
sneaked into Baroque Works.
A certain kingdom? W-Wait a sec!
Although I'm wearing a crown,
I'm not a king or anything!
It's just my hobby!
We're not talking about you!
The sinners are those who're missing
from Alabasta Kingdom right now...
They know! It's all over!
Die! Igarappappa!
I won't let you lay a finger on our princess!
On my name as Squad Captain
of Alabasta Kingdom Security!
Igaram!!
Igaram, the Squad Captain
of Alabasta Kingdom Security.
And its princess, Nefertari Vivi.
In the name of the Baroque Works' boss,
we'll eliminate you two.
This isn't good...
I left Luffy down there...
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Ah yasashi uta nee
Ah, gentle song
Todoke futari no tame ni
Make it there for us
Nami ga saratta chisana suna no oshiro
After a wave washed away that little sand castle
nagareru kumo o miagete naki souna egao
You looked up at the passing clouds with a sad smile
Moshi mo sekai juu ni teki shika inai nara
If you find the world is full of enemies,
senaka o makasete
I've got your back
Shinjiru kimochi o wasurenaide
Don't lose faith
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Ah itoshii hito nee
Ah, my love
Zutto daiteite ageru
I'll hold you in my arms forever
Watashi ga iru yo
You've got me!
Why do I have to help Nami make money?!
– Zoro!!
– What's the matter, Luffy? Oh, you too?!
I'll beat up an ungrateful jerk like you!
What're you talking about?!
Shut up! I won't forgive you! Fight me!
Are you really serious?!
Next time, on One Piece:
All-Out Battle!
Luffy vs. Zoro, Mysterious Grand Duel!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
All-Out Battle!
Luffy vs. Zoro,
Mysterious Grand Duel!