Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hody's merciless plot puts Fishman Island in unprecedented danger!
Weren't you listening to what I said?
I will save Fishman Island and Shirahoshi...
Luffy-sama...
...and keep my promise to a friend.
Straw Hat...
I'll protect...
...everything!
Scoring Song: Blizzard Slice!
Impact Wolf!
Hoofprint: Palme!
Franky...
Squid! Squid! Squid!
...Radical Beam!
Vagabond Drill!
Hell Memories!
Purgatory...
...Demon Slash!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
I will stop the Noah!
Keep falling, Noah!
Kill all the pride-less Fishmen!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gatling!
"Stop, Noah! Desperate Elephant Gatling!"
Even those demon-like officers are a joke to them. That's how strong they are!
Stay alert!
Look up! You're in danger!
What?!
--Wadatsumi is... --...Falling toward us!
You should've dropped him elsewhere, you worthless chef!
Shut up! I'll make someone fall onto you next time!
That was amazing, Sanji.
Hey Chopper! Could you shrink yourself a little bit?
You're upstaging the giant robot!
Franky, I loved the beam!
That robot was totally useless.
Oh! Nami-san!
What?
Please wear a miniskirt.
Shut up!
That's just what I'd expect from Luffy-kun's friends.
He did it!
This time for sure! Luffy-san beat Hody!
--Did you hear that? --Yeah...
The Straw Hats defeated the New Fishman Pirates!
Hey.
The Noah!
The Noah is right there!
Run!
It's gonna destroy us along with the island!
If we stay here any longer, Neptune's army will bar us in the plaza!
Hurry up! Those crazy officers are gone now!
Oh my goodness! How is the evacuation going?!
Only a few citizens have escaped to the sea.
Most people are still here on the island!
Are you okay?
Is it too late?!
Can't you do anything, Straw Hat?!
Straw Hat!
The threat of rebellion is now gone but...
This is it!
No, not yet!
What?
He is not...
...giving up yet!
Straw Hat Luffy-san is...
...trying his best...
...to destroy...
...the Noah!
Destroy the Noah?!
Trying to destroy it?
Destroy that giant ship?!
Really?! That's impossible!
Prepare for the worst, guys!
Yeah. Let's just stand by him.
Luffy-san!
Luffy-sama!
If he can destroy the Noah before it hits the island, we'll be okay but...
...if he can't,
Fishman Island will fall!
Give it everything you got, Luffy!
--Luffy-san! --We're counting on you, Luffy!
Luffy!
Luffy-kun!
What's wrong?!
I'm not gonna run!
Don't be ridiculous! Can't you see the Noah?!
I know! I know, but...
...Straw Hat's heroic actions bring back memories of...
...what happened 20 years ago when I was a kid!
There was one human that the people of this kingdom thanked with all our hearts!
What a haul!
Hey wait!
No!
Who are you?! Do you wanna die?!
You got to be kidding me! Why is he...
...taking the Fishmen's side?!
Neptune helped me when we were young and we exchanged
cups of sake as a pledge of friendship!
Don't kill me! I promise I'll never kidnap Mermaids and Fishmen!
Don't mess with my friend's country!
You wet-nosed brats!
I declare that this island is my territory now!
Are you talking about Whitebeard?!
Are you saying you trust them like you trusted the great pirate?!
Because,
to be honest, I don't even like humans
and this is the Fishmen's kingdom,
but they...
Our minds were made up when we arrived at the plaza that,
along with Jinbe, we wouldn't let anyone harm the island!
Leave it all up to us, Brother-hoshi!
We're friends, right?
He said such things and they're all risking their lives...
Straw Hat...
Don't lose, Straw Hat!
Yeah, Straw Hat, we're supporting you!
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
--You're a human and you're fighting for us! --We're not gonna run!
Go, Big Bro Straw Hat!
Please save Fishman Island, Straw Hat!
Go, Straw Hat!
We believe in you!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-chan!
--Straw Hat! --Straw Hat!
Stop, Noah!
Stop!
I only broke half of it so far!
Luffy-sama!
The wound is opening up...
Stay away!
Stay there and watch!
I need to keep destroying this thing now!
Stop, ship!
--Straw Hat! --Straw Hat!
Luffy, go for it!
Break it into pieces!
Super!
I'm sorry, Father.
Destroying the Noah is the only way.
Straw Hat!
The Ship of Promise...
But it cannot be helped.
People's lives are the most important.
I am sorry. I cannot keep the promise-jamon,
Joyboy!
Just a little more to go!
Please...
Stop.
Who is it?!
Luffy-sama! Please stop!
Luffy-sama, you have to stop!
Move, Wimpyhoshi! I need to destroy it to save the island!
It's okay now!
It's not okay! Everybody's on the island!
The Noah is already...
...stopped!
Sea Kings? Why?
Luffy-sama is angry!
Hey, this is no time for crying!
I don't quite understand, either.
But the Noah is stopped now!
What happened?!
What's going on here? The Sea Kings stopped the ship!
Luffy-sama! The wound is opening up again!
You are bleeding a lot!
Well... Well... That's good...
...as long as the ship is stopped.
I'm glad everybody's...
...safe.
Luffy-sama!
He's fine.
Boy, what a human!
He is a very strong one, isn't he?
If we were late, we could still have saved the island
but the Noah would have been completely destroyed.
I'm glad that we made it!
I'm glad that Princess Shirahoshi called us!
What? I didn't do anything and I was just sad...
No, you were moved by Straw Hat boy's strong determination
and prayed.
You wished strongly to help him save the island.
Our power is your power.
We helped him because you called us.
A-All people of the kingdom.
Wh-What just happened here was beyond words
but it happened for sure!
The Noah is stopped!
The ship didn't get destroyed completely
and Fishman Island has been saved!
Straw Hat did it!
--Straw Hat! --So we're safe, aren't we?
Yeah!
Straw Hat!
I'm so relieved!
--Yeah! --Oh, he did it!
Luffy did it!!
Fishman Island is saved.
However, in his fight to achieve this...
...Luffy is in critical condition with a multitude of wounds.
Yet the Fishmen, still bound by the island's past...
...hesitate to come to his aid.
Just when Luffy is almost out of time...
...a single man's actions alter the course of history.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Secret Revealed! The Truth about the Ancient Weapon!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!