Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates
who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil.
If I join the Warlords,
Aladdin and the others who don't want to be pirates...
...can live in this country without being chased
under the amnesty of the Government.
Big Brother is dead!
We'll go our own way, just like we used to!
The Sun Pirates split into three groups
and went separate ways.
"Shaking Fishman Island! A Celestial Dragon Drifts In!"
FISHMAN ISLAND
I'm back!
I still can't believe that this day has come!
When we were the Celestial Dragons' slaves,
we were hopeless and all we had was hatred toward them.
We got away from the Celestial Dragons thanks to Boss Tai
but still they were looking for us.
I thought being a pirate was the only way to survive.
But now we can even go back to our hometown without hiding!
We are free!
Captain! No, Brother Jinbe!
I'll never forget what you've done for us!
Don't be so dramatic.
I won't, but we know what you did.
You needed the amnesty of the Government to help free us.
That's why you joined the Warlords.
It's not as though you wanted to join them.
Quit this chatting and go to your family already!
Look! They're becoming impatient.
--Honey... --Dad!
--Baby... --Just go to them.
--Dad! --Honey!
Aladdin, you were a slave just like them.
But now you can get off of the ship finally.
Jinbe.
We will no longer be chased as renegade slaves.
All of us can stay with family without fear.
But just like the mark of the Celestial Dragons,
because of our terrible experience as slaves, our hatred toward humans...
...will never go away!
Of course I understand what Brother Tai truly meant...
But...
I can't believe that Boss Jinbe
is becoming a tool of the World Government... or humans!
Did he forget who killed Tiger-san?
I've lost respect for Boss Jinbe.
I knew that there were many islanders
who didn't like the idea of me joining the Warlords.
THE RYUGU PALACE
Thanks to Jinbe's momentous decision,
now we have a relationship with the World Government.
In order to use this opportunity to establish friendly relations with humans,
I will keep trying hard!
But even if it's for his friends,
I can't believe Jinbe took on such a big burden-jamon.
When he gets an order from the World Government,
he has no choice but to fight...
...whether he likes it or not-jamon.
He will put himself in harm's way and occasionally
his blood will be spilled.
I know.
I won't let Jinbe's sacrifice end up wasted.
I have to do my best, as well!
But don't push yourself too hard.
Because I don't want you to suffer another hangover-jamon!
Oh...
And then something happened that would
change Queen Otohime's life forever.
An uninvited visitor came to the island...
Ryugu Kingdom! Ryugu Kingdom!
This is border patrol speaking!
A huge wrecked ship is seeking emergency entry into the country!
What are you waiting for?! Accept them already...
It can't be true!
A Celestial Dragon is on board!
What?!
King Neptune!
A Celestial Dragon?!
Accept them!
--Send a rescue team immediately! --Yes, ma'am!
I'll meet them myself!
Otohime-sama!
What is a Celestial Dragon doing on the seafloor?
It's a Celestial Dragon's ship!
Must've been attacked by some deep-sea creature.
They look down on us Fishmen.
How come they were in such deep water?
Hurry up!
Damn! They are all dead! What weaklings!
Bring me a breathing mask now, you fishes!
A WORLD NOBLE (CELESTIAL DRAGON) SAINT MYOSGARD
I can't stand this Fishman's smell!
Bring me a mask now!
Hurry up and save my life, you fools!
He has no respect of us!
That's not how you ask somebody to help you!
Doctor!
I need a doctor!
--Is a medical team here? --They're here but...
...they don't know what to do with "it."
We have to kill him.
They are the scum of the world!
The Seven Warlords are nothing!
I'm not gonna work for the World Government
or anybody, even if they beg me to!
That's our Captain Vander Decken!
Jinbe is no match for me as a pirate in the first place,
no match at all, I suspect!
Hm? What's going on at the harbor?
Hey.
Captain, he said that a Celestial Dragon is here.
Celestial Dragon?
Looks like his ship has wrecked and he's asking for help.
Sounds like fun. Let's go see it.
This wasn't how it was supposed to be...
What?! The Fishman slaves went back to their island?!
Why is it, My Daddy?
Here is the thing, My Son.
A Fishman named Jinbe just joined the Seven Warlords.
Jinbe?
And the Sun Pirates which he belongs to were hiding all those slaves
but their evasion charges were dropped by the amnesty of the
Government so they went back home, My Son.
I think the slaves who escaped from my place are among them, My Daddy.
I'm sure of it.
It makes me sick to think that they are living a
free and easy life now.
I'm gonna go get them back, My Daddy!
Because I've spent a lot of money to collect those Fishman slaves!
Gee! I didn't know that the deep sea was such a horrifying place.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
What?
It's been a while, huh? Myosgard.
How dare you address me without my title! Oh?
Oh, you were my slaves!
You just have to come home with me!
I didn't give you my permission to be free, fishes!
D-Don't do it, guys!
He's a Celestial Dragon!
If you kill him, the amnesty will become void!
Don't do it, fools! Know your place!
Who do you think I am?!
I'm... I'm...
The Navy admirals will come to the aid of a
Celestial Dragon in danger in the world above.
That's why people are afraid of your folk.
But you're on Fishman Island at the seafloor.
As long as the islanders stay quiet, whatever happens to you here,
they'll think it was an accident.
He's right...
--I won't say anything! --Me too! Of course!
He's barely alive. He's gonna die soon anyway!
Let him suffer the same way that you slaves did!
--Kill him! --Make him suffer!
Show him no mercy!
What's going on?
I thought I was a respected man...
For the life of me...
I can't forgive you!
Hey, don't!
--Do it! --Kill him!
Don't do it!
You stupid fishes!
Queen Otohime!!
The Queen has been shot!
Queen Otohime...
Everybody, drop your gun!
Children are watching!
Aladdin!
Where is the Celestial Dragon who's ship was wrecked?!
I just got here, myself.
Boss Jinbe!
Our mother rushed out of the palace!
What?
Brother-sama, who are the Celestial Dragons?
They are humans, Shirahoshi.
Humans?
There are quite a few humans out there and they are the scary ones.
I heard some gunshots too.
Let's go.
O-Otohime-sama...
It's just a scratch.
Why do you protect him?
You don't know what he did to us in the past!
He treated us like we were animals, not even slaves.
I can feel your anguish - it's very painful.
Mother-sama!
I know it's hard but...
...you can't plant your anger and resentment toward humans in children's mind!
They need a chance to meet humans and figure them out on their own.
So, please!
Don't tell the people on the island anything!
Neither the tragedy we endured nor of our anger towards humans!
Brother Tai...
Watch out, Mother-sama!
Don't move!
Oh no! Your Majesty!
Mother!
That bastard!
Queen?
To a Celestial Dragon like me,
the Queen of a fish country is just another commoner...
...or even less!
What an asshole!
Mother-sama!
You fools! What are you doing?!
Get me a mask and a doctor! Otherwise...
Mother-sama!!
What?!
It's the Sea Kings!!
What was that?
It didn't look like a coincidence...
Shirahoshi... Don't tell me you are...
What's the matter, Captain?
According to the family legend, a long long time ago, there was a Mermaid...
...who possessed mysterious power that could even control the Sea Kings!
Vander Decken I decided to look into the legend and headed for the seafloor.
My ancestors! I finally found her!
Shirahoshi is the legendary Mermaid?
You did it, Captain!
Shh! Don't let anybody hear about it.
It's a secret legend that only my family knows, I suspect!
If I can control the Sea Kings as I wish, I can do anything I want.
I can have anything I want!
So, what are we gonna do now?
Kidnap Princess Shirahoshi?
First, I have to marry her.
What?!
But she's still a kid now.
Hmmm... that's the problem!
Aladdin...
Let me treat him.
Thank you.
I'll treat you next.
A few weeks later,
when the Celestial Dragon who's life has been saved was
about to leave for home,
Queen Otohime did an unexpected thing.
I'll get even with you!
Although I'm a respected World Noble, you insulted me
and harassed me terribly.
You fishes, I'll make you feel sorry for what you did!
Is that what we get for saving his life?
We provided a ship and crew for him to go home!
How could he say that?!
We shouldn't let him go! It's dangerous to this island!
Wait a minute!
You seem like you have more to say.
In that case, I'll come with you to the world above.
To the world above?!
That's too dangerous, Otohime-sama!
Mother-sama!
Wait-jamon, Otohime! I won't let you do that!
If you wish to negotiate with the Nobles, I'll go!
I'm sure humans won't catch you
since you're the King and a Great Knight.
Then let me...
No, there is no point if it's a strong man like you!
We have to show that
even a weak woman can go there and return home
if we want to prove to our nation it's totally safe up there.
I'm physically more fragile than anyone - that's why it makes
more sense for me to go.
--Mother-sama! --Mother-sama!
Otohime-sama!
Where are you going, Otohime-sama?
Otohime...
Trust the woman who you chose to be your wife
and the humans.
She's just a fish queen - how arrogant!
Mother-sama!
Jinbe...
No one can stop her.
All we can do is trust her and wait.
Your Majesty! Please be careful!
Otohime-sama!
Mother-sama!
Otohime brought a single paper back from the surface.
It represents a light of hope for Fishman Island.
Gathering numerous signatures,
her dream becomes the dream of all of Fishman Island.
Fishman Island seemed ready to change,
when all of a sudden,
a gunshot rings out across all of Fishman Island!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Sudden Tragedy! A Gunshot Shuts Down the Future!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!