Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and in order to move on
to the next stage—the New World—
they return to Sabaody Archipelago!
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
Hey, you! Don't you know who I am?!
Stand aside, unless you want me to kill you and rip out your guts!
You're not Straw Hat,
you piece of trash!
What?!
Now I get it.
These fake Straw Hats had them fooled.
And I don't know why,
but the real Straw Hat is here too.
That was close!
I-It's the same face...
It's the same face on the wanted poster!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
Jet Pistol!
That Straw Hat...
He used Haki!
Luffy! I knew it!
Why are you constantly
in the middle of some huge fight?!
It's been so long!
I wonder how everyone's doing?
I'm so happy!
I came to check up on you just in case.
But I see you're fine.
Uh-huh!
Rayleigh!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Everyone Together
Luffy, Setting Out for the New World
It seems like things are getting rather hectic over there...
What are you doing?!
Take down Straw Hat already!
Oops!
Oh?
Hurry up, Luffy!
Rayleigh, thanks for everything!
Well then, Rayleigh...
Thanks again... for everything!
I'm off!
Yeah...
They went that way!
After them!
Don't let them get away!
Go all the way to the top!
The Straw Hats are heading for Grove #42!
Catch them no matter what!
What was that?
Dark King Rayleigh!
It's my student's farewell!
I want it to be proper!
Wh-What's this line?
I'd advise against crossing it.
Oh, bubble packs! And lots of them!
What's inside?
It's all provisions.
I'm sure everyone's stomach
has grown these past two years.
I'll make plenty to eat later!
Really?! Can't wait to eat your food again!
We found them! Over here!
Oh? They have us surrounded!
Guess we have no choice...
All troops, charge!
Understood!
I... wanna become a flea...
What's wrong?! What are you...
I wanna become a mite...
What?!
What happened?!
I... I...
I wanna become a louse...
Hey, isn't that...
I knew you people were behind this.
Honestly!
Why are you still here anyway?!
Oh! You're the lady from Thriller Bark!
Who was she again?
What about you?
What're you still doing here?
How can you speak to me like that?
I was the one who brought you here!
Without me, you'd probably be...
Know your place!
Sniff, sniff...
A real woman... A real woman...
Well, duh!
Are you sick in the head or something?!
Anyway, just hurry up and go!
I saw some warships
closing in on the island!
What?!
Soon, there'll be no way out!
That's no good.
But it's strange...
I can't move from this spot.
What nonsense are you spouting?!
Real ladies are the best!
I'm... human trash...
What's that?
There you are!
Grove #42, the Straw Hats' meeting spot
Oh!
That voice!
Usopp-saan! Naaami-san! Robiiin-saaan!
FFFranky-saaaaaan!
Brook!
I can't believe it!
You really gave up stardom!
Attaboy!
It's been a long time, everybody!
The two of you have become even more beautiful!
Now then, Nami-san...
It's been two years, so...
Oh, are you gonna sing something?
May I look at your panties...
What do you think?!
I didn't show them to you
two years ago and I won't now!
My chest is shaking with joy at our reunion!
Even though... I don't even have a chest!
Hey, our superstar is convulsing.
I swear, none of you have matured at all.
Incidentally, I don't see everybody on board yet.
No need to worry.
Chopper went to get the others.
Hey!
Here they come at last!
You guys!
I brought them!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Hey!
Luffy-san! I missed you so much!
You guys look more like men now!
We're all together again at last!
Finally...
Guys!
What?!
Sanji?!
Well then, thank you!
Say "hi" to everyone in the Birdie Kingdom for me!
Usopp! Is Sanji alright?!
O-O-One beautiful woman...
Hey, stay with me!
Two beautiful woman...
Hey, this is bad, Chopper!
You have to stop the bleeding!
F-F-Franky, you're...
What's the matter?
Is there something that concerns you-mecha?
"Mecha"?! I wanna play!
Wait, Luffy!
I don't know what's so great and besides...
it looks like the Navy is already here!
Oh no! When'd they get here?!
There's three warships!
Hey, are we gonna fight back or what?!
They're gonna sink us!
Fire! Sink that ship!
Not good!
Those'll hit us!
Slave...
Arrow!
Wh-What just happened?
T-That's...
The Kuja Pirates!
Who...
dares to sail a warship...
in my path?
That's the Kuja's insignia!
The Kuja?
They're a band of female pirates
led by the might Pirate Empress—a Warlord.
A Warlord?!
Her name is Boa Hancock.
Rumor has it anyone who witnesses her beauty
is overwhelmed and turns to stone!
Oh, so bright! She's dazzling!
Her beauty knows no bounds!
She's the most beautiful woman I've ever seen!
The most beautiful woman?!
Where is she?!
Beautiful woman?! Beautiful woman?!
Beautiful woman... Beautiful woman...
Beautiful woman... Beautiful...
B—
He turned to stone!
Oh, it's Hancock and the others!
Move your ship, Boa Hancock!
Are you trying to interfere with our mission?!
Cease these accusations.
I merely do not wish to let you pass.
H-How selfish!
Is that a problem?
Go, Luffy... Now's your chance!
She just... winked at us...
We're saved.
Now's our chance to set sail!
You know that Warlord?
Yeah, I ended up on Maiden Island.
They're all friends of mine.
Maiden Island? The legendary island populated entirely by women?
It really exists?
Friends with the Pirate Empress?!
Hey, you better have actually
been training during the last two years!
I did. It went great.
Damn... It's not fair... It's not fair...
What's the matter, Sanji?
Whoa, so those are Luffy's friends!
There are a bunch of creatures
I've never seen before.
One, two, three, four...
They seem fun!
Alright, prepare to set sail!
Yes, Nami-swan!
Yeah!
What's wrong, Usopp?
I was just thinking... did you guys take out
all the soldiers on your way here?
No, I still heard a bunch of them shouting
while we were flying over here.
Well, I don't see any of them coming at us from the coast.
This is the Third Reinforcement Platoon!
Can anybody hear us?!
What's wrong?!
What's going on?!
We can't reach Grove #42!
Why not?
W-Well...
We encountered some gigantic bugs
that're blocking our path!
What?! Bugs?!
What are these things?!
Shoot!
I will not let you get in the way of Usopp'n's new adventure'n!
When men part ways,
we don't shed tears'n.
I wish you luck, Usopp'n!
If they're not coming, that's fine too.
We're in luck if they ran into trouble.
Let's just leave now!
Nami, lead the way!
You can count on me!
Alright!
Fourth Platoon, reporting in!
I'm sorry, but this sudden downpour has soaked our gunpowder, our weapons are useless!
Downpour?! Where is it raining?!
Sabaody Archipelago is supposed to be sunny today!
Don't use lightning!
You don't want to hurt any civilians, do you?
The bubbles really do get in the way around here...
Even so, the winds are favorable!
What a pleasant way to drift to the Sabaody Archipelago!
Pleasant because Nami-chan is herself such a lovely girl!
Do your best!
Weatheria will be lonely without you though!
Oh, it's expanding!
What? This jelly inflates?
Woah! It's a bubble roof!
Listen up, guys.
A coated ship is less susceptible
to all kinds of pressure.
In other words, if we remove
the buoyancy pouch supporting us,
the coated Sunny will lose buoyancy and sink.
That's how it works.
I see.
Too complicated, huh?
Anyway, unfurl the sails!
Sails?
A coated sailing ship
is propelled by ocean currents instead of the wind.
I thought we'd get there automatically once we went under!
Alright, we better hurry before the Navy catches up!
Fifth Platoon, reporting from Grove #42's center!
It's an emergency!
All the Second Platoon troops,
dispatched ahead of us, have become negative...
What're you saying? Negative?!
I wanna become moss...
I'm finished. I'd rather be a water flea...
According to reports, Straw Hat Luffy
fled on a giant bird!
A bird?! What are you guys doing there?!
We're in battle with an unidentified enemy!
Damn, that bastard!
Nothing but trouble up to the very end!
I'll have to find a new toy now...
Navy reinforcements!
Just when we were about to leave...
Everyone!
Straw Hat's ship is within range!
Wait a minute!
A giant bird is coming our way!
He's—
They're coming from behind too!
I got this!
What do you think, Nami-san?
Did you see...
how much I've grown?
Sanji!
Answer, Fifth Platoon!
What's the situation?!
W-We're...
We're facing an... unexpected contingency...
Please, stop!
You're turning down my invitation?
How could you?!
Maybe they're just shy?
You don't have to be embarrassed!
Let's have tea together!
M-My heart... My heart feels like it's gonna shatter!
Oh my, what a cute face!
No, don't do it!
What's wrong?
Answer, Fifth Platoon!
Sanji-kyun, now's your chance!
Hey, hey, what's wrong, Sanji?!
I-I-I don't know... Suddenly,
it felt like somebody just tried to rip out my heart.
I just removed the buoyancy pouch!
Roger that!
What about the sails?
Ready at any time!
Are we ready to set sail, Nami?
Yes, at your command, Captain.
Alright...
You guys!
There's a whole lot of stuff I want to talk to you about!
But never mind that!
I just want to thank you for going along
with my selfish request for the last two years!
It won't be the first time. Or the last.
Got that right!
You've always been like this!
Rear Admiral-dono,
the pirate ship's submerging!
What?! Dammit...
You fools!
Do you have any idea...
how dangerous they are? Hey!
Rear Admiral!
Take care, Luffy...
Unfurl the sails!
Yes!
Yeah!
Set sail!!
Let's go to Fishman Island!
Having departed for the New World,
the Straw Hats are mesmerized
by the alien underwater scenery.
Franky tells the crew
about a man they owe a great debt.
Meanwhile something dark lurks behind the Sunny.
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Surprising Fact
The Man Who Guarded the Sunny"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Surprising Fact
The Man Who Guarded the Sunny