Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
Those ranked Lieutenant
Commander or below, stay put!
To the two hundred elite Captains and
Commanders, go take them out quickly!
Get them!
Recapture Nico Robin!
I'm part of the Straw Hats, too.
When we fight, we fight together.
Hold strong until Luffy comes!
I'll pursue that woman who threatens
the World Government's plans
to the very ends of the
earth and eliminate her...
...in the name of dark justice!
We came to take Robin away from all that!
Jet Stamp!
Six King Gun!
Luffy!
--I got him!
--Watch out!
Hey! Now's not the time
to be spacing out, Soge...
Luffy!
What're you doing?!
Get up!
Luffy!
Fists Full of Emotion!
Luffy Unleashes Gatling with All His Might
Weapons Left!
Super...!
Commander!
What's with those pirates?!
What a crazy brawl! They're holding
their own against Captains!
Is that woman a power holder?!
I'll take care of her. Stay back!
Cien Fleurs:
Flip!
Here we go! Thunder Ball!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Done!
So I guess these guys aren't
the typical small fries, huh?
Two-Sword Style...
...Hawk Wave!
Who's next?!
Usopp...
Luffy!
Get up!
U-Usopp...
S-So... you came?
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
I came here to rescue Robin!
I didn't come here to see your face!
Geez... He's such a...
Hey, you! Boss cat of CP9!
I'm talking to you!
Now, I'll take you on! Bring it on!
Th-That's right! I'm your opponent!
Now, don't be surprised when I tell you this!
I'm the great Captain Usopp,
a pirate among pirates,
the great warrior of the sea who
has 8,000 men under his command!
I've traveled all over the Grand Line
and wreaked havoc on every single island!
Anyone who falls into my hands...
...even you guys, the World Government...
...will be crushed by the tip of my little finger!
If that pisses you off, then bring it on!
You no-good little kitten!
Hey...
Hey... don't! Don't! Hey!
Leave him alone!
You've already lost.
I have no business with you.
They're all gonna be killed anyway.
You just stay there and watch.
All right, come on, boss cat!
I'm gonna blow you away!
Are you stupid?! Stop it, Usopp! He'll kill you!
Shut up! What can you do
when you're almost dead?!
He's mine! I'm gonna beat him up!
Then get up already!
Then don't look like you're about to die!
It's not like you!
Even though there's nothing but smoke
above us, we can still see the sky!
We can see the sea, too!
This isn't... This isn't hell!
Don't look like you're about to die, you jerk!
Don't make us worry, you bastard!
Are you done?
You'd better be prepared.
I know...
This isn't hell or anything.
Luffy...!
Defeat him! We'll all go back together, Luffy!
Of course!
So you can still move...
I never said... I gave in.
Until I defeat you...
...I won't... sink to the ground ever again!
I'm terminating Life Return.
I've had enough with you guys' farce.
I'll crush you with pure power once and for all!
Don't worry about your friends, Straw Hat.
As you wish... to be together with them again...
...I'll send you all to the same hell!
Spots!
They've given us quite a bit of trouble!
If we're just careful about that thunderbolt...
Ahhh! There's another cloud!
Guys, don't gather in one place!
Spread out and attack all at...
What is it, at a time like this?!
What'd you do that for?!
--Guys!
--Hm?!
When the lightning strikes,
please be careful not to get electrocuted!
Thunder Ball!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Good job, pirate ladies!
We're okay, so go up there
and help the guys already!
Leave the raccoon dog guy to us!
I'm not a raccoon dog. I'm a reindeer.
Okay! Then we'll leave Chopper to you!
--Robin!
--Yeah.
When everyone's fighting so hard,
to think that I can't do anything...
It's frustrating...!
Everyone! Hang in there!
H-Hey! What do you mean run away?!
It's our duty to guard this place!
This isn't the time for that!
This island will be entirely eliminated!
Click. Beep...
--Beep... beep... beep...
--Dammit!
Bingo!
Luffy...
Victory Bird!
Dammit! What's the deal
with them?! I can't hit them!
Hey! I beat them!
Oh, I see! All my shots
must've actually hit them!
That's right! I'm the Sniper King, Sogeking!
I was born on the...
Take this!
I'll show you the power of the Berry-Berry Fruit!
Dammit! I can't make a wrong move here!
You can't do anything, can you?!
Thanks!
Hey you, hold on a sec.
If you like flying so much...
Hey! D-Don't!
Weapons Left!
Be careful! There are some
power holders among them!
They could say the same about us!
Treinta Fleurs: Clutch!
So you're Roronoa Zoro?
And if I am?
I'll defeat you!
Fine!
I ate the Rust-Rust Fruit and became a rust man.
You can't defeat me.
Dammit! My Yubashiri...
I'll turn all your proud swords to rust.
Interesting...
I'll test you.
Now you get it, right?
You can't defeat me with swords!
I... I can't move my body!
I rusted your joint. I'll continue
until your entire body is rusted!
Dammit!
Firebird Star!
Are you okay, Zoro-kun?!
Gum-Gum... Jet Pistol!
I'm not gonna take that a second time!
Ultimate Radius...
Six King Gun!
Until I defeat you...
...I won't... sink to the ground ever again!
In the not-so-distant future, you'll regret
that you took in a troublesome woman.
Gum-Gum...
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
It's not a matter that people
like you can get involved in.
Robin intends to die for us!
Iron Body!
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
after making the entire world your enemy!
I'll pursue that woman to the very
ends of the earth and eliminate her...
I want to live!
...Jet...
...Gatling!
What's going on?!
What happened?!
Luffy!
Luffy...!
The first column is...!
H-Hey... What's that?
Hey! Look over there!
Th-This is a report to all ships.
This is a report to all ships!
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 has just...
Has just been defeated...
by pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy...
It's over...
We'll be okay now.
We're gonna go back together!
Robin!
So you came... You're such a... You're such a...
Luffy! Into the sea! Jump into the sea!
We've got one more friend, right?!
Next time, on One Piece:
"From the Sea, a Friend Arrives!
The Straw Hats Share the Strongest Bond"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
From the Sea, a Friend Arrives!
The Straw Hats Share the Strongest Bond