Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Couldn't eat another bite!
--Look, my stomach is bulging!
--It's the Navy's food and drinks!
I can't believe that I was thinking "I'll never get out!"
All thanks to...
...Captain Buggy! Thank you!
No problem! No problem!
So, how's it going, Jinbe?
Hm?
Don't hm me, you jerk!
I'm asking you when we will get to Navy HQ so I can conquer the world!
That attitude really gets me!
I can't stop shaking!
The Seven Warlords who sold their souls to the Government
and the 3 Navy admirals are no match for us!
That's right!
You should be the next Pirate King since you're following in the wake of Roger!
Special Retrospective Before Marineford
The Three Navy Admirals Assemble!
Meanwhile, at Navy Headquarters on Marineford...
May I come in?
Everybody, it's time. We need you to come to the harbor with us.
Without First Son of the Sea Jinbe who is with Luffy
and Marshall D. Teach who has burst into Impel Down,
4 of the Seven Warlords are about to leave Mary Geoise.
In addition, Boa Hancock is here waiting as well
after her stopover at Impel Down.
4 of these 5 have had dealings with the Straw Hats in the past.
Whitebeard is just a man but you people are beside yourselves with fear.
We still have 3 hours before the execution.
Yes, that's true but we need to be prepared for any contingency.
Bartholomew Kuma!
Ursus Shock!
So, you're still alive, Roronoa...
If you were to take a trip, where would you want to go?
I will protect you, even if it costs me my life!
Damn it!
Luffy... Help m--
Robin!
Luffy!
We will never meet again.
Farewell...
You look so eager to do it.
You're so uncouth.
Dracule Mihawk a.k.a. "Hawk-Eye" Mihawk!
Is it possible... that's...
...Hawk-Eye...!
I came out to sea to meet you.
What's your goal?
To become the strongest!
How foolish...
Tiger...
...Hunt!
Kid! State your name.
Roronoa Zoro.
I'll remember it, strong one. I haven't seen any one like you in a while...
As a swordsman's courtesy, I'll sink you using the world's strongest Black Blade.
Three-Sword Style Secret Art:
Fall!
Three Thousand Worlds!
What are you...?
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame...
Admirable!
Zoro!!
Don't live so hastily, young man.
Don't worry. I didn't kill that man.
It's still too early for you to die. My name is Dracule Mihawk!
Learn about yourself! Learn about the world! And become strong!
No matter how many years it takes,
I will hold this seat of the strongest and wait for you.
Surpass this sword! Try to surpass me! Roronoa Zoro!
I don't want to get behind!
Being able to steal shadows and corpses of strong men in the world as I please,
it'll be a great war for me!
Gecko Moria!
Now, all the shadows in Thriller Bark,
empower me!
Shadows Asgard!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Rocket!
Brick Bat!
Black Box!
He got me!
Break into pieces!
This is...
...a baptism for you!
Doflamingo-dono and Hancock-dono, please hurry.
I know. Don't call my name so casually!
Boa Hancock!
For being charmed by me, your guilty consciences...
...will turn your bodies solid!
Love-Love Beam!
Hanco--!
You piss me off!
Big Sis! Stay strong!
This can't be! No man exists that won't be my slave!
I cannot stand that man's existence!
Medusa Hair...
...Eight-Headed Serpent!
...Salamander!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Gatling!
Ouch! Hot!
That man!
You'd rather die than let people see this, right?!
So don't move!
Luffy! Please be safe!
This is the only one who has never met Luffy or the others.
Donquixote Doflamingo!
Please! Don't do this anymore! Why're you doing this?!
Because I don't need any punks to work under me, kids.
Augh! Damn! My body is hardening!
Don't do this! Have mercy on me!
No!
O-One more chance...
Give me just one more chance.
I... We will follow you!
Such an eager underling! Don't make me cry.
However, I don't need you to follow me.
Doflamingo!
The day is coming! So hurry and prepare!
For a world where only true pirates can survive!
The powerless should flee!
The unstoppable swell of the new era of daring men is coming!
His capability is still unknown.
Also, at Navy Headquarters,
under the command of Fleet Admiral Sengoku...
You're here! It's time, Blue Pheasant-san!
Oh, it's time for lunch already?
Admiral Blue Pheasant!
Ice Age!
The ocean turns... to ice!
This is what a Navy admiral can do.
You got good friends! But you can't change yourself, Nico Robin!
You're wrong! I'm not...
Robin! Look out! Run!
You!
Stop screaming. If you defrost her right, she'll live.
But her body's fragile now so be careful.
If you break her, she'll die. For example...
...if you crush her like this!
No!
Th-That was close!
--Yeah!
--You did it, Usopp!
What's going on here?
Usopp! Chopper! Just run to the ship!
Treat her and help her!
G-Got it!
We won't let you...
Wait, guys!
Stand aside. I wanna fight him man-to-man.
Let's sort this out--me and you!
No problem but since there's no ship to take you into custody,
I'll kill you all one by one.
Gum-Gum...
...Storm!
Ice Time!
Not lunch! What are you talking about?!
It's the execution of Portgas D. Ace...
Yeah, I know. Don't get so uptight.
Please hurry!
Summoning us at lunchtime? So you guys really want to boss us around, huh?
Admiral Yellow Monkey!
Zoro!
Wh-What?! Who are you?!
Get away! Get away from Zoro, you dumbass!
Z-Z-Zoro-san! Zoro-san's been hit by a beam!
Yellow Monkey?!
Be careful! That man is a Navy admiral!
Admiral?!
Now you can have a nice, long rest...
Zoro!
Hey! He shoots beams, too! This ain't good! Do something!
At that distance, the beams'll kill him!
Oh no! Zoro's in trouble!
H-Hey, you! Stop that!
Take this!
Damn! What's going on?! Why can't I hit him!
I-I can't even stab him! Hold on! What should we do?!
Take this! Dammit!
Move your foot!
Move it aside!
It's no use; I ate the Glint-Glint Fruit, you see.
I'm made of light. I'm a Logia.
Made of light?!
This can't be for real! He's going to die!
Zoro! Run!
Veinte Fleurs!
I won't let you move, either. It's no use.
Now you will die.
You're getting involved in this...
...Dark King Rayleigh?!
Old guy!
Don't be plucking these young sprouts!
Their era is just about to begin!
Well I guess if Whitebeard is on the move, it can't be helped!
And the extreme emissary of justice -
Admiral Red Hound!
The Navy's greatest powers - the three admirals!
The Seven Warlords of the Sea!
This formidable lineup stands in the way of Luffy who is heading to Marineford!
It's 3 hours to the execution. We'll take the criminal to the scaffold.
It's time.
Fifty battleships and one hundred thousand marines.
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
and the three admirals, Red Hound, Blue Pheasant and Yellow Monkey.
When the world's greatest powers have gathered,
Fleet Admiral Sengoku reveals the shocking truth!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Ticking Down to the Time of Battle!
The Navy's Strongest Lineup in Position!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Ticking Down to the Time of Battle!
The Navy's Strongest Lineup in Position!