Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece...
head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago!
In order to move on
to the next stage—the New World—
they set sail for Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
You guys!
Set sail!!
I'll give you an option.
Do you wanna enlist under our banner—
the New Fishman Pirates?
Or do you refuse?
If you refuse, we'll sink you.
No way! Stupid!
Here we go!
Coup de Burst!
The bubble here is a double structure!
We're gonna run into one more bubble!
Hold on tight!
Water?!
The current is strong!
Help... me...
Can't breathe...
We have four Devil Fruit users but...
Reach...
out!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Damn! I can't swim against the current!
Where am I?
Oh, Luffy-chin!
I'm glad that you're okay!
This is a coral apartment in the sea.
The dorm is at the very bottom so the rent is cheap.
We're here, on the surface!
Hey, Camie!
Everybody!
I found it!
This is my All Blue!
I see.
Straw Hat Luffy finally got this far.
What should we do, Boss?
Bring him...
here!
Excitement Blow-out!
Sanji's Life Under Threat!
Even if the Straw Hats survived, they're humans,
they can't live in the water.
Then they must be somewhere above the water?
Let's just find them!
Now, what should I do?
It's hard to believe that this place is in the deep sea.
Super!
Hey, Nami!
I'm glad that you're okay!
I just thought I was gonna die because of you!
Robin!
Robin.
Nami?
Are you alright?
Where are we?
Fishman Island?
Yeah, probably.
Franky is scouting it out now.
Oh, you're up, Robin!
Thanks to you.
See the others?
No, I can't find them.
We just got together again...
But there's no need to worry! They wouldn't die so easily.
He's right.
We have to find the Sunny too
but first, should we check with some inhabitants?
I found a town nearby.
Sanji-chan!
I'm on my way!
I'll...
live...
here!
Sanji-chan, you're so funny!
He seems to have recovered after all.
By his willpower alone?
I wanna swim like you guys.
Luffy-chin, you can swim with a bubble on.
Really?
Yeah, any craftsman in the city can make one for you right away.
I'm glad because if he has a nosebleed now,
we don't have blood for a transfusion.
And Sanji's blood type is very rare.
Huh? That's not good, is it?
Hey, Camie.
There is somebody
I really wanna see on Fishman Island.
Who is it?
The Mermaid Princess?
Nope.
It's Jinbe!
Boss Jinbe?
Hey Luffy, you mean Jinbe the Warlord?!
No, he resigned during the war
so he's a former Warlord.
Yeah, he's my friend!
What's up with you?
You know the Pirate Empress, too.
When Ace died two years ago, I didn't lose heart...
thanks to him!
You brat!
Can't you see things clearly now?!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
I still have my friends!
I wanna see Jinbe!
See you at Fishman Island in two years!
I'm looking forward to the day when you and your friends visit us!
We made a promise to meet again on this island.
Oh yeah, I read in the newspaper that you were with Jinbe.
Yoo-hoo!
Where's Jinbe?
Um, Boss is not on the island now.
Huh?
He resigned from the Warlords during the war two years ago.
So the former crew of the Fishman Pirates
could no longer stay here
and they left with Boss Jinbe.
What?! So I can't see him here?
It's a long story.
But the war had a lot of effects on this island too...
Camie!
A ship is coming!
It might be!
The royal family's ship!
Maybe no one's on it!
I'm sure somebody is!
Who's on it, Medaka-chin sisters?
We don't know yet.
You don't often see the royal family's ship.
They seldom come here.
Maybe they're coming to catch Luffy-chin and the others for illegal entry!
So what?
What?
You guys need to hide!
Sanji-chan, this way!
Okay!
"Ryugu Palace"
Is it the royal family's gondola?
You think so?
It is!
Maybe!
I bet so!
So what?
But it can't be somebody from the royal family!
They don't bother coming all the way
to this corner of the island.
The three Neptune Brothers have arrived!
Hello, girls of the cove.
Ryugu Kingdom
The three Neptune Brothers
I want to ask you something.
Princes!
What brought you here?
Princes?
No, Sanji-chan!
Hide here and stay still.
What is this?
Marshmallow?
Ah, no, it's not.
The milky sweet smell.
Don't know why but it makes me feel comfortable.
Is it a fruit from Fishman Island? Sniff, sniff.
Hey, what is...
I received a report of an illegal entry.
First Son Fukaboshi (Shark Merman)
Didn't they come here?
If you've seen them, tell me-fa-so-la-ti-do!
Second Son Ryuboshi (Oarfish Merman)
If you haven't seen them, that's fine-mi-re-do!
Moonfish! Shake, shake!
Third Son Manboshi (Moonfish Merman)
I wanna stay here and play!
We haven't seen anybody.
Are they that important?
That you princes have to come all the way here?
Well, I'm not sure if they're who I think they are yet.
He's not sure-mi-re-do!
I can't hold it any longer!
Everybody, let's dance together!
What's going on?
Hey, look!
They're the princes of Neptune's army!
Why're they here?
What a pain in the ass.
What should we do?
Let's see how things go.
Hmmm. Okay.
Thank you very much.
We'll check somewhere else.
Sorry to bother you when you're having fun.
Let's dance another time!
Sorry for the bother-so-fa-mi-re-do!
Anytime!
Maybe the border guards were just seeing things.
They're leaving.
Sniff, sniff!
Sniff!
Sanji!
What is that?!
Sanji-chan!
That was too much blood!
He's in danger!
He couldn't hold it in!
All that pent-up excitement exploded!
Sanji!
That's...
No mistaking him.
The pirate—Straw Hat Luffy!
Ammo Knights!
Yes, sir!
Damn!
They look all the same!
Doesn't feel like I've advanced even a little!
Are you Pirate Hunter Zoro from the Straw Hats?
Yeah, so what?
There they are!
Straw Hat and the others.
What should we do?
They'll catch them first.
But we don't wanna cause
any trouble with Neptune's army.
Wait a minute!
We're sorry about the illegal entry!
But you can't arrest us now!
Can somebody donate blood now?!
If nothing is done,
our friend is gonna die within an hour!
His blood type is S RH negative.
It's rare but does anybody here share the same blood type?
Or are Fishmen and Mermaid blood
totally different?
Chopper-chin.
We don't have time! Anyone?!
This is... This is the dumbest way to die!
Somebody please! I beg you!
Give blood to Sanji!
Luffy-chin, Chopper-chin!
Mermaid and Fishmen blood
are the same as humans so we can donate blood!
But...
Those humans are talking nonsense!
Those guys with sea monsters!
Prince Fukaboshi, that's Hammond from the Fishman District.
There is nobody on this island who would give blood to such lowly creatures as humans.
Even if you found someone,
the human-haters on this island would subject them
to the Judgment of the Dark Night.
Judgment?
He can just keep losing blood helplessly and die!
There is this old law in our kingdom:
"Donating blood to humans is prohibited."
What?!
Make no mistake!
You humans set the rule first!
You people have a long history of fearing us as monsters
and refused to get your blood mixed-up!
That's why Fisher Tiger,
the hero of Fishman Island, died.
Fisher... Tiger?
He risked his own life to free slaves of all races
but after a bloody war,
he lost his life although he could've survived
if he had a transfusion!
Those heartless humans refused to give blood so he died!
Straw Hat, here is what I want you to do.
Just give up on your crewmember's life
and come to the Fishman District with us!
The captain of the New Fishman Pirates,
Hody Jones, is expecting you guys.
Shut up!
Hey, I don't know about the law but please!
Isn't there anyone with S RH negative?!
I'll do anything to repay you!
Just as long as you save his life now!
I'm telling you, it's no use!
Camie!
If you don't comply...
Gear 2!
I'll take you by force!
Trawl Net!
I told you that we weren't gonna join you!
Jet...
Pistol!
Luffy, a monster behind you!
Hammond and the others got...
The monster gave up without fighting!
Cool!
What was that?
Luffy-chan's unbelievable!
Impressive.
Luffy-chin and everybody!
Bring Sanji-chin, too!
Let's go to the town!
It's the Ryugu!
There are many humans
at the harbor of the town! Hurry up!
Okay!
Alright, we're ready!
Camie, let's go!
Uh-huh! Please, Ryugu-chin, take us to the town!
Mosu!
Hey you, wait!
The Ryugu is the Princes'—
I'm sorry! I'll bring it back to you as soon as we save Sanji-chin!
They're leaving!
We don't have a ride home-fa-mi-re-do!
Hmm.
I'm sorry.
If my blood type matched, I wouldn't refuse.
You don't have to apologize.
It all started because of his lecherous feelings.
Look. He's still smiling a little.
...And at the same time, it's nice and bouncy...
Sanji, that's enough!
Don't think about anything!
You're in a delicate state!
You and Hachi were discriminated against
at Sabaody two years ago
so I guess it really runs deep.
I can't believe Sanji's dirty mind
caused such a big issue!
Yeah, and even if we get to the town,
I don't know if we can find a donor right away.
What?
We haven't had that many human visitors for a month.
You guys are our first visitors in a while.
Why? I thought this was the famous scoop.
Yes, it is a famous spot.
We don't know why.
They say maybe somebody
is standing in the voyagers' way.
Somebody powerful is up to something - that's the talk of the Kingdom.
That was no good, ladies.
Why were you hiding the pirates?
I'm sorry, Prince Fukaboshi.
They were Camie's friends.
And they were good people
and we didn't want them to be arrested.
I hope Sanji-chan will be fine.
You ladies mistook us.
He's a well-known pirate,
he didn't need to go through immigration.
Because we know his identity.
We were looking for them for another reason-re-mi-fa!
Oh, is that so?
And we were unable to deliver the message from Jinbe, as well.
Sanji's overexcitement has put him in danger.
Camie leads Luffy and his crew to the Mermaid Cafe
in search of a blood donor to save his life.
There, they meet a gifted psychic, Madame Sharley,
and she predicts a terrible future for Luffy's crew!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Fishman Island Will Be Annihilated!?
Sharley's Prophecy"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Fishman Island Will Be Annihilated!?
Sharley's Prophecy