Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil.
Back to the Present!
Hody Makes a Move
Jinbe!
Damn! Who shot our queen?!
Look for the shooter!
Leave no stone unturned!
Brother Tai! Queen Otohime! I... I...
What should I do with this anger?!
Shit! Dammit!
There he is! We found the shooter!
Go! Get to the rooftop now!
Is he the shooter?!
He had a gun in his hand. There is no doubt.
What?
Where is he?!
Jinbe-san! We just killed him.
Who was it?
Well...
It's a...
...human!
Hide the body!
What? Boss Jinbe!
It will ruin the Queen's efforts!
She won't be able to rest in peace like this!
But it is what it is.
No, because he was a pirate!
It doesn't matter if he was a pirate or not.
No, Hody! Don't do it!
Listen, everyone!
It was a human...
...who killed our queen!
Queen Otohime was killed by a human!!
She didn't deserve it!
A human...
...killed the Queen who wanted nothing but peaceful coexistence
and broke our hearts just when we were inspired by her words and about to...
...extend our friendship!
He took our beloved one's life!
Even by taking your life, Otohime-sama can never come back, human!
Is there no justice in this world?!
It's so sad! Unbelievably sad!
Is the King still in Hard Shell Tower?
Minister of the Left!
Can you hear that? He's lost all control.
King-sama!
Lock the door!
Don't open it while I have this urge to kill someone!
King-sama, it's me.
Minister of the Left.
The shooter had a gun in his hand so one of our soldiers shot him dead.
It was a human.
I would have killed him even if he were unarmed.
But Otohime would not allow that.
I don't know when this cycle of revenge started.
But if I kill somebody, I would only perpetuate that cycle.
Witnessing my actions would make children's eyes cold
and they would harbor hatred and become bitter,
the cycle of revenge spiraling on.
I could relate to what Otohime was saying...
...as long as it was somebody else's problem!
But...
...why shouldn't I kill the man who shot my wife to death?!
I can't understand that-jamon...
As a soldier, I have taken many lives in reprisal for my friends.
I killed many humans who besieged us!
That is why I thought I have no place helping Otohime in what she was doing
so I just stood by and watched.
Why should an innocent one like her die and a man like me still live?!
I can't take over her quest because my hands are sullied
by what I have done in the past-jamon.
B-But we all change and we all are full of contradictions.
We Fishmen, and humans too. And there are things that only soldiers can protect.
A few days later
King-sama!
Thank you all.
It's my own wife's funeral - I have to attend it-jamon.
Father-sama! Father-sama!
Shirahoshi...
Father...
My sons.
I'm glad to see you.
I'm sorry to make you feel so left alone.
Um... Father-sama, look at this.
"To Shirahoshi"
What is it?
These letters keep flying in wherever I go.
There are already 5 of them, Father-sama!
It's...
...a love letter! But Shirahoshi is only 6 years old.
"I'm in luv with you. I suspect. Marry me.
Vander Decken"
Who is Vander Decken?
That is the name of a pirate family.
My children won't attend the funeral!
What?
There could be an accomplice still lurking around.
And catch this pirate named Decken now!
Yes, sir!
Everyone!
Look at the monitor!
--Prince Fukaboshi! --Prince-sama!
Fukaboshi...
Citizens of Fishman Island.
There is something I want to tell you all today.
So please give me your attention.
In her last moment, my mother said happily,
"We are almost there at that place under the real sun."
We have decided to take over
our mother's dream and dedicate our lives to seeing it through.
Princes...
You probably are not going to be ready for the World Summit in 2 years.
But there will be another one in 6 years and another in 10 years.
I'm sure this tragedy made you change your view of humans.
So I will get rid of all the signatures that were left unburned.
Let's start from the beginning!
And when your emotional wounds heal someday,
let's dream about the sun together again!
And for the decade that followed, not just Fukaboshi, Ryuboshi and Manboshi
but also the King and the Princess spoke to the nation through the monitor
all while signatures kept mounting up again.
So that was how we have been fighting against discrimination for the last 16 years
and the beginning of the Fishman Pirates.
Arlong, who did horrible things to your hometown,
was like a brother to me.
If he engaged in violence, we were willing to go anywhere in order to stop him ourselves
but he always paid off the Navy soldiers around him...
...to keep his actions secret from the Navy.
As a result, I made you and many others suffer.
I feel responsible!
Oh yeah?
Then why don't you cut your own belly?!
Sanji...
Pay her with your life!
I still won't forgive you but it could relieve Nami-san of her pain!
Stop, Sanji-kun!
But Nami-san, what they have done to you was...
That's a different story! This man didn't mean to hurt us.
Nami-san...
I will take any punishment! If it makes you happy...
Stop!
Stop. The only one I hate is Arlong.
Anyway, I'm glad that you are not the mastermind of the Arlong Pirates.
Because you're Luffy's friend, aren't you?
It's true that I've gone through hell because of the Arlong Pirates
but I met my friends in that horrible turmoil.
One thing led to another and I am who I am today.
I'm not gonna hate you because you're a Fishman.
So don't pity me because of my life!
It's not so bad because I'm enjoying it in the present!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Don't get angry on my behalf.
Don't tell the people on the island anything!
Neither the tragedy we endured nor of our anger towards humans!
Don't worry, Jinbe.
You two grew up together and he's like a brother to you.
No wonder you couldn't just kill him even though you were justified.
I don't deserve such words of kindness!
Thank you!
Nami!
Boss Jinbe-sama...
Oh! I know how hard it is to be a big brother! You're the man, Jinbe!
I like Tiger and Otoshime and everybody very much!
Shut up, Franky!
He must've been feeling so much pain...
What?
Luffy?
What?!
Hey, wake up!
That was a good nap.
I can't believe it! I thought it was unusual for you to listen so quietly.
Huh? Jinbe, are you crying?!
What are you saying? I am not crying!
Why is that?
Cut it out! I said I am not crying!
Hmmm... Oh, well!
And Jinbe, what did happen to the thief that Wimpy's mother caught?
You must've been sleeping most of the time! That was the very beginning!
--Was it? --It was!
Hey, so your name is Shirahoshi?
N-Nami-chin, she's the Princess! You can't say "Hey"...
Yes. Oh, excuse me.
I was crying remembering my mother.
She was quite a woman, wasn't she?
Yes!
So you are Nami-chin-sama.
No, Mermaid Princess-sama!
Nami-chin is like her nickname. Her real name has no "chin."
It feels like I have known you since I was a kid although we just met for the first time...
I feel comfortable with you.
Yeah? Maybe that's because we've been through similar things.
Now, excuse me.
I took too much time. I need to know who is still at the Ryugu Palace now.
Hody and his crew invaded the palace and captured the King and his soldiers.
And you don't know what happened to four of your crew.
That's all the information we have so far.
Jinbe-san.
If things are going as Hody planned,
the whole country might be in a terrible state by now.
Do you know what his plan is?!
I suspected he was up to something in the Fishman District
after retiring from the army,
but he never revealed it to me.
Yeah, I know.
Hody hates humans more than Arlong-san did.
He has been living on the resentment and anger of the Fishmen, and nothing else.
And there is something about him clearly different from Arlong-san.
Arlong-san would look down on humans but he would never hurt other Fishmen.
But Hody will attack those Fishmen who are sympathetic to humans...
...without mercy!
This year is the World Summit which takes place every four years.
Since they gathered enough signatures,
King Neptune will express his intention to the world finally,
to relocate Fishman Island.
Don't tell me he is planning to block it!
No, he wants more than that.
Wh-What is that?!
That's a big Transponder Snail!
It's a Video Transponder Snail!
Why is it here?
Look! It's activated!
Oh, it's projecting something on the bubble!
That's...
He's the...
Nami-san, do you know him?
Hody!
What?! That's him?!
Hatchin!
Uh, everybody on Fishman Island.
Can you hear me?
I'm the captain of the New Fishman Pirates from the Fishman District,
Hody Jones!
Hody broadcasts his ambition across all of Fishman Island.
His shocking intention is to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
and establish himself as the new king.
The citizens of Fishman Island had been deeply unsettled already,
but Hody's announcement has further filled them with dread!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Kingdom in Shock
Orders to Execute Neptune"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Kingdom in Shock
Orders to Execute Neptune