All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
They learned about the puppet
master of Land of the Dead - Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate ally - Trafalgar Law,
were drawn into a climactic battle
which ended with Caesar's defeat.
You haven't eaten anything until today,f have you?
That's my son!
But it must've been hard!
You don't have to worry about anything anymore!
Let's hope that everybody else is okay, too!
Now,
let's keep living, Momonosuke!
Uh-huh.
Guys!
Somebody's coming after us.
So...
...you gotta hurry!
It's a banquet!
Thus, they started the victory banquet.
"It's Time to Say Goodbye! Leaving Punk Hazard!"
Super!
Law.
I know you don't really think that
I'll keep my promise with a pirate like you.
But if you really wanted to silence me,
there were several occasions that you could've killed me.
What are you up to, taking advantage of Straw Hat?
I'm taking advantage of him? Maybe he's taking advantage of me.
Which of the Four Emperors are you talking about?
The Emperor's name is...
...Kaido the "Beast King"!
As long as Shanks is not the first one to fight,
I have no problem.
Because...
...I plan to beat all of the Four Emperors!
"Beat all of the Four Emperors"?
We share a mutual interest but you're underestimating them.
They are the emperors of the sea
who have skirmished over territories even against Whitebeard himself.
And above all, they say Kaido the Beast King
is the strongest creature in the world.
Huh? What? He's not even a human?!
We'll ally with each other until we kill Kaido.
And our chances of success are...
Well, I'll just say they're really low.
What?! We shouldn't go along with this, Luffy!
I see.
Okay, let's do it!
What?!
Wait a minute!
There is no particular reason
that I didn't kill you, Asher.
By the way,
I'm thinking about going to Green Bit.
I wonder if I can handle the Straw Hats.
You're doing great!
He can barely lift the kid up!
Gum-Gum...
...Big-eater!
Brother Luffy, you're big!
--Stretchy! --Cool!
Mocha, are you alright?
Aren't you cold?
Uh-huh, I'm fine!
You guys are kind of nice!
Shut up! We are the fearsome Navy G-5!
Law!
It's all ready now!
I thought you guys were gonna take the tanker.
Well, no, because Nami and Chopper claimed
we're not going anywhere until we see the children sailing out.
It's a pain to wait for other Navy people
so take the tanker with the children.
Get on board, kids!
We're gonna take you home!
There is no need to hurry. One by one.
Take care!
Hey hey, Straw Hats!
If the tanker is ours,
this is the line!
Don't think of crossing it!
This is the line between good and evil!
Don't step on it! Stay away!
Again?! You were enjoying the banquet a few minutes ago.
No, no! No, idiot!
About that, we really...
...Thank you for the meal!
But you guys are pirates! A dishonor to the human race!
Looks like they're leaving.
1, 2, 3!
Hm? What's that?
Big Sis Nami!
Chopper-chan!
--Where is the robot? --Oh? Where are the pirates?
Take that down! How annoying!
It's a barrier!
Even just looking at pirates hurts your eyes!
You guys are not so different from us, G-5!
But they got on board safely.
Hey!
--Brother! --Sis!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
We are the champions of justice!
And we're gonna exterminate all pirates who cause civilians grief!
Pirates are the scum of the world!
And we're men of justice! Don't let the kids see them!
--Sis! --Robot!
No! You shouldn't see them!
--Brother! --Where are you?!
You don't wanna see them!
--They lifted it up! --Move it!
I can't see them!
You shouldn't see them, brats!
It's nice to see them well and yelling like that.
She said she'll ask Vegapunk for assistance about their treatment.
Oh yeah?! That's great!
Franky, I've been thinking.
What happened to the Mini-Merry after we took it to get to the island?
Oh, Robin! You're the fifth person to ask that question.
Don't make eye-contact with those trashy pirates!
It'll ruin your eyes!
But we Navy won't let it happen!
We're men of justice!
Run, guys!
The deadly gas from earlier!
What?!
Run if you don't wanna die!
We're... men of justice!
The spiral-eyebrowed brother!
The Navy's in our way!
Move!
If you wanna say goodbye to pirates, you're a bad kid!
If you say "Thank you" to them,
we'll drag you out of the tanker and leave you here!
Listen! Pirates are bad and the Navy is good!
Pirates have been causing so much chaos in the world!
You should know that even if you're just a kid!
We'll never forgive pirates! Because we should not!
Unforgivable! Unforgivable! Pirates are unforgivable!
We don't want pirates! Say "No" to pirates!
We don't want pirates! Pirates are unforgivable!
We don't want pirates!
But when we asked them to help us,
they helped us!
They didn't even know what was going on with us
but they took us with them without being bothered by our size!
I wanna go home!
We can go home soon! Hang tight!
There was nothing on the island and no one had come to help us!
But they came!
I'm sorry!
That we didn't find you sooner!
Pirates stink and they're disgusting!
But the Navy is...
...always clean and beautiful!
Pirates are a bunch of cowards and they're sloppy!
We don't want pirates! The Navy is great!
If they don't let us say "Thank you" to them,
the Navy is...
Wait! I'm sorry!
We don't want pirates! The Navy is great!
But, in contrast, the Navy is...
...very brave and righteous...
Stop it, you guys!
Shame on you!
B...
But Tashigi-chan,
unless we keep saying bad things about them,
we will start...
liking these outlaws!
E-Even though they're pirates!
They're odd Navy soldiers!
Pirate brothers and sisters!
Thank you for helping us!
When we grow up, we will become...
...Pirates!
Don't!
Take care!
Get good rest!
When you get home, you deserve to be spoiled by
your father and mother!
Kids! You gotta eat something healthy!
Super!
Alright, shall we go?
The weather is good considering it's the New World.
But I know the sea will be rough.
Hey, is he coming with us?
Oh yeah! We haven't told you about the alliance.
Luffy got us involved in trouble again.
Straw Hat! Next time we see you, we'll take you down!
--You're our enemy next time! --Be ready for it!
See you!
We will catch you!
Whenever you're ready, Luffy!
Yeah!
Hey you, what's your name?! Where are you?!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
...Punk Hazard!
Who are they?
What?!
NHC10.
I detected it in their body.
Although it was just a trace amount, it's...
...a drug!
There are children who were
kidnapped two years ago in this laboratory!
Steal a ship and let's escape from Punk Hazard!
Wait for me, Caesar!
I'll beat you up and kidnap you!
Mocha!!
Catch me if you can! But I'm protected!
Doflamingo! The Four Emperors!
Do you even have balls to pick a fight with them?
A fight?
I've been...
...picking fights all along!
Caesar!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
Let's sail out!
Looks like those squirts have the devil's luck.
I can't believe the Sky Path ended there.
Young Master!
Damn! That bastard Law really betrayed us!
I'm sorry-dasuyan! I want to pay for it with death!
You needed me but I couldn't please you!
This is a life yacht that was on our tanker.
I'm so ashamed-dasuyan! After I hung up...
It's okay. You don't have to explain.
You two were just following my orders.
What a surprise.
I didn't expect the boss himself to show up!
Is that Law?
I haven't seen you for a while.
It's a shame that you're not here.
If you're looking for Caesar, he's with me.
J-Joker! Help me!
Where are Baby 5 and Buffalo's bodies?
I don't know.
Don't ask me about such frivolous things.
Let's negotiate.
Hey Law, come to your senses.
A squirt like you shouldn't imitate what grown-ups do.
Where are you now? Don't make me mad.
Make you mad?
Your most important business partner is one of the Four Emperors.
The big-time pirate - Kaido the Beast King.
And I know you can't make him mad at any cost.
What would happen if he finds out you can't produce SMILE anymore?
Since he's not the negotiating type, there'll probably be a fierce battle.
Young Master, you're turning blue.
And he'll destroy you.
Hey, you carried the joke too far, Law.
What do you want in exchange for Caesar?
Name your price.
Resign from the Seven Warlords.
I can't believe this squirt-dasuyan!
Then he can no longer stay in Dressrosa!
All I want is for you to abandon everything
that you spent a decade to attain
and go back to being a common pirate again.
In that case, however,
the Admirals from the Navy HQ will hunt you down!
I'm expecting to see it in the newspaper tomorrow morning.
If your resignation from the Warlords is in the paper,
I will call you.
If I don't see it, the negotiation is off.
Goodbye.
Clank.
Wait a minute! Law!
Young Master!
Damn squirt!