Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After the Paramount War against the Navy,
Luffy reached Maiden Island...
...only to became depressed by
his own feelings of weakness.
What is it that you still have?!
Reunion with Dark King Rayleigh
Time for Luffy's Decision
Calm Belt
Maiden Island, Rocky Bay
He stopped screaming.
Now that you mention it, I
wonder where Straw Hat is.
He's gonna die if his wound opens up, right?
I got one!
What's wrong?
I think I just saw a fish...
Th-That's big!
Look! That's a huge Sea King!
Is it fighting?
It's dead! It got killed!
--But it's huge!
--I couldn't see what did it!
It's scary around here.
Huh?!
--A man?
--Hey! Who are you?!
Oh boy...
D...
--Dark King Rayleigh!!
--What?!
Oh, it's you guys. We met
at Sabaody Archipelago.
He was the first mate of Roger,
the Pirate King!
Well, my ship sank in the storm
and I had no choice but to swim.
Storm?! The Calm Belt is always
calm - it's never rough!
There shouldn't be a storm!
That means his ship wrecked further
away and he swam all the way here?!
I have a good breaststroke.
That's not the point.
Then, that Sea King was fighting with...
...you?!
Only a legendary pirate could do that!
Oh, I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?!
Oh yeah!
I assume Luffy-kun must
be here on this island.
Hey, did you hear?
At the center of the island
The female-only empire of Amazon Lily
That Snake Princess-sama and the others...
...have just gone to deliver food to Luffy?
I wanna stretch his body again!
They said they'll invite him
over when he gets better.
I can't wait!
I didn't expect to see him again this soon!
Men are interesting!
If I could become a man, my body
would be stretchable like his!
I can't wait!
Yeah, maybe I'll make
clothes for him again...
...without frills!
We're separated although we're newlyweds!
I feel like a tragic heroine!
"But Hancock... No, my dear wife!"
"Y-Yes!"
"No matter how far away from each
other we are, our love is forever!"
"Luffy!"
Oh, my sweet husband! My heart is aflame!
Like I said before, Snake Princess,
just because someone hugs
you and uses your name,
it doesn't mean you are married.
Then, what counts as marriage?
Hmmm... That's a difficult question.
You can't go to Sabaody now with that wound.
But I wanna see my friends
as soon as possible.
I have to be there just like I promised.
But...
Hmm? The submarine is gone.
Oh, Luffy-kun!
Huh?! Old man Rayleigh!
I'm glad to see you this soon!
Why are you here?!
I was about to head to Sabaody
using the Vivre Card.
Did you see my friends?
No, I don't think they made it there yet.
I gave my Vivre Card to Shakky...
...in order to go anywhere I want.
Dark King Rayleigh! Is it really
you? I can't believe it!
You must be the former Warlord...
He's Jinbe, he saved my life.
What's wrong?
Well, I didn't expect to
see a living legend here.
Here. Isn't this hat important to you?
It is. Thanks.
It doesn't feel right without it after all!
Have you seen a group of pirates here?
If you're talking about
Trafalgar Law, he just left.
He said that you have to rest
in bed for 2 more weeks.
He saved your life, didn't he?
What a waste! We got that far...
I wanted to get in the female-only empire.
They were allowing bears in.
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
So weak!
I wonder what the Dark King is up to.
Whatever it is I'm sure that "D." will
cause quite a storm once again...
Can't wait to see him again.
Oh, Rayleigh?! You must be Rayleigh!
Oh, Gloriosa! It's been awhile!
--Rayleigh!
--Ray-san!
Oh, you two are here too!
Luffy!
Hey, Big Sis! How could you ignore
the man who saved your life?
You know old man Rayleigh?
--Yes!
--It's a long story.
Luffy, so you're awake now.
I haven't
slept for days worrying about you.
You must be hungry. I brought some food.
So go ahead and dig in...
You can't even look at him.
How could you call it marriage?
Serve him...
Serve him a meal already!
Jinbe! These are not for you!
You can have just a little bit.
O-Okay. Luffy-kun, why don't we just eat?
Luffy-kun, you have to eat. Eating is living!
That's it! That's my Luffy-kun!
Jinbe! I said "just a little bit"!
Thank you for bringing me
the letter from Shakky.
Sounds like she hasn't changed.
Yeah, she's just the way she was
when you were living in Sabaody.
She's doing fine.
These girls have become very beautiful
and strong over the past 13 years.
Rayleigh, Shakky, Granny Nyon.
You three protected us when we were
running from the Celestial Dragons.
But we have a problem.
We should be providing shelter
for Luffy from the Navy.
Even though Rayleigh
knows Luffy from before,
if it's easy enough for someone
to guess that Luffy's here,
we should be worrying.
Huh?! What an old familiar face!
You're Rayleigh, aren't you?
You just noticed?!
How mad are you about him?!
No, I don't think the Navy
can guess that he's here.
First of all, the one who sent him away
told me that he sent him in this direction.
Kuma...
I work for the Revolutionary Army.
Since I have a connection with them.
I wanna let them get away from here.
Oh, I can't believe it.
And where's Monkey-chan now?
I don't know.
I'm sorry about my abrupt manner earlier.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
I don't have...
...much time left.
Straw Hat should be...
In the direction that Bartholomew
Kuma blew Luffy-kun away,
there is Maiden Island.
That's not all.
I found out some interesting
information about the Paramount War.
It's with regards to the prison break at
Impel Down by Luffy-kun and the others.
When I thought about how Luffy-kun was
able to infiltrate the great prison,
it dawned on me that Luffy-kun
must have stowed away on a
Navy ship with Hancock, but...
Since Hancock hates both
the Government and men,
I don't think that she'd
get on a Government ship,
especially not to help a man.
Now, this part is all theoretical.
But how about this?
Say that Hancock fell in
love with Monkey-chan,
everything makes sense.
Monkey-chan is a good-looking guy.
And if I were Hancock,
I'd give him refuge on Maiden Island to spite the Navy.
That's a very subjective theory, Shakky.
Women's intuition is unbelievable.
--That's my Shakky!
--She couldn't be any more right, as you can see.
Yeah? You like it? Good!
The Navy won't take action based
on a ridiculous theory like that.
So this place is safe.
Now, let's get down to business.
Luffy-kun.
You said you're gonna head
for Sabaody, didn't you?
I need to see my friends.
Is that what you really want?
Sabaody Archipelago.
Remember what happened to
you guys on that island?
Everyone focus on escaping!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
Do you think you can face those
tremendous powers as you are now?
But I...
Do you want to be reunited with your
friends just to endure the same fate?
I have a suggestion for you.
Of course it's up to you to...
...do it or not.
Meanwhile, on the Bowin Islands in the Grand Line...
Grand Line
Bowin Islands
Stop! Usopp'n!
Don't stop me, Heracles'n!
Usopp is...
...shaking his body which has grown huge
from eating an abundant variety
of food in the forest...
...and running.
It's impossible'n!
No, it's not! That's why I'll try again!
I can do it this time!
There you are!
Get out of my way!
Sure Kill...
Oh no'n! Usopp'n!
Are you okay, Usopp'n?
Damn...
You can't do that. If you try
to get off of this island,
terrifying living things
will stand in your way
and push you back to the forest'n.
Nothing will stop you from
entering the island'n
but once you've set foot on it, you're dead!
No one ever leaves this island alive'n!
And my name is Heracles'n!
Oh?! Usopp'n! Where did you go?!
Oh, he's in danger'n!
The sea creature has just
come onto the island!
Usopp'n is in danger!
The sweet scent from Bowin Islands
draws the attention of...
...giant insects and giant birds...
...and even sea creatures and Sea Kings.
It's a sea hippo!
I shouldn't get fascinated by it now!
The scents lure them
deeper into the island...
...where they find the
forest filled with food.
It's easy to enter the island...
But it's hard to leave...
Outta my way! Sure Kill - Exploding Star!
I'm gonna get out of here!
Don't get in my way!
I have to go back!
To Sabaody!
Exploding Star!
Usopp'n!
The islands are gonna move again!
What?
Usopp'n! Hang onto a tree!
It's happening again?!
It's gonna eat something!
The name of this flower that
looks like an island is...
People call them Bowin Islands
but the scientific name is Stomach Baron: a meat-eating plant!
Usopp'n!
What's the matter with you, Usopp'n?
You changed since reading the
newspaper that News Coo brought!
I...
...have no time to waste here now!
Luffy lost his brother in the war!
He must be having a very hard time now!
When your friend is having a hard time,
you should be there for him!
Luffy!!
Luffy's friends take
action, concerned for him,
but Nami is held captive by
the researchers of Weatheria.
Meanwhile, on the Winter Island, Franky heads to
a certain place in search of an ice-breaker.
What extremely dangerous
button has he found there?!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Back to Our Captain
Escape From Sky Island
and the Winter Island's Incident"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Back to Our Captain
Escape From Sky Island
and the Winter Island's Incident