Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates,
who are plotting to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom,
alongside Vander Decken, who is after
Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi, move in secret.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
Zoro, Usopp and Brook have been
captured by Hody at Ryugu Palace.
She broke... She broke my heart!
Oh yeah.
What's wrong?
I got an idea!
What don't I just destroy everything altogether?!
Boy, he gave me a lot of trouble...
Take care of Hachi, Camie!
Y-Yes.
Go, Megalo!
So that was the true power of the drug!
A Shocking Confession
The Truth Behind Otohime's Death
We are almost at the plaza! Hurry up, Megalo!
Father-sama...
Hey! I'm here-jamon!
Boss Jinbe-sama! Megalo!
I'm so happy to see you!
Father-sama!
I'm coming!
No, wait!
Father-sama!
Please stop!
Princess Shirahoshi!
If you don't wanna see the Princess get hurt, freeze!
L-Let me go!
Alright, let's take her!
Conchcorde Plaza
No way!
We have quite an audience.
Damn!
What a view!
Prince Mamboshi!
Prince Ryuboshi!
Prince Fukaboshi-sama!
How did the pirates manage that?!
The Princes were winning by far!
Suddenly, the tables have turned against them!
Oh, I wanna fight some more-zugon!
Much! Don't get so heated up! Or I'm gonna become a piece of dried squid-ch!
Soldiers of the army. The ministers.
And the royal family. There is no one left in this country, who can fight us now!
What unbelievable power!
I'm sorry, Father!
You don't have to be! Those powers are fake-jamon!
That doesn't really matter if it enables them to take over the country!
Captain Hody, let's put them to death!
--Burn them alive! --No, impale them!
I wish a terrible death on those who lack pride and look to coexist with the humans!
Let's show the audience!
Let's just kill them!
Kill them! Kill them!
Kill them!
Silence.
I haven't heard from Decken's crew yet, with regards to Shirahoshi's death.
There is no point in doing this if we can't lure her here!
Don't do anything to our sister! She won't fight!
She wouldn't harm you in any way!
You think that I don't know anything?
She's the Mermaid with that troublesome power so I want to be rid of her the most.
Hody!
Captain Hody!
We got them!
Princess Shirahoshi and Jinbe got caught in a trap!
Shirahoshi!
Father-sama! Brothers-sama!
How lucky I am!
We caught the two that I concerned about most, all at once.
This is too good to be true!
I-I am very sorry!
You wouldn't have to go through this if I hadn't been fooled...
What's done is done so never mind.
So you're here as I thought, Jinbe.
I liked you back when you were a wild man.
What happened to you, Hody? You look so different from before.
It's Boss Jinbe!
I thought he left the island after he quit the Warlords!
I heard that Princess Shirahoshi had been kidnapped by Straw Hat Luffy.
Did Boss Jinbe rescue her?
Now, everyone that I wanted to see is here.
It was easier than I thought.
My only concern now is what the Straw Hats will do.
But I assume they're desperately looking for a way in to the Ryugu Palace now.
Even if they make it here after they find their friends dead,
we're totally ready to ambush them!
There are 30,000 human slaves we've caught in the sea over the past month.
And 70,000 Fishmen who know how to use arms.
Wh-What the...
They moved here from the closed Fishman District.
Behold...
...100,000 outlaws altogether!
There are a few female and child slaves who can't fight, outside the plaza.
We will take care of them later.
But we'll soon have more human slaves!
So, 100,000 of you islanders!
You fools are a dishonor to our race so vacate your houses!
You can either drop dead or run. Think about what you want!
Horsing around in public... You kids have no class at all!
Don't push your luck!
Hody Jones.
I haven't seen you for a long time. What do you want?
I just wanted to say one thing to you since you're at the height of your glory!
Madame Sharley?!
According to my prevision, a man will destroy Fishman Island.
I may be the one.
Was it me that you saw?
No.
The man who will destroy the island is...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
What?!
I can't tell what the Straw Hat boy will do specifically.
What is your point?
My point is that it's not you!
That's all I can say.
The one who determines the fate of Fishman Island is...
...not you, Hody.
Oh, I see! Madame's previsions are accurate!
That means Hody will never reign over the island!
Madame Sharley!
--Madame! --How could he do this?!
That's nonsense!
What do you mean by that, Sharley? What do you have against me?!
I'm not like your brother.
Well, when I was a kid, everybody in the Fishman District
may have looked up to your brother Arlong.
But then we seized power.
In fact, the name "Arlong Pirates" is nothing but a symbol to unite us now.
We don't even need the name "Arlong" anymore!
The only man who can break the whole country to its foundation and rebuild it, is...
...me! Because I have enough power to do so!
Look how powerful I am!
This is the power that I'm talking about!
I started this whole thing 10 years ago.
Let me tell you something.
Concerning the late Queen of the Ryugu Kingdom, who you fools still love!
Otohime was killed by...
...me!
What?!
No...
What about the human then?
How could you not notice it, idiots?!
The day before that fateful day 10 years ago...
I don't know who you are but...
...I would do anything if I can make some big money.
Is this real money?!
That's just a half of it. You can have the rest after you finish the job.
Alright, I'll do it!
Just this is enough to drink all day for quite some time.
And what do you want me to do?
It's so easy. Even a child can do it.
However, don't let anyone notice.
And on that day...
Get away! Fire!
--Put out the fire! --Run!
--Protect the royal family! --Put out the fire now!
Otohime-sama has been shot!
Hey, give me the rest of that money now!
I set fire to those signatures like you told me to!
I wanna make a run for it already so give me the money!
What's going on here?
You stupid human.
Shit! Dammit!
It was a human...
...who killed our queen!
Queen Otohime was killed by a human!!
Everybody got fooled completely!
Damn! It was him!
He killed Queen Otohime!
Hody, you bastard!
Father!
Hody, stop!
She was annoying. Don't you think so, Shirahoshi?
She begged everyone not to seek revenge against humans
but to become friends with them instead.
She was bugging me because she almost accomplished her goal.
I knew I wouldn't be satisfied with just killing her.
To me, your mother was...
...someone who deserved death!
Don't say such a thing to the Princess!
How dare you?!
And then I came up with an idea to make the best of her death.
Which would allow me to stoke the hatred towards humans,
that citizens of Fishman Island once had
and destroy the islanders' stupid dream along with Otohime - all at once!
I'd point the finger at a human for killing Otohime.
If I blamed it on a human, I knew that the islanders will get pissed off at humans again.
And it turned out that you all got fooled by my trick exactly as I wanted!
She was worth killing! Right, Shirahoshi?
Your mother was not murdered by a human!
I, her kinsman, did it!
I, standing in front of you now, killed her!
I already knew it.
Shirahoshi!
What?
A long time ago, everyone on Fishman Island came together
and built a mysterious giant ship called Noah.
The reason remains a mystery.
It's just a leftover from the past now.
Let me touch it with my right hand.
Captain Decken, what are you up to?
Wh-What is it? What's going on?!
The pain of heartbreak will never go away.
It's moving!
--Wh-What's going on?! --Run!
I'm throwing the Noah...
...at Shirahoshi!
What?!
The ship is half the size of Fishman Island!
That means if it hits the island, not just Shirahoshi
but the whole island will be shattered!
She can't run or hide from me anymore!
Shirahoshi has no choice but to stay with me in my heart forever!
Burn in hell with the island! Goodbye my sweet Shirahoshi!
Goodbye Fishman Island!
Shirahoshi continues to fulfill her promise to her mother, Otohime.
Hody ridicules her and commences Neptune's execution.
The despairing citizens call out the name of their last hope.
And their voice resounds throughout Fishman Island!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Shirahoshi's Tears!
Luffy Arrives at Last"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Shirahoshi's Tears!
Luffy Arrives at Last