Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
I owe you!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Together with Red-Nosed Buggy
and former Baroque Works
agents Mr. 3 and Bon clay,
he reached Level 4 the Inferno Hell...
...but was poisoned by Magellan,
the warden of Impel Down
and taken into custody!
As Luffy was taken into custody
on Level 5--the Frozen Hell,
Bon Clay tried his hardest
to find a way to save him!
No way?!
I mean, what do you mean that
you can't make an antidote!
A miracle?
Oh yeah! He is in Impel Down!
The Queen of Queers--
Iva-san!
We better find him now!
A Paradise in Hell
Impel Down Level 5.5
T-This is no good!
We have no choice!
We should lock ourselves up!
Alright! I'll draw their attention!
Open it quick!
Dammit! Chew on this,
my special weapon--Muggy Ball!
Ha! How's that?!
What?!
I did it!
Did you?!
I did it... I broke the key!
What're you doing?!
It's too late!
Candle Shield!
That was close!
You better get into the cell now!
We don't need to!
I have an idea!
Stupid wolves! You can't get us now!
It's no use biting it!
This Candle House is as hard as iron!
Even with your big fangs, you can't break it!
Let's go!
Oh yes!
1, 2! 1, 2!
Wow! This is nice!
They can't even touch us!
It's heavier than I thought!
I made it thicker than usual to protect us!
Yeah? Well, good job!
Even if it's a tortoise's pace,
as long as we can get to the stairs,
then we can get out of here!
That's right!
And as long as we're in here,
we can avoid the cold wind!
Alright!
1, 2! 1, 2!
Wait! Let's go back a little!
What's the matter?
Something is wrong.
What happened to the wolves?
Yeah, where the hell do they go?!
All of them are gone!
What's that noise?
T-This must be...
That was pretty clever of them!
Who the hell is this guy
all covered in blood?!
Earlier, I was...
We have no chance to win!
I'm sorry but I gotta run!
Straw-chan! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry that I ran!
How do you know this guy?
I'm his friend!
Straw-chan! I'm not gonna let you die!
We better go now!
He left the keys!
I never thought about breaking out.
I gotta find Iva-san as soon as possible!
Iva-san?!
How should I know
where that queer went?!
Who the hell are you?!
Emporio Ivankov?
Oh yeah, I remember him!
He must be dead!
What are you looking at?!
Why are you looking for a missing person?!
How did you get out of your cell?!
Why don't you set me free?!
Do you know where the man named Iva-san is?!
Hello?! Can you hear me?!
Hey, why don't you say something?!
It's no use!
They're all frozen in that cell!
I wanna know...
Yeah, I heard you.
You're looking for that fairy, Ivankov, right?
Do you know something?
Look! Do you see the forest?
Yeah.
There's an abandoned jailer's room in there.
I once saw a strange guy moving around there.
Really?!
Why don't you go and check?
Thank you!
No problem!
I thought that's where the wolves live.
Oh? Is that so?
People have disappeared
occasionally in Impel Down.
They didn't break out because
some of them could barely move.
They just disappeared without a trace.
We call it "Demoning away!"
We all fear these unnatural disappearances,
and assume that they're pulled
into the gate of hell.
That's why we call it "Demoning Away!"
"The gate of hell?" "Demoning Away?"
Yeah, right!
I don't think that's the reason
that Iva-san disappeared!
I've never met him but he's a miracle worker!
He must be able to work miracles
in a place like this, too!
Iva-san is the God of all queers!
Please!
Save Straw-chan!
If antidotes won't help him...
...you're his only hope!
And I won't give up on hoping!
Aak! No!
Straw-chan!
What do you think you're doing to...
...Bon-chan?!
Leave Bon-chan...
...alone!
S-Straw-chan! What did you do...
...to them...?
Time until Ace's execution:
26 hours!
Damn!
Where are you?!
This place is too hot! It's like hell!
Wow! Nice! She's exactly my type!
Healthy, young and beautiful!
Wait a minute! But...
...where's that quick pansy prisoner
who beat all of these guards?!
Who are you?!
That doesn't matter, sweetie!
Why don't you come here?
Huh?
I'm all sweaty!
Can you help me undress?
Please!
Puff-puff!
Why don't you unlock this door?
Yeah, alright!
Smash!
Here you go!
Alright, how can I help you?
Ha ha! Do you have extra clothes?
I got you!
I can't take this!
That queer! I'm coming after you!
It's nice to be able to
lay the blame on Warden
but I don't like the fact he outsmarted me!
And I wanna become the warden!
I used too much poison!
My stomach! Oh, my stomach!
Yes, the riot is completely
under control now!
We put all the prisoners back in their
cells and got the keys back but...
...I think some keys are missing.
What a pain in the butt!
You got to... mmm... find him!
Catch him alive now!
This queer must be... mmm... on this floor!
Yes, Madam!
Several hours later, Mr. 2 Bon Clay is...
Where... is this?
Oh yeah!
Straw-chan?!
Where did Straw-chan go?!
I hear people talking...
This is it!
It's so bright!
What?!
Oh! So you finally woke up, young man!
You've been sleeping quite
a while! Want a drink?
Cheers to the newcomer!
Cheers!
We've been watching you guys on the monitor!
I really enjoyed it!
What is this place?
I'll take you to your seat!
What floor did you come from?
We got plenty to eat! You must be hungry!
Wait! Where am I?! Where's Straw-chan?!
Do you think that you're outside the prison?!
Don't worry! You're still in Impel Down.
No way! No one's wearing
their jail clothes here!
And you're eating and drinking as you want!
Is this some kind of paradise?!
Oh yeah, I remember!
I was chased by the wolves
and Straw-chan helped me!
And I just passed out!
Then, am I dreaming?!
No! I think I died from the cold
so I'm in heaven now!
Did you wake up?
You've been sleeping like a
baby for about 10 hours now.
10 hours?!
Are you kidding me?! Who are you?!
My name is Inazuma.
You're being rude!
I'm the one who moved the two of you.
You were nearly dying of exposure!
What? Did you say "two?"
Straw-chan is here, too?
Where is he? Is he alright?
Are you people jailers?
What is this place?!
Now, now, calm down.
He is going to tell you!
W-Who is He?
Oh! The lights are going down!
The shows starting!
Let's go to the front.
What is this?
Did you sleep alright, candy-boy?
No, you're Mr. 2 Bon-boy.
Who are you? Why do you know my name?!
Thank you for coming.
This is...
You're great! Very sexy!
Down the sewage line of Impel Down
and just take the route that shouldn't be there,
then, you'll get here!
It's a paradise for prisoners!
You've got everything here, so enjoy!
Drinks!
"Weapons!"
Games!
And most of all, we have freedom!
Yes, that's right! We're all free!
Yes! The jailers are
panicking today as usual!
"Prisoners have disappeared!"
"They've been pulled into hell!"
Just like that!
Sorry but they're all here!
Do you say that this is hell?!
Maybe you're right,
but at least it's a gay one!
The underground that nobody knows!
Welcome to...
Impel Down—Level 5.5!
It's a secret garden for prisoners!
New Kama Land!
Heehaw!
Who are these perverts?!
Yeah! Iva-sama!
What?!
Iva-sama!
Iva-sama?! No way!
He is the legendary...
...queen of Kamabakka Queendom.
Heehaw!
Emporio Ivankov?!
Bon Clay implores the miracle worker,
Iva-san, to cure Luffy's poisoning.
However, Iva-san's remedy is
a cruel procedure that will
leave Luffy battered and torn.
A fierce battle commences against the poison.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Luffy's Treatment Begins
Iva-san's Miraculous Power!!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Luffy's Treatment Begins
Iva-san's Miraculous Power!!