New Year's Special!
The Detective Memoirs of Boss Straw Hat Luffy
This is Grand Zipangu.
It bears similarities to another land in another time.
But hey, don't sweat it.
It's a New Years's Special!
And so, this is Grand Zipangu.
It may be a new year,
but this land is already in the midst of spring-
A season when
sakura blossoms and fireworks dance in the air.
The pleasant weather, the peaceful atmosphere.
The people live lives of merriment and joy!
Until...
You okay, Boss?
That's what you get for laughing in all this smoke!
Huh? What? What's going on?
Someone just started rampaging in front of the store.
I'm not just going to stand here!
Sir, wait!
I'm just going to see who it is.
It's me.
You're a brave man to say that when you
know full well we're the Clown Clan.
Th-The Clown Clan?!
I've never heard of you.
Okay, enough comedy!
Here's the deal.
You're going to flashily learn that name!
We're going to be running things around here from now on.
You damn Kabuki clown!
The public officials won't stand for that!
Kabuki clown? Say what you will.
What kind of crime boss would I
be if I was afraid of the police?
You're all talk, you cheap thug!
And what's with that fake nose?
Let me tell you something else.
This is not a fake nose.
It's my own, bona fide, big, red nose...
...and I like it a lot.
That's why no one-and I mean no
one gets to make fun of it!
It makes me mad!
Boss, I think you should reconsider.
I know how you must feel, but we're just here for the money.
That's right. Remember?
Fine.
let's flashily check out!
Aye!
Hey, Onami! More rice!
No way! Not one more bowl!
Huh? That's all?
Do you know how big your tab is, Chief!?
You're supposed to be a police officer, but all you do is eat!
Come on. Don't be so harsh.
Money comes and goes, you know.
I'm sure one of these days - Err...
Looks like she's not listening...
Oh wait!
I was actually going to pay my tab today!
That's right!
I was so busy eating that it slipped my mind.
How much do I owe you?
Heck, maybe I can pay for tomorrow too!
What do you think of that, Onami-san?
Wow! You're giving it all to me?
Of course!
I'm not gonna be stingy! It's all yours!
Yay!
That's why we love you, Chief!
You're so generous!
I dunno if being nice to me all of a sudden
can make up for what you said.
Hey, just forget all bout it!
Sanji-kun!
Yes, ma'am?
Give the Chief a feast like none other!
As you wish!
Here you go!
The Pinwheel's finest!
What a meal!
Silly Chief. So, you were saving up your money.
You didn't even need to have a tab.
We were ready to throw you out.
Seriously! I thought we were being duped
by some good-for-nothing half-wit.
But that's Okay! I forgive you! I forgive everything!
Money is enough to make any number of sins disappear!
How long did it take you to save this much?
Oh, I made an arrest a few days ago.
You mean you got a reward for the bad guys?
Nope. When I went into their hideout,
there was money everywhere.
And you took it?
Are you sure-
Don't worry. That's nothing.
The great heavenly sun will forgive everything.
So, who were the culprits?
Oh, they were a gang of counterfeiters.
THEN THE MONEY'S COUNTERFEIT!
What was that for-for-for?
I was a fool for trusting him. That's it, isn't it?
Don't cry, Onami-san.
You still have me.
Huh,
I'll give you a life of happiness.
Sanji-kun...
Hi. We'd like a fruit parfait.
Mellorine! Coming right up
The Pinwheel's most luxurious parfait-
"Love Is a Bolt from the Heavens".
Wow! It's beautiful!
How do you like it?
But we didn't order anything like this.
You needn't worry.
I wouldn't dream of demanding money from you.
The fee shall be...
...deducted from Sanji-kun's wages!
What?
That's like the 10th time today, Sanji!
At this rate you'll be working for free!
We've got trouble!
Oi! Chief!
Chief Straw Hat!
What're you babbling about?
Is the Chief here? I heard he was having lunch.
What're you messing around for?
The Clown Clan has moved into town.
The Clown Clan?
They use brute force to obtain anything they set their eyes on!
Every last one of them is rotten to the core!
They've made this town their next target.
They just attacked a money exchange on the main street.
In broad daylight?
Why aren't you doing anything?
Get out there and beat 'em up!
Oh, I'm not sure that's a good idea.
What!? You'd better explain youself-
This is how they operate.
They're ruthless toward anyone who stands up to them.
That's why everyone's too scared to tell the authorities.
Anf if no one tells the authorities, there's nothing we can do.
What a bunch of cowards.
Hey!
Are you just goona lie there?
This is why we feed you for free, isn't it?
Now get up!
And here I thought I could enjoy my afternoon.
I can't ignore things when food is on the line.
Yosha, I'll head over there and arrest 'em.
Get things ready!
Right away! I'll get the flint!
No, I meant some food to keep my spirits up!
SCRAM!
You better not be hiding any.
That's all I have!
Now let me go!
You're a fiesty one.
All of you!
Remember this well!
As of today, all the money in this town belongs to me!
Don't try to hide any from me.
Because if you do...
...I'll blow you to hell with my Special Buggy Bomb!
Don't get so cocky, you thug!
What was that!?
You deaf or something?
You ears aren't just for decoration, are they?
If you can't hear...
...then at least get a good look at this face!
I'm Usopp-sama, partner of Chief Straw
Hat and protector of this town!
Even the lowly policeman are feisty around here!
Come on.
Do you really think you can take us all by yourself?
Don't get ahead of yourself!
The Chief will be here any second.
Three...
Two...
One!
Another dead-on kick by Onami-san.
Chief Straw Hat!
Take care of them!
This brat is with the police?
Good one!
From what I've seen so far, this town sure is pathetic!
Quit babbling, you big-nose!
I don't know why you came to this town...
...but you don't belong here.
Jeez.
You don't go destroying property in broad daylight!
You just did that...
That's irrelevant!
If you leave town now, I'll forget any of this ever happened.
Did you just call me a big-nose!?
Boss!
Oi!
You bastard!
Do you think I'm just gonna sit here quietly
while you run your mouth like that!?
What'd you expect?
I won't let you cause trouble for the townsfolk.
Trouble?
Who's causing trouble?
Oi!
Does anyone here think I'm a troublemaker?
Dammit...
Oi, mister! You must have been pretty roughed up!
Huh?
This guy here?
He flashily recognized my manliness and decided to fund me!
There's no reason to involve the authorities.
I saw it all!
I'll testify.
He beat up the owner and stole his money!
Chief! Please arrest him!
What was that, you midget tanuki!?
Come here!
That's right. Come here.
W-What just happened?
I'm not sure.
You wanna get hurt, punk?
Shut up!
It's better than staying quiet!
As you wish
I'll flashily make myself a tanuki purse!
I'm a reindeer!
Oi! You-
Chief!
Oi, big-nose!
Insulting!
You better duck!
GOMU GOMU NO MUCHI!
What the hell's up with your leg!?
Oh, this?
I ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit.
I'm a rubberman.
A rubberman?
The Gomu Gomu Fruit?
So you're a Devil's Fruit user too!?
Chomp!
Ow!
You little bastard!
Usopp!
Yosh!
Got you!
You're under arrest!
Pretty good, as usual.
You should come to the station with us.
We'll hear what you have to say there.
You rubber shithead!
Richie!
What's that!?
It's a bomb!
Shit! It was a smoke bomb!
That punk!
He's gone!
And so is the money!
His crew also escaped!
I wonder how he untied himself.
Yeah.
But what are we gonna do?
He got away with the money!
Well, there's nothing we can do for now.
I'm sure we'll figure something out, though.
How can you be so carefree?
Oh?
This doctor is going to testify?
You sure are brave!
Thanks to him, we were able to drive away big-nose.
Thank you!
It was nothing!
I don't need your gratitude, you asshole!
Oh, that's right!
Onami, give him some food t-
"That's right" my ass.
Who's gonna pay for it?
Oi! I'm not doing it for tha-
Don't worry about it.
The Chief's treating you because he likes you.
Nice meeting you!
Y-Yeah! You too!
Well then...
I'm going out.
Huh? For what?
Unfinished business.
Damn that rubber shithead!
Flashily hurry up!
It's infuriating!
Oh?
What exactly happened?
Huh?
It's you!
It's been a while!
Save the pleasantries for later.
First...
...fill us in on the situation.
God. I don't ask for much.
All I want is an abundance of wealthy customers!
Make it how it was when the restaurant first opened!
Otherwise, the restaurant will go bankrupt!
I'm serious! This isn't a joke!
It's up to you now, God!
I feel much better now!
Hey, guys! Can I... join.... in..
What'd you say!?
Someone shot an arrow with a note on it!
"If you want Onami to live, the Chief
is to come to the river bank, alone."
Man, these guys sure play dirty.
What should we do, Chief?
If they have a hostage, we're in trouble.
Don't worry. I have a plan.
A plan?
Yosha, Usopp! Let's go!
You haven't paid, Chief.
Credit?
No chance!
Damn, she was a handful!
I trust the note was delivered successfully.
Of course!
Oh! I see you actually came and you even brought me a present!
Don't call me a present!
Man, it was pretty low of you to take a hostage!
A hostage?
Don't play dumb! Release Onami!
I'll return her unharmed.
However...
...before that a couple of guys I helped out recently
want to test their strength against you.
Won't you fight them?
Chief!
Hey, guys! Come on out.
Bare-handed killer Gedatsu!
Rokutouryuu swordsman Hachi!
Those bastards had backup waiting for us!
That's right.
My crew is just a bunch of brutish thugs.
Sometimes, they don't listen to a word I say...
...and are just completely unruly.
I'd had enough!
So, you're the one who embarrassed
the Chief of the Clown Clan?
Unforgivable!
I'm the land's strongest swordsman, Hachi-sama, and
I'm gonna crush you with my Rokutouryuu style!
Huh? Strongest, my ass.
No way! What's going on?
Chief, we have to make a run for-
GOMU GOMU NO
Rokutouryuu ougi!
SECRET SIX-SWORD TECHNIQUE
Rokutou no waltz!
SIX-SWORD WALTZ
Truncheon!
JUTTE
There's no way your jutte can win against six swords!
Huh? Ten against six? I'm outnumbered!?
Jutte-Truncheon and "Ten hands"
WHAT!
What an idiot.
Yosh!
Chief!?
Hey! Don't forget.
We have a hostage here!
Onami will be fine! ...probably
No, she-
Where'd you come from!?
Usopp!?
Usopp!!
Why...?
Hey, you! What the hell did you do just now!?
How did you get over there!?
How could I miss like that?
Are you blind!?
He's so fast that I couldn't see him at all!
That's right. The technique is called "Jet Punch".
It's impossible for you to see it.
Its only weakness is that
it can only be used once.
Say something, you bastard!
What's with you!?
How dare you humiliate me!
You did it to yourself!
Shut up! Take this!
Jet Punch!
Huh?
Didn't you just use that?
Oh, crap!
They're all idiots.
What the hell!?
Are you brain-dead or something!?
Don't forget we fashily have a hostage here!
Be careful who you attack!
Quit your babbling.
I'm gonna knock you out!
Anyway, Onami isn't a hostage anymore.
Sanji-kun!
Who the hell are you!?
You were late coming back so I thought
something must've happened.
You've really gone and done something shitty.
I have no idea who you are, but I admire your courage.
Men!
You're the only one left, shit-nose.
"Shit", you say!?
I'm gonna make you pay for this.
Nami-san, are you hurt?
What's so funny?
Don't underestimate me.
I'm the head of this Clan.
I'm your opponent!
BARA BARA KINKYUU DASSHITSU
Are you surprised?
I have a Devil's Fruit power!
I can detach any part of my body.
I'm a splitting man!
Well now, rubberman.
I've found your weakness-
Anything sharp!
Yep. That's right.
Don't just admit it!
Prepare yourself.
You're gonna take a real beating.
Here I come, Straw Hat!
Bring it!
You left your bottom half wide open
Damn you!
You're not supposed to hit a man there!
This coming from someone who takes hostages!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
GOMU GOMU NO
BAZOOKA
Buggy!
That's that!
Whoa. He sure is flying!
I hope he learned his lesson.
Oi, are you okay, Usopp!?
Let me untie you, Onami-san.
Thanks, Sanji-kun!
That's right!
That's how the incredible Chief tore
the entire Clown Clan to pieces.
That's the Chief for you!
By the looks of your injuries, you
must have done your best too!
Y-Yeah, of course!
I must have taken out a hundred men!
A hundred!? Amazing!
All before breakfast!
On an empty stomach!? Amazing!
Still they got away with all the money,
didn't they?
Oh, that won't be a problem.
Why not?
Well, about the money they stole-
It was all counterfeit!
Huh?
It's true!
A raid is being condcuted as we speak.
The Chief recognized the counterfeiter's face.
Turns out it was the guy from the money exchange!
He told the guardhouse about it afterward.
I can't believe he did his job.
Well, you can count on him when it matters.
I sure hope so!
Otherwise he's just another useless mouth to feed.
Indeed.
That's right!
Someone must be talking about me.
It's not easy being popular!
Give it up.
We'll never let you get away.
You're worth a lot of money.
If you come quietly, we'll go easy on you!
Back off!
Why, you...!
Don't underestimate us!
Who the hell are you?
What do you want?
I just want to talk.
We don't have time for sermons.
Or are you here to attempt a rescue?
Saving people is the task of the gods.
I have no interest in that.
I was just wondering if I could get in on this.
I haven't had anything to eat or drink for three days.
At this rate, I'll soon be too weak to earn any money.
Get lost, you shitty monk!
Oops. My mistake.
My hand slipped.
Damn you!
Oi, Usopp. I don't mind the night watch...
...but let's stop at a stand somewhere and get some food!
I'm hungry!
Why, you!
A brawl!
You bastard!
He's pretty good!
It's over already!
Crap, it's Straw Hat!
Retreat!
Shit!
This isn't over yet!
What a waste of energy.
Huh? I feel like I've seen those guys before.
Oi, are you okay?
Yes.
Hey, What's wrong!?
Oi, you're wounded!
Hold it!
We need to question you.
We'll have to bring you in.
Question me?
That's right! You're a suspect!
You're the one who inflicted those wounds!
Surrender yourself!
It wasn't him, Usopp!
Those are katana wounds.
Someone as skilled as him wouldn't miss his mark.
See you around, Chief Straw Hat.
Okay! Bye!
Wait, how does he know who I am?
Oi, where are you going?
Oi, are you okay?
Chief!
It's a girl!
Her wounds have closed.
There's no more need to worry.
But she looks extremely exhausted.
Make sure she gets her rest and takes her medicine.
You can relax.
She'll be as good as new by tomorrow.
I see. Thank goodness.
I brought you your futon, Nami-san.
Thanks. Leave it over there.
Sure thing!
How's she doing?
It looks like she'll be fine.
She was just really tired.
She's sound asleep.
Such divine beauty!
Fate has brought her to me!
I'm glad she's okay.
I don't get why she tried to run away, though.
If my suspicions are correct...
So, it was a flashily strong shitty monk.
Th-That's about the size of it.
We were stopped by a monk with monstrous strength.
I heard you the first time!
Stop acting half asleep!
And how dare you all come back empty-handed,
you rotten pumpkin-heads!
You have no idea how much money that girl is worth!
Forgive us!
Boss...
We have a good idea of where the girl is.
With Straw Hat, huh?
Yosh!
Bring the monk here.
We're extremely close to raking in some serious cash.
Get to it!
Vivi?
Her name is Vivi?
Yeah.
But she only told me her name.
She didn't want to say anything else.
She's completely recovered, though.
I see. Well, that's all that matters.
Hey, Onami! I want some food!
Me too!
Welcome.
Chief Straw Hat and Doctor Blue Nose.
Huh? What's with the outfit?
I'll be working here starting today.
Vivi-chan's the best!
So cute!
She wanted to help out to show her
gratitude, so I couldn't refuse.
So, you feel fine now?
Yes.
It's all thanks to Doctor Blue Nose.
I've never felt better!
Shut up!
It's not like I want your compliments, you asshole!
Asshole!
I see. Good to hear.
Vivi, why don't you bring them some tea?
Okay!
Hey! Over here, Vivi!
I'm trying to go thay way.
It's hard...
...to carry tea!
But you must've served tea at least once before.
This is my first time!
Huh?
Almost there... almost there...
HOT!!
I-I'm so sorry!
Are you okay, Vivi-chan?
WORRY ABOUT US!!
Hey, hey!
Why don't you eat some delicious food to help you cheer up?
Get on it, Sanji-kun!
Aye, Mellorine!
A-Are you okay?
I'll manage somehow.
Looks tasty!
It's still alive!
Are you alright, Vivi-chan?
I appreciate Vivi's good intentions...
...but this might not work out.
Oi, tea please!
Vivi-chan, me too!
Okay! Got it!
Don't forget me!
Sure!
Me neither!
Here you go!
It sure got crowded in here!
It's because of all the talk about Vivi.
Talk about Vivi?
Yep! Talk that there's a beautiful new girl working here!
Thanks to her, business is up fifty percent!
Vivi's amazing!
I'm so busy!
Vivi-chan, one Tenpura Soba please!
Over here!
Coming!
Vivi-chan's so cute!
Well, Onami-chan's cute too, but she only loves money.
Gotta go with Vivi-chan!
From now on, I'm going to come here every day!
Me too!
Cut it out, you two!
Quit staring at Vivi-chan!
You shitty customers!
Who's a shitty customer, you shithead!?
Shut up!
Your dirty stares are a stain...
...on Vivi-chan's beauty!
We don't need your money!
Get the hell out!
Sanji-san...
Stop that!
Don't treat customers like that!
You're only making things worse, Chief!
Things are back to normal.
Those creeps won't be back anytime soon.
You're safe now, Vivi-chwan!
How am I going to stay in business without any customers!?
I guess this place is doomed after all.
I'm sorry, Onami-san.
I went too far.
It's okay.
It wasn't your fault.
Yeah, no worries!
Oh, crap.
I forgot about something important.
I gotta go.
Oh, Vivi. You come too.
The only thing important to the Chief is having fun.
There are no customers right now, so why don't you go?
We're going to play? Where?
Come on! I said it'll be fun!
Coming through!
I've finally found you.
My, how troublesome.
I heard you had monstrous strength...
...but you even eat like a monster!
He ate our share.
That was good.
So, what do you want?
Check it out, Vivi!
I'm gonna catch a real lunker.
Don't get grossed out again!
I'm fine now!
You don't have to worry.
The Chief isn't actually gonna catch one.
He's a Bouzu master!
That's mean!
I'll show you.
Bouzu?
"Bouzu" is what we call it when someone
can't catch a single fish.
Here we go!
He really did catch a lunker!
His first one ever!
Man, that was strange.
You try, Vivi!
I wonder if I'll be any good.
Th-The fish eat those!?
Huh? Haven't you ever seen a worm before?
Vivi doesn't know anything!
She's even dumber than we are!
I find it a bit strange too...
...but don't put it that way, guys!
The carp bait at the castle is nothing like that!
The castle!?
N-Nevermind...
So, how does this work?
Show me!
W-We've got trouble!
No way!
Why is Vivi-chan on a wanted poster?
They were distributing these at the magistrate's office.
It's an order to secretly seek out someone whose
identity and circumstances are unknown.
I knew there was something about her.
I suspect she's a Western spy...
...or maybe a member of a band of thieves.
Why...?
You shithead!
How dare you talk about Vivi-chan that way!
Still... What is Vivi hiding?
Later, Chief!
Bye!
Yeah!
Come back next time, Vivi!
Don't forget!
Okay! See you later, everyone!
Take care!
Oh! If it isn't the monk from before.
I have no grudge against you...
...but I have a debt to repay.
Don't take it personally.
Huh? What're you talking about?
We meet again, Straw Hat!
This is just a formality...
...but won't you accept a small year-end present from us?
A free trip into the Sanzu river!
Oh, it's you, Buggy?
If you've got a problem with me then fight me yourself!
Don't flatter yourself.
The one I'm after is that precious girl!
Precious girl?
If you want to stop me you'll have to
go through him first, you bastard!
I'm afraid he's right, Chief Straw Hat.
I don't get it.
What are you up to?
I wonder.
Santouryuu, huh?
This'll be good.
GOMU GOMU NO
JUTTE
Boss!
Huh!
Oi, Chief Straw Hat!
What's with those lame punches?
Take this then!
GOMU GOMU NO
SENJUKANNON
Oi, what are you trying to hit? I'm over here!
You bastard!
Oi, guys! Fight somewhere else!
Oi!
Now's our chance.
Come, Richie!
SANZE HYAKU HACH BONNOU
( Three Temporal Worlds: 108 Earthly Desires )
HYAKU HACH PONDO HOU
(108 Pound Cannon)
Oops. My hand slipped.
Liar!
You tricked us, you bastard!
Oops. It slipped again.
Um...
Thank you very much.
That's the second time you've saved me.
You rubber shithead!
I'm flashily angry!
I'm going to blow you to hell along with that deceitful monk!
Huh? Where'd he get that cannon?
Die flashily!
Huh? What the hell!?
Oh, that's really hot.
This is bad.
Boss is a Hammer!
We've gotta save him!
Let's call it a day.
Let's call it a day!
What just happened?
Chief!!
Vivi!
There she is. Vivi!
Vivi-chwan!
Huh? What's going on, guys?
C-Chief! That girl's an imposter!
Look at this wanted poster!
Oh? What's this? That's Vivi-chan?
What's the deal?
What's the deal!? It's just as I thought!
Just as I thought....
You're not bad, right, Vivi?
They're wrong, right?
She's bad.
Hey!
Of course!
I have nothing to hide.
You there!
Do you know who you are talking to!?
That's Zipangu's princess, Vivi-sama!
Unhand her at once!
Princess!?
Uncle!
Wow, Vivi!
You're a princess?
Awesome! A real princess!
Yeah...
What part of "unhand her" don't you understand!?
You really do look like a princess now!
Watch your mouth, you punk!
It's okay, Uncle!
Are you sure, Vivi-sama?
I'm sorry, everyone.
I had never left the castle before.
I just wanted to see what life was like out here.
Man, If that's all you wanted, why didn't you just ask someone
to escort you and avoid this whole mess?
Because no matter how many times
I ask, Uncle always refuses.
Of course. What would we do if something happened to you?
I get it. So the Clown Clan was after Vivi
so they could hold her ransom!
I knew something scary would happen!
Forgive me, Uncle!
But... but...
...I'm glad I met these people.
I had fun.
There was a lot I didn't know but I learned
so much from Chief Straw Hat and the others.
Everyone was so nice to me.
That's why I want to make this land an even better place!
Vivi...
Okay, but please don't do anything like this again.
My heart can't take much more.
Don't worry.
I won't slip out of the castle unannounced again.
Thanks, everyone.
It was only a short while but I'll
never forget the time I spent with you.
Vivi-chan!
Vivi-sama's skill has improved.
Yeah.
She's been more enthusiastic about
her studies ever since that incident.
That's great news.
Yeah.
Vivi-sama, please return soon!
I can't take much more of this!
It must be rough for the Chief Counselor.
I did it! It's spinning!
That's pretty good!
You're a natural!
Really?
Vivi-chan! I thought I'd never see you again!
Didn't she promise not to leave the castle again?
Only unannounced.
But since she gave notice, she isn't breaking her word.
The Chief Counselor must be suffering quite a bit!
Yosh!
Chief! You aren't allowed to use Gomu Gomu moves!
Oops!
Okay!
How noisy.
Them again?
Jeez. Can't a man get some sleep?
Chief! We've got trouble!
An eye that seems real, huge dreams...
...will never see anything but...
...only extraordinary dreamers...
...are allowed on our mother ship!
Forget about being sentimental...
All you need is a smile!
The word family...
...doesn't have just one meaning!
For food and for tears, you can count on our mother ship!
We're not acquaintances...
We're not friends... We are family! Never be alone!
We're not relatives...
We're not even siblings!