Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and in order to move on
to the next stage, the New World,
they returned to Sabaody Archipelago!
Go all the way to the top!
You guys!
There's a whole lot of stuff I want to talk to you about!
But never mind that!
I just want to thank you for going along
with my selfish request for the last two years!
Set sail!!
A Surprising Fact
The Man Who Guarded the Sunny
Brother, it's hard to dig!
Sabaody Archipelago
That's because this island is made mostly out of tree roots.
Please forgive us, don't bury us!
I'll do anything, just don't kill me!
The captain, Black, forced us to do it!
Once we joined them, we thought...
we could kill the Straw Hats...
with high bounties...
easily from within, as we like!
Drip!
Hey, stop! He's gonna die!
Are you a Devil Fruit user?
Don't do it!
Yes! I got him...
Huh? What's going on here? Logia?!
But, look what happened!
I thought he just looked different because I hadn't seen him for two years.
The pirate—Straw Hat... No wonder!
He was just a fake.
Do you think the gods will forgive them, Coribou?
I dig! I dig!
That's right! Let's bury them!
Oh gods!
Let us bury these fools!
Don't! Please don't kill us!
But I saw the real Straw Hat Luffy for myself!
I told you that I had no choice!
Former meeting spot of the Fake Straw Hats
Dark King Rayleigh stood in our way!
He could even fight Uncle Yellow Monkey equally—
what would you expect us to do?
The Caribou brothers and their crew and some of the Fake Straw Hats...
got away successfully.
We caught all the others
but two Pacifistas were
severely damaged by the real Straw Hats.
One of them was the prototype
that cornered the Straw Hats two years ago.
Of course, his strength hasn't changed.
So they must have gotten stronger!
They've improved themselves in last two years, big time!
Make sure to tell Navy HQ in the New World.
The Straw Hats are completely revived!
They're gone before you know it.
Monkey-chan and everybody, they all got stronger.
Were you watching?
Yes, I'm a fan of theirs.
You're thinking about something,
aren't you, Ray-san?
Hmm? Well... Yeah...
Hey, that's a nice ship!
I stole it.
My house burned down so I'm living here.
Yeah? And what's your name?
Rayleigh.
I'm Roger!
I think we were destined to meet, Rayleigh!
Destined?
Do you wanna turn the world upside down with me?
Huh? The world?
Who are you and where you from?
Go away!
Your ship is small but it looks like
it can endure storms if you handle it right.
It's perfect for us to set sail in!
Us? Set sail? Don't decide for me.
Why should I join you?
Like I said, to turn the world upside down!
Alright, let's set sail, Rayleigh!
Maybe nothing in this world happens by accident.
As everything happens for a reason,
our destiny slowly takes form.
At any rate, Luffy looks great in that hat,
better than ever.
Maybe I want to live a little longer.
Under the sea near Sabaody Archipelago
The surface is far up there already.
What a view!
Submarines can't have windows this wide!
We're sinking and sinking!
I can't stop worrying about flooding!
Feels like we're leaving the inhabited world.
It makes me nervous!
C-C-Can we go back on the surface again for sure?
I-It's not like I'm scared but...
It's beautiful down here!
Look at that!
Trees... No, roots!
Oh yeah! Come to think of it,
Sabaody Archipelago consists of giant mangroves!
I'm overwhelmed by the beauty of nature!
I'm so surprised—my eyes could pop out!
I don't have eyes though!
I've seen this already.
Yeah, because you got on the wrong ship!
Shut up! Everybody's having a great time!
I can't believe these roots
are running down to the sea bottom!
They're enormous and magnificent!
I can't hold it any longer!
Hey, Chopper...
There's something behind that tree!
What?
Wow, it's huge!
How exciting!
An underwater adventure! It's like a dream come true!
Oh, fish!
I think I can catch them!
The fish here look delicious too.
Stop it, you fools!
What if the bubble pops!
Don't ever do that again or I kill you!
Nami-san, give us some
dos and don'ts on the coated ship
before they do something stupid.
Okay, Sanji-kun! Rayleigh-san gave me a note.
Alright, everyone, listen...
She's moving! A real, beautiful woman!
Sanji!
It's gonna pop! It's gonna pop!
How can you fly that far with nosebleed!
What?!
Sanji flew out into the water!
It's amazing.
The bubble doesn't break even under tremendous pressure in this deep water
but things can pass through it just like that.
Sanji! Come back!
I feel weak in the water...
Hang in there!
What happened to you, Sanji?!
You've become even more susceptible to women!
This isn't like you!
I feel sorry for him... What happened to
this ladies' man, Sanji-san, in the past two years?
At this rate, he's gonna
bleed to death once he meets
the Mermaids that he's longing to see.
I can't help worrying.
We'll have to call for
blood donations at Fishman Island.
I wonder if Fishmen and Mermaids have the same blood as humans.
The bubble that coats the Sunny
has the same quality...
as the bubbles
at Sabaody Archipelago as we just saw.
Stop analyzing the bubble in such a calm manner!
Yes, Robin's right.
Basically, they're the same.
It stretches to a certain point
and beyond that, it allows things to get through.
Which means if we fire a gun
or a cannon at a creature that attacks us,
the bubble won't break.
Huh? Then, on what occasion will it break instead?
As you can imagine, when there are too many holes at once, it'll break.
For example...
if we are bitten by
a Sea Kings' fangs, it'll be trouble.
It's coming from behind!
They're fighting... We're safe!
Or if the ship itself breaks up
by crashing into a rock or a trench,
the broken mast or planking will break the bubble and that also spells danger.
So we have to be careful
with creatures and obstacles in the sea.
As long as we don't do anything foolish
from inside, it'll be fine.
I see! It's tougher than I thought!
But 70% of ships that head for Fishman Island...
end up sinking, so be cautious.
What's gonna happen?!
With my Gatling, I can catch a whole school of fish!
Then let's see which of us can catch more fish!
Weren't you guys listening to what Nami said?!
"Too many holes" is no good!
Don't ever try it again or I'll kill you!
Damn! Hachi said he'd show us
the way to Fishman Island
so I thought it was gonna be a safe trip!
Oh yeah!
They gave me a lot of lunches!
Since Sanji is sick,
let's eat these, everybody!
I'm so starved!
My bones are starved!
Nami, the ship is gonna be stable for a while?
Don't we have to do anything?
Nope.
We just have to ride this big sea current for now.
So, yeah, we can continue on like this for a while.
We don't have much to do until later.
Then we have a little time, huh?
There's something that I have to tell you all about.
Could it be about...
The robot's secrets?!
You have more secrets?!
What can you transform into?! Or you have a secret weapon?!
Tell us, robot brother!
Super Armored Me!
No, I'm afraid...
I'm afraid it's not about that-robo.
Wow, cool! He speaks Robotese!
This is what I wanna tell you about.
Go ahead and eat while you're listening.
Hachi told us that he would show us
the way to Fishman Island
but he got severely injured at Sabaody
and he's under medical care at Fishman Island.
He got injured for the same reason as Duval.
He had been protecting the Thousand Sunny.
Around a year ago,
the Navy found out about the Sunny
and those two both faced fierce battles and were taken out of commission.
Huh? Then how did the ship remain undamaged after that?
There was someone else who fought for it.
There was someone else?
He's the one who separated us two years ago.
The big Warlord—Bartholomew Kuma!
I couldn't believe my eyes
when I got to the Sunny a few days ago...
I've been expecting you.
What are you doing here?!
Mission accomplished.
There wasn't even a scratch on the Sunny.
And Rayleigh told me later...
I work for the Revolutionary Army.
Since I have a connection with them, I wanna let them get away from here.
I think you guys half expected that.
He saved our lives!
And after we vanished from the island,
Kuma-san visited Rayleigh and told him...
I don't have much time left.
I don't know what made him obey the Navy
but he agreed to be a guinea pig
and let his body be modified into a cyborg
piece by piece and he somehow
lost his personality before the Paramount War.
But I don't think he could guess
what each of us would do after we get separated!
Even so he waited for us
at the ship without his personality?
He made Dr. Vegapunk, who modified him,
agree to program a mission into his mind.
"Defend the pirate ship until the day
that one of the Straw Hats comes back to the ship."
That's why, for the past two years,
without his own memory,
he had been carrying out his own orders,
as a human weapon, waiting for us.
That's insane.
Why did he do such a thing for us?
Terms like "connection," "Revolutionary Army,"
remind me of Luffy's father—
the leader of the Revolutionary Army.
I don't know my father that well.
But that bear-like guy was a good guy, huh?
Kuma...
There is no mistake that he's the one
who gave us the past two worthwhile years.
We can't even ask him
why he did it but just remember that.
Bartholomew Kuma turned out to be one of our greatest allies.
But even if we meet him again,
Kuma is now a heartless human weapon.
That's all I have to say.
I appreciate what he did
but there are still some mysteries.
I hope we can find out his motive one day.
Ally?
Oh, you woke up, Sanji.
Eat lunch! It's from Maiden Island!
Maiden Island?
Is that Kuma guy really an ally?
Don't you realize
where I was for the past two years?
What kind of training were you doing
at the dream island full of women, Luffy?
Whoa, whoa, Sanji-san,
I don't know what you've been through
but let's enjoy the voyage now!
Do you wanna sing with me?
Stop trying to cheer me up! I feel pathetic!
Brother, there he is. Straw Hat.
I can see that, you fool!
I'm gonna join them this time for sure!
How deeply are we submerged now?
It's getting darker and darker.
We went through the euphotic zone
and we're at the bottom of the twilight zone.
It must be more than 1000 meters below.
It's really quiet.
It feels different from submersibles.
It feels like flying in the sky.
The sky, huh?
I have to start using what I studied
on Weatheria for two years.
Whale! There is a whale!
Laboon! Laboon!
No, that's old man Whitebeard!
Hey, hey, there is no time to relax and watch whales.
70% will sink! 70%!
I can't just sit around!
I can't believe we have less than a 50% chance
to get to Fishman Island.
I don't see any creatures or Sea Kings or obstacles that look dangerous yet.
There's something at six o'clock!
Is it a creature? No...
Are you guys all ready?!
Yes, brother!
Yes, yes!
The target is right there!
It's easier to just destroy their ship and let it be swallowed by the sea
but that's no good because they won't know who did it to them.
We gotta cut their heads off and bring them back
to show the world what Caribou is capable of!
Yes!
They're not ready to fight!
It's a complete surprise attack!
Don't make a mistake, guys!
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Hey, guys!
There is a ship kind of thing coming from behind!
What?
A ship?
It's coming towards us!
Charge!
It's a pirate ship!
They're pushing against us!
Go away! The bubble's gonna pop!
No! They're gonna come through the bubble!
Who are they?
Along with the attacking Caribou Pirates, the Sunny sinks to greater depths.
They reach the giant submarine waterfall—Plume.
But there, the bane of the high seas,
the Kraken, is living.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Deadly Combat under the Sea
The Demon of the Ocean Strikes"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Deadly Combat under the Sea
The Demon of the Ocean Strikes