Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
Gear 3!
They opened...
--Huh?!
--All right! I'm heading there now!
What?! How come you're small now?!
Oops!
All right! My body's back to normal!
Just wait, Robin!
I'll be sure to beat the crap
out of that pigeon guy!
Solid Beast Secret Technique...
...Owl Thrashing!
Chapapapapa!
Beans Left!
What was that?!
Ahh! This is terrible!
That's right! He's on our side right now!
I'll do what he told me to.
That's cola! Cola without doubt!
Thanks!
Super!
Chapapa... What's the deal?
It's not like drinking cola would
make a difference or anything.
Guard yourself.
Chapa? What a fool.
Are you gonna give me another pathetic punch?
Strong... Hammer!
Agh!
Whoooa! Amazing!
Sorry. My punches earlier
were indeed pathetic.
Zoro Busts Out a New Technique!
The Sword's Name is Sogeking?
Oh, that's right. Franky, I want
to tell you something while I can.
Hm?
Zoro and Sogeking got connected
by Sea Prism Stone handcuffs, and...
What?!
Then we can't do anything unless
we find that #2 key first?!
Yeah. That's right.
How stupid...
Well, at least I know what's going on.
Chapa!
I'm really angry now! Chapapa!
He sure is tough. He's up now.
Stay there and watch.
Franky...
...Destroyer Cannon!
Wow...
Ow, ow, ow...! I don't like this attack
because it dislocates my joints!
What?! You shouldn't do it, then!
Chapapa! What a moron.
I'm a Six Powers master.
Cannonballs would never hit me!
No matter how much you run around,
you can't escape from my
Franky Destroyer Cannon...
...because it's got chasing cannonballs!
Chasing cannonballs?!
Could it be that the cannonballs
sense the enemy and follow them?!
I've never heard of such technology!
What the heck is he?
Huh?
Hold it!
So it's you who chases the enemy?!
You jerk! Hold it!
Chapapa... I'm being fooled! That bastard!
He disappeared again.
Where are you hiding?!
It's no use searching for me.
I'm an expert at Shave, one of the Six Powers.
In addition to my lightning speed,
I make no noise when moving about,
just like owls when they hunt.
I carry out a perfect assassination.
An owl, huh?
My target won't see me until
the very moment he gets killed.
Take this!
He was hiding here.
Looks like that attack caught
you completely off guard, huh?
How impertinent!
I've never experienced such humiliation!
I'm a CP9 member!
Shave!
Whoa!
Iron Ball!
Ah! Watch out!
Dammit! We're above the sea!
Franky!
This is terrible!
If he gets swept away...
...he'll be headed straight
to the basin of the waterfall!
Since he's in the sea, I can't go rescue him.
Franky! Hang in there!
Chapapa!
Even if I get thrown into the
waterfall, I can use Moon Walk.
This is bad! I can't stop falling!
What a strong current! I can't
keep holding my breath, either!
I have to go up, at any rate!
Chapapa! Sink deep!
Yoyoi!
That voice... Don't tell me
he broke the fridge door...
I... I... I... I...
I... I... I... I... I...
I had a feast!
He got a little fatter!
Just how much stuff in that fridge did you eat?!
I don't wanna drown in a place like this!
Ahhh! I'm almost at the basin of the falls!
I'll die! I'll die! I'm falling! Ahhh!
Franky Butterfly!
Chapapa! I'm not gonna let you do that!
Moon Walk!
Solid Beast!
That son of a bitch!
Hiyaaa!
--Chapa!
--Weapons Left!
Paper Art!
Slime!
Chapapa.
Dammit! What the hell was that?!
Oh, so close!
This is really bad.
At any rate, I'd better get to the shore!
1.0 Cola Cannon! Coup de Boo!
Chapa.
Did you learn your lesson?
It takes more than just strength
to defeat a Six Powers master!
--Strong Hammer!
--Paper Art.
Fall into the falls!
Strong Right!
What...?
What?!
Now, come!
Chapa!
Let go of me, you bastard!
Moon Walk with just one leg
can't support two people!
We're gonna fall!
Yeah, seems like it.
So why don't you bring both of us
back to the shore before we fall?
Or do you wanna try fighting me
while supporting our weight?
It's clear how it'll turn out,
but in that case, my life will be in danger, too.
We're certainly in the same boat.
Let's go back to the shore.
Okay! That's right!
Good job, good job.
Let's go back to the shore together.
Chapapa! But I think the fight
will end the moment we get there.
Oh? You think so?
Chapapapapapa!
Yeah, because I just thought of a way
to finish you off with just one blow.
Oh? So did I, Fukurou-kun.
Chapa...
Robin! Robin! Can you hear me?!
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
We're gonna rescue you for sure. We promised.
We'll take you back no matter what!
Robin!
Isn't the #2 key here yet?
Zoro-kun! This is it for me! I'm exhausted.
Carry me on your back.
Why would I?!
Tempest Kick.
Finger Pistol!
What're you doing?!
You just aimed at me while pretending
to attack those two, didn't you?!
That's a false accusation,
but if you want, we can fight.
I've been frustrated for a while now
that you've been in my way.
What'd you say?! That's what I
wanna say, you stupid herbivore!
No, I'd have to say I prefer meat.
Giraffes should just eat tree leaves!
Looks like we can't avoid fighting, huh?
Okay, then, you just wait here.
I'll go kill our prey.
Don't worry. It won't take long.
Wait! I don't object to us fighting,
but I won't let you have my prey!
Wow, I'm so curious!
Zoro-kun, which do you think is stronger,
Mr. Giraffe or Mr. Wolf?
Hm?
Don't you wanna see?
--Not really.
--I see! So you wanna see their fight, too, huh?!
No, like I said...
Leave things to me here.
Zoro-kun used to be a
well-known pirate hunter,
and is now the swordsman of the Luffy Pirates.
According to his prediction...
Oh, I see! He says the wolf is stronger after all!
That's just natural.
What is it? I see. Still, it's hard
to ignore Mr. Giraffe, he says.
I see, I see. That Sky Slicer, was it?
That was incredible, wasn't it?
They know their stuff.
Wolves are just sly, that's all.
The fact is, they aren't that capable at all.
You son of a bitch! I can't take it anymore!
Do you wanna fight right here right now?
Good, good. All right,
now is our chance, Zoro-kun.
Oh, I see!
It'd be good for us if we can get
them to fight and kill each other.
At the least, we'll get a chance
to run while they're fighting, huh?
Hey! You're just noticing it now?!
And don't say it so clearly!
We almost got tricked into it.
Our prey come first, after all.
Zoro-kun! What do I do with you?
You completely ruined my plan!
It wasn't that great of a
plan from the start, was it?
Ah! Here is survival plan #2!
Zoro-kun. Please make sure you
keep your mouth shut this time.
I wonder which one is cool, a giraffe or a wolf?!
Hm?
Being strong isn't enough!
True strength means one is beautiful and cool!
Hmm, I wonder which one.
Hmm, he indeed has a point.
There's nothing to discuss. It's obvious
that wolves are stronger and cooler.
What're you saying?!
Giraffes are definitely more popular
among kids in a zoo than wolves!
So giraffes are cooler!
As expected, it seems we
fight like cats and dogs.
I'm a giraffe, okay? Not a cat.
Now is our chance, Zoro-kun!
A trick like that won't last for long.
Th-Then are you saying that
you've got a different plan?
We'll play rock-paper-scissors, Sogeking.
--What?
--The problem is these handcuffs.
There's a way to get them off of us.
What?! Does it have anything to do
with playing rock-paper-scissors?
I'll cut off the hand of the loser.
Wh-What's with you coming up with
such a scary idea with a serious look?!
I'm not done! Listen further!
So the one who got the handcuffs off like that
will hurry to Chopper with the cut-off hand
and have Chopper put it back
by re-connecting it to his wrist!
We're not stuffed animals! Don't be ridiculous!
I've got another idea.
Ahh! Ahh! I don't wanna hear it!
I'm tired of arguing.
I can start anytime. The winner can
keep the prey all to himself, so...
--Hm?
--That's...
Snap!
Listen, Sogeking. Don't lose your posture.
You are a sword!
Someone get me a lawyer! I'll sue you for sure!
Now, what're you gonna do?
Take me to the shore already
so that I can knock you out!
You don't have to tell me!
I'll shut you up right here, right now!
Super Cartwheel, Iron Ball!
I'll slam you into the corner of
the tower using this momentum!
I see. It indeed looks like
I'll get smashed into pieces.
Franky Centaur!
--Chapa!
--I've got both your legs!
Now you can't move around at will in the air!
So what?! Even if you do that,
you can't stop this momentum!
That's not totally true.
70 mm 0.2 Cola Cannon!
A bit of Coup de Vent!
Ahh! The momentum has died down!
The rotation stopped! Damn you!
But this is enough!
We're already above the shore!
Now, take this!
70 mm 1.5 Max Cola Power!
Coup de...
What're you doing?!
Give up already, you bastard!
Coup de...
...Vent!
Super!
Doctorine...
I promised you that I wouldn't
use the third rumble ball...
...but I want to save Robin.
I want to put my life on the
line to save our friend, too.
Doctorine... I'm sorry.
Rumble!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Uncontrollable! Chopper's Forbidden Rumble"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Uncontrollable!
Chopper's Forbidden Rumble