Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
However, there they find the New Fishman Pirates
have been plotting to destroy Ryugu Kingdom,
arm in arm with Vander Decken, who has been
stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up
in the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hody's merciless plot puts Fishman Island
in unprecedented danger!
Straw Hat! Please!
We don't need the past!
Reset our history to zero!
Wipe out those phantoms who shut the island away from the sun!
Bring Fishman Island back...
...to zero!
Brother-hoshi.
As long as you let me handle it my way, don't worry.
Our minds were made up when we arrived at the plaza that,
along with Jinbe, we wouldn't let anyone harm the island!
Leave it all up to us, Brother-hoshi!
We're friends, right?
You can't get away from me!
Hody-sama!
Wimpyhoshi!
Stay with me! I promise I won't let you be hurt!
Okay!
Luffy's All-Out Attack!
The Red Hawk Explodes
Oh? Huh?
I lost him.
The guy in stripes.
Where did he go?
Fool! I'm here!
You're gonna be dead before you notice!
Take this!
Camouflage Carpet!
Huh?
I heard a voice around here!
Z-Zeo-san got...
...Stabbed!
How was that, Skeleton?
My weapon-destroying technique called Body Sword Crush made...
...the tip of your sword crumble...
I stabbed you.
He still has too much pride!
Just think that way and get defatted...
Get defeated!
This time, he...
...Stumbled.
Shh! Don't say that.
You just fumbled your words.
Hey!
You dumbhead!
Oh? Oh?! I lost him again! Where did he go?!
Hidden Flail...
...66 Neck!
I learned something...
...in the last 2 years,
about the true power of the Revive-Revive Fruit.
When people die,
their souls must go to the next world.
But my soul,
in order to keep its existence in this world,
radiates a strong energy almost like other corporeal beings.
It enables me to rock a crowd
of people better than anybody else when I play music.
I can draw them into my world and even create illusions for them.
Even when my soul leaves my body, people can see me clearly.
I certainly exist in this world.
I did it!
I took down one of the Straw Hats!
No, you didn't.
What keeps me alive in this world is neither bodily organs...
...nor muscles.
It's my...
...soul!
What?!
Oh! I've got a lot of spunk! All right!
He's pretending he wasn't surprised!
Did you get it?
So, in other words, as long as my bones don't get damaged,
your attack can't pierce me to the bone.
And,
this sword cane which the Longarm Tribe sharpened for me -
it's called Soul Solid!
Its soulful slash will make you feel
the cold air from the land of the dead!
It's the "Freezing Sword"!
Have a good look!
That's awesome, Brook!
The Freezing Sword - how cool is that?!
That's my Soul King!
Oh, thank you very much.
Oh! Oh no! Dammit!
I lost him again!
I have to keep it up too!
Everybody's gained skills to go on to the New World!
Concerning your friends?
Don't worry!
I'll make sure you all get drowned in the deep sea!
Sure-Kill...
Fireball Cutter!
Green Star!
Whoa! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You bastard!
Looks like you're a burden to the Straw Hats!
You didn't hit me at all!
Don't rush around, mole shark.
I'm a cookie-cutter shark!
I just...
...finished setting a trap!
Luffy-sama!
Hody-sama is coming!
You wouldn't let anyone harm the island?
Give it your best shot!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Bazooka!
It's not working!
Luffy-sama!
It's no use, Straw Hat.
We were granted power from heaven!
Give it up! You can't stop the Noah now!
And you will lose everything!
No, I'm gonna finish the whole thing with this one!
You can't finish anything!
Drop dead!
Gear 2, Armament!
I'll never...
...let anyone die again!
Gum-Gum...
I'm gonna bite your arm off!
...Red Hawk!
Luffy-sama!
Straw Hat!
He...
He did it!
Straw Hat Luffy-san defeated...
...Hody, the captain of the New Fishman Pirates,
finally!!
It's not over yet!
Wimpyhoshi, take me to the Noah!
Okay!
At your full speed!
What?! No way! Captain Hody lost?!
What's gonna happen to the Noah?!
This is it! For the island and all of us!
Run!
Zeo-san, please! You know this island is...
Don't be fooled!
Captain Hody was chosen by heaven!
Some loser human could never beat him!
B-But if the Noah destroys the island, we're getting nothing anyway!
Death is another way to get revenge.
Hate humans even in death!
Tragedies will become our flesh and blood.
And our grudge will never go away.
Somebody will take it over and get our revenge for us!
There he is.
Captain Hody and all you officers are insane!
Humans made us insane!
Stop running!
Direct all of your anger toward humans-bogon!
Humans are responsible for every single disaster that Fishmen meet-zugan!
Are humans that terrible?
That's ridiculous!
I mean, when you look at history,
humans did horrible things to Fishmen...
Stop!
Madame Sharley!
See it with your own eyes!
In the plaza and up in the sky,
humans are fighting against the pirates from the Fishman District!
Is he a human, too?
There are some strange ones but...
...you have to see it with your own eyes!
If you don't, you have no right to say something!
No matter what happens,
you have to look at things with an impartial eye.
Those of you who won't fight to the death will get
killed by me in order to leave your hatred toward humans behind!
You can't do that to your own people!
Oh, that was close! Thank you, Skeleton Mask!
It's you again.
You've never died before so don't talk like you know all about it!
Get killed and leave hatred behind? How ridiculous!
Nothing is left behind when you die!
All you can leave behind is your bones!
Very persuasive!
Thank you!
I don't like people who devalue the lives of others!
I can't even stand their smell!
Even though I don't have a nose!
It's you guys who are devaluing lives.
It's so impressive that none of you is trying to escape
but you humans will die once the Noah hits the island!
Although I can't tell if you're a human or not!
Our captain - Luffy will become the Pirate King someday.
And he said it clearly.
That he wouldn't let anyone harm the island and
we can leave it all up to him!
I believe in him so there is nothing to worry about.
Now, I'll do my part.
I won't let you disappear in front of my eyes again!
Although I don't have eyes!
How's this? Surprised?
Yeah, that's enough. Oh, I'm so surprised!
Oh yeah?
Now, shall we finish this up, Jinbe?
Yes, let's do it.
Hey, wait! I've lost my swords.
How can I fight now?
Don't ask me.
How annoying!
I'm gonna end this fight by using a daring technique!
One, two...
On the third step, you will get shot by me and that'll be it!
Don't talk nonsense!
Stop dreaming your stupid dream!
You weakling! Are you crying sour grapes?!
Oh boy, I'm losing my edge.
I used to bluff better in the past.
But now, I can actually do these things.
What the hell is that monster?!
Was it here before?!
Oh, that's...
Chopper!
Th-That little guy got bigger suddenly!
Hey! Whoa, whoa!
You didn't have to go out of control!
I'm okay, Usopp.
What's wrong?
L-Look at that!
H-Hody is...
I can't believe it!
Luffy-sama!
Let's go!
There is air!
The Straw Hat crew finally demonstrates its true power...
...and attempts to overpower the New Fishman Pirates.
Meanwhile, Hody, having derived immeasurable power from the Energy Steroids...
...and the severely wounded Luffy...
...grapple in a final battle!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Long Awaited Conclusion!
Decisive Battle Against Hody"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Long Awaited Conclusion!
Decisive Battle Against Hody