Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
2 years have passed since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew returned to Sabaody Archipelago.
And on their way to the New World,
they reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates, who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
along with Vander Decken, who is after the
Mermaid Princess, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up little by little in the turmoil.
Vander Decken blocks Luffy and Shirahoshi's way to the Sea Forest.
I found you! I suspect!
Shirahoshi!
Vander Decken-sama!
Why do you wanna interfere with my business with Shirahoshi?!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Hammer!
Go Shark!
Meanwhile, at the Ryugu Palace, Zoro and the others...
...are fighting an intense battle with the New Fishman Pirates led by Hody!
Drop dead, you lowly creature!
One-Sword Style, Draw...
...Lion Song!
"The Straw Hats Defeated?! Hody Gains Control of the Ryugu Palace"
Zoro!
--Boss! --Boss!
How could a human move faster than a Fishman in the water?!
What's wrong with that man?!
I need to breathe now!
Damn! How dare he cut Boss!
Don't be afraid! He's just a human! He can't stay long in the water!
Catch the swordsman!
Let's take the Energy Steroid!
Screw this! Kill them all --Neptune's army, too!
Damn!
What's this? I sense a great deal of madness!
Zoro!
Zoro! Is he okay?! He's not surfacing!
I can't take it! I'm losing my strength and I can't take it!
What's going on?
Take this!
Beat him up!
All you can do is defend yourself! Just give up.
You're choking already, aren't you?!
Ah-ha!
You're desperate, huh?
But this is the end of the line!
Drop dead!
Don't push your luck, bastard!
One-Sword Style: 36-Pound Phoenix!
Damn! Now let's just kill them all!
Zoro!
This place is going to be filled with water!
You have to hang onto me, too!
They defeated my strong army very easily.
They've got some kind of uncanny strength.
I have to get all my men out of the palace!
Here! Secure some air with this-jamon!
Oh, thanks!
Hang onto my body very tightly!
Got it!
We don't have time-jamon!
Zoro, this way! Hang onto the old man!
I hope my strained back can take it!
Now, my soldiers! Here is your way out!
Abandon the battle and get out of here!
Merman...
...Combat!
Zoro! Use this!
Here we go!
Neptune's up to something!
Zoro!
Ultramarine!
Ow, ow, ow...
All soldiers, go!
Yes, sir!
Ride the current at any cost-jamon!
Damn! They're escaping without fighting us!
Boss Hody! You gotta take this now!
We're out now! Keep going!
Get through the gateway and go inland!
Hey, old man! Don't pass out, please!
I hate getting old!
I can't move even a millimeter-jamon!
What?!
--King-sama! --King Neptune!
Hey hey, what should we do?!
This is the end-jamon!
No!
Whale!
Oh, Hoe!
Great!
Thank you. Ow, ow, ow... I can't even turn my head-jamon.
Are you okay?!
Good! Well done, Hoe!
Go!
Can't take it anymore!
What was that?!
What's going on?!
King-sama!
Oh no! King-sama's been caught by Hody!
Hody has been severely wounded, hasn't he?!
Minister of the Right-sama, let's go back! If nothing is done, King-sama will...
No, don't turn back-jamon!
You have to keep going and...
...bring Fukaboshi and the others!
There's no time to lose! Do as he said!
Yes, sir!
Boss Hody, should we go after them?
No, just let them go.
Soldiers who abandon their king can't amount to much.
Anyway, tie the stupid king up!
Yes, sir!
I'm sorry, you guys!
But I'm not going to let you down!
What is it?
No idea. Whose skeletonized body is it?
Prince Fukaboshi.
Did you find the Straw Hats' crew?
Yes. I mean, no. Someone from the store had seen them here
but he said Neptune-sama took Straw Hat Luffy and 4 others away.
I think those are the ones occupying the palace now.
I think so.
So they're not here. What about the two from their crew who were in the Coral Hill?
I've been trying to reach them but I can't-mi-re-do.
I see. I have a bad feeling about this.
Moonfish! Shake, shake!
I think something happened there. We better go check.
Oh, you got a call?
Prince Fukaboshi! Prince Fukaboshi, come in!
Brother.
This is Fukaboshi.
Prince, we have a problem! I'm in Waterwheel Town.
Waterwheel Town?
Men from the Fishman District invaded the town
WATERWHEEL TOWN
and Queen Otohime...
You shouldn't have done that.
What about my mother?! Hey! Answer me!
--Let's go to Waterwheel Town! --Yes, sir!
Are they gone?
Yes, to Waterwheel Town I assume.
Dosun acted too early-ch.
There's no point in doing it unless it's simultaneous.
But that's okay. Alright, let's do this-ch.
Listen, guys! Our dreams will finally come true!
Be as wild as you like -ch!
Yeah!
SEA FOREST
It's a beautiful place!
So this is the Sea Forest!
I... always wanted to come here!
Thank you very much, Luffy-sama!
Maybe I can treat him carefully here.
Mermai-do!
Sanji...
Oh, that's the Sunny!
Yeah, Franky is there too!
Hey, Franky! I didn't know that you were here!
Luffy?!
What the hell?! You're with quite a pin-up girl!
Let me introduce you. She's Wimpy.
Oh, you're Wimpy! You have to get tougher, don't you Sis?
Yes, I'm sorry. My name is Shirahoshi.
Franky, no one else is here?
Yeah. Actually Robin came here too but she said she had to look for something
and went into the forest of huge coral.
Hmmm...
Luffy-kun!
Jinbe! Oh, Jinbe!
It's been a while!
You look stronger. I hardly recognized you.
They said you weren't here so I thought I couldn't meet you!
Oh, I thought you came here because you got my message.
What's that? I didn't hear about any message.
Hm, that's odd.
Boss Jinbe-sama. It has been a long time.
Oh, Princess Shirahoshi-sama, you're here too! Long time no...
What?! Princess Shirahoshi!
Why are you here?!
Hey, Franky! Can you help me with Hachi and Sanji?
Yeah!
You're the octopus guy!
What happened to you?
Hachi?! What?!
How were you injured?!
Before that, why are you here on Fishman Island?
I thought you'd been caught with Arlong!
Jinbe-san, why are you here?
Franky, Sanji is next!
No, you don't need to do that.
Oh, Mermaid Princess!
I feel like such a bad painter when I'm standing in front of you!
Because I can't depict your splendor in any of the paint that I have!
Um...
That's the way he always acts in front of women!
He's okay now!
Your beauty won't fit on my canvas!
--Yeah, he's back to his old self! --So I can't draw!
It's so noisy. What's going on?
Huh?!
Why is Princess Shirahoshi here?!
Hey, who the hell are you?! Why are you on board the Sunny?!
That's Den-chan, brother of Tom - my shipwright master...
...doing the recoating for us.
Oh, okay!
So he's a shipwright who's coating Franky's brother!
Yeah, something like that!
What?
Princess Shirahoshi-sama, I know why you wanted to come here but...
Again?
I beat him up so badly but he kept throwing dozens of things! How persistent he is!
Look at what you've done. Why did you bring her here, Luffy-kun?
Don't worry. You know I got your back, right?
Yes!
How careless!
So that's the grave she talked about.
She's been at that for a long time.
That is her mother--Queen Otohime's grave.
Vander Decken's relentless courtship began right after the Queen's death.
That's why the Princess couldn't even attend her mother's funeral
and has spent last 10 years in Hard Shell Tower.
The things that she wanted to tell her mother...
...kept building up inside her heart, probably.
Luffy!
Luffy-chin!
Nami! Camie!
Nami-chin, look!
That's Boss Jinbe who's standing right by Luffy-chin's side!
Oh?
Princess Shirahoshi is with them...
Shocking!!
Nami! Did the banquet start?
--Nami-san! --H-He's cured completely...
Hatchin! What happened to you?!
Camie...
Is that true?! Hody did it?!
Uh-huh.
I never thought that such things could happen at the Ryugu Palace!
What happened to Zoro and the others?!
I don't know. I was gonna go back as soon as I met you.
N-No!
I can't believe Father-sama has been caught!
Luffy-kun, I'm sorry!
I left you the message because I didn't want to get you into trouble
but I let you get involved already.
We have to hurry but let me just say,
2 years ago when I met Luffy-kun, it was harder for me to talk about it than it is now.
I've been feeling very thankful...
...to those people who stopped the Arlong Pirates running wild in the East Blue.
That was you guys, wasn't it?
Thank you! Let me express my gratitude.
And I want to apologize at the same time.
Jinbe-san...
The person who is responsible for setting Arlong loose into the East Blue was...
...me!
Jinbe reveals shocking past events as Nami recalls her difficult time with Arlong
Things become tense between the crew and Jinbe.
Jinbe then tells the great story of two individuals
who tried to change the bitter history between Fishmen and humans.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Haunting Ties! Nami and the Fishman Pirates!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!