We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for... ONE PIECE
Compasses and stuff'll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Blast through the stingy night!
We've no interest in treasure chests
Pockets bulging with dreams, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
My name is...
...Monkey D. Luffy!
Gum-Gum...
...Rifle!
What?!
I am the one and only Luffy!
Gum-Gum...
...Storm!
This isn't a dream, is it?
He won, didn't he?
He did! The Star of Hope won!
He defeated Oars and Moria!
Everyone will get their shadows back!
Thriller Bark has fallen!
The End of Battle Is Nigh!
Pound in the Finishing Move
You're incredible, Straw Hat!
He took out Oars!
Hey, Luffy! Hang in there!
--Luffy!
--Luffy, get up!
It's not my place to ask after
pushing him, but will he be okay?
I bet his body is absolutely exhausted.
He single-handedly wielded
the power of a hundred men.
Anyway, we need to recover all of
the shadows as quickly as possible!
Right! Let's hurry.
The eastern sky is starting
to get dangerously bright!
Dawn is on the horizon.
So how do you get your shadows back?
Four of my crewmates have lost theirs!
I'm sure this has been
a trying ordeal for you.
Really, I'd like Straw Hat
to recover them for us.
Forget it! I bet he can't move a muscle.
Moria reigns over the shadows
in all of the zombies.
Unless he personally says,
"Return to your original master,"
our shadows won't come back.
Let's stop worrying and get to business.
Right! We'll just have to wake
Moria up and force him to say that.
What was the point in defeating him
if we don't reclaim our shadows?
O-Oars is back on his feet!
He shouldn't be able to move
after taking a beating like that!
This is horrible! We're screwed.
The Straw Hat Crew can't fight anymore!
And we used up our trump card, the shadows!
We don't have enough strength
left to level this monster!
That didn't hurt at all.
Damn it!
You really can't defeat a zombie
in a contest of strength.
We've reached our limit.
The sun is going to rise any minute now.
We'll never be free from this
life trapped in the darkness!
Let's give up. If we stay here,
we're just gonna die.
Let's hurry back to the forest.
Let's return... to the dark forest,
where the sun never shines.
Aren't you...?
I don't know what happened to Luffy,
but he dealt plenty of damage.
H-Hey, mister! You'll croak if you
try to run around as you are now.
You can still stand after taking
a blow from that massive Giant?
You're almost as immortal as the zombies!
Hey, where are the members of the
Straw Hat Crew that we moved over here?
B-Beats me! How could they
move when they're out cold?
Huh? What happened to
the two that were here?
You're right! The long-nosed guy
and the lady are gone.
You don't think...
they bailed out on us, do you?
Eh?! When did they run off?
Anyway, this looks bad!
Let's split this scene.
So that... didn't quite cut it!
Huh? Straw Hat?!
Aw, man! Not you too, Straw Hat!
Just one more attack... Damn it!
That really took a lot outta me.
--Robin!
--Yes, I'm here.
She didn't hightail it!
I want up!
Roger.
I'll provide the footing.
If there is anything I could do for you...
Even the skeleton is up and moving!
What?! Why?
Great! Brook, I have a favor to ask of you.
I figured as much.
Everyone has taken positions
to offer support.
What is that lady doing way up there?!
I-It never even occurred
to these guys to run!
The moment Oars stood up...
...they started to prepare
for a counterattack!
Just you watch.
Chopper, hurry! The sun is rising.
Yeah!
Think you can use this, Franky?
That'll be great! Come lend me a hand!
I can't believe it!
These guys haven't given up at all!
Hey, you're in the way! Clear the area!
It would be our pleasure!
Pierna Fleurs!
Here we go!
Thanks!
Wait! Where are you going?
What is this? Smoke? Clouds?
The weather forecast is rain!
Cool Ball!
Rain Tempo!
Wha--?!
It's raining! But why?
Can that lady use magic?
All right! The emergency
plumbing job is done.
Jeez! I'm sopping wet.
Coup de Vent!
What was that?
Crank it like mad!
I'm cranking it!
Here it comes! It's the Super Cold Cannon
connected to the extra-large freezer!
Fire!
I'm frozen!
I can't move.
Incredible!
The cold air froze him.
Now it's my turn!
Darn it!
Go!
Not a chain!
It worked!
Darn rudder chain!
You're amazing, Sanji!
Thanks!
Throw me!
I'm really going to throw you.
I'll be fine! I'm a rubber man!
Be careful.
Gear 3:
Bone Balloon!
Zoro, push in Oars' stomach.
I'm on it.
Three-Sword Style...
...Secret Art:
Three Thousand Worlds!
Wha--?!
Now's our chance.
Here goes nothing.
Looking good, Sanji!
Oars' back is perfectly straight.
What the heck are they doing?
A human spine normally bends in an S-shape
to soften the impact
and weight that goes on it.
But if you straighten it out,
it won't be able to disperse the shock.
It will take all of the damage!
Go, Luffy!
Good luck.
Eat my extra-large bazooka!
I'll repel it with a bazooka of my own!
Gum-Gum... Huh?
It won't move! I can't move my right arm!
It won't extend, either.
The zombies' shortcoming is
their inability to perceive damage.
That's your shadow. Settle the score, Luffy.
Gum-Gum...
Go!
Get him, Straw Hat!
Whatcha think of that?
...Gigant...
...Bazooka!
He did it!
Even a zombie can't get up again
after a beating like that.
He lost...
Oars truly lost this time.
Now what will become of Thriller Bark?
I'm amazed they pulled it off.
They're something else.
We certainly invited a
fearsome crew onto our ship!
What happened to the master?
They won! This time, they
really pulled it off!
They won!
--They really won!
--Thank you! You guys are the best!
You really were the Star of Hope!
You were everything we
hoped you'd be, Straw Hat!
You're tiny!
Who are you?!
Why did you shrink?!
Even though it doesn't hurt, I can't move.
I can't believe he's still ticking
even after we crushed his bones.
His vitality is making a mockery of life!
The morning light!
I wonder why... I have shivers
running down my spine.
Yay! He did it!
Hurray!
He won!
Hey, Luffy! Hurry and get
everyone's shadows back.
This is no time for partying.
All of you are toast without them!
Our shadows...!
You're right. We need to hurry.
Now go smack Moria awake
and make him return our shadows.
The sun is almost up!
I don't need... a wakeup call.
Moria!
Master!
I'm so glad you're all right!
There is no way Moria-sama could lose!
I-If you're up, that works just fine for us.
Now, if you don't want Straw Hat
to kick your butt again,
you'd better return all of our shadows!
Right! Give them back, jerk!
This isn't a schoolyard fight.
Even the threat of death is
meaningless before a true pirate.
I'm able to solve the mystery behind
Straw Hat's excessive level-up
if you "whipped dogs of
the forest" were involved.
How vile of you to use my
shadow ability against me!
Stuff it! Give our shadows back!
Straw Hat, how dare you...
...trash my Thriller Bark
like there is no tomorrow?!
That's what you get for
interfering with our voyage!
Now give back our shadows
before the sun comes up!
At your current strength, you would
have died if you continued your journey.
You're nowhere near strong
enough to face the New World!
You seem to have a pretty decent crew...
...but you'd lose all of them.
Do you know why?
Hey, Straw Hat! You don't have time to chat!
Look at the sky! It's getting so bright.
Please get our shadows back already!
We're running out of time!
I found the answer
through personal experience.
Why did I lose such infamous
and skilled subordinates?
I lost my crew because they were alive!
But with undead zombies,
I have nothing to lose!
Zombies are immortal!
They are unlimited soldiers that can
be replaced if someone purifies them.
With my army of the dead, I shall fight
to become Pirate King once more!
Consider yourselves fortunate that your
shadows get to serve as my subordinates.
It stuck to me!
Come to me, all of the
shadows on Thriller Bark!
Serve as my power!
Shadows Asgard!
Bro!
His shadow came out.
The shadows...!
No way...!
He's collecting all of the shadows
on the island and absorbing them.
Straw Hat, I'd say you absorbed
around 100 shadows.
In that case, I'm absorbing 100...
200!
300!
400!
500!
600!
700!
800!
900!
1,000 shadows!
Darn it! Gosh darn it!
And here I thought we'd won!
But now he's 1,000 times bigger and stronger.
Size and strength don't mean squat!
I'll put everything I've got
into taking him down!
I'm going back out onto the ocean!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Our Bodies Vanish!
Daybreak on the Nightmarish Island!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Our Bodies Vanish!
Daybreak on the Nightmarish Island!