Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has landed on Marineford
to save his brother, Ace, from execution.
Luffy and the Whitebeards are trying to make it
to the execution platform but have been walled in.
With Jinbe's help, Luffy was able to breach the barricades and finally make it to the plaza.
Luffy!
I'm on my way!
Ace!
Wh-What is that?!
We're enclosed!
What the hell is this?!
Do it, Red Hound!
Meteor Volcano!
He's firing lava fists into the air!
They can't get away!
Melt the ice that they're standing on!
I'm sorry...
The plan is going well!
Now let's move on to...
...the execution of Portgas D. Ace...
...immediately!
Jinbe!
I need you to do me a favor!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Oh no! You finally made it!
You're standing tall, Dragon's son!
It scares me! His youthfulness!
I'm gonna get Ace back!!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp Gatling!
Moving into the Final Phase!
Whitebeard's Trump Card for Recovery
I can't believe that he's attacking
the 3 admirals openly!
He's a damn fool! They're gonna kill him!
Gear 2!
I don't have time to fight those guys!
He fooled us!
You're too slow!
Luffy-san!
I told you!
Damn!
Be ready!
Yes, sir!
Do it!
Ace!
Ace-san!
Ace!!
Who did this?!
You bastard!
I thought that it was to our advantage to have you
since you hold a grudge against Whitebeard.
Crocodile!
That guy!
What is this? I thought
this was my chance to show off.
He was trying to kill the old chap before.
The winds have changed!
I can kill that old, dying buzzard later.
But before that,
I don't want to let you taste victory!
Hey, you, gator guy!
D-Doflamingo!
You turned me down and now,
you wanna team up with Whitebeard?
It makes me jealous.
I'm not gonna team up with anybody.
So that means you are still giving me the cold shoulder.
Looks like it.
I don't know what this is all about but it's helpful!
This is it, Straw Hat!
Die!
Don't get in...
...my way!
Stop, Straw Hat!
I won't let you go any further!
Outta my way!
Shave!
Moon Walk!
Iron Body...
...Smash!
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
...Bullet!
Stop Straw Hat!
Don't let him go any further!
Admiral Sakazuki!
That hurts! Dammit!
I owed a favor to your grandfather
but I have no choice!
Because you chose to risk your life!
You fool! I won't let you do that to Luffy...
Admiral!
That's...!
1st division commander—Marco!
Thanks! You saved me!
Don't mention it!
We've got three invaders in the plaza!
Devil Fruit users can fly over the walls!
Th... Three?
A-Am I one of the three that they're talking about?
But when did they find out about me?!
I escaped Admiral Blue Pheasant's attack by a hair
and survived so many deadly crises!
And finally I got this far!
But I'm not safe here either!
Isn't there any place safe?!
Someone's coming!
That was...
Inside Marineford bay
Go across the sea towards Oars!
Get to the plaza whatever it takes!
Fleet Admiral-dono!
The pirates inside the bay are acting strangely!
Go across the sea towards Oars!
Get to the plaza whatever it takes!
They are desperate.
Defend the open space in the wall!
Yes, sir!
They've gone crazy after losing their ships and the
ice they stood on, stupid pirates!
They're fair game for us! Shoot!
Don't hesitate! Keep going forward!
Head towards Oars!
Get to the plaza!
Wh-What's wrong with them?
How can they keep their morale in this situation?!
Advance!
Everybody, get on board!
Hold on tight!
N-No way! It's a ship!
We have a problem!
Another coated ship is entering the bay!
Dammit! It must've been hidden at the bottom of sea all this!
I don't remember saying that that was all of our ships.
It's a paddle boat! It's coming towards us at full speed!
What?!
Sink it like the Moby Dick!
No! Not the boat! Shoot at Oars!
Huh? Why Oars?
It's too late!
Get ready, everybody!
He pulled the boat out of the water!
Through the barricades!
We made it to the plaza!
Let's save Ace!
Let's burn down Navy HQ!
Wait for us, Ace!
They got us!
There was only a space the size of a rathole!
But they went for it wisely!
The walls could become an obstacle for us this time!
Pops!
Whitebeard!
You still have your head, right, Ace?!
We did it!
Now we can save Ace-kun...
Oars!
Save Ace-kun at any cost...
Oars...
Whitebeard has descended to the plaza!
Stay back, my sons!
Guys! Rescue Ace and...
...destroy the Navy!!
Garp.
Yeah.
I don't think we can make it through this unscathed!
I'm on my way, Ace!
At last, Whitebeard stands before Ace!
But he's faced with
the two admirals Blue Pheasant and Red Hound,
and the conflict becomes a battle royal.
Amidst the chaos, Marco finds an opportunity
to make a dash toward Ace!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Luffy at the End of His Tether!
An All-out Battle at Oris Plaza!!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Luffy at the End of His Tether!
An All-out Battle at Oris Plaza!!