Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats, Luffy hurries
for Navy HQ in order to rescue his brother, Ace.
Meanwhile, at Navy HQ, with Ace's execution at hand,
the Whitebeard Pirates suddenly appear.
You better tell me that my beloved son...
...is all right.
Pops!
Finally, the war has begun!
I can hear the ground rumbling!
Now it's coming!
The seaquake that he set up before!
Coming in the form of a tsunami!
It's a tsunami!
Ice Age!
What? Do you wanna fight?
I just want to figure out the true distance...
...between us and that man
who seems like right in front of us.
An All-Consuming Inferno!!
Admiral Red Hound's Power!
Oh no!
Run!
Pops!
He deflected the blow
of the world's greatest swordsman!
H-H-He must be...!
...3rd division commander—Diamond Jozu!
You better keep your wits about you!
Guys! Let's keep advancing!
Fight them back!
What fools!
They want to break through from the front!
Artillery unit!
Fire at the enemy ships and approaching pirates!
Yes, sir!
Forward units, don't allow them access to this plaza!
Oh boy...
The commanders of the Whitebeards are true to their reputation.
They are all pretty much like monsters.
To finish this with minimum damage,
we just have to cut off their head nice and quick.
I-It's bright!
Wh-What is it?!
I-It's Yellow Monkey!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
Hey, that's so bright.
He warded off the admiral's attack!
What's that?
He's engulfed in a blue flame!
Blue flame?
You can't reach...
...the king...
...so easily!
So fearsome, these Whitebeard Pirates.
What's with his body?!
He took Yellow Monkey-san's attack directly but didn't fall!
So he has this power as they say?!
It's even rarer than Logia.
Zoan type—Mythical Creature.
Look! His wounds are disappearing!
I-I can't believe it! It didn't hurt him?!
It did.
Don't lie.
So he's the 1st division commander...
No matter what kind of attack
he absorbs, he recovers by flames...
Marco the Phoenix!
I have never seen a bird like that.
How painful.
Don't lie!
Yellow Monkey-san got blown away!
I can't believe it! Yellow Monkey-san!
I knew that you wouldn't let me...
...strike your head that easily.
Giant unit, you better pay attention to the sky, too.
Yes, sir!
Here come the Giants!
Attack their feet! Let's topple them!
All of you! Stand back!
Jozu!
What power!
Withdraw for now!
What is he doing?!
Stop this if you can!
It's a block of ice!
It's gigantic!
Damn! Those two...
They shouldn't leave their positions like that.
If all three of us left our positions...
...who would cover them?!
Red Hound-san!
Great Eruption!
That gigantic block of ice disappeared...
...into thin air!
No...
Get away!
Volcanic rocks!
Too many of them!
Dammit!
One of our ships has been hit!
Get away from the ship!
This is like watching the end of the world!
He lit up the place too brightly.
Why don't you light up
birthday cakes instead, you magma squirt!
Don't you want an illuminated funeral
for yourself, Whitebeard?
There're 3 more!
Keep firing! Don't fall back!
Don't be afraid!
Get to the plaza!
Stop the commanders!
Don't let them get ashore!
Sink the Moby Dick and kill Whitebeard!
Th-Th-They are pirates...
And this is a real battlefield!
Oh no!
I feel weak at the knees and I can barely move!
It's impossible...
We have nothing on these guys!
Don't you think so?
They are all monsters.
There's no role to play for fledglings like us!
Let's get away from here. Okay?
Okay?
But...
Are you nuts?
If we try to fight this battle,
we won't last even a second and you know that!
Don't you wanna become an admiral?!
I'll become a Navy...
...ad...
...admiral someday!
You wanna fight me, right?
Then, of course you have to become a big deal like that!
D-Don't take this the wrong way!
That's why, that's why...
...neither of us can die here!
Our place to die is still far away!
But I promised Luffy-san so...
Wh-What is it this time?!
Here he comes!
Get him! Get him!
Break the artillery defense of the Navy ships!
Ace-kun!
Nice! Get them!
Little Oars Jr.!
He must be a descendant
of the Continent Puller Oars.
He's big!
He's way bigger than common Giants!
Don't let him invade the island!
It'll give them the advantage!
I didn't know that the descendant of Oars
was allied with Whitebeard!
I want it!
I want his dead body!
He makes me tingle!
Oars!
Ace-kun is a nice person!
I won't let him...
...die!
In the past, the Straw Hats suffered at the hands of the beast, Oars.
Now, to save Ace, an ally of the Whitebeard Pirates,
the descendant of Oars breaks through to the bay.
How will the Navy deal with an attacker whose power
overwhelms even the Giants?!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Descendent of the Beast!
Little Oars Jr.—Full Speed Ahead!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Descendent of the Beast!
Little Oars Jr.—Full Speed Ahead!