Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has landed on Marineford
to save his brother, Ace, from execution.
The battle in the bay heats up as the Navy tries
to stop Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates
from advancing towards
the execution platform holding Ace.
I'm sorry, Red-Haired.
I will not hold back my power.
That's...
...Hawk-Eye!
Now, I wonder if fate...
...will end the life of the child of the next generation here.
Or, if it will save him from this Black Blade!
The Great Swordsman Mihawk
Luffy Attacked by the Black Blade
I don't have time to face such a strong guy.
I'm here to save Ace!
Gear 2!
Heehaw!
Death Wink!
Galaxy Wink!
That's it, Straw boy.
Just focus on advancing.
We'll handle the rest!
We'll get this guy!
Heehaw!
Hawk-Eye, do you remember us?!
We're the guys who challenged you once!
But now we're powered up as New Kamas!
I don't remember the face of every worm.
Great! Just gotta keep running and...
You are in range.
Ow... Ouch! I got cut!
Only Ace-san's brother could avoid getting a fatal wound like that.
First Son of the Sea Jinbe!
I won't let you so much as touch Luffy-kun again!
Even if it means death!
Why are you doing this?
I want to rescue Ace-san!
For one reason, to save our sea!
It is too late to stop this war now
but we still have hope.
Namely, Luffy-kun over there.
I understand. But I still don't know
what fate has in store.
Therefore, I need you to step back.
Fishman Karate:
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
Shark Brick Fist!
He's really strong as I thought.
Hawk-Eye jumped into the air?
You bastard!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazoo...!
That was close! If I had reached out, my arms would've been severed!
You could be level-headed.
He sliced the mountain of ice with just the swing of a sword!
S-So this is what
the world's strongest swordsman can do!
How strong is he?!
Straw Hat's dead because he's the target now!
The blocks of ice are falling on us!
Stealthy footsteps oily feet.
Ready, guys?
Let's get the "Make Captain Buggy
a Star in Front of Everyone" plan in action!
I know that they're broadcasting the war to the whole world.
There must be
a Video Transponder Snail somewhere.
Find it!
Yeah!
"Find it?" "Yeah?" I don't think that things are that simple.
Team up? Me and you?
Yes. The reign of outdated pirates like Whitebeard will end soon.
And the new era will be our era where power conquers everything.
Don't you wanna get a piece of it?
Not bad, is it?
Your title has been stripped away but...
...when you get down to it, we're both Warlords, aren't we?
You better stop looking at me
as if I'm on par with you.
You should be pledging to work under me instead.
I thought that you became a better person
in hell—Impel Down, the great prison!
If so, then I wouldn't be here now.
Sables!
Get lost, Flamingo shit!
I thought that you could be reasoned with.
If you don't fight the Navy, it's easy!
We can breeze through!
B-Breeze through! Breeze...!
Captain Buggy!
He got caught up in the whirlwind of someone else's fight!
You're not gonna move aside at any cost, Hancock?
Of course not! I won't let you hurt my beloved husband!
Husband?
Yes, my husband!
After the wedding, we will go on a honeymoon!
It's a sweet sweet honeymoon with Luffy my love!
But what if...
It's about time to eat.
But the food storage is empty.
There are a lot of things that we can catch and eat!
My honey! I wanna eat your homemade dishes!
Okay! If you want it...
Could you give me a little time?
If things go like that,
I'll have to make tons of dishes
that could satisfy Luffy's appetite all by myself!
Snake Princess-sama! Let us make it for you!
Luffy wants to eat my homemade dishes!
Keep your hands away!
Honey! Isn't it ready yet?
It's coming!
How admirable!
I'm ready for any trouble. Because I'm... I'm...
...his wife!
"Wife?"
I don't know if she wants to fight or not.
I'll get Straw Hat!
I told you, you outrageous fool,
that I won't let you pass through here!
Perfume Femur!
Hancock! You...!
What are you gonna do now?!
You're getting farther from your brother!
Damn!
So this is it after all.
Breeze through! Breeze! Breeze!
His fighting capability has improved a bit but I've already seen it all.
I won't miss it again from this distance!
Don't mind me! Just breezing through!
Gum-Gum...
Oh, you save...
...Jet Human Shield!
You! What're you doing?! Straw Hat!
What?! I'm not the one who cut you!
Plus you just said "Don't mind me!
I'm here to save you!"
How deluded is your hearing?
Gum-Gum Human Shield!
Stop it!
I can't take it! You must be Hawk-Eye!
The Special Muggy Ball! Blow away!
Here's a joke!
How is the Muggy Ball useful for tunnel construction?
And the answer is?
Say it together, everyone! Because it goes...
BOOM!
Great, Buggy!
Yeah, Captain Buggy!
That was a good one!
Thank you, Buggy! I'll never forget you!
It's far from over!
Vista, Pops said that we can't let Ace's brother die!
Back him up!
I got it! Count on me!
5th division commander
of the Whitebeards—Flower Sword Vista!
5th Division Commander, Flower Sword Vista
Nice to meet you, Hawk-Eye Mihawk.
You've heard of me?
Everybody knows you.
That was close! Who is that old guy?
It's not because of his power or skills!
Whatever! Thank you!
He seems to rally all those around him to his side!
Stay at it! Straw boy!
He made it through fine.
Luffy! Save your brother!
Outta my way!
Among all people on the sea,
he has the most formidable ability!
Ace!
S-Straw Hat! I'll get even with you!
You're great, Captain Buggy!
You pretended that you were beaten by Hawk-Eye
but shrewdly executed the plan!
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb, Captain Buggy!
Video Transponder Snail?!
Y-Yeah, that's right!
A hero who can change the world is someone
who can open his own way
to the future by his own hands!
I'll follow you to the end, Captain Buggy!
Shh...
Yeah!
Now, the important part begins here.
How optimistic can you be?
As time ticks down toward the execution,
shocking truths have been revealed one after another.
From the great, iron-tight prison Impel Down,
surprisingly more than 200 people had escaped
and those same notorious prisoners have been caught up in the war.
The expanse of the battlefield is an unearthly site.
It's certainly the showdown
at the summit that will change history!
People all over the world can do nothing...
...but follow the war that will change their future
that seems so changeable now.
Fleet Admiral, we are all set.
Those at the bay area, too?
Yes, everything.
Huh?
They're getting ready for the execution.
Those bastards!
What are they gonna do to Ace? It's not time yet!
Will it begin already?!
That's impossible! It's before the announced time!
Cut the connection
of the Video Transponder Snail right away!
We the Navy and the World Government
must win this war in the name of absolute justice!
No matter what it takes.
But it's too much to see, for this naive world.
We don't have to show them
the horrific images that will unfold here soon.
Pops...
Hurry up!
They're really gonna execute Ace ahead of time!
Ace!
The news that will go
around the world afterwards...
...should be of our victory and only that!
Our ships!
Look at the bay head! There's something!
They're not our buddies!
The Navy soldiers must've gotten around the ice wall!
They still have soldiers who can destroy big ships?
That's...!
Wh-What are they?!
So that's the Government's human weapon that I heard of.
The bear guy from Sabaody!
There're so many of them!
K-Kuma?
An hour and a half since the war began,
the Navy makes a big move!
The tide of the war changes
its course quickly and flows into its final stage!
Alright, guys! I'm getting tired of waiting!
It's showtime!
The Whitebeard Pirates and the Navy
seem to have fallen into a stalemate as neither
force can manage to get the upper hand.
But then an army of human weapons
that look like Bartholomew Kuma appears,
and the Whitebeard Pirates and Luffy are under attack from both sides.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Extermination Strategy in Action
The Power of the Pacifistas"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Extermination Strategy in Action
The Power of the Pacifistas