Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
If you really intend to take him with you...
...do whatever it takes.
Take him by force!
That's the only way to free him!
Goodbye My Dear Underlings!
Franky Departs
Put something on!
You perv!
How dare you destroy the town again?!
Leave town, you perv!
You good-for-nothing!
Give me my swimsuit back, Straw Hat.
Then join us!
Don't be silly! You think
you can make me join you
just by stealing my swimsuit?!
Yow!
"Nothing should phase men."
Nothing should phase men.
"A man should be resourceful,
even with only the skin on his back."
A man should be resourceful,
even with only the skin on his back.
"He should be like a lion that
stands against the waves!"
He should be like a lion that
stands against the waves!
He struck a pose, completely
exposing his private parts!
Don't look at him!
He's the worst... He's the worst!
I underestimated him!
What a strong-willed guy he is!
He's a man among men!
He's just a total perv!
If it's okay to get rough
with him, I can help you.
What?
Come to think of it, Ice pops said that we
had no choice but to take him by force.
But how?
Dos Fleurs:
What?
Grab!
What?! Hey, Robin!
You grabbed them! Ouch!
--You're gonna crush them, Robin!
--Ow, ow, ow...!
They're gonna come off!
They're gonna be plucked off!
Just like tangerines!
Hey, Robin! I want him to still
be a man when he joins us!
Don't tear them off!
It hurts just to watch!
What's going on?! Franky's in pain!
What's this gut-wrenching cry?!
It sounds like he's on the verge of death!
I kinda feel sorry for him...
...even though he's a perv.
If you're telling us, pirates, to give up
the treasure right in front of us,
we can't back off unless
you give us a good reason.
L-Like I said...
...I-I wanna stay on this island!
I-I do appreciate you guys!
In fact, I can't thank you enough!
I wanna go with you and help you out,
but there's something I need to do here.
That's why I gave you the ship as a gift!
Besides, I'm not a shipwright
anymore in the first place!
So that ship is the last ship I'll ever build!
It was my long-cherished desire.
That, indeed, is a dream ship!
Hold it, Franky.
I don't think that ship has become
the dream ship you're referring to yet.
A dream ship?
That's right! Blueprints alone
can't complete that ship!
After setting sail, it has to cross many seas
and overcome many battles and hardships...
...before it reaches the end of the sea.
After doing all those things,
then you can finally call it a dream ship.
And when my best ship is completed one day,
I'll board that ship as a shipwright
in order to witness that fated day.
By that day, the ship will
probably be falling apart,
but I'm sure that it'll be
giving off a magnificent light!
What do you think? Isn't that great, Tom-san?
Yeah, that's great!
If you also become a sailor, you'll beat me.
I wonder if your pirate blood is affecting you.
Ha! Moron-ky, someone like
you can't surpass Tom-san!
What'd you say?!
What're you doing, you Moron-ky?!
Ribbit, ribbit.
Well, if you're a man, do it resolutely!
What I wanna do has changed!
What you wanna do? That's not true.
Everything you're doing on
this island right now is...
...atonement.
You're still regretting that Tom-san
was taken that day because of you.
But Tom-san had already
forgiven you on that day...
...and tried to guide you.
Ships that would do something like that...
They're no longer my ships!
Tom-san... hit Franky for the first time...
What'd you do that for?!
"They're no longer my ships," you say?
You can say anything but that!
What's wrong with saying that?!
I'm regretting it!
If only those ships didn't exist,
no one would have had to get hurt!
No matter what kind of ship it is,
the act of building it...
...is neither an act of good nor evil!
I don't care what kind of
ships you choose to build,
but even if the ships you built hurt someone,
or even if they destroy the world,
at least the one who created
them must love them!
Their creator mustn't deny them!
Don't blame the ships!
A man should be resolutely proud...
of the ships he created!
That you brought the punks
on the backstreets together...
That you called yourself a bounty hunter
and protected this island from looters...
You did all that to protect this
city of water that Tom-san loved,
which was your way of atoning...
...though it doesn't appear that way to others.
Of course it doesn't.
That's not why I did what I did at all!
Ow, ow, ow...!
You quit building ships,
which was your favorite thing to do,
and have lived suppressing yourself.
Are you going to live like that
for the rest of your life?
Even if Tom-san forgives you,
or even if I forgive you,
nothing is gonna change, is it...?
Isn't it about time...
...for you to forgive yourself, Franky?
Isn't it about time for you to
start living for your own dream?
What the heck?!
A bag?!
It has what you'll need for your journey, Bro!
Out of the way, you bastards!
It's the Franky Family!
--Bro!
Those guys...
Bro! Please forgive us for all that
stuff we pulled! We're really sorry!
We're sorry!
We're prepared to receive
any kind of punishment!
Since we're fools, we racked what
little brains we have thinking about it!
Just what did you rack what little
brains you have thinking about?!
How to steal my swimsuit? Well?!
How to make me a pirate?!
Mind your own business!
It's my life! No one can decide it but me!
How can I, your boss, willingly walk
on the way paved by my underlings?!
That's shameful!
If your brains are so small, then don't
try to use them in the first place!
I-I'm sorry. But...
...aren't we even allowed to think a little?
We're deeply indebted to you
for taking in thugs like us.
Aren't we even allowed to
think about your happiness?!
Who's the fool here?
You guys are all...
Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
--B-Bro!
--Ow, ow, ow, ow...
--Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
--H-Hey, Robin!
Go easy on him! Please!
You're gonna make him a woman!
He's crying!
They're gonna come off!
They're gonna be plucked off!
Just like grapes!
Ow, grapes!
Damn you, Nico Robin!
You're not gonna get away with this!
They're gonna come off!
They're gonna be plucked off!
Just like apples!
Ah... pples...
My tears won't stop because of the pain!
Robin!
H-Huh? You aren't doing anything?
I only did it once, the very first time.
How sly of him to pretend
that he's crying out of pain.
--What?
--Just once?
Dammit! Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
It hurts so bad I can't stop the tears!
You still haven't found them yet?!
Don't let them get away no matter what!
Look far and wide for them!
It hurts! It hurts! I can't stop the tears!
Bro!
Are you okay?!
How could I be okay?!
I've never seen you around.
What's with you, bikini guy?
Don't be so stuck-up on these backstreets.
Get him!
Wh... What the hell?!
How dare you mock us?!
You're quite strong. You're just
wasting that strength by being a thug.
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Zambai!
I'm Franky. I've decided to make the
backstreets of Water Seven my turf.
Nice meeting you!
Y-Yes, sir.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Bro!
I'm feeling great!
Let's go to one more bar!
Hey, you over there with the stylish bikini!
Let's have a drink together.
We'll take you to a bar.
Wh-What're you doing?!
Let go of us!
You young girls, don't sponge booze
from others in broad daylight!
I know a place that serves good cola!
Why don't you come with me?
Bro! Bro!
G-Give me something to eat.
Bring everyone who has nothing to eat!
Go as nuts as you want!
We're starting the Franky Family!
Yeah!
--It's our start!
--We're the Franky Family!
Yahoo!
Franky! Franky! Franky!
Franky! Franky! Franky!...
Can you... live without me?!
Bro...
The face of the Water Seven underworld...
We'll work together to take
over that role splendidly!
So don't worry!
Don't cry, Bro!
Bro!
No matter how far you go,
we're your underlings for the rest of our lives!
Bro!
Ow, ow, ow...
I can't stop the tears!
Hurry!
This isn't good.
Luffy!
Ah! Zoro! Sanji!
We've got trouble!
Your grandpa is back, Luffy!
They're at the opposite seashore.
They're looking for us now!
They're going to attack us!
What?! Why?! I thought he said
he wasn't gonna capture us.
How would we know?!
Hurry up and get ready to set sail!
Whoa!
Franky! You still haven't
put on your swimsuit yet?!
I'm giving this back!
Now, come on board, Franky...
Board my ship.
Don't be so cocky!
You guys are total amateurs who
could only manage makeshift repairs!
It'd be a pity for such a magnificent ship
not to have a shipwright on board.
I guess I don't have much choice
but to help you guys out!
I, Franky, will be the shipwright on your ship!
All right! We've got a new crew member!
Yay! All right!
Bro...!
Don't cry! Don't cry!
Straw Hat is a man we can trust!
Tom-san... I'm leaving this island.
Say, teach me how to draw
blueprints for a pirate ship!
What's so funny?
Aren't you going to bed yet, Tom-san?
What're you drawing?
Mm... It's this island's hope.
Hope?
I wasn't a good disciple. I always
caused you nothing but trouble, but...
Did you guys hear about the scrap heap island?!
Tom's Workers has finished
building the sea train, you say?!
Thank you for everything!
Galley-La's foremen...
Take good care of Iceberg!
I've caused you nothing
but trouble, too, Iceberg.
Old hag Kokoro, little one and bunny...
R-Ribbit...
Yokozuna...
Perv!
--Lively townspeople...
--Where're you going?!
You're coming back, aren't you?!
My little sisters...
Sodom... Gomorrah...
And... my dear underlings...
I'm stepping out for a bit!
Put on your swimsuit.
What?! Usopp's coming back?!
Really?! All right!
Okay, then! Let's go get him right away!
Hold it, you guys!
--What?
--I won't allow any of us to go get him.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Departing the City of Water!
Usopp Mans Up; the Duel Concludes"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Departing the City of Water!
Usopp Mans Up; the Duel Concludes