Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy hurries for Navy HQ in order
to stop his brother, Ace, from being executed.
No way!
I think he'll appear from where we least expect.
Maybe we got the wrong lineup.
I see a shadow in the bay!
I get it now!
They got all their ships...
...coated and approached from underwater!
Here comes Moby Dick!
The Beginning of the War!
Ace and Whitebeard's Past
No way!
There's more?
Th-There are 3 more Whitebeard Pirates ships!
They've infiltrated the bay!
Th-That's the...
...1st division commander—Marco!
The 14 commanders...
they're all here!
It's been awhile, Sengoku.
Whitebeard.
You better tell me that my beloved son...
...is all right.
I can't believe that we let them get this close!
We made it through the gate...
but what Vi'm concerned about is whether your guys' father is here or not.
"Your guys'"?
Vi don't think that Dragon
would let them kill his own son...
Oh, my dad and Ace's are not the same.
My dad is Dragon
but Ace's dad is Gold Roger.
He got such a great father but he never met him.
He'd get mad every time I mentioned it.
Oh, I shouldn't have said that.
Give me a second, Ace.
Pops!
Wh-What is that?!
He cracked the air?
Where's that explosion coming from?!
No good! The water surface is too high!
A seaquake! He's distorting the sea!
The other side, too!
This is the power of Whitebeard!
I'm heading out first!
Take care, Ace!
Yeah. See you, Luffy!
Uh-huh!
I'll be a lot stronger when I leave here in 3 years!
You bet!
Ace!
We'll show them how it's done!
That bastard! He became a pirate!
It's a pirate ship! I never seen their flag!
This is a pirate who's become very powerful rapidly recently.
"D?" Where is he from?
We can't quite figure that out
but even as a rookie, he has the power of Logia.
Such a dashing young man in the Grand Line.
He refused the offer to join the Warlords.
How long have they been at this?
They're still young.
They shouldn't rush.
Are you serious, Captain?!
I have to see him...
...Red-Haired Shanks.
Spade Pirates?
The infamous super rookie came to say hello to me?
It's not what you're thinking.
My brother was always talking about you as his lifesaver
so I came to say thank you.
You're Luffy's brother?
I didn't know that he had a brother.
Great, I'm glad to meet you!
Tell me all about yourself!
Let's have a banquet!
So he's still talking about becoming the Pirate King?
I guess that's his favorite phrase.
I feel sorry for him because...
I'm the one who'll become the next King.
Yeah? You think?
First, I'll let the whole world know the power I have.
Oh? How'll you do that?
By beating the strongest man in this world!
You mean Whitebeard?
Hey, big guy, I wanna see
the guy who goes by Whitebeard.
I cannot introduce a sharp
young man like you to the old chap!
Captain, that's Jinbe!
Oh, the Warlord?
Then I'd gain prestige if I beat him.
I'm not on the crew of the Whitebeard Pirates
but I owe him, so I'll fight you!
It's been 5 days since they started fighting.
They're both gonna die!
Ace!
What is that?!
Which one of you wants to kill me?
I'm gonna fight you as you wish.
Whitebeard Pirates!
I'm gonna fight you people single-handedly.
Guys!
Flame Fence!
Captain!
Captain Ace, what are you doing?!
Run, guys!
Captain!
What's the matter? Are you backing away after all?
Let my crew get way. Instead...
...I'm staying!
You snot-nosed brat!
How cheeky you are!
So this is the guy who contended for supremacy with him.
I won't...
Still some fight left in you?
You are too valuable to let die now, boy.
If you still wanna run wild,
run as wild as you want on the sea under my name.
Become my son!
Screw you!
Hey!
I'm the 4th division commander.
My name is Thatch.
If you're gonna join us,
we should become friends!
Shut up!
So you're grumpy when you wake up?
Oh yeah, you wanna know
what happened after you passed out?
Your crew came to get you back
so we beat the hell out of them.
But they're not dead. They're on this ship, too.
Don't you have to put me in cuffs or shackles?
Shackles? We don't need them!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Do you know what time it is?
Guys, he fell overboard!
He can't swim.
Somebody, help him.
He's been at it every day.
How gutsy he is.
Must be more than 100 times now?
I guess.
Why...
...do you people call him Pops?
Because he calls us "sons."
We are all hated by the world.
So it makes us happy.
I know it's just a word.
But it still makes us happy.
Are you gonna keep doing this after your life has been saved?
You got to make up your mind.
You're not capable of killing him.
It's either get off of this ship and start over again...
...or stay here and...
...wear the Whitebeard logo on your back!
Are you Doma?
Ace did it again!
He made Doma and his crew surrender by himself!
You want me to command 2nd division?
It's been a vacant post
for a long time. If you took it...
...nobody would complain.
You're one of the originals, right?
Don't you mind it at all?
I'm okay, don't worry.
I've got no such ambition.
Do it for us! Commander Ace!
Pops, you got a minute?
Well, that was surprising.
I didn't know that.
Your character is nothing like Roger's.
He was your enemy, right? Don't you wanna kick me out?
You said that it's important but it's such a small matter.
No matter who your father is, we are all children of the sea.
Ace will be our 2nd division commander!
You're a star, don't look dazed. Here!
Here!
Hey, the food's not leaving so don't rush.
And you're the star of this banquet so...
He falls asleep!
Whitebeard got a powerful newbie again.
I heard that he's insanely strong!
2nd division came to cover us!
Ace!
Thatch, you okay?
Yeah. Thank you!
Your bounty will rise again!
Maybe.
Ace, I found something interesting.
Oh, is it a devil fruit?
I don't know what fruit it is yet.
Come on, Ace, just calm down!
Pops said that this is an exception.
You don't have to go after Teach!
Let me go! I am his commander!
If I don't do anything about it,
Thatch's spirit can't rest!
Ace.
It's okay. This is an exception.
I have a bad feeling about this.
He killed his crewmate and ran away!
He had been beholden to you for decades
and then he threw dirt in your face!
And above all, he disgraced my father's name
and I can't allow that.
I'll take care of this!
Hey, wait! Come back, Ace!
Is it over?
What caused that quake?
Pops.
Everybody.
I ignored your advice and took off!
Why didn't you just give up on me?!
I'm the one who caused all of this!
No.
I'm the one who told you to go.
Son.
All of the cast has assembled.
Whitebeard's tremendous power
brings a huge tsunami
that threatens to swallow up
all the brave men of Marineford,
as well as the peace and justice there.
A battle crossing generations begins at last!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Force That Could Destroy the World! The Power of the Tremor-Tremor Fruit"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Force That Could Destroy the World!
The Power of the Tremor-Tremor Fruit