Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
The public execution of Ace is in 4 and a
half hours and Luffy has gotten to Level 1
and was about to get out of Impel Down
but Warden Magellan caught up with him,
so he has been held up!
What is going on here?!
There's no Navy ship at all!
Take a good look!
You can see shadows of
sails slightly in the fog!
There they are! Crowds of Navy ships!
I'm going to launch you
onto the deck! Hold tight!
Huh? W-What?! What did
you just say, fish face?!
Oh? That bastard's gone!
Ugh! What's going on here?!
Ocean Current...
...Shoulder Throw!
They're trying to hijack the
ship! Stop them at any cost!
We can just throw those Devil Fruit users off into the water!
The Escapee Team in Trouble
Forbidden Move: "Venom Demon"
Hey.
You're gonna throw who into the water?
You don't know your limits.
Don't be scared! Throw them overboard!
What the...
Jinbe!
Fishman Karate:
Spear Wave!
Hey, man...
Oops, I shouldn't have done that.
We were gonna use that boat!
Gum-Gum...
Hydra!
...Champion...
...Gatling!
How's that?!
Yes! Just one more push!
Take this, bastard!
It's no use stalling for time!
I've told all ships to
take off from Impel Down!
There are no ships left for you to steal!
The old Fishman and others went to get one!
I know that they will find a way!
You're talking about Jinbe?
Then
I should end this all the faster!
Gum-Gum...
No no! Run, Straw Hat!
...Champion...
...Stamp!
You pushed it too far! The
wax won't work anymore!
Wax-Wax...
...Release!
That was close!
Venom...
...Demon!
--We better run!
--Hurry up!
Hell's Judgement!
Damn!
Guys, help me! Let me go with you!
Hey!
Stupid! You can't touch me!
The poison's spreading!
It doesn't matter if it's wax or rock,
the poison is spreading like an infection!
Dammit! No wonder the
Wax-Wax Armor didn't work!
Main Entrance
First floor of Impel Down, above sea level
I wonder how Straw-chan and others are doing!
--What about the ships?!
--I can hear the sound of gunfire...
...but can't figure out
what's going on in the fog!
I know that they're capable of
stealing a ship for sure but...
But it's too far!
They have to steal it and bring
it all the way back here!
You mean they can't make
it here before Magellan?!
I know that Straw Hat Luffy is strong...
...but I don't think that he can stall
the unbeatable Magellan for that long!
Straw-chan!
Damn! Please hurry, Jinbe!
Throw them off! Don't
let them have this ship!
Damn you!
What's wrong with his body?!
The whole body's like a knife!
I ate the Dice-Dice Fruit.
I remember him! He's an
assassin from the West Blue...
...named Daz!
Sables!
It's only a matter of time
before they steal that ship!
It'll be a dishonor to the Navy!
--Sink it right away!
--Yes, sir!
Get ready to fire!
There's the column again!
--Dammit! The gunpowder got wet!
--That must be Jinbe!
Shoot him from the other batteries!
Hurry up! Hurry! He's right behind us!
--Jinbe!
--Crocodile!
Captain Buggy!
Hey! Is everybody there?!
I hear Straw-chan!
You gotta run!
They're being chased by something horrible!
It's Magellan! We have nowhere to go!
Did you get a ship?!
Straw-chan! I'm afraid that
we don't have a ship yet!
What?!
I've injected some hormones and
managed to walk a little bit...
But I have had it...
Hell Wink!
Iva-chan?!
You scared us!
I-It seems like I made it in time! Thud!
He passed out from hitting his head!
Iva-san! Inazuma! You both are alive!
--I'm so glad!
--Iva-sama!
Those two!
Straw Hat! It's from Jinbe!
The Baby Transponder Snail?!
Good job, you guys!
Why did you even come?
--Clank!
--Luffy-kun, you got out?!
Yeah, but he's still chasing us!
And we're running out of places to run!
Sorry! We got a ship but...
...it'll take some time to get there!
Don't stop! Just jump into the water!
Throw everyone off into the water as well!
What're you saying, Jinbe?!
This is the Calm Belt!
You can leave the rest up to me!
--Let's do as he says!
--What?!
Three, help me again!
Are you nuts?! If we dive into
the water, we're gonna die!
He's a minion of the Government
and we can't trust him! Damn Fishman!
He's a friend of Ace! I trust him!
Into the water?! Go ahead and dive if you want!
There are Sea King nests everywhere!
Be careful! You can't touch
even a drop of his poison!
--That's impossible!
--We're gonna die!
What should we do?!
Hell's Judgement!
Gear 3:
Here's an oversized treat! Candle Wall!
It's no use!
Straw Hat! Hurry up!
I can't hold it any longer!
Gum-Gum...
...Gigant Stamp!
Wow! He pushed it back!
The poison keeps spreading!
Should we dive into the water?!
Here it comes!
Iva-chan! Iva-chan, wake up!
We're in trouble! Iva-chan! Wake up!
Hey, you gotta wake up now!
--What do you want?
--We got to hurry!
--Who are you? Straw-boy's son?
--Can you do the wink?!
Okay!
No way! If you do that, we're gonna...
Here you go!
Wait a minute, Iva-sama!
That's unthinkable to me!
There's no way to survive by diving
into the water without a ship!
--Everybody, hold onto the face!
--The face?!
But I'm not gonna let you get away!
--Hurry up!
--Hold onto Iva-sama!
I won't allow anyone to
escape from Impel Down!
Hell...
...Wink!
I won't!
We're gonna fall!
Something's under the ship!
What are they?!
Fly, Ivankov!
It's impossible! He's losing consciousness!
What's this?!
We landed on something!
Hey, look!
What's this?!
You made it!
I'm sorry that I should ask you
to come to this dangerous area!
--It's a school of whale sharks!
--Jinbe must have called them!
Cool!
Luffy and the others have at last escaped Impel Down.
However, there isn't any time for celebration.
The Gate of Justice stand in their way,
and the Navy is hot on their tails.
Just when it seems like all hope is lost,
a friend makes the ultimate sacrifice!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Cause One Final Miracle
Break Through the Gate of Justice"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Cause One Final Miracle
Break Through the Gate of Justice