Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has landed on Marineford
to save his brother, Ace, from execution.
The battle heats up as the Navy tries to stop
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates
from advancing towards
the execution platform holding Ace.
Then suddenly, a group of Pacifistas,
the Navy's secret human weapons, reveal themselves.
Look at the bay head! There's something!
Wh-What are they?!
So that's the human weapon
of the Government that I heard of.
K-Kuma?
The Extermination Strategy in Action
The Power of the Pacifistas
The Warlord—Bartholomew Kuma!
How come there're so many Kumas?
What's going on here?
They're the ones who ran wild here on Sabaody a while ago!
There're a number of Bartholomew Kumas!
Now they've got way more of them!
Head Office! Head Office!
I have big news!
Hello? Hello?!
Is this the real one?
I've heard about it from time to time
that Dr. Vegapunk was trying to build a human weapon
and was repeatedly
sending prototypes to various places.
So they're the human weapon?
Why do they all look like Kuma?
Uncle! Didn't everything go as you guys planned?!
I heard that pirates were
going to be easily encircled
inside the bay when we came out!
But they're scattered all over!
The broad-axe guy is yelling something.
I see what the Navy is up to!
First, they leaked the information that they moved Ace's execution
to make us rush.
Then they slowly backed up
and lured all the pirates inside the bay, and...
...blocked the bay head
with the human weapons to close the trap.
Checkmate!
That's why Whitebeard said that
we should sink the Navy ships around us first.
He saw it coming.
We didn't get trapped, thanks to him.
Yeah.
Even though we couldn't trap them,
we can go at them from the front and the back!
Attack the allied pirates first as we planned.
Get rid of the ones
who wander off of the enclosure!
Did you hear that?
Uncle, is it okay if some Navy ships
get caught in the crossfire?
Keep it to a minimum.
Alright!
Let's begin!
I don't know what's going on but you can't beat us that easily!
Oh... Oh no!
Go, Pacifistas!
He blew them away!
They're even willing to sacrifice their own.
Don't be afraid, guys!
Let's charge the plaza without stopping!
Backing down is not even an option.
I'll get to Ace before they get me!
Everyone, get off of the ship!
Counter the human weapons!
Come on.
I'll fight you!
All units, get off of the ice right away!
Don't let the pirates reach the plaza!
Fall back!
Hurry up!
I didn't expect that I'd get to fight
the world's greatest swordsman in this war.
How lucky I am.
You're the number one swordsman
of the Whitebeards.
Let me see the Flower Sword's swordsmanship.
You can have a good look at it.
Rose Rondo!
What kind of flower should I make bloom next?
Drive them in, Pacifistas!
I won't let you! Take this!
I got you!
What are they made of?!
They're not human!
Are they unbreakable?!
The picture...
No matter how much you struggle,
we will keep the upper hand, Whitebeard!
When all videos have been cut, activate the barricades.
Thereupon, we will execute Ace and round up all our enemies.
Yes, sir!
Outta my way!
Ace's in danger! I gotta hurry!
Go back to the beginning!
Luffy-kun!
Jinbe!
The admiral has come out!
Damn!
It's tough but we need to hurry!
We came here knowing
that powerful enemies would stand in our way!
Die, Dragon's son!
Ace's brother, are you out of energy already?
The commanders are here!
What a tremendous help!
You can't get blocked by just one guy!
Come with us!
Okay! That bastard!
The Navy is backing down so now is our chance!
Let's break through at once!
That's kinda tough!
10th division commander—Curiel!
If you're gonna come for me,
I'll just knock you down!
You're dead if you stay inside the bay!
Ace will die and you guys
will be trapped and wiped out!
I couldn't care less about who's gonna win
but it'll nice to see Whitebeard to die!
I won't let Pops and Ace die!
Shall we put this match on hold, Vista?
Seems like it'd be good for both of us.
We're ordered to back down, Smoker-san!
We've got to go!
Yeah.
I know.
Straw Hat!
Luffy! Hurry up and save your brother!
Have you cut the videos yet?
No, give us another minute!
Hey, did you find it?!
N-No! We're still looking for it!
"PLEASE WAIT A MOMENT"
We're all set!
Gaffer, move aside.
They cut all videos except for one but...
Why do we have to wait?!
You're good to go on camera!
Okay, let's go on the air!
5 seconds to go!
4, 3, 2, 1, action!
The picture's back!
Er... Um...
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone.
Somebody's talking!
We're here at Marineford.
There're dead bodies of pirates and the Navy.
A commentary?
Hey! What's this?! What's going on?!
Hmmm?! The guy over there must be...!
Oh, he's...! Don't tell me that he's...!
He's been hiding his origin but...
...he was one of the legendary crew
of the Pirate King—Gold Roger!
Who's that?
The great pirate—Captain Buggy the Clown?!
Yes, that's who I am indeed!
It's top secret but I am...
...the legendary pirate.
H-Hey! Captain Buggy!
Your nose is bleeding!
Cut! Cut!
Wipe it up!
What the hell is this?!
I'm saying "cut the stupid video right away!"
We can't move on like this!
I-I'm afraid that...
...one of the Video Transponder Snails
has been stolen by the prisoners from Impel Down!
What did you just say?!
Make-up!
We're ready!
Alright, now it's take 2!
3, 2, 1 and...
Oh! That guy right there!
He was one of Roger's legendary crew and...
...the sworn brother of Red-Haired
one of the Four Emperors!
The great pirate—Captain Buggy the Clown?!
Yes, indeed!
Stop them right now!
Whoa! That was close!
They found us! Run!
You just got cut by the famous Hawk-Eye Mihawk
but you don't seem like you got hurt at all!
Talking about me?
Yes, I'm Buggy!
The legendary!
Blow all of them away!
Let us see the war!
What happened to other videos?!
Let us see Ace who was about to be executed!
Let us see the group of Bartholomew Kumas!
They keep driving us to the corner!
Don't give up!
We can't go down until we save Ace!
Let's go!
Pops.
Squard!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Yeah, barely.
I see. I was calling for you a while ago.
How is it at the bay head now?
Your allies were beaten badly.
I made it here because I found the way out luckily.
Sengoku has no mercy.
He's using all the forces he has in order to defeat us.
Pops, did you notice what the Navy was up to?
I've known Sengoku for a long time.
I see.
It's better for us if they're gonna attack us from the rear.
I'm gonna go forward, too! We gotta invade without stopping!
I agree.
Squard? Why is he up there?
There are 43 allied captains here
and we are all in your debt beyond words!
We risk our lives for the Whitebeard Pirates!
Thank you.
But we are...!
I know.
You are fighting to save a member of your family.
The pirate, Whitebeard, won't give up on his family.
Everybody followed you to this hell because you're that kind of person.
I wish that...
...we were also...
...members of your family.
No one expected Squard's betrayal.
As they see him approaching Whitebeard,
suspicion grows in the Navy men as well.
The strong bond shared among
the Whitebeard Pirates has been destroyed...
That is the scenario described by the Navy.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Red Hound's Plot!
Whitebeard Entrapped"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Red Hound's Plot!
Whitebeard Entrapped