Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece...
head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and on their way
to the next stage—the New World—
they reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
Go, Shark!
To the Sea Forest!
Ryugu Palace in Shock!
The Kidnapping of Shirahoshi
In the deep sea southeast of Fishman Island
Thank you for coming all the way to see me!
Well, Tom-san told me one of his family members
at home is also a shipwright, so...
But it must've been difficult to come to Fishman Island.
Difficult?
I was trained by Tom-san since I was a kid and I came here with a ship that I made.
Since you were my brother's pupil,
I bet it's quite a ship.
Yeah, it's called the Thousand Sunny
and it's my masterpiece!
I'd love to see it.
Well, after we entered Fishman Island,
it was taken away by the tide.
That's part of reason that I came to see you.
I was wondering if you could give me a clue
as to the Sunny's whereabouts.
You'll find it.
I hope so...
When a ship sinks in these parts, it usually gets carried by the tide
and ends up at a certain place.
I think the Sunny will be there too.
Don not worry about it!
Don, huh?
We'll get there soon.
The place known as the Sea Forest!
The Sea Forest?
Hey hey, Luffy-san!
Hey wait, Megalo!
Where are you going?!
Father-sama, Brother-sama,
everybody at the palace, please forgive me!
I am going out without permission!
I'll be home by dinner!
Let's go for a "walk"!
What is going on, Megalo?!
I can't believe he left the doors open!
What if something happens to...
Skeleton, hurry up!
See if the Princess is okay!
Hey! You're riding my bones too hard!
She's not here!
Princess Shirahoshi is not here!
What?! The Mermaid Princess is not here?!
This is bad! This is a matter
of great consequence to the kingdom!
When did this happen?! Who did this?!
She must have been kidnapped!
Kidnapped?!
Princess-sama!
Princess-sama...
She must've been kidnapped?
Hey, what are you doing?!
The gate that connects
Fishman Island and Ryugu Palace...
Where is the switch to open it?!
Huh? The switch?
Skeleton, hurry and go back to Neptune-sama!
We have to tell him what is going on here!
We have no choice but to do as we're told.
They told us the only way we'll live
is if we obey them.
Just tell us!
Who are "they"?
They're gonna kill us if you don't tell us!
Kill you?
Tell us!
I don't know what you're talking about!
A few hours earlier; Fishman District, Noah
What a pain in the ass!
Humans are such lowly creatures—
they can't even breathe in the water!
Listen, you pirates under the control of Hody Jones!
You should all be happy!
Because you can be part of this historic mission!
That's Vander Decken of the Flying Dutchman?!
The captain of that cursed ghost ship?!
Don't worry, I'm his descendant. I'm not a ghost.
Though I am cursed as well.
I can't swim even though I'm a Fishman.
I got this devil power
alongside the Mark-Mark curse.
Let me show it to you!
Alright, you human right there! Step forward.
Huh?
Hody!
Are you guys serious?
Don't be crazy!
It's Hachi-san!
Hatchan-san!
It's Hatchan-san!
Hachi-san...
The Energy Steroids will do nothing but ruin you!
What's the point of destroying this island?
Don't underestimate the Great Knight Neptune!
Hachi-san, give me a break.
I don't want to hear your voice anymore.
I can't believe you were an officer of the pirate group I admired.
You became a coward.
It's time for a generation change.
To teach the humans a lesson,
we need Fishman Island.
So Neptune is in our way!
You all taught us that we're the supreme race!
But Arlong-san lost!
Decken! Hyouzou!
Why are you doing this?!
You even refused Arlong-san's offer back then
so why are you helping these youths now?!
Helping? I'm just in this for the money.
Arlong was stingy so he couldn't pay me much.
I felt sorry for him that he could only take crappy swordsmen like you with him.
Hachi from the Arlong Pirates?
Oh, sweet memories!
Your captain even tried to make me
work under him back then.
That was ridiculous!
I won't work under anybody!
Hody understands that.
Arlong-san had a dream
and an ability to take action that I could respect.
But at the same time,
he was too rough and lacked cleverness.
When you guys were running wild on the sea, we were all too young to become pirates.
We all witnessed what they did so we plan things more carefully.
Because we've learned
from our predecessors' failure.
I will continue where Arlong left off.
As a member of the group I admired so much,
your opposition is so discouraging, Hachi-san!
Straw Hat Luffy who shattered Arlong's dream is here, by the way.
But you don't mind at all?
He called me his friend even though
I'm a former member of the Arlong Pirates.
All three of you are my friends now!
Plus, Straw Hat Luffy saved my life. I wish I could go see him now but...
I'm too ashamed to face him when somebody is trying to keep Arlong's dream alive!
How pathetic of you
to become friends with a human!
I'm disgusted by you!
I'm locked on to you, Hachi!
Forgot how pirates do things?
If there is something to say, you have to use violence!
I suspect!
Here!
Where is he throwing it?
When I touched you just now,
you became my mark.
No matter what I throw
or where I throw it, it's like a living bird,
it will strike you at full speed!
The knife he just threw somewhere else...
Flew at the octopus Fishman!
The Mark-Mark curse...
Of course, there are a number of ways
to defend yourself.
Give it a try.
No... You have so many arrows.
I knew about your power—I heard the rumors!
Hey, Hody, he's trying to kill me!
Stop Decken!
As he told you, Hachi-san.
Vander Decken is not working under me.
We are allies on equal footing.
And you're annoying me anyway!
Coward!
Damn!
Alright, get him!
That's it!
Run, run!
But they will chase you, chase you,
chase you and chase you to the end of the world!
If I can get out of here...
Yes, now I can get away!
In the water, the arrows will...
Damn! They aren't even slowing down!
Stop following me!
I can have two marks—one for each palm!
I haven't washed my right hand for ten years
ever since I touched Princess Shirahoshi and designated her as my mark!
Do you understand? It doesn't matter if it's love or a weapon that I throw,
they'll both follow until the furthest reaches of hell!
That is my power!
Awesome!
That's why he could continue stalking her insidiously...
without showing himself
or getting caught by Neptune's army!
That's right!
What a sinister guy!
Sinister! Sinister! Sinister!
Now you human pirates.
Now that you've seen Decken's power.
Here is the first stage of the mission.
They say the Ryugu Palace is impregnable, but...
someone has been able to pierce the defenses for ten years
and that's him—Vander Decken.
So for this mission, you'll be thrown by Decken
and fly to the Mermaid Princess in the palace.
What?!
Where you'll be landing
is the solid wall of the tower though.
Then, open the gate from inside the palace
and let us in—that is your duty.
No way! If we get thrown...
We could die from hitting the wall!
You're right!
That's why I want you humans to do it because your lives aren't that important!
You humans are less valuable than slaves here!
Those of you who survive
hitting the wall carry out your duty.
If you succeed, I'll set you free.
If you refuse to do it,
I'll kick you out of the bubble right now!
You lowly creatures!
N-No way...
If we leave the bubble, we'll drown for sure!
In that case, you have no choice
but wager on the possibility you'll survive, right?!
Go!
Today, a new history for the Fishmen will begin!
First, we conquer the Ryugu Kingdom!
Yeah!
I'm coming to you soon, Shirahoshi!
Ryugu Palace, Northwest Side
Passageway to the Hard Shell Tower
And now...
Wait!
No way!
Hurry up, Skeleton,
get to the King!
Wait... We have to open the gate or...
Hody will kill us!
Hey, I have a question for you guys. Um...
Sanji, you have to stay in bed!
I mean, at that place
called Ryugu Palace... Is she there?
You know, the Mermaid Princess!
S-She is there!
So what?!
Then I'll go.
Even if it kills me.
You're going?! You never learn! If she's beautiful, you'll die!
Of course she's beautiful, isn't she?!
I've never met her
but I heard she's very beautiful.
So she's beautiful,
just as I thought!
I'll go, I'll go, at any cost!
Now lead me to Ryugu Palace!
What's wrong with him?
I don't know but we have to take him.
You need to be handcuffed if you're going to the palace!
Do whatever you want
as long as I can see the Mermaid Princess!
Sanji!
No! Wake up!
Fools!
I can't cook for the Mermaid Princess
if you handcuff me!
That's the reason?!
I knew you were gonna resist!
Cart them off!
You bastards wanna ruin my chance to get close to the Mermaid Princess?!
Do you?! Do you?!
Hey, Sanji!
Oh no, you beat all the soldiers...
We didn't do anything wrong but now...
It's their fault—they tried to handcuff me.
They're part of the Straw Hats...
Such dangerous people...
Look, everybody's looking at us coldly like they're a bunch of deep-sea fish!
Stop complaining!
What's done is done!
Think before you act!
You beat the half of them with kung fu!
You were pretty strong...
Don't try to compliment me, you jerk!
It's the voice of a lady!
There is a man covered with blood at the shore!
You're the guy from the Fishman District!
What happened?
Call a doctor!
Huh? I am a doctor!
What? Hachi?
What happened to you?!
Hey, Hachi!
It's us!
Why are you hurt?!
What happened to you?!
Oh... It's you guys...
Good to see you...
Is Straw Hat with you?
He's not here! Wait for a moment!
I'll treat you in a sec!
Summon all your friends... Hurry...
You guys don't wanna get involved...
with this island!
Get off the island!
The New Fishman Pirates will come
and attack the island soon!
And the Ryugu Kingdom will... fall!
Neptune-sama!
There was a kidnapping! Somebody kidnapped the Princess!
And pirates are falling like rain
at the tower! In any event,
they're your enemies!
They're attacking!
Kidnapped?! Shirahoshi?! Who did it?!
An enemy attack, now?
What should we do?
Why now?!
We're occupying the palace ourselves!
Wh-What should we do?!
No, don't answer!
I'll cut them.
I said "Don't answer"!
In order for us to survive...
We have to open the gate at any cost!
Th-They're here!
Why don't you come out of Shark now?
N-No, I'd rather stay in here still...
How do you like it out here after ten years?
My heart is racing!
This is very bad...
How can it be bad?
You just got out of the tower.
You're weird!
This is...
what they call an adventure?!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
If your heart is racing,
that's an adventure!
Did you say "the Sea Forest"?
What is that?
Something fun?
It's a graveyard.
There is a grave
that I haven't been to since they built it.
That is the place I've wanted to go to the most
for the past ten years!
Sea Forest in the deep sea
It's been ten years already.
Since her assassination in broad daylight,
that threw Fishman Island into chaos.
How time flies.
The princes have grown into tough soldiers.
Princess Shirahoshi is still in the tower.
But nobody forgets your ideals.
Queen Otohime!
Hody's plans for revenge are underway!
The pirates he has sent
lay siege to Ryugu Palace,
and throw it into a state of panic.
The crew has been caught up in the attack,
and the once impregnable Ryugu Palace gate is breached.
The New Fishman Pirates have arrived—
intent on destroying the kingdom!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Hody's Onslaught
The Retaliatory Plan Set Into Motion"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Hody's Onslaught
The Retaliatory Plan Set Into Motion