Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue his brother, Ace, who will be executed!
Inside the bay, the Whitebeards are trying to get to the scaffold
but the Navy stands in their way.
And at the bay head, the Pacifistas began to attack
the allies of the Whitebeards to exterminate them!
Squard!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Yeah, barely.
I see. I was calling for you a while ago.
How is it at the bay head now?
Your allies were beaten badly.
I made it here because I found the way out luckily.
Sengoku has no mercy.
He's using all the forces he has in order to defeat us.
Pops, did you notice what the Navy was up to?
I've known Sengoku for a long time.
Squard? Why is he up there?
There are 43 allied captains here
and we are all in your debt beyond words!
We risk our lives for the Whitebeard Pirates!
Red Hound's Plot!
Whitebeard Entrapped
L-Look! Whitebeard has...
Whitebeard has...
Whitebeard has been stabbed!
Old man!
Wh-Who stabbed him?!
I think he is...!
Yes! But the man who did it
is a captain from among the allies...
...from the New World—Whirl Spider...
Squard!
Why did you do that?! Answer me, Squard!
S-Shut up! You guys made me do it!
What do you mean?!
Do you know what you've done...?
Pops! Don't push yourself! Your health is...
Old man!
Stop perpetrating this farce, Whitebeard!
I know about your deal with the Navy!
You have their assurance
that the Whitebeards and Ace will remain safe!
What is he talking about?
What's going on here?!
Everyone, listen very closely!
We've all been trapped!
You never told me...
...that Ace was a son of that hateful Gold Roger!
When you first found me, I was all alone...
Squard is out of control again!
He's dangerous! Stay away!
Again?! Please!
We can't do anything about it when it starts!
Isn't there any strong man?!
Hey! Bring it on!
Bring Gold Roger here!
What? Are you all scared?
What are you waiting for, guys?
You know why I was all alone.
Because Roger killed all my precious crew who had fought alongside me for so long.
I despise Roger and...
...you know it!!
Then you should have told me
that Ace was Roger's son
and you want to make him the next Pirate King!
Don't mind the Whitebeards!
Back down to the plaza immediately!
Old man wants Ace to be King?
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate I know.
I wanna help him become Pirate King...
You were already betraying me at that time!
But I didn't know. I even befriended Ace!
I must've looked so stupid!
And then, your dearest son Ace got caught!
With the Whitebeard Pirates all inside the bay
and we allied pirates on the outside.
You have sold out the 43 captains
of the allied pirates to the Navy...
...in exchange for Ace's life!
The allied pirates will be vanquished
and the Whitebeards and Ace will be safe.
That's your deal with Sengoku, isn't it?!
Ace is Roger's son?!
Yes and our superiors have an agreement over how they're gonna end this war.
That's a lie! I can't believe that crap!
Whether you like or not, there's only one truth
and you all will die in vain.
Silence! I won't fall for your line!
Can't you see it?
Soon you will know that I'm not lying.
Look closely and see the outcome for yourself!
Our converging attack will start soon
and only you—the allied pirates—will be attacked.
The Navy won't even touch the Whitebeard Pirates.
We didn't know anything about it
and we followed you here
sacrificing our lives to save Ace and help you
and this is what happens!
In fact, we're the ones
who have been attacked by the Navy!
Those monsters approach from the back and the ice is blocking us on both sides
and we have no way out now!
Old man, is he telling the truth?!
Say that he's lying, old man!
It's a miracle that I could stab you once.
I'm prepared for it! Kill me!
The wall of ice is blocking us! There's no place to go!
Is this it?!
When I come to think of it, they're attacking just us!
Run!
Old man, did you really trade us...
...For Ace's life?!
Please say something, old man!
Old man!
It can't be true!
Whitebeard wouldn't sell out to the Navy.
He sold out his allies?
No way, Whitebeard wouldn't do that!
Whitebeard and the Navy made a deal?
Then the pirates who trusted and followed Whitebeard...
...are betrayed and will be killed by the Navy?!
I didn't wanna believe it, I couldn't believe it!
I never thought you'd betray us, old man!
You fool!
You've been deceived, Squard! Why couldn't you trust Pops?!
Don't play innocent, Marco!
You're the 1st division commander,
I know that you knew
about Ace and the deal with the Navy!
It's true that Ace is Roger's son.
They used that to their advantage,
tricking the one man who would be most angered by that fact.
Their strategy was a notch above us.
I don't want any delay. Blue Pheasant!
He's coming towards us?!
This war was a setup?!
Everything up to now meant nothing?!
There'll be no win or lose?!
Turned off!
What's wrong?
Is it broken?
Activate the barricades!
That bastard!
How could he let his own allies stab him that easily?
Shame on you, Whitebeard!
I've no recollection
of being beaten by such a weakling!
Croco-boy...
Crocodile.
It's true,
he could've fended off that attack
if he was the same guy he used to be.
Even if it was a surprise attack
or the attacker was one of his fellows,
he could've avoid it!
That's the problem!
Are you telling me to draw their sympathy
by putting these on?
Pops!
He allows himself to get out of shape!
You know what you have done, right, Squard?
You thrust a sword into your father's body.
You're such a stupid son!
But I love you, son, even if you are a fool.
Cut the crap...
You sold our lives to...
Who pulled your upright
and loyal heart into the darkness?
Tell me.
He's an insurgent in the Navy.
I'm opposed to this plan.
People who don't know the truth
are calling him a legendary pirate and honoring him
but that's not true.
He's just a scumbag who offered a secret deal to the Navy
just to protect his own interests
and betrays and sells out his allies.
They made up all his legends.
The one that we have to kill in this war is Whitebeard!
It's absolutely unthinkable not to!
If you're gonna help me,
I'll save you all—the allied pirates.
Stab Whitebeard.
He said he would save us allied pirates if I slew you.
So that's what Red Hound told you.
I know how much you hate Roger...
...so much so that I can feel your pain.
But, Squard,
it's ridiculous to lay the blame
on a child for the sins of his father.
Did Ace do something to you?
You and Ace have weathered agony,
joy and pain together...
...so many times along with the others, isn't it right?
I don't give a damn who Ace's father is.
We all met each other on this wide sea by chance!
Not only the two of you
but all of you, I take as my sons!
So, Squard, treat him kindly.
I don't love him any more than any other.
You are all family to me!
Anyway...
...he has never...
...changed at all, Sengoku.
He shook us up very well.
How ridiculous to say that I sold out my sons!
He gave the pirates the way out.
I should never underestimate that guy.
The wall of ice has broken down.
This Navy ship is in good condition!
We can get away at any time!
If you are a pirate, you pick
what you want to believe on your own!
I knew that it was a lie! That was the Navy's plan!
Damn! They fooled us!
Old man would never betray us!
I'm sorry! I will never lose trust in you, old man!
Me too, old man! I'm so sorry!
I'll follow you to the end!
Old man!
Did you call me a weakling? Please, Croco brat.
I'm just a human with one heart.
People would call me a devil or a monster
but I can't continue to be the strongest forever.
If I can save this one young man's life,
I will earn my right to retire from the world.
Those of you who'll follow me,
lay down your life for it!
Be ready! He's gonna run wild!
He's the strongest man in the world!
Let's go!!
The world's strongest pirate, Whitebeard, has joined the battle himself.
Unleashing his
Tremor-Tremor fruit powers to the max,
he decimates the Navy's forces one after another.
In response, Sengoku finally enacts the greatest counterattack plan
in Navy history!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Engage the Barricades!
Certain Doom for the Whitebeard Pirates!!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Engage the Barricades!
Certain Doom for the Whitebeard Pirates!!