Wealth, fame, power...
And the man that had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger...
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
To this day, men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams...
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
ONE
PIECE
!
Compasses and stuff’ll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let’s take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn’t a legend if it’s been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We’re gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we’re looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins,
I ask:
You
wanna
be
my
Friend
?
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise
!
We Are!
You have as horrible a reputation as ever.
That's fine. I am a pirate!
But Arlong's a reasonable guy.
Just a little more until our agreement.
No matter what, I'm going
to earn 100 million berries
and buy this village!
Usopp Dead?!
When is Luffy Going
to Make Landfall?
Go! To Arlong Park!
Hang on, Nami!
Let go! Let go, I said!
Have they still not caught
that Long-nose yet?!
A mere, lowly human, defying our species!
We're returning to Arlong Park!
Damn! I can't lose 'em!
W-Where is he?
Who thinks Usopp-sama is too
important of a person to have die yet?!
Me!
Me! Me! Me! Me!
Fool! What are you thinking?!
Oh, you guys think so, too? I agree!
W-What?
Special Attack: Egg Star!
Rotten eggs!
I can't breathe!
Howdya like that?! I guess Fishmen
aren't all they're cracked up to be!
Looks like every one of 'em
let Captain Usopp escape!
Y-Yikes.
I somehow wound up at a shore!
– I heard his voice over here!
– Let's check it out!
No one here.
Was it just our imagination?
The guy's quick to run away, that's for sure!
Let's look somewhere else!
Whew...
I-I don't know!
It's not in your best interest to lie.
Oww...
Huh? What?
Thanks for your cheering!
As you can see, I'm perfectly okay!
Maybe a little too okay?
Yeah...
What's taking so long?!
When is Luffy gonna show up?!
Five more minutes and
I'm gonna die of boredom!
Ohh! Oh!
Oh! Incredible!
Not even Hatchan, major octopus
leader of the Arlong Pirates,
can pull you up!
You're a super-grade fish!
Dunno who you are, but you're
the gutsiest fish in the East Blue!
What the... Oh! It was me all along?
You're indeed the gutsiest
fish in the East Blue, me.
Wait, does that seem strange?
Sure does.
W-Who are you?!
Me? I'm Hatchan!
Call me Hachi!
You a Fishman, too?
Of course, of course!
I'm a fascinating octopus Fishman!
From the looks of it, you're a human?
Y-Yeah.
A marine? Or maybe a guest?
Guest?
I guess you could say I'm a guest.
Arlong-san's not here right now, is he?
Nope. Where'd he go?
Apparently, there's a long-nosed
outsider running all over the place.
He locked up his friend here
and went to Cocoyashi Village
to get this other guy.
Usopp, huh?
Guess I'll save him for now.
This Cocoyashi Village...
How do I get there?
Get in.
You're a guest.
I'll take you there, swordsman!
W-What the hell happened?!
What happened here...
...my brothers?!
Roronoa...
What? What are you trying to say?!
Roronoa Zoro...
What?!
The pirate hunter?!
Did he come to collect my head?!
N-No, he didn't come... Th-That guy...
He was Zoro!
What?!
That haramaki guy we caught was Roronoa...
I caught him, Arlong-san!
W-What in the world?!
Took you long enough, Choo.
D-Don't tell me Zoro-
Well, here we are!
Cocoyashi Village.
Arlong-san should be here.
Great. Thanks.
No problem! Bye, now!
Whoops! I just remembered,
I forgot to ask your name!
Huh? Me? What are you
asking my name again for?
It's Hatchan!
Come back again!
Strange guy.
Catching this scum isn't
enough to satisfy my hunger!
Y-Yeah, huh?! So you should let me go!
I was just saying hello earlier!
Th-That's how we do it in my village!
But you are one of Zoro's men.
Though, it's only natural for famous
bounty hunters to come after me.
Don't kill me!
I don't have anything to do with Zoro!
Enough of your poor lies.
You stood up to Arlong-san, too.
Doesn't look like you're going to live either way.
H-Hey! As a matter of fact,
Zoro and I are really close!
So just try and lay a finger on me!
Zoro won't stand by quietly!
Oh? Which means if I kill you,
Zoro will come back?
N-No, you're wrong!
Killing me'd be very bad!
If you keep me alive, Zoro'll show up!
But if you don't keep me alive,
Zoro won't come!
But how exactly did Zoro...
...escape from our prison?
What do you mean?
What I mean is, someone let him escape.
Arlong-san.
Does this sound plausible to you?
Perhaps Nami let Zoro infiltrate this place so he could take your head?
N-Now that you mention it,
Nami has been acting strange lately.
Yeah. She even helped Zoro
when he jumped into the water.
Don't tell me she was working
with Zoro from the very start...
...and tricked us all?!
Betrayal is her specialty.
That's enough of that!
Quit discussing stuff based
on a bunch of conjecture!
Nami...
Watch what you say!
Me, a traitor?
I swore I was a member of this group
eight years ago, with this tattoo!
Sorry, sorry.
Nami.
It's only natural for you to be upset.
But rest easy.
I don't suspect you one bit.
You and me've known each
other for eight years now!
We were just a little on edge is all.
Right, Nami?
The ones we do need to get rid of
are Roronoa Zoro and his group!
H-Hey, Nami! S-Say something!
Nami!
Zoro just had to go and do that...
What's wrong, Nami?
You seem a little pale.
But, as for Long-nose here...
...not even you can save him now.
Not after he's defied Arlong-san.
How long...
How long are you going to suspect me?!
You're too smart, you see.
I'll have the amount Arlong
and I agreed to soon!
Why would I betray you now?!
Agreed amount?!
I know.
You agreed eight years ago to buy
Cocoyashi Village from Arlong-san
for 100 million berries.
But I just can't make sense of it.
You betrayed the villagers and your parent,
and only trust money,
so why do you care so much
about Cocoyashi Village?
Why such a puny little village?
Actually, I found this...
in your room.
Th-That's my...
S-Say what?!
Usopp's been captured?!
Yeah! They took him to
Arlong Park a little while ago!
Brave as he was,
that youngster defied Arlong!
He's surely dead by now!
Damn.
Of all times to get caught, it had
to be after I killed some time there!
Usopp! Stay alive!
Is this a treasure map?
It seems to be pointing to Cocoyashi Village...
Treasure in Cocoyashi Village?!
Really?!
That's my own personal map!
It has nothing to do with you at all!
Oh! What's wrong?
You suddenly look so furious...
What is this?!
What in the world happened here?!
It's the work of Roronoa Zoro,
the pirate hunter!
But where were you, Hachi?!
This could've been prevented,
had you been here!
Of course it could've!
Had I only been here!
This is unforgivable!
Meaning you don't know
where Zoro disappeared to?
Well, all I saw was one
slightly suspicious swordsman
whom I'd never met before...
It was him?!
You did see him, you idiot!
So, where did Zoro go?!
He wanted to see Arlong-san,
so I just took him to Cocoyashi Village!
Meaning there's no reason to rush out in a hurry.
He's looking for me, too.
He said he was a guest of yours, you see.
And I didn't think you'd be
back so soon, Arlong-san...
Zoro, huh?!
Which means, if I can just
buy me a little more time...
Why are you getting in the way?!
Everything's so close to working out!
So close!
D-Damn you! You picking a fight?!
You're getting in the way!
You're the one to blame!
This is what you get for messing with Arlong!
Nami! You really disappoint me!
Even after you stole our ship and ran off,
Luffy didn't suspect you one bit!
Even now, he completely trusts you!
How can you trick someone like
that with such an uncaring look?!
The only thing I trust is money.
Those who get fooled are the fools!
Say what?!
Everything was supposed to go smoothly.
You guys are going to make my
eight years of business meaningless.
So the least I can do is
get rid of you by my own hand!
Seems you've become a lot more
pirate-like since you were last here!
Get rid of?
You, get rid of me?!
Don't make me laugh!
I wouldn't underestimate me if I were you.
Dammit...
If I stay here, I'm dead for sure!
Special Attack!
Smoke Star!
Bastard used a smoke bomb!
Surround him! Don't let him escape!
Now's my chance!
This is just like something you'd think up.
Nami!
D-Don't...
It's for my business!
This was my only choice!
N-Nami... How could you...
Die like a good little boy.
– Way to go, Nami!
– Way to get revenge!
Now that's why you're a
leader of the Arlong Pirates!
B-Big Sis Nami k-killed Big Bro Usopp!
That's what you wanted, right?
To die at sea...
Nami. I'm sorry for doubting you.
You're our friend.
Friend?
I have no friends!
There's only one reason why I joined this group!
To buy Cocoyashi Village!
Keep your part of the bargain!
I'll have the 100 million berries soon!
But of course.
I'd rather cut my belly open and die
than break a promise concerning money.
That's the kind of man I am.
Glad to hear it, Arlong.
You know the score.
She's one creepy girl.
What a truly great woman she's become!
A witch! She's really a witch!
There it is! Arlong Park!
Hey! Don't get tired, cow!
Yeah, Big Bro Sanji's kicks
must've really taken their toll!
Hey! Not that way!
To the left! That building!
After I've come so far...
I've endured eight whole years since that day...
Alright! As of today, this is your room!
Your desk, your pens...
Everything you'll need is here!
I endured it all this time...
so I had no other choice than to do that!
It's almost like we're flying!
Not "like"!
We are flying, dumbass!
W-We're falling!
Landing successful!
Yo! Zoro!
We made it! We made it!
W-What the hell...
are you guys doing?!
What do you mean?
We're here to get Nami.
Have you still not found her?
Oh, yeah!
And what about Usopp and Johnny?
Usopp!
Th-That's right!
There's no time to be loafing around here!
What's wrong?!
That bastard's been caught by Arlong!
We gotta hurry before he's killed!
He was killed!
What?!
We're too late...
Big Bro Usopp is dead!
He was killed!
By Big Sis Nami!
Am I...
a ghost?
Nami would never kill Usopp!
We're friends!
Who're friends?
N-Nami-san! It's me!
Do you remember?!
– Why are you here?!
– To get you!
– Hey! Where's Usopp?!
– Bottom of the ocean.
Damn it! Cut the crap!
Shut up! Get the hell out, outsiders!
You're an eyesore!
Next time, on One Piece:
Everyone's Gathered!
Usopp Speaks the Truth About Nami
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Everyone's Gathered!
Usopp Speaks the
Truth About Nami