Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace, who was to be executed!
Blackbeard who stole
Whitebeard's power is now in a standoff
with the Navy at the plaza!
Meanwhile, Jinbe rushed to the bay head
carrying the unconscious Luffy
but they got attacked by Admiral Red Hound!
Good job, young Navy soldier.
That moment of courage,
you risked your life for,
will have a massive impact...
on the destiny of the world,
be that for better or worse.
I'm here to...
...end this war!
Here Comes Shanks!
The Paramount War is Finally Over
Red-Haired! He's the one
who motivated Luffy to become a pirate!
There he is!
It's the Red-Haired Pirates!
Prepare for surgery!
Both of them have lost far too much blood!
Hook them up for blood transfusions!
Captain, it's dangerous!
Sure, you can't often see one of
the Four Emperors but close the door already!
No way!
Red-Haired had a run-in with Kaido, another one of the Four Emperors,
just yesterday in the New World!
And he made it here already?!
Sh... Shanks?!
Why the hell are you here?!
Buggy!
The straw hat?!
Give it back to Luffy!
Why should I?!
I refuse! I was in the middle of my magnificent disappearing act!
I don't wanna draw their attention anymore!
Oh no! That's too bad!
There's a treasure map I wanted to give you!
Really?!
Yeah and it's a great one!
Yeah, right! Don't think I'm gonna fall for a deal
that sounds too good to be true!
Alright, guess I gotta ask somebody else then...
W-Wait, hang on! I'll give it to him!
Boss!
You haven't seen Luffy in 10 years.
Don't you wanna see him?
Yeah...
He got you good, boss!
Why are you laughing?!
That was so uncool!
Why didn't you fight them?!
No matter how many there are
or how strong they seem,
you're not men—or pirates—
if you laugh after something like that!
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
But... Shanks...!
Your arm!
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
I'm just glad you're alright...
I wanna see him.
Captain! Captain!
They're gonna attack us if we don't submerge soon!
Please close the door!
Okay.
Wait a minute!
We can't wait anymore!
Oh no!
You forgot this! Here, catch!
He threw something.
This is...
Captain, hurry up, hurry up!
Okay.
I wanna see him but...
I'll leave this hat with you.
Come bring it back to me someday!
Once you've become a great pirate!
That's our promise, Luffy!
To see him now
would violate our agreement, wouldn't it...
...Luffy?
Alright, let's do this.
This one's chest's been pierced, he's on the verge of death.
Straw Hatter is severely injured too,
but I think his worst problems are internal.
Do they need anesthesia?
No, they don't.
They're both so seriously hurt that they can't feel any pain.
They won't have the energy to complain
no matter how drastic the treatment gets.
This should be a fun operation!
Red-Haired, you bastard!
You let Dragon's son get away!
Ice Age!
He's after the submarine! The sea is freezing over!
His pulse is steadying.
What's that?
It's an emergency!
The water is starting to turn into ice!
Oh no! Oh no!
If nothing's done, we're gonna get caught, Captain!
Do something!
We'll submerge rapidly!
Did I lose him?
W-We made it!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
What is it this time?!
Let's go deeper—to the bottom of the sea!
It's gonna hit us! I'm sure that it's gonna hit us!
Hurry up! At full speed!
Luffy!
Damn! They're so persistent!
It didn't hit them, did it?!
Ace's brother! Jinbe!
Luffy...
If they're still alive after this,
they sure are lucky!
We have no choice but to give up on them for now.
Why is that Navy ship taking off on its own?
Hurry up! Go after the submarine!
But they went underwater
and I doubt they could've escaped
the attacks from the admirals!
No, I'm sure that they're alive!
Listen to me!
Tell the Navy that, being a Warlord,
I will catch and kill Straw Hat Luffy at any cost!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
But I don't know where to go...
Shut up and advance!
She's so reckless yet beautiful!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh...
What did you just say?!
You lied about the treasure map?!
Y-You bastard!
I just said that in the spur of the moment, Buggy!
It's been awhile, huh?
Cut the "It's been awhile, huh?" crap!
Don't forget that I have a reason to be mad at you, Shanks!
What's that?
Don't tell me you forgot?!
If you didn't surprise me at that time,
I wouldn't have lost the treasure map
and become a Devil Fruit user!
Is that what happened?
Thank you for that great reaction.
I always hated that about you!
How could you make me work for free
the moment we meet again!
You said you were here
to stop the war or something
but I can start a war with you right now if you want!
Did you see that?
Yes, I did.
He has such sass, even against
Red-Haired—one of the Four Emperors...
Captain Buggy!
We will follow you for the rest of our lives!
I understand so just relax.
Say what?!
But, wait a minute!
If I stay with them, I can get off this island safely!
Red-Haired...
Marco.
Stop fighting. Just back out nice and easy.
Hawk-Eye, where are you going?
I agreed to fight Whitebeard
but fighting Red-Haired was not in the agreement.
It's time to quit.
To go on fighting...
will only lead to more loss of life on both sides!
But if any of you still want to fight...
Bring it on!
We'll happily take you on!
What do you think, Teach?
No, Blackbeard!
You're more handsome than ever, Red-Haired.
Those scars look good on you.
Let's stop this, then!
I already got what I wanted.
And we're not ready to fight you guys just yet.
Let's go, guys!
Everybody.
For now,
you need to do as I say!
Looks like our coverage
of the war will soon be over!
Whitebeard, Ace...
We'll see to the burial of those two.
You've already broadcast
the battle throughout the world.
I won't allow you to go on
making a spectacle of their deaths.
That's ridiculous!
We need to show off their heads
to celebrate our victory!
The Vice Admiral is right!
Are you trying to disgrace our victory?!
We're not gonna listen to a pirate!
I agree!
Fleet Admiral-dono!
Only because it's you, I allow it, Red-Haired!
But...!
I will take the blame myself!
Thanks.
Treat the injured now!
This war is...
...over!
Those of you who are able, help the medics!
Care for the seriously injured first!
Don't let anyone else die here!
Thus the greatest battle of the Great Pirate Era—
the "Paramount War" at Marineford—came to an end.
Carving its place into the tablets of history.
The Paramount War
has shattered the balance of the world.
The end of the war becomes the sign
for the pirates to set out upon the wave of a new era.
With the menace that was Whitebeard gone,
the seas are growing rough again.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Mighty Leaders Face Each Other Down!
Heralding the 'New Era'!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Mighty Leaders Face Each Other Down!
Heralding the "New Era"!