A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
Gum-Gum...
...Fireworks!!
They defeated...
...the White Berets!
You fools!
You should've just behaved
and done what I told you to.
We, the White Berets, are the gentlest
upholders of the law in God's Land.
However, they are not as nice as we are!
You are now 2nd degree criminals!
No matter if you cry or scream...
...you'll be judged...
...by the priests of Upper Yard!!
Heso!!
Is Escape Possible?!
God's Challenge
is Set in Motion!
What's their problem?
More importantly, we were tricked!
That old lady said it was okay to pass through.
And when we do, they say we entered illegally?!
That's fraud! I'll sue for this!
Exactly...
Of course, even if we were told,
"Don't pass through,"
we would've entered by force anyway.
Shut up!
In any case, you are in big trouble.
Since you've become 2nd
degree criminals, we can't...
...help you.
Why are you talking to us from way over there?!
Well, what's the fuss?
We're used to being pursued.
More importantly, why did you come back?
Huh?!
We were finally about to go to that place
that we're never to enter for a big adventu—
err... no, to look for you!
You're really easy to figure out.
What big adventure?!
I told you, didn't I?!
You can say that because you haven't seen
how scary those people on that island are!
It's true that we don't know
if this guy is God or what,
but his supernatural powers are the real thing!
I will never go back to...
...that island!!
Then, you can just wait here while we go.
No way, they're gonna come after me!
We have to leave this place!
Leave here?! Are you nuts?!
Which is more important to you,
adventure or life?!
Life! Then money!
Oh! Then, next would be me?!
Shut it!
But it's true.
Come to think of it, we were desperately
trying to reach this sky island,
so we weren't thinking at all about how to go back.
Say, is there a way for us to go back safely?
Can we go back to the Blue Sea?
There is a way,
though at this point,
I can no longer say it's safe...
...if you go to Cloud End,
the farthest edge of the clouds.
Cloud End? How do we get there?
Cloud End is in the far east.
To get there, you need to go
down to the White Sea first.
Good!
Then, we can go back down
to our sea from there, right?
No! I'm not going back!
Hey, do you wanna stay here
and get sentenced to death?
In any case, if we stay here,
it'll cause trouble for Conis and her dad.
Oh, it's no trouble...
Well, even if we run away, we may
not be able to get away from them.
If that's the case, no matter where
we are in Skypiea, it'll be the same.
Since they know our whereabouts,
we'd better leave here right away!
Now, everyone! Let's set sail!
Conis! Mister! Thanks for everything!
Oh, yeah!
Hey, Luffy!
Hey, old guy!
What is it?
Can I take all the leftover
food from earlier with me?
Yes, of course.
Alright! Sanji, prepare some lunch boxes!
He's on the ball.
In that case, can I ask you a favor as well?
You're an engineer, right, old guy?
Would you give me some
fixtures for the ship repair?
Sure, no problem.
Then, let's go to our house again.
Hey! Where're you guys going?!
I'm gonna go get some food from them!
You guys go on ahead and prepare
the ship for our adventure!
He's definitely planning to go there.
Those guys're really scary!
Who cares? I don't care either way.
Don't take it out on me.
Chopper, you're on my side... aren't you?!
– What?!
– Don't threaten him!
Heavy Point!
I was about to drop a rope ladder.
Oops.
You realize that there's no
persuading Luffy, don't you?
Even if we all get together
and protest, he won't listen.
Fine! Then, I'll stay here.
Hm? Go right ahead.
Go right ahead?!
Hey, I'll be killed by those creeps!
Ah? Then so be it.
How dare you...?!
Robin,
why don't you and I beat Luffy together?
That's impossible.
I guess we've got a better chance
taking on those creeps, huh?
Those White Berets must be
gathering other members by now.
Come after you? How foolish!
God and his priests are as
immovable as a mountain.
They simply wait on the sacred ground
for those to be judged to come.
When you weigh anchor, your ordeal starts.
You'll be led...
...to the forbidden sacred ground...
Upper Yard!
Excuse me, I'd like to discuss
something with you all.
Hmm?
So there's a special cloud current that
can take us down to the White Sea?
Yes. By getting on the cloud,
you can cross the vast ocean
and go to the White Sea.
And you can also get to
Cloud End without getting lost.
Really?!
As long as you get on the current,
no one can chase after you.
If we don't tell Luffy and get
the Going Merry on that current...
By the time he notices, it'll be too late, huh?
But that doesn't mean he'll give up on it.
I can guide you to the entrance
of that current riding a waver.
Now all we need to do is
keep that fool from noticing.
We'll take care of that part.
Then please weigh anchor and wait for me.
Okay.
I really appreciate it, Conis.
No problem.
This is good!
Hey, don't eat our lunch!
There's a lot, so don't hold back.
You're the one who should hold back.
Conis, give me some tea!
Do it yourself!
Oh? Conis-chan's not here.
Looks like she went to bid a
fond farewell to the others.
I brought some tea, if you'd like some.
So, you're the shipwright for that ship?
Hmm? No, I'm not. I'm a sniper.
Oh, that's wonderful!
Right?
Our ship still doesn't have a shipwright.
Well, how should I put it?
Since I'm almighty and skillful in everything,
everyone depends on me!
It's a lot of work.
That ship just wouldn't function without me.
Although I'm a sniper, it's like I'm also co-captain.
And, everyone calls me, "Captain Usopp"!
Oh, dear! This color arrangement
is clearly done by a professional!
Oh, yeah! Arranging food is art.
See you later, Conis!
Heso!
I can finally see rays of hope.
For a while there, I was worried.
But I wonder if there really is such a current...
What?
If such a convenient current existed,
you'd expect to see more survivors
from the sky island in the Blue Sea.
Don't be silly.
Since it's difficult for people to come up here in the first place,
it's just natural that not many
people escape here safely as well.
It's possible that quite a lot of the
people who tried couldn't escape
because they were too slow.
That's right.
Not knowing when to back off
can cost you your life.
Hurry up and get ready to set sail.
Weigh anchor quickly.
Chopper, use your Heavy Bonus
now and start on the heavy lifting.
Err... I told you, it's Heavy Point.
What?!
N-Nothing.
Now, wake up Zoro.
That's impossible.
Don't worry. I can do it alone!
We'd better hurry up,
or Conis' kindness will be wasted.
Heavy Point!
I put this one here...
Hm? No, this is in the wrong place.
I put the red one there,
and put the emerald green broad beans here.
Now, they look more delicious than before.
This one is for Nami-san and Robin-chan.
Wow, they don't look like food!
No, thank you. I'm sorry.
I've never seen such a pretty lunch before.
Really?
This is for you, Conis-chan.
Oh?! You made one for me, too?!
Of course! The title of this lunch is...
"Love is a dilemma. Lunch for the falling angel."
Oh...
Well, once they're in your stomach,
they're all the same.
Don't say stuff that tears down my hard work!
Listen up. With food, presentation comes first!
Really?
See? Now they're the same.
You're just chowing down
without looking at them!
Really?
Umph!
They're the same after all.
They taste the same.
Like I said, enjoy them with your eyes first!
Don't be rude! Not even I can eat with my eyes!
Hmm?
That's not what I mean!
But I've eaten with my nose before...
Don't do that!
...though I didn't mean to.
Now we'll just wait until Luffy
and the others come back.
Okay!
Chopper!
What just happened?!
What's going on?!
I wonder if we're already on that current.
Hey!
Something's wrong with the ship!
What?!
What's going on, Usopp?!
Look at that! The ship's rocking!
A party?
No fair, having a party without us!
Ah! Nami-san!
Why...
Why is she wearing a t-shirt?
Just where the heck is your mind at?!
Ahh! The ship started moving!
What?! Why?!
What're they doing? Where're they going?
Whoa!
It's moving backwards! That's incredible!
That's not it! They didn't set sail!
Huh?
Look underneath the ship!
Hold on! What is this? What's going on?!
Did we get on that current
thing earlier than we expected?
No, it doesn't look that way.
Wh-What the...?!
Ahh...!
That's...
...the famous White-White Sea
Super-Express Lobster!
What?!
It's trying to take us somewhere!
Hey! Everyone off the ship! There's still time!
What about the ship?! If our ship is taken...
Don't worry. I'll stay.
C'mon! What can you do by yourself?!
I'll pull it off somehow!
So, it doesn't work...?
There we go.
Alright, this'll work!
Unfortunately, it seems that won't work.
Come on board!
What'd you say?!
Even if that works,
it looks like they'll just move
right on to their next move. Look.
What?!
Large skyfish are following us
with their mouths open.
We can't jump off the ship and escape now.
Even if we could defeat them,
another batch will probably arrive soon.
There's nothing we can do.
It's probably already started.
Heaven's Judgment, huh?
So, instead of sending people
after us, they're bringing us in.
What an impudent guy...
Then... I'm going back to that island?
Luffy!! Usopp!! Sanji-kun!!
Why...? Why a t-shirt...?
You're still talking about that?!
Hey, Luffy! This is terrible!
What will we do?! What will we do?!
Where'd they go?
Where?! Of course...! Err...
So where?
Where...
...did they...
...go?
The Super-Express Lobster
is a messenger for God.
What it transports is always an offering to God.
So, it's headed to northeast Upper Yard...
...to the sacrificial altar.
Sacrifice?!
Nami-san, Robin-chan, and the rest...
The rest?!
...will be sacrificed?!
For that darn God?!
That son of a bitch!
Don't mess with us!! You bastard!!
Hold on a second, please! But, I'm sorry.
That's not the case!
What?!
I've heard that although it's called sacrifice,
in Heaven's Judgment,
there're two kinds of punishment that criminals receive.
Sacrifice and an ordeal.
They're currently hostages,
so to speak, in God's hands.
Hostages?!
So, the ones who are actually being judged are...
...the three of you.
Huh? What do you mean?
If we had some sort of map...
Oh... I have a map of Skypiea with me.
This one is very old, too.
But the shape of the island seems correct.
Are you all right, Conis-chan?
Yes.
But...
Don't worry.
It's them we're talking about. They're fine.
How can you be so sure?
This is where you are right now.
The sacrificial altar is in the
left upper direction, northeast.
There's only one way to get there.
You take the Milky Road that leaves this island
by using a dial boat,
and go across to the forest
where the priests await you.
Well, old guy, instead of taking the trouble
of going through the middle of the island,
all we have to do is go around
the island by boat, right?
That lobster went to Upper Yard that way, too, right?
Well... even if you can go ashore nearby,
you can't get to the altar on foot.
The big difference between this
map and the current Upper Yard
is the Milky Roads that are
stretched all around the island.
The cloud canals that you mentioned, huh?
Yes.
I hear that there're several hundred Milky Roads,
large and small in size, over there.
Hmm... I see...
That's why entering the island by boat
and taking the Milky Roads
within the island is the only way.
I see...
So no matter where we go ashore,
the canals will block our way.
That's right.
By the way, there're man-eating fish in the canals.
Man-eating fish?!
They've really covered all their bases.
So, they're saying that if we
want our friends and ship back,
we just have to come in from the front.
So that's our ordeal and...
Heaven's Judgment?!
Yes.
In Upper Yard, four priests who are
strong beyond imagination await you.
Oh, then it's easy.
To put it simply, all we have to do
is beat up those priests, right?
You're so simpleminded.
This is becoming fun!
Tooku hanarete shimattemo
Even if we're far apart
wasure naide ite hoshii yo
I don't want you to forget
Namida no hi ni wa itami o wakachiaeru hito ga
That on those days when you're brought to tears
koko ni iru koto
You have a friend here to share the pain
Yuzurenai bokura no haruka na omoi
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
yume de owarase wa shinai
I won't let it just be a dream
Daremo ga sagashiteru towa no kagayaki
The eternal brilliance that everyone is searching for
kitto sono te ni idaite
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
Conis, why are you shaking like that?
Oh? You think so?
Now that I look closer, you look pale, too.
I...
You look like you're afraid of something.
Would you please run?
What?
Once we know someone's a criminal,
if we don't lead them to the place of judgment,
we'll be killed, so...
Next time, on One Piece:
A Trap On Lovely Street!
The Almighty Eneru
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
A Trap On Lovely Street!
The Almighty Eneru