We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for... ONE PIECE
Compasses and stuff'll only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust
isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
If a storm brews within, all you have to do
is hold fast to the biorhythm of another
and let the feeling pass you by!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Blast through the stingy night!
We've no interest in treasure chests
Pockets bulging with dreams, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
We're gonna pool all our dreams together,
and go find what we're looking for...
Pockets bulging with coins, I ask:
You wanna be my Friend?
We are,We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
Isn't it a quiet night?
I'm on watch, but it's
been calm all night long.
There is no need to man the helm.
I'm working myself to the bone for nothing.
Never mind that I'm all bones!
I'm so bored.
Laboon...
You know Luffy-san and his buddies?
I've joined their crew.
They are great people.
But they are more than just that.
I found something incredible
earlier this afternoon!
It told of Luffy-san and his crew's fearsome
adventures and their battle-filled days.
Now that I have joined them,
I must prove that I am worthy
to call myself a crewmate!
Wouldn't you agree, Laboon?
Good morning, everyone!
I'll wake you up with a song.
White handkerchief,
Shut up!
don't let him find you
The sun hasn't risen yet!
Run for it
Let me catch some more Z's!
White handkerchief...
Forget Brook. Someone make Luffy stop snoring!
Brook's Great Struggle
A Bumpy Road to True Companionship?
What's the plan, Navigator?
If we use the paddle, we could keep
moving through these calm waters.
Based on the weather,
this lull should only last today.
Then we don't need to use our precious cola.
This is good!
Sanji, your cooking really is the best!
Robin-chan, have a second
helping of the seafood salad.
Thank you.
What's gotten into you, Brook?
Why have you been so hyper all morning?
Did something exciting happen, Brook?
He said that he saw our ship's log
while he was on watch yesterday.
Right! I just so happened
to read a small portion of it.
To be honest, it left me astonished!
I haven't been able to
settle down ever since.
The incident at Thriller Bark was
only the tip of the iceberg for you!
You stopped a civil war in
the desert kingdom, Alabasta.
You had a grand adventure
on the legendary sky island!
Furthermore, you took on
the World Government in a
massive fight at Water Seven!
I was so surprised, I
nearly had a heart attack!
Oh, but I don't have a heart.
Yeah. I wonder what sort of stories
will get added to the log.
Brook, your name is going to
start appearing in it now, too.
About that! Now that I am your crewmate,
it is imperative that I make myself useful!
I get why you're eager to work hard,
but first let me give you a word of advice.
I'd love to hear it, Nami-san!
With this crew, never let your
guard down during a meal.
Got it! I, Quick Draw Brook, shall be
ready for the enemy to strike at any time!
Apparently we didn't warn you soon enough.
I claim those noodles!
P-Please wait a second! Luffy-san!
They're good!
I should not have let my guard down,
even for a moment.
Very well! I shall work
myself to the bone to become
a true pal as soon as possible!
But I'm already nothing but bones...
Sanji-san!
I appreciate it. Since
you're washing the dishes,
I can take my time with Nami-san's tea.
As your pal, I am dying to help
everyone in extravagant ways,
but I'll do anything to make
myself useful for the time being.
That's a great attitude.
Since I'm a skeleton, I should work
till I'm bone tired on the small stuff.
Well, I'm going to give Nami-san her tea.
Ah! Sanji-san, where do these go?
Oh, over in the...
Don't drop them, even if it kills you!
But I'm already dead!
--And "kaboom!"
--Don't say that!
Hold this!
Splendid!
Don't give me that!
I can't trust you to do the dishes!
Oh, then I'll take this
tea to Nami-san instead.
Wait! Wait! I was gonna take it to her!
Nami-san, I've brought you some tea.
Come in!
May I see your panties?
--Bam!
--That came out of nowhere!
Is that a nautical chart?
We've been pretty busy lately.
This is a great chance to work on it,
since the ship isn't going anywhere.
Isn't it your dream to
draw a map of the world?
Right. I want to navigate
across the oceans of the world
and make a world map based on what I've seen.
That's wonderful!
If there is anything
I could do to help, please let me know.
Oh, would you like another cup?
Thank you.
That sentiment is enough for now.
You are both beautiful and humble!
Nami-san, you truly are wonderful!
Really! I'm not that great.
No, you truly are--ouch! Hot! Hot!
Whoa, are you okay?
My, I nearly burned my fingers.
Not that I have any skin to burn!
My map!
What have I done?!
That was horribly careless of me.
Don't you worry!
Look! I wiped it clean.
Yeah, you wiped it clean of everything...
That's not what I wanted!
I'll be taking my leave!
I get the feeling that I won't be
the least bit useful if this keeps up...
Hey, Brook!
Luffy-san?
These two are about to do something neat.
You should watch.
Uh, okay...
Chopper-san, what are you doing up here?
I'm drying these herbs in the sun,
since the weather is so nice.
You see, Franky is gonna test his new weapon.
All right! This is the long-distance
"Super Franky Cannon."
It runs on cola energy.
Its range is several times
that of a conventional cannon.
Plus it's super accurate!
Combined with my sniper skills,
we'll be totally unstoppable!
This is exciting!
I have butterflies in my stomach!
I know, right?
Excuse me! Let me know if there
is anything I could do to help.
All right. In that case, please get
another barrel of cola to play it safe.
Not a problem. It would be my pleasure!
This must be it.
Here's the barrel of cola!
Great! Now if you could pour it in.
Certainly!
Target: That rock.
Got it! Locking on to the rock at 2 o'clock.
--Fire!
--Firing!
--Huh?
--That's strange.
Usopp, increase the pressure.
Okay, you've got it.
Man, this doesn't look good.
Crap!
This was a huge flop!
It should have worked.
This is kinda salty.
Something is mixed with the cola.
This is soy sauce.
What's the matter, everyone?
Show a little remorse!
You mistook a soy sauce barrel
for a cola barrel, didn't you?!
Oh, you're right! This
was a soy sauce barrel.
I cannon believe I made that mistake!
Shut up, you jerk!
--I'm terribly sorry!
--Why did you grab a soy sauce barrel?!
--I'm sorry!
--This is no time for puns!
Brook, you're hilarious!
--Don't give me any "I'm only bones" crap!
--Now I'm all sticky!
Aw, I have to wash all of
the herbs I had set out to dry.
This meat tastes great
with the soy sauce and cola!
Can you find a bright side to anything?
Everything I try ends up going horribly awry.
Excuse me, Zoro-san...
This is no time to watch in admiration!
I'm a fellow swordsman.
Isn't this meditation?
You enter a state of nothingness
while making your mind and body one.
I shall join you.
Excuse me, Zoro-san...
I am fully aware that it is improper to
talk during meditation sessions, but...
I don't mind.
--Well, you see...
--What is it?!
I need to use the restroom.
I didn't need to know that! Head on over--
--The thing is...
--What?
...my legs went numb, so I can't stand!
Do you have any muscles to go numb?!
Zoro-san, I'm on the verge
of having an accident.
For real? W-Wait, hold it!
--I'm gonna leak! It's coming!
--I'll take you! W-Wait! Hey, hold it in!
Despite what I want, I've
been nothing but a nuisance.
This is awful!
Robin-san!
Excuse me...
Is there anything I could
do to be of assistance?
Not in particular.
Is that right?
Brook, why are you so anxious?
Anxious?
I get the feeling you're afraid
of something.
Am I mistaken?
You are absolutely right, Robin-san.
That's right. I am terribly
anxious and scared.
When Luffy-san first asked me
to join his crew, I was thrilled!
Those simple words filled me with joy.
And then my heart danced
with excitement when I defeated
Oars alongside everyone.
May I join your crew?
Yeah, sure.
What?!
But does he truly want me in his crew?
If we continue to head toward the New World,
I have no doubt that powerful foes and
trials beyond our imagination await us.
I'm afraid that I will be
both useless and a hindrance.
And if that proves true, I
might get kicked off the ship!
That's right... I'm afraid
of losing my friends again
and returning to that
painfully long life of solitude.
I was...
...also anxious for the longest of times.
I was constantly afraid that I
was unworthy to be their friend.
That is why I believed I could
become worthy of them
by throwing away my life for their sake.
Robin-san...
No matter how far I go on the sea,
I have a huge enemy that I can't shake off...
...because the world and
its darkness are my enemy!
That's why I didn't want
you to come to rescue me!
If I'm going to die someday anyway,
I want to die right here, right now!
I didn't realize that was how you felt...
But I was mistaken.
That isn't what it means to be a true friend.
Robin-san...
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Oomph!
Brook, we've got food! It's lunchtime.
Luffy-san...
Sanji worked extra hard to make
a full-course seafood lunch!
I just know it'll be good!
Luffy-san!
What's keeping you? Get a move on!
Are you absolutely certain I'm welcome?
That I may join the Straw Hat Crew?
Yup.
Jeez, give it some thought!
I decided to let you join,
so I'm glad to have you.
Now forget about that. Let's eat! Food!
Everyone's waiting!
Even the Straw Hats have
calm days like this...
Usopp, let's catch dinner!
Yeah!
How many years--no, decades--has it been
since I enjoyed such a carefree nap?
Hey, Brook! Are you gonna sleep forever?
Wake up! We spotted an island!
It's a Summer Island! It has a beach!
Huh? What?
When I was wandering the ocean alone,
I would dream about my old
friends and Laboon in my sleep.
I would jump awake with happiness,
only to face the painful reality
filled with despair and solitude.
Sleep was by no means a peaceful escape.
But if I listen carefully now...
So, Robin, what do you
think of these outfits?
Well, I think you'd look
good in this and this.
I knew it!
Perfect.
My pals are near me.
Even dead and skeletonized...
...I'm truly glad to be alive!
This is a short break time
before the next adventure
eventually falls upon us.
Yes, let your weary bones rest.
Laboon,
it looks like I will have
a slew of stories to
share when we meet again.
I hope you're looking forward to them!
The wind has picked up.
Everyone!
Guys!
Oomph!
It's about time we set out.
Yeah!
I promise to work my butt off!
But I'm a skeleton, so I don't have a butt.
We've reached the Red Line at last!
We'll finally get to see Fishman Island.
Where are the Mermaids?
I don't see any Mermaids,
but there is a sea monster.
The jerk!
Something popped out
when I whacked its stomach.
Could that be a--?!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Halfway Across the Grand Line
Arriving at the Red Line!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Halfway Across the Grand Line
Arriving at the Red Line!