Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
10 years ago in the East Blue,
there were 3 boys who dreamed
of becoming pirates.
First, Sabo set sail and then Ace
went out to sea 7 years later.
See you, Luffy! I'm going now!
And 3 years later,
Luffy departed
from his hometown - Windmill Village.
Sabo was first and Ace was second.
And I'm third but I'm gonna top them!
Wait for me, Ace!
I'll catch up with you soon!
And now, Luffy is...
The Pirate King?!
I'm...
I'm too...
...weak!!
I Wanna See Them!
Luffy's Tearful Cry
Let's go along the Grand Line!
We're gonna take over the world!
Let's start with that island!
Give me cannonballs!
Meteor Fist Shower!
Here, here, here, here!
You've had enough for today.
--It's Garp-san!
--Garp-san is back with his ship!
On business?!
Goa Kingdom in the East Blue, Windmill Village
Garp-san, I've read about
the war in the newspaper!
It said it was a great victory for the Navy!
--Hey, how is everybody here doing?
--What happened to Luffy?
What's gonna happen to the world
after Whitebeard's death, Garp-san?
I've seen pirate ships offshore
frequently over the past few days.
We can't even sleep in peace at night
because we fear their invasion.
Don't worry! I just sank
three of them out at sea!
Really?! That's great!
They were all amateurs who
don't even know how to fight.
But for a while,
the seas will be uneasy all over the
world because Whitebeard was a deterrent.
This is a remote village in the East Blue
but you have to be careful.
--Hey!
--Yes, sir!
"Protected by Navy Vice Admiral Garp"
"Protected by Navy Vice Admiral Garp"?
Oh, I feel safe!
We don't have to be afraid of anything!
Garp-san, we have another problem.
Mountain bandits came down to the village
and they're taking over Makino's bar.
Mountain bandits?
No! You can't do that!
Hey, Garp!
Oh, that's her!
How dare you come back
and show your face here?!
Garp-san!
B-Boss!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Stay out of it! I know her.
You bastard...
You were there at the battlefield...
You were there with them!
What did you do to help?!
Why?! Why?! Why?! Why?! Why?!
Why did you stand by and watch Ace die?!
You chose your job over your family?!
Hey, Garp! You're the hero of the Navy?!
Go to hell, you old bastard!
--Easy, easy, boss, stop it!
--Boss!
Garp, say something!
Why didn't you help him?! Why
didn't you do something?!
Get on your feet!
You cold-blooded scum!
Stop it, Dadan-san!
Makino...
Can't you see that he's taking
it harder than anybody else
because he couldn't help them
even though he was there?!
Th-That's not true.
That's not true.
That's not true!
Luffy's having a harder time than anyone!
Okay, let's start today's lesson
of how to express gratitude.
Yeah, let's get started already!
Oh, you got it, Ace!
No, that's not right.
You have to say "Thank you
in advance" on that occasion.
Oh, that wasn't right?
It sounded cool though.
Ace-kun wants to learn this
because he
wants to say "thank you" properly...
...to the captain of the Red-Haired
Pirates who helped Luffy.
To Shanks?!
Yeah, I will be a pirate by
the time I see Red-Haired.
As a pirate and as your old
brother, it's my job to thank him.
Now, let's do it pretending that
he's right in front of you.
I'm Ace. Who the hell are you?
Booh! That's not right. It's
not nice to say "the hell."
Is it "Who the heck are you"?
Give me your name.
Booh.
You have to say "you fool"!
Who are you, you bastard?
Booh!
Who is this?
"Whom" is this?
Booh!
Stop it! Are you serious?
You're bugging me by saying
stupid things! Go away!
Listen, Ace, I found an anaconda's
nest filled with big eggs!
Let's go get some now!
What? Big eggs?!
No, I can't!
I wanna learn how to pay respect!
I could get hurt if no one's
there and the anaconda finds me!
But I'll be safe if you come with me! So...
Shut up!
He loved his brother so much!
Makino!
Garp.
What happened to Luffy?
It said in the newspaper
that he went missing.
Mayor.
He got away by submarine.
The Navy went after him in full force
and searched for him desperately
but they didn't find any shipwreck.
So he's probably alive!
Oh, that's great!
But how does Navy Vice Admiral
Garp-san know the mountain bandit?
Don't know.
Luffy is so stupid.
But I'll take his side no matter
what kind of pirate he becomes.
It breaks my heart when I think
about how he must feel now.
Luffy!!
Don't be defeated!!
Meanwhile, far away in the
second half of the Grand Line -
the New World...
Red-Haired,
I've no words to express my gratitude.
Stop talking nonsense.
I always respected Whitebeard,
even though he was my enemy.
Even Sengoku respected him.
Whitebeard, Ace...
Let us handle the burial of those two.
I agree! I will take the blame on myself!
Alright, we should go now.
Yes. Thanks.
Luffy must be having a hard time.
I can't believe what Ace did.
Take back what you just said!
Don't make fun of the man who saved me!
The name of this era should be "Whitebeard"!
That's what Captain Roger would've done.
I wanted the captain to run away sometimes
and be able to shed tears.
Listen, Luffy.
By experiencing both victory and defeat,
running away and shedding tears,
a man will become a man.
It's okay to cry.
But you have to move on!
Calm Belt, Maiden Island
Damn!
I'm too weak! I can't save anybody!
Damn! Damn!
Dammit!!
Luffy-kun.
Go away!
Leave me alone!
I can't!
I can't just watch you hurt yourself anymore.
It's my own body! It's none of your business!
Then you can't blame Ace
for doing what he did.
His death was not your business!
Shut up, you bastard! I'm gonna
beat you if you say another word!
Do it if it makes you happy!
I'm injured too but I'm not gonna
get beaten by you in that condition!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Jinbe...
When I was going after Teach,
I saw my brother for the first time
in 3 years in Alabasta Kingdom.
And I felt relieved instantly as I saw him.
Do you know why?
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
That hurts, you brat!
Can't you see things clearly now?!
You believed that you
could overcome anything!
And you've never doubted your strength!
But all those formidable enemies
took away your confidence!
And your brother was your guide on the sea!
I know that you have lost a lot!
And the toughest enemies in the world
blocked your way time after time!
Your power is not enough to beat me!
You could be level-headed.
Go, Pacifistas!
You can't get away from me!
You'll never find your way like this!
Because you've lost yourself
in regret and guilt!
I know that it's painful now, Luffy,
but you have to bottle up those feelings!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
Luffy, don't fool around
here. I'm training now.
Luffy! Tell everybody to take their post!
A storm is coming!
Luffy, you just see if I don't!
I'm gonna catch a big one soon!
Luffy, it's almost ready
so just shut up and wait.
Luffy, no matter how serious your
injury is, you're in good hands!
I'll treat you!
Oh, Luffy!
I can teach you about archeology
if you're interested.
Hey, Luffy! The Cola engine
is in top shape as always!
You can leave everything
about the Sunny to me!
Good morning, Luffy-san! It's morning!
Now here is the first song for today!
Luffy.
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
I still have...
I still have my friends!
Zoro! Nami! Usopp! Sanji!
Chopper! Robin! Franky! Brook!
They are my friends!
I see.
I have to meet them on the ship.
Guys! Meet on the Sunny in three days!
Okay!
I gotta go! It took a while but...
...I know that they're waiting for me!
What I saw there, Jinbe, was...
Older brothers can't help worrying...
...if their younger brother is weak.
I know that he'll be a handful
but please look after him.
Luffy wasn't just the kid who
used to follow me around anymore.
He had...
...such reliable friends!
He'll be alright no matter what happens.
That's why I felt relieved.
I wanna see them now...
I wanna see them!!
Luffy is missing his friends...
At the same time, far across the sea,
the friends he'd been separated from are still fighting
their own battles to make it back to Sabaody Archipelago.
Meanwhile, news of the "Paramount War"
makes its way to the separated friends!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Straw Hats in Shock!
Receiving the Bad News"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Straw Hats in Shock!
Receiving the Bad News