Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is headed to Navy Headquarters...
...with Ivankov, Jinbe,
Buggy, Crocodile and others,
in order to rescue his brother,
Ace who is about to be executed!
Meanwhile, the rest of the Straw Hats are...
Is this the fighting costume...
...that you were talking about?!
Cute!
Quit it! Shut up!
How odd! Why can't I land a single blow?!
That's because you have doubt in your heart!
That can't be it!
Are you sure?!
What?!
"Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan,
how are you both doing?"
"I'm looking forward to seeing you two!"
"When the time comes, I'm sure
that we'll become good friends!"
There it is! Right there!
Damn! We're on a cliff!
Are you guys here to save us?!
I didn't know that she was her baby!
I'm sick of this place!
The Crew's Whereabouts
Revolutionaries and a Gorging Forest's Trap!
East Blue
Tequila Wolf
Maximum security prison tower
How do you like the Sea Prism Stone armlet?
It just goes to show there are men...
...who don't have any taste
when it comes to presents.
Out with it! Where are the Straw Hats now?!
If you're trying to seduce me,
you need to create a better mood.
You bitch!
Nico Robin...
We didn't want that troublemaker here!
I heard that she sank
6 ships when she was only 8.
And I don't think somebody like
her could adjust well to prison.
And if she broke out, she'd
turn this country on its side!
I have to make sure that no one
outside knows who she is...
May I come in?
What's the matter?
It's about the construction delays...
Double the work hours of the laborers!
One meal a day is enough for them!
But they say that there are people
who are opposed to the construction.
We shouldn't be too strict.
There aren't that many of them
and they can't do anything.
The only threat we have is Nico Ro...
Well, anyway...
You need to see the laborers as expendable!
Hey, don't stop! Pull harder!
Hurry up! We're hungry!
Old man! Are you okay?!
Why are you goofing around?!
He's dying! Just leave him!
What are you looking at?!
W-What're you guys doing?
H-Hey!
You fools, don't leave your posts!
If you don't wanna work, I can
send you to the prison tower!
The prison tower?
That lady...
It's seawater just like you like!
Taste it to your heart's content!
It's lukewarm.
If we hand you over to a Navy
ship, it'll bring us a fortune!
Even if you're dead!
What crude pleasure!
Bitch!
Oh boy, the potato skin soup again?
We can't get any energy out of this!
You're cooperative. Have a chocolate, too.
Thank you, mister!
Humph! Informant!
I did it to survive! You're not getting any!
Old lady!
You can't have this!
Leave her alone!
The lady that you took the trouble to save...
...was sent to the tower
because she snitched!
That young lady gave herself
up in order to save us.
She's a strong woman. She'll
forgive the old lady!
Why are you here?!
This is mine!
I-I wanted to get out of here!
I don't feel sorry at all!
Uh-huh.
You can have this.
Thank you!
Old lady, you're kind!
I'm sorry! But I couldn't help it!
We're all helpless!
We have to stay here and suffer
for the rest of our lives!
I haven't say "thank you" to that lady.
I want to give this chocolate to her.
What are you doing?! Get back to work!
Here's your meal!
Finish it then we'll start questioning again!
Can't wait.
Sounds like you have been
hurt bad, young girl.
Who are you?
I'm just an old man. I was
sent to this country today
but they said that the elderly
are useless and put me in here.
I'm sorry about that.
I...
I have no time to waste!
I've got to get out of here!
Even it means that I have to cut my arms off!
Young girl, don't feel so pressed!
Listen carefully.
Don't you hear something?!
What's the matter?
What's that?!
Dissidents are running wild!
The warden ordered all of
us to go and break it up!
Lady!
Lady, where are you?
--Lady!
--Soran!
Lady! I just wanted to thank you...
What are you doing there?!
Dissidents?
Yes, but as you ordered,
all teams went to break it up
so it didn't become serious!
I didn't give that order.
Don't tell me that you even sent the
security soldiers stationed at the tower!
Lady!
Soran! How did you get here?
I'm an agent of the Revolutionary Army!
Are you alright? The diversion went well!
Good job!
With your command, we can win!
Yeah, you can count on me!
Oh yeah!
While you're at it, free
that young girl, too.
Hey lady, you're in luck!
Thanks.
You fool! I don't care about the dissidents!
Look out for Nico Robin!
This doesn't fit, either.
Young girl, it's gonna be messy for awhile.
Why don't you hide somewhere safe?
I don't want you to slow us down.
What?!
Oh no!
Nico Robin! Shoot her to death!
Clutch!
You are Nico Robin?!
I owe the people here!
I have to pay them back!
The woman in the tower has broken
out and is coming after us!
Help me!
--W-Warden!
--Robin... Robin is coming!
It's over! Everything's over!
Nico Robin!
You have a nice name!
Luffy-kun, you need to rest if only a little.
Yeah. Thank you.
But I'm okay.
The wind has died down.
Even though we are moving
forward with the current,
we may not arrive in time.
Luffy-kun!
No. I should not give him needless anxiety.
When we get to Navy Headquarters, he will
get involved in an unimaginable war!
Ace!
Grand Line
Bowin Islands
It's a man-eating sunflower!
And my name is Heracles'n!
Heracles'n!
Help me!
Hera...
I said "help!" I'm sick of this!
Why?! Why are you depressed?
Sleeping sulkily?!
Help me, Heracles! You're
the hero of the forest!
The hero... of the forest?
Yes, you're the strong, cool hero!
I'm the hero of the forest--Heracles'n!
Wow! Cool!
Usopp'n! I'm coming for you'n!
Heracles!
Look out!
Heracles! Heracles! Heracle...
What... are... you... doing?!
--Whiz!
--Zunk!
I'm alive!
But why're they attacking just me?
To survive on this island, you need
to look sharp and have stamina'n!
You're the weakest one on this island
now! Ants and worms are better than you!
Screw you! I'm stronger
than ants and worms...
Huge!
--Wanna eat this'n?
--Yeah, right'n!
You need to build up stamina if
you don't wanna get beat up'n!
I know! But there's nothing
here that I really wanna eat!
Oh, I'm hungry!
Oh well'n.
Are you sure that there are
things to eat beyond this?
Yes, those are too good so be careful'n!
Wow!
What the hell is this place?!
Smells so good! Yeah, I
think I can eat these!
Ramen Falls! Spaghetti Patches!
Ham Fruits! Chocolat Rocks for dessert!
You can eat whatever you see!
Oh, can I eat these?!
--Go ahead'n.
--Yum-yum!
Eat a lot and build your stamina, then
the man-eating plants won't attack you'n!
Yeah? That's great!
These are really good,
I can eat these forever!
Don't just eat'n! You need to work out, too!
I know! But I need to eat a lot...
...to become a cool hero of
the forest like you, right?
You wanna become a hero, too?
We're the heroes of the forest Heracles'n!
And Usopp'n!
U-Usopp'n! Oh?
Usopp'n! Where'd you go'n?!
Wow! This is good, too!
I can eat this even if I'm full!
That way'n?
This is too good! I can't stop!
Usopp'n! Where are you'n?
If you eat too much, you're
gonna be in big trouble'n!
I can't control my hands! I can't stop!
There you are, finally!
What do you think, Heracles'n?
Now I can become the hero of the forest!
Usopp'n! You're way too big!
You'd better work off some calories
or you're gonna be in big trouble!
What's this? An earthquake?
It's beginning!
Whoa, w-what a huge mouth!
Don't wanna fall! Don't wanna fall!
--Usopp'n!
--Heracles!
--Wow!
--Too heavy!
Hey!
Hera!
Goodbye, Usopp'n.
So this is goodbye?!
Oh, ramen!
Usopp'n!
Sup!
I can't eat anymore!
Usopp'n!
Fat things will surely be
eaten on this island'n!
Surely be eaten?!
It's impossible to escape
from here - Bowin Islands!
Impossible to escape?!
And I'm the hero of the forest H...
Zoro wanders the island with Perona
in hopes of reuniting with their friends.
When Zoro gets lost as always,
a mysterious shadow attacks!
Around that time,
Brook attempts to fulfill a pledge for panties!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Crew's Whereabouts
A Giant Gravestone and the Panty Pledge"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Crew's Whereabouts
A Giant Gravestone and the Panty Pledge