Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hody's merciless plot puts Fishman Island in unprecedented danger!
My axe! Hit Hody!
The Noah is falling!
Just in time!
Fishman Island...
...is in danger!
"Luffy Loses the Fight?! Hody's Long-Awaited Revenge!"
So he's dead finally!
Now, Vander Decken's power became ineffective
and the Noah will crash into Fishman Island!
Go to hell, Straw Hats!
And all those people who stand in the way of our vengeance!
--Fishman Island... --...Will be no more!
We have to stop the ship somehow!
Straw Hat!
You wanna stop the Noah, don't you? Then you have to beat me.
Otherwise, you can't save Fishman Island!
You bastard!
If the Noah crashes into Fishman Island, it will be the end of everything.
Both the kingdom and the Noah's purpose
that has been protected for hundreds of years!
Listen, my sons.
That ark - the Noah is not just a relic from history-jamon.
Hundreds of years ago, a promise was made to a great man
and that ship has been kept on the seafloor until the appointed day comes.
The ship has not served its purpose yet-jamon.
Now, we don't even know how they made that ship.
The Noah cannot be damaged until the day comes!
Understood, Father.
We will go and find out why it moved and take care of it.
I have to save both the kingdom and the Noah at any cost!
Straw Hat, you have neither a strategy to stop the Noah
nor a chance to beat me!
What's the matter? If nothing is done,
your friends will have no choice
but to be swallowed by the sea, along with Fishman Island!
Were you fooling yourself when you said you'd protect them all, Straw Hat?!
I will stop it!
I'm gonna break it to pieces before it gets to the island!
You can't do that, Straw Hat! Even if you could do so,
as I told you, the Noah has
a long history and will serve a purpose in the future!
Then how can we save the island?!
We don't have time!
That's all I can think of!
Decken could still be alive.
If we can wake him up, maybe we can change the course of the ship.
What if he's dead? Then what are we gonna do? We gotta destroy it...
I said "Wait"!
Are you guys splitting? While you're arguing,
look, the Noah is falling towards the island!
Wait, Noah! There are people who I love on the island!
Decken-sama! If you are alive, please make it come after me!
Please don't harm Fishman Island!
Drop dead now and watch it from beyond the grave, as the Ryugu Kingdom falls!
Fishman Karate!
Shirahoshi!
Sea Drums!
Brother Mamboshi-sama!
Mamboshi!
It's your turn now!
Fishman Karate!
Hody!
Straw Hat!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
Luffy-sama!
...Jet Pistol!
Damn! I can defend myself with the Armament Haki
but my Haki is not good enough for these kind of attacks yet!
I shouldn't be fighting in the water.
In order to beat him, I need...
He wants to fight on the falling ship, doesn't he?
But what he really wants is...
...the air on its deck!
If I could get in there, I can beat Hody with a single blow!
I knew he was going to do it!
Those bubbles are susceptible to large gashes!
Damn! The air on the deck is gone!
It's so easy to render you humans helpless!
You should realize you're no better than us Fishmen!
Not only can you not stop the Noah but you can't even beat me!
Drop dead, Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Snake Shot!
Screw you!
Do you think I'm stupid enough to get hit by the same attack twice?
I wonder which comes first - your friends
being shattered to death along with the island
or your last breath! Can't wait to see!
Oh no! He's gonna break my bubble again!
You dullard!
Luffy-sama!
Shirahoshi!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
Listen to me very carefully.
I want you to handle Straw Hat.
Handle Luffy-sama?
I'm going to stop Hody at any cost!
You have to trust me no matter what happens and stay close to the Noah!
No matter what happens! Understood?
Yes.
There's no way I can miss now! Even with my eyes closed!
Oh no!
This is it!
Wh-What happened?
Luffy-sama.
I'm sorry.
Wimpyhoshi!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama asked me to do this.
Brother-hoshi!
Hody! What's wrong with you?!
There are so many lives on that island! How could you?
What's wrong with you?!
You three Princes are the strongest in the Ryugu Kingdom?!
After all, you are sons of that stupid Otohime.
She had no pride in being a Fishman and died a dog's death
trying to become friendly with humans.
You three are worthless Princes who can't even save your own country!
Brother-hoshi!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
Even your power is fake,
I admit that I couldn't fight back because I'm not strong enough.
But there is still hope!
Merman Combat!
Ultramarine!
Don't you get it?!
You can't beat me with those crappy attacks now!
Why, Hody?!
What is it that you want badly enough to sacrifice
so many innocent fellowmen's lives?!
How can you do such a horrible thing?!
Hody! Ultra...
Shark Slicer!
...Marine!
Go to hell!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
How pathetic, you piss-poor Prince!
This power is a gift from heaven!
Now, it's your turn, you two.
Damn!
You can't beat me with that fake power!
Drop dead already!
Hody, what's with you?!
You petitioned for vengeance against the humans to Fishmen, but now
you're trying to take those fellow Fishmen's lives along with the island!
You even abandoned the ones you grew up with in the Fishman District!
Don't you realize what you are doing?!
Or is your hatred for humans so deep that makes you lose your mind?
What happened to you?
Did humans beat you?!
Did humans kill your loved ones or someone dear to you?!
What did you go through in the past?!
Answer me, Hody!
What did humans do to you?!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
That bastard!
Wimpyhoshi! Brother-hoshi is in trouble! Let's go!
What are you doing?! Hey! Wimpyhoshi!
Where are you going, Wimpyhoshi?!
You have to trust me no matter what happens and stay close to the Noah!
No matter what happens! Understood?
Wimpyhoshi...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Straw Hat Luffy-san, this is the Air Tank. We met you a while ago.
Oh, it's you guys.
AIR TANK
We've been listening to what's been going on out there.
And we see the Noah falling towards the island.
CONTROL ROOM
We're getting ready as planned.
That's what Brother-hoshi was talking about.
You wanna go to the deck?
Hody!
--Go after him! --No, wait, Straw Hat!
Why?!
I'm sure you know it by now.
Hody has an advantage in the water since he is a Fishman.
--If nothing is done... --What should we do?
I have an idea!
Hey, where are you going?! Brother-hoshi!
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF FISHMAN ISLAND
Prince Fukaboshi?
What brought you here, Prince?
Listen, we might need a large amount of air soon.
Make preparations!
Yes, sir!
It's fine. There is some air on the deck.
Then I can beat him up there.
Aside from Decken,
do you think Hody would leave the bubble so you can fight there?
I want you to take this Baby Transponder Snail just in case.
We need to be well-prepared. Let's go!
Luffy-sama! What should I do about the Noah?
Brother Fukaboshi-sama told me to stay close to the Noah along
with Luffy-sama, no matter what happens!
So that's what Brother-hoshi...
H-Hey, hello? How can we get air from you?
We can shoot all the air from the Air Tank.
What is the Air Tank?
It's an air conditioning facility that's providing air to Fishman Island.
If we make a bubble and shoot it, maybe we can surround the Noah.
But the bubbles neutralize ascending forces
so it's not going to make the Noah float.
That means we can't stop it from falling.
On top of that, we have to use all the air
we have in order to engulf that giant ship.
In other words, there is only one chance.
If we don't shoot it at the exact moment
that the Noah comes right beside us,
there will be no second chance.
So basically, it's a hit-or-miss situation.
Y-Yes. And I'm afraid you'll have to take it from there!
Again, I can't emphasize enough that...
Enough with the difficult stuff and just do it!
I can handle anything as long as there is air!
All right. We'll do our best!
Luffy-san, please save the island!
Straw Hat! Shirahoshi!
What can they accomplish by swimming alongside the Noah?
They are only a human and a Mermaid Princess!
Shark Slicer!
Straw Hat!
Screw this!
Armament: Hardening!
He's putting up quite a fight!
Hey, human! Give it up, human!
It makes me sick to my stomach just looking at you people!
Even if it shortens my life and even if it comes at the ultimate price,
I will execute my revenge on you humans!
That bastard!
Don't miss it! You don't have a second chance!
If you miss it, Fishman Island will be...
Hey, Straw Hat. Can you hear me?
It's Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
Brother-hoshi, are you okay?!
Barely alive. Anyway, listen carefully.
About Hody Jones...
I found out who he really is!
As the Noah once again draws near,
Fishman Island is in chaos as the citizens evacuate.
The Straw Hats continue to believe in Luffy and fight on.
Neptune's army finally joins the battle, as well.
The battle at the Conchcorde Plaza is unfolding rapidly,
as a new truth further shakes up the citizens!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Shocking Fact! The True Identity of Hody!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!