Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil.
There are 30,000 human slaves we've caught in the sea over the past month.
And 70,000 Fishmen who know how to use arms.
They moved here from the closed Fishman District.
Behold...
...100,000 outlaws altogether!
Look how powerful I am!
This is the power that I'm talking about!
I started this whole thing 10 years ago.
Let me tell you something.
Concerning the late Queen of the Ryugu Kingdom, who you fools still love!
Otohime was killed by...
...me!
What?!
Your mother was not murdered by a human!
I, her kinsman, did it!
I, standing in front of you now, killed her!
I already knew it.
Shirahoshi!
What?
"Shirahoshi's Tears! Luffy Finally Shows Up!"
What do you mean you already knew that...
...I killed your mother, Shirahoshi?!
Father! Are you all right?!
Stay with us!
Shirahoshi!
A few years after it happened,
Megalo told me secretly.
Megalo?!
He did?!
Is that true, Megalo?!
No...
Megalo was owned by Neptune's army back then.
And he witnessed everything that day!
Mother! Mother!
I can't believe it.
Princess Shirahoshi, why didn't you...
If I told anyone...!
Someone would hold a grudge against Hody-sama, I thought.
And that is not what Mother-sama wanted!
That was the last promise we made with her.
She told us that no matter who did it to her,
we should not get angry or hate anybody!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Don't get angry on my behalf.
Don't let resentment or hatred get the better of you for my sake.
Shirahoshi, you...
Don't tell me that you...
You did as Mother said to do 10 years ago and...
...you have been keeping this to yourself all this time, alone in Hard Shell Tower?!
She tried not to harbor hate for the one who killed her mother?
Even though it was her dying mother's wish,
it's almost unthinkable someone would be able to keep such a promise!
She is such an obedient, admirable girl!
Who else could have done such a thing?!
Stop laughing, you fool!
I can't help it! Hey, Megalo?
If you had cried out right there, you could've drawn everybody's attention
and let them know that I was the one who did it.
So thank you for shutting your mouth!
And thank you for confiding only in this dumb girl!
If it were anybody else, we couldn't have come this far!
You know, Shirahoshi, what you did was pretty stupid!
That's what we call those actions in this world!
Because you tried to stymie your hate for me, this kingdom will fall.
Because of you,
your father, your brothers, the citizens, and you yourself are all going to die!
Shirahoshi!
No, don't listen to him, Princess-sama! You did nothing wrong!
No, it was definitely foolish!
Shark Arrows!
King! Princes!
Stop! Please stop!
Father-sama! Brothers-sama!
Look how miserable they are!
No...
We are doomed!
Great warriors?! Pathetic! They're barely alive now!
It's because Captain Hody is so strong-ch!
They can't make it until the time of execution-ch!
That's not good. They must be executed by beheading.
Hey, I need a sword.
Our only concern was Jinbe and Shirahoshi, and we got them now.
There is no reason for us to wait until the appointed time now.
I'm going to execute these worthless creatures...
...of the royal family!
Yeah! Kill them!
They deserve death!
Kill them! Kill them!
No! They're really gonna kill Neptune the Great Knight!
It's hell on earth!
They have 100,000 outlaws on their side.
This is it for our country!
Madame Sharley!
Children...
Tell me! When will the pirate with a hat come to destroy the island?!
Tell me! When will it be?!
I don't know. All I know is what will happen in the future.
It could be tomorrow or a year from now.
I want them to come now...
If they create havoc here now,
we might be in trouble but those villains would be too, right?
I want them to come now, too! I don't want them to kill the King!
Me neither!
You're right, children.
It's better if they came now.
Yes, yes...
Hey! Straw Hat Luffy!
If you want to destroy the island, why don't you do it now?!
Do your worst - right here, right now!
Yeah! Can you hear us, Straw Hat?!
If you're hiding somewhere on the island, come here now!
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
How pathetic! They're literally clutching at straws!
Sharley's previsions were always accurate but this time, it's bullshit!
How meaningless...
Those fools must be out of their minds. Let's bring them to their senses.
Listen, you stupid citizens!
I'm going to proceed with the execution of the former king, Neptune - now!
Father...
Watch very closely!
As I cut former king Neptune's head off!
Then, this half-assed king without a drop of racial pride will be gone forever
and the new kingdom of Fishmen will rise, which will dominate the pathetic humans!
I'll put an end to the shameless Ryugu Kingdom!
How regrettable!
Farewell!
Luffy-sama...
Luffy-sama!
Please save Father-sama!
Megalo?
What?!
Th-That's...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
He really showed up!
Hey, did you see that? He saved King Neptune.
Yeah! And right before that, Princess Shirahoshi cried for his help!
Luffy-sama!
Did he come out of the shark?
Was he hiding in its stomach?! But why?!
You're out already... But I guess you had no choice!
Hurry up, you all!
Much! What the... Who is he talking to-ch?!
Don't worry! We were ready from the beginning!
Because we knew that Luffy would never...
...sit tight as we had planned!
Mirage, release!
A woman appeared all of a sudden-ch!
Is this it, Jinbe-chan? The letter from the Celestial Dragons?
That's it! Good job!
No way! Whoa! The letter is gone! When did she take it?!
What were you doing, idiot?!
And I handed the key over to Robin!
No, don't tell me...
The key's gone!
What were you doing?!
It's unlocked!
Who did this?
Robin-sama?
Is this...
Father! Are you all right?!
Hey, look up! What's that?
That's...
A whale and a lion?
No, wait! That's...
Gaon Cannon!
It's a pirate ship!
Fire!
Now is your chance! Go, Whale!
Hoe?
Princes! Take the King and go!
Okay!
I won't let you do that! Wait-zugan!
Oh no, it took the King and the Princes!
Damn! Give us back the royal family-gaban!
What happened?
I think Jinbe hatched a plan with the Straw Hats.
I can't believe that he really came.
Hey, look! That's...
Wow! Look how many people there are!
Oh no, are they all our enemies?!
I think so. It looks like there are 70,000 or 80,000...
No, 100,000 of them, maybe.
That's a little tough!
You can go take a nap or something if you want. I'll take care of them.
What do you mean, you fool?!
I can't wait!
Let's go wild, guys!
Look, the members of the Straw Hats are coming out of the ship!
Hey! Straw Hat Luffy!
Are you really going to destroy the island?!
Why did you occupy the Ryugu Palace?! Do you want to kill the royal family too?!
Was it you guys who kidnapped the Mermaids?!
Hey! Answer us!
Are you people friends or foes to Fishman Island?!
Answer, Straw Hat!
Friends or foes? That's something...
...you'll have to decide on your own!
The Straw Hats have gathered in the Conchcorde Plaza.
But Hody proclaims that he will become Pirate King,
and sends the vast force of the New Fishman Pirates to attack Luffy's crew.
Ten pirates will battle to decide the fate of Fishman Island!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Big Clash! The Straw Hats vs. A Hundred Thousand Enemies!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!