Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and crew reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war
against the New Fishman Pirates,
who held a grudge against humans
and plotted to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom.
In the end, Luffy managed to defeat Hody,
the New Fishman Pirates' captain, in an intense fight.
Ultimately thwarting his plot.
Listen. You all need to know the two biggest changes...
...which have occurred in the New World.
First, Navy Headquarters led by Sakazuki...
...has become an even more powerful force for justice.
And second,
the Blackbeard Pirates have advanced.
You fools! Why did you kick him out?!
Why didn't you just punch him and tie him up here!
I love it even when you...
Go find him now!
They were sent by Big Mom. This is not a good time!
We don't have any sweets to pay them for this month.
Hody and the others destroyed the factory
and the undamaged sweets have
been sent to the banquet since everybody wanted the
Straw Hats to have them!
I wonder if we can explain the situation.
She is like a monster who would destroy a whole country for sweets!
One of the Four Emperors...
Big Mom!
She Loves Sweets!
Big Mom of the Four Emperors
After the banquet reaches its climax, it comes to an end.
What?! They'll give us their treasure?!
Wow!
That's really nice!
I wonder if Luffy-sama and the others are doing okay, Nami-chin-sama.
They're fine!
We're finally gonna become a rich pirate group!
Things in life usually aren't that easy...
Hey Usopp, do you wanna go look for him too?
No, we better not. I did some research
and found out that his bounty is over 200 million.
Fishman Island
Outskirts of Coral Hill near the Candy Factory
What?! Mine's only 50 berries...
Hey look, Zoro, Sanji! There he is! That was easy!
He got knocked out cold already by your punch. How pathetic!
There is so much treasure scattered around here.
Is that furry king really going to give us all of this?
Cool! We can buy lots of meat!
I can't believe he was storing all of this in his gloopy body!
1, 2, 3!
--Alright! Let's go back to the palace! --How?
We need a flying fish.
--Which way is the town, Zoro? --That way.
--Okay, let's head in the opposite direction. --Hey!
All right, Minister of the Left?
Please show us mercy!
It was all unexpected! Hody and the others destroyed the factory and...
That's none of our concern! Grr!
I was planning on snatching some for myself so I'm very hungry!
You pay us with sweets once a month.
And we allow you to use Mama's name.
Big Mom Pirates, Crewmate Pekoms
That was the agreement, wasn't it? Grr!
Now, I don't want to say this to you seeing as how we're business partners
but you know how scary Mama can be! If you make her mad, she will...
...destroy you all!
He's cute when he does that!
Now, what are you gonna do?! Grr!
Look - a crowd.
Oh, this is the Candy Factory! Pappagu told me about it!
Yeah?
I hope we can find a flying fish here.
I guess they're making those yummy sweets here!
Hey, Candy Factory!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy-san, is the banquet over already?!
Luffy-kun, why are you here?!
Yeah, I ate a lot!
The meat was good but those sweets
from Fishman Island were unbelievable!
What?!
No, Straw Hat-san!
Don't talk about them!
Oh, old Mr. Catfish, it's you!
Did he say "sweets"?! Who are they?!
Oh yeah, he's Straw Hat Luffy! Definitely!
What is that notorious pirate doing here?
Well, um...
Hey brat! Which sweets are you talking about?!
Well, Mr. Pekoms, let me explain...
Who are you?!
You're not a Fishman, are you?
You came to buy sweets?
I just finished stuffing myself full of them!
What?!
What's going on here?! He just said he ate them!
W-Well... There is an explanation...
Oh?! A talking lion!
But I guess that's not such a big deal. We've got something similar.
Atchoo!
Whoa, what's wrong? Did you catch a cold?
Maybe somebody's talking about me.
You're popular.
This lion's got an unique face!
What?! Are you messing with me?!
Yuck! You fool!
Pekoms.
Making such threatening faces doesn't help us in collecting the sweets.
Let's settle this peacefully-soir. The tea party is 4 days from now-bon.
We can make it on time if we leave here tomorrow morning-jour.
There's another odd one! Who are you?
Bon to meet you, you half-boiled pirates.
My name is Baron Tamago-soir!
Big Mom Pirates, Crewmate Baron Tamago (Longleg Tribe)
Tamago, like an egg?!
Remember my name at least-s'il vous plait!
Now, you gentlemen...
Did you just say you ate the sweets from this factory-c'est si bon?
He looks like a compass.
Yes, I did! I wanna have some more if they have any!
They don't. That's why we don't know what to do-bon!
That big mark on the factory is...
...the Jolly Roger of the great pirate and our boss- Charlotte Linlin-soir.
It claims this island as Big Mom's territory - she is one of the Four Emperors.
Which means, Fishman Island is protected under Big Mom's name-bon!
Sounds like a nice person! I wanna meet your boss! Big Mom, huh?
Don't mistake our arrangement. We have a business arrangement.
In exchange for 10 tons of sweets a month,
we allow them to use the mark-bon.
--10 tons? --That's right.
Mama loves sweet candies more than anything-soir.
Sweets from Fishman Island are her favorite.
So we'll wait until tomorrow morning.
No, Baron, I already told you.
The factory's giant cooking machines are broken
and we need at least 2 weeks to repair them!
That's not acceptable-soir.
Hey Tamago! Why can't you wait?!
Is your boss's mind as small as his balls? He's one of the Four Emperors, isn't he?
It's not "he." Mama is a great woman pirate-vous plait.
I don't think she has balls-jour.
Oh, she's a madam.
I love sweets!
And I love you too since you can make them!
What's gonna happen if you can't have them on time?
In that case...
The deal is off!
Vicious members of the Big Mom Pirates will...
...descend on the island and destroy it in no time-vous plait!
Destroy the island?!
Are you guys nuts? You can't destroy a country over candies!
This island has just been saved!
Whole Cake Island
Somewhere in the New World
You look happy, Mama.
One of the Four Emperors
The Great Pirate "Big Mom" Charlotte Linlin
I can't wait for the tea party
four days from now because...
...I'll get my hands on those delicious sweets from Fishman Island!
I can't wait and my stomach is already producing so much acid!
Can't wait! Can't wait! The sweets from Fishman Island!
You guys can't wait either?
Of course, we can't! They are so good!
Then why don't you wait for them inside of my stomach?!
Mama!
I'm home! Boyoyon!
Oh! How did it go, Bobbin?
I beat them up and burned the place!
How lovely!
That country had the best baked goods!
It must have smelled so good as it burned to the ground!
It's a shame but we had no choice.
Because they couldn't reach their quotas on time.
Can I have some snacks?
We have to kill them if they don't give us sweets!
I don't like people who don't keep their promises!
Just like I don't like bitter candies!
Oh yeah! I heard Fishman Island may not have sweets to pay this month.
I just got word from Pekoms. Do you want Fishman Island
to be burned down too?
I can't have the sweets from Fishman Island?!
Get them on the Transponder Snail now!
Destroy the island?!
Are you guys nuts?
You can't destroy a country over candies!
This island has just been saved!
I can't believe it-bon.
They aren't even half-boiled, they are raw.
What should I do with those fearless rookies-jour?
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
It must be Mama! Grr! I told them what was going on a while ago.
B-Big Mom is calling in person?!
Hey, Pekoms!
Why don't you pick it up? Grr! I don't wanna get yelled at!
Clank!
--Hello? --Hey!
Are you Big Mom?!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
You're not Tamago, are you? Nor Pekoms.
Who are you?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy! I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
--Luffy-kun! --Straw Hat-san...
Monkey D.?
You're Garp's grandson!
Now I remember!
You were the brat who meddled in the war 2 years ago.
The sweets are gone!
I ate them all!
So it's true that they don't have any!
They must have 10 tons of them!
I ate 10 tons of them!
Straw Hat-san, that's too...!
Why is he saying that?
You fool! Stop lying!
You're covering up for Fishmen, aren't you?
But it's true that I ate them!
I didn't know they had to go to you!
We have a lot of treasure with us here.
You can have it all! In compensation for the sweets!
Treasure?!
I can't eat treasure!
What I want is sweet candies!
Hey, wait a minute! Is that all treasure?
Yes, it is.
Mama, this is Tamago! Let's think about this.
A few days ago, that brat - Captain Kid sank two of our allies' ships-bon!
Kid?
It's that guy!
The rookie who's worth over a 100 million that we met at Sabaody!
It was a huge loss
and to be honest, we've been in need of money lately-bon.
So how about we save the fun of eating sweets for a couple of weeks
and take the treasure and forgive them? I think it's the best plan for us-jour.
If you want candies,
we could get something sweet and delicious on our way back.
Screw that, Tamago!
How could you say such an embarrassing thing?!
Pirates shouldn't compromise on what they want!
I-I'm sorry-soir!
Having said that,
That brat who stood up to me has piqued my interest.
Have it your way, instead of Fishman Island,
I'll have my vengeance against you all!
Luffy-sama and the others are not back yet.
Are you sure they are going to be okay, Nami-chin-sama?
Yeah, it's taking so long.
Boy! I wonder what they're doing!
I won't forgive them if they can't get the treasure back!
Monkey D. Luffy. I know your name now.
Come to the New World!
Luffy-kun!
Sure, wait for me there.
There's some business I want to settle with you, too.
I can't leave it in your hands - that's too dangerous!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
...and make Fishman Island my territory!
You insolent brat!
Fishman Island's treasure,
the Tamate Box, hold a surprising secret.
One that further intensifies the conflict...
...between Luffy and Big Mom of the Four Emperors.
Uncertainty grows concerning the Straw Hats' next destination.
On the oceans of the New World, that man
whose fate is closely tied to theirs makes a move.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Difficulties Ahead
A Trap Waiting in the New World"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Difficulties Ahead
A Trap Waiting in the New World