Good day
all you hopeless jailbirds waiting to
end your lives locked up in these cells!
If y'all are just waiting for
your death, how 'bout it?
Why don't y'all fight to
the death in those cells?!
Whoever lives... I'll make you part of my crew
and take y'all with me outside!
Take the others, but not him.
So, he was alive...
The man known as the "Demon Heir."
2 Years Later
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the Pirate King, once
attained everything this world had to offer.
The last words before his death drove
people around the world to the seas.
"My treasure? If you want it, you can have it.
Find it. I left everything
the world has to offer there."
These words sparked the Great Pirate Era.
That moment... I died once...
and so did you.
But I'll go along with your proposal.
I, Buena Festa, have the
greatest information of my life!
The treasure he hid away is within my hands!
And with that, everything that
you desire will be yours!
Let's do it!
The world's largest festival of the pirates,
by the pirates, for the pirates!
The Pirates Fest!
Ahem, "To all of my dearest pirates!
A mix of enemies and allies
exchanging toasts can be fun.
Anyone is free to come and go as they please.
We invite you to this world's
largest banquet, the Pirates Fest.
Sincerely, Buena Festa,
Festival Pirates Captain."
I see it!
Festival, here we come!
I have heard of the Pirates Fest.
It is an enormous pirate festival
suddenly held once every few years.
I hear rare ships, food, weapons, information,
and such from around the world will be there.
Like a pirates' black market, eh?
Sounds like there'll be good booze, too.
"Furthermore, this time around,
as entertainment, a—
Gold Roger, the Pirate King
-related treasure hunt is planned."
Sounds like fun!
"Hunt for the Pirate King's treasure!"
A pirate festival?
Treasure hunt! Treasure hunt!
They even sent us an Eternal Pose
to the festival's island.
And what's more, the Pirate King's—
Treasure hunt!
Hey! Have some suspicions!
She’s scary!
Buena Festa was known as the
world's No. 1 Festival Master,
as well as a pirate who had strong ties
to informants and weapon merchants,
and was the subject of endless dark rumors.
But I thought he was dead.
A dead man and the Pirate King's treasure...
Well, whatever the truth is,
we can't ignore the words
"Pirate King." Right, Captain?
It's a treasure hunt among pirates!
Of course it's gonna be fun!
Let's go! To the Pirates Fest!
Marvelous...
The main players are arriving...
Excuse me, Mr. Festa.
You sure do look feisty, Monkey D. Luffy.
This is the grand festival
to celebrate our launch.
Make sure you fire it up!
My dear pirates!
You havin' fun at the Pirates Fest?!
I'm sure you all know, but fights,
kidnapping, stealing, etc...
Anything is allowed in this Pirates Fest!
But there's just one solid rule!
Never tell the Navy about this festival!
Anyone who does will be chased to the ends
of hell and eliminated by all the pirates here.
Ooh, how scary!
Oops, I haven't introduced myself!
I am the MC and your host, Donald Moderate!
And here is our special guest!
Everyone's favorite songstress, Ann!
Nice to meet you, everyone!
As you all know,
Ann is a Devil Fruit power-user!
Viso-Viso Vision!
Whoa! Hot!
The Viso-Viso Fruit!
It's power can turn any touched
image into a visual illusion!
Though it vanishes right away.
Thank you!
Now, we're resurrecting this
Pirates Fest after 20 long years.
And there's a reason why
it takes place on this island!
It is said that a little before
the dawn of the Great Pirate Era,
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
discovered this island
and hid an amazing treasure
somewhere on this island!
And this is what he said:
"In a deep, lofty darkness
we leave our answer."
Now, my friends! This is a challenge
from the Pirate King!
Let us solve this mystery and
get our hands on that treasure!
Hey, hurry! They're saying somethin'!
We're super late!
That's your guys' fault!
I said we were just getting ready for the treasure hunt!
Why'd you have to stuff yourselves like that?!
Look who's talking.
At any rate, this pumped-up crowd...
This is the real deal!
Yeah! Can't wait!
Don't you all worry! The almighty Usopp
will get the treasure for sure!
Let's go, Chopper!
Yeah!
Guess we just have to go along with them.
But as far as I can tell from
the pirates gathered here...
Yeah... I see tons of crazy guys.
What?!
Hey all, the Sunny's ready to go anytime!
Countin' on ya, Franky!
My "Mustn't Treasure Hunt"
disease is getting to me...
You okay, Usopp?!
What the hell are you doing...
ya flashy idiots?!
Not me! It's this guy's fault!
Why is it my fault?!
Shut up flashily! Hurry up and find him!
You're the one responsible for security!
Correct! I am responsible for security here!
I’m one of the terrifying
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
The living legend...
Captain Buggy, the Genius Jester!
We sent in 200 security pirates,
and yet, still can't catch one rat...!
Our pay from that festival geezer's
gonna go down! Find him flashily!
Looks like the situation's gonna
be far worse than I thought.
Straw Hat!
Aha!
Found you! Trafalgar Law!
Room!
Chambres!
He vanished?!
The Pirates Fest.
To think that this many pirates actually gathered...
"Arrest them all this second"
is what I wanna say, but...
Our main target is the big boss,
Festa the "Festival Master."
A big-time pirate from the days of Roger
who we thought died in a Sea King accident.
And this guy, too.
The man Navy Headquarters
won't even admit is alive.
Douglas Bullet, the worst escapee
from Level 6 at Impel Down.
If these two are teamed up,
this is clearly no ordinary festival.
What was that?
What's goin' on?
S-S-S-S-S-Stop! It's a sign to stop!
No, this must be...
The current’s flow is...
My god! S-Something crazy
has started to happen!
Ah! My friends!
Remember those words I said earlier!
"In a deep, lofty darkness...
...we leave our answer."
But what does it mean by "lofty"?!
C-Could this be...?!
Wait... I get it.
From the darkness of the deep sea,
it climbs to the heavens above!
Awesome!
It's the shooting sea current,
the Knock-Up Stream!
Whoa!
And a bunch of bubbles have appeared!
Furthermore...! A very, very large—
Whoa! What is that?!
An... island?!
It's a bubble with a whole island inside it!
How pretty!
There's no mistake!
That's gotta be Roger's hidden answer!
Now, my friends! How will you
proceed to that treasure island?!
All right! Go, Franky!
Leave it to me, Cap'n!
This is why we have a secret weapon!
A secret weapon?!
Out of my way, shrimps.
Ooh!
The first ones to kick things off are the infamous Kid Pirates from the Worst Generation!
Their captain, Eustass "Captain" Kid, and his partner,
"Massacre Soldier" Killer, are in the game!
Now the Pirates Fest is heating up!
The hunt for the treasure of Gold Roger,
the Pirate King—
No! This is pretty much like a Treasure Race!
Now start!
Kid, you're gonna play along with this game?
A game, eh?
A-pa-pa!
Now! Pirates aiming for the
treasure are following Kid!
The On-Air Pirates are sailing rhythmically!
This is their captain, Scratchmen Apoo!
What's all the rush, yo?!
Ohh! And the Drake Pirates got ahead!
X Drake is closing in on Kid!
Red Flag and Sea Roar, huh?
And! With the only female captain in
the Worst Generation... the Bonney Pirates!
This is Bonney, the "Glutton"!
More pizzas!
The hell are you doin'?!
Please make way, young lady.
The Fallen Monk Pirates have cut in!
This is their captain... Urouge!
Ohh! What a merciless blast
from the Firetank Pirates!
It's Capone "Gang" Bege!
Can't beat me in numbers.
Next, the Hawkins Pirates follow!
Hey... Is this the time to be reading fortunes?!
We'll support Mistah Luffy with all we got!
I'm going to stand out the most!
Hey! Let me do the introductions, too!
The ones who are closing in
on the Worst Generation
are Bartolomeo the Cannibal
and White Horse Cavendish!
And! And...!
A bunch of other pirates, too.
Introduce us properly!
What's gonna happen in this Treasure Race?!
They're climbing neck-and-neck
up the Knock-Up Stream!
So that's where the treasure is?
I'll leave the ruckus at the center to you.
What?!
Report the situation via Transponder Snail.
Where are you going, Smoker?!
I'm taking this chance to sneak
into Festa's hideout.
I'm going straight for the one behind all this.
Sorry for the wait, guys!
This is the Thousand Sunny flying version!
Emperor Penguin Form!
So cool!
Now, let's go and catch up!
Stop right there, you damn rubber man!
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
Now, hand him over!
Oh, Buggy.
Ugh.
You guys ready?!
Coup de... Burst!
Buggyyyn!
Here we go!
Wh-Whoaaa!
Th-Th-This is incredible!
From rock bottom
they've shot up towards the top!
There's not a soul at sea
who doesn't know this guy!
The man with a 1.5 billion bounty on his head!
It’s Monkey D. Luffy!
With the Straw Hats joining the game,
this Treasure Race is heating up even more!
Straw Hat! I’m cheering for you!
Mistah Luffy!
Don't stand out more than me!
That's not fair, Straw Hat!
Eeeeek!
We're gonna blast right through!
Excellent.
Now, it's about time to get on with your plan.
The heck is that?!
The Straw Hat Pirates jumped
straight into the lead!
Way to make things interesting, Straw Hat.
Splashdown complete!
Thank goodness...
We got pretty far ahead, but make sure
you prepare for attacks from behind.
Franky, that was awesome!
'Course it was!
All right! Let’s zip right through this!
Zip through!
What's the matter?
Traffy!
Straw... Hat...
I need the first-aid kit!
What on earth happened?
You need to be treated immediately!
Don't need it. I'll be leaving right away.
You guys leave this island right this second.
Festa... is...
Talking about the host of the Pirates Fest?
Not just Festa.
They're plotting something bad.
I've managed to let my crew escape,
but this place will become a warzone.
Hey, hey, what's the deal all of a sudden?!
Wait, Traffy!
Traffy, you need to be resting!
Sorry for intruding. This is the matter
I've been investigating.
Where are you going in that condition?!
I'm gonna go pay them back.
Whoa! Those guys behind us
are already catchin' up!
This is bad! What'll we do?!
We're gonna keep going!
But we can't leave Traffy like that, either!
Chopper, look after him!
Got it!
Hey! I'm leaving!
Then I'll go, too.
"Not just Festa"
means there are parties engaging in deals
and conflicts behind the scenes.
If this festival is a trap, this isn't
only Traffy's problem.
Let me go investigate.
Then I'll be Robin's bodyguard!
If it's covert work, I shall accompany them.
Okay, got it!
Hey!
It's gettin' interesting.
You mean bad.
It could be connected to
the treasure, so be thorough.
Roger that, Nami!
Let's do it, Traffy!
Do what you want.
If we're splitting up, you can use that.
What're we gonna do?!
We're going to die!
Oh, but I'm already dead!
Mil Fleur!
You saved us, Robin.
If anything happens
call with this Transponder Snail!
Roger.
Let me treat you first.
No...
Let's hurry. We're going to the
underground of this island
to find Festa!
Let's go now! We're almost
to the treasure island!
Now! The pirate ships' close race
is reaching its climax!
I see the top!
Wh-What's gonna happen to us?!
Full speed ahead!
The top group has climbed all the
way up the Knock-Up Stream!
Countless pirate ships are
soaring through the air!
I've never seen anything like this!
And! The first to reach
the treasure island is...
...sure enough, the Straw Hat Pirates!
Whoa!
Wow! Wh-What's this?!
A giant galleon ship lays
on the treasure island!
And look at what's there!
There's a mountain of treasure!
The whole situation is getting crazy!
Whoa!
Mountain of treasure! A treasure ship!
Luffy!
The treasure's ours!
That treasure chest looks older and extra fishy.
I can smell the air of mystery
all the way from here!
Luffy! There's a small, old treasure
chest within the pile of treasure!
That's probably the Pirate King's treasure!
Got it!
All right! You guys go grab it!
You're going, too! What're you scared of?!
Don't be silly!
I'm a sniper. Assisting them is my role.
You're just being a chicken.
This is getting fun!
There's treasure!
Get the treasure!
Now, the treasure hunt race
has reached its final stage!
Go on ahead!
Got it!
You’re fightin' me.
Pirate Hunter!
Boom!
Straw Hat!
Who're you?!
We are sick 'n' tired of your craziness!
I'm gonna get that treasure!
See ya!
Just keep fighting each other, ya idiots!
Hey!
Are you gonna get in my way?
This is a race. You're supposed
to get in people's way.
Sounds like you wanna die.
Get outta my way!
Gum-Gum...
Elephant Gun!
Stop, Straw Hat!
This is becoming one heck of a race!
Who's gonna—
Huh?!
Who on earth is gonna win?!
It's an easy win with my troops!
Outta my way!
What a sight!
Why, you little...
Captain! Let's hurry!
Stealing, success rate... 40%...
Here we go, guys!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Impact Wolf!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Franky Radical Beam!
Move, move, move!
Gum-Gum... Gigant Pistol!
There it is!
Everybody's strong. This is fun!
Be quiet, you!
Treasure's more important than security.
Get him!
These dudes are crazy!
Knock him out!
Up ahead is his hideout. But watch out.
I was ambushed here earlier.
It stinks, Brook!
Please excuse me.
Be quiet!
I apologize.
It doesn't look like we can
go any further. Robin.
Okay.
Then I shall, too.
Don't worry, it won’t cause
you sponsors any trouble.
Everything's going smoothly.
Just as planned, we'll have 'em launch...
...a Buster Call on this island.
Hm? What's wrong?
What's the deal?!
As in that Buster Call?!
It's a large-scale Navy attack that
obliterates everything and everyone.
The whole island will be wiped off the map.
We know that! But why do that now?!
Not sure... but we need to let everyone know.
Why the hell are you bastards here?!
It's quite rude of you to suddenly attack.
Brook, watch out!
A Sea Prism Stone is built into it!
That's right.
The stone emits the same energy as the sea.
Any Devil Fruit power-user that
touches this becomes helpless.
I'll stop him here. You guys get to Luffy!
You think I'd let you?!
Take Robin with you and run!
I don't think so!
Leave her the hell alone!
Haki, huh?
What are you all up to?
That's our line!
Behold! This is a close race!
And many pirates are dropping out!
Who is gonna get their hands on the treasure?!
Out of my way!
Get out of mine.
I got it!
The Pirate King's treasure is all mine!
That damn clown!
Buggy! The treasure's mine!
You damn rubber man!
Let's get out of here!
I don't think so!
Seize that guy! Get the treasure!
Yes, sir!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
This treasure is mine!
It's Captain Roger's treasure.
It must be something incredi—
What?! Wait a sec, this is...
The first one to grab the treasure chest was
one of the Seven Warlords, the Genius Jester Buggy!
What could be in the—
What the heck?!
What's going on?!
The bubble!
I'm falling!
My treasure!
What the hell is going on?!
Hang on, Sunny!
Luffy!
I don't wanna die yet!
His "Iron Arm" hasn't changed.
The immense power trained
for 20 years within prison.
Make sure it gets delivered!
You okay, Kid?!
High Priest! Please hang on!
This is crazy...
Captain!
Relax, I don't see any shadows of death.
What the heck happened?!
Hang in there!
I thought I was dead!
Captain Buggy!
All right! I did it! This is the Pirate King's—
This is... Is this really...?!
A galleon ship suddenly flew over
to the island and destroyed it!
And where did the Pirate King's treasure go?!
Dammit, who the hell did that?!
Kid.
What?!
You're kidding me...
That's...
Usopp!
This sea is a battlefield.
Die.
What the hell are you doin'?!
Luffy!
You bastard!
You must be the one who attacked Traffy!
Oh? You're pretty tough.
This is looking awfully bad!
Who the hell is he?
Thought I was dead!
Oh, you're alive.
'Course I'm alive!
Dammit! I dropped the treasure!
Who's responsible?!
That's...
You know him?
Y-Yeah... Just like me, he used to be
a member of the Roger Pirates...
His name is Douglas Bullet.
He was a monster that was as strong as Rayleigh back then.
Rayleigh? You mean the
Pirate King's right-hand man?!
Now, let's begin.
Wh-What was that?!
Wha...? Hey...
Emergency!
No way! This festival was supposed
to be a complete secret!
Hey, Festa! What happened to
your information control, huh?!
Hey... Don't tell me..
I-I-It's a huge Navy fleet!
Run!
Wait for me!
Who's the damn snitch?!
The first fleet of Navy warships has
arrived as planned to the open sea.
A message from the Navy fleet.
"Siege complete. We appreciate
your cooperation."
Vice Admiral Momonga, eh?
Now, what'cha gonna do, pirates?
Face them... or run from them?
Dammit! We were set up by Festa!
He sold us out to the Navy!
Wha—
Hey, wait for me!
I see no openings.
It's not just the treasure he's after?
Hey, you.
You messed with my friend.
You'd better be ready to deal with me.
Friend?
You mean this piece of scum who
couldn't protect a single treasure?
I hear the Worst Generation is strong.
If you all want this treasure...
...come at me.
Conqueror's Haki!
Truly a demon...
This is whack!
Bring it on!
What's the matter, Worst Generation?
Too scared to move?
You're fighting... me!
Zoro!
We'll get in touch with Sanji
and the others and prepare to escape!
It won't be easy getting through
that many warships!
We need a plan!
Leave Usopp to me!
You take care of the Sunny!
Roger that!
Sirs and madam!
Please let us help you, too!
Ugh! What is that?
You guys!
All right! Come with me!
Zoro! Wrong way!
A miracle?!
Mistah Zoro! You're the man!
I've come for you, too! Be grateful!
Run before you get dragged in!
Ya damn old rookie! Don't get excited
just because you're out of your coop!
Come.
I'll start with you guys.
The stage is set.
There's a little over ten minutes left.
You're called "Demon Heir."
Now, let me see your power.
Ring, ring, ring...
Did something happen to Usopp?
Even the Navy snuck in. What's going on?
Long time no see...
Miss All Sunday.
You're Crocodile!
Color me surprised.
If you're going after it, too, then that treasure...
...must be something that
could shake the very world.
You are perceptive.
Douglas Bullet is secretly involved with this festival.
The pirate who caused that massacre?!
The Tragedy of Galzburg?
His power is a bit of a pain.
What do you want from me?
Not you...
I have business with you.
I have a plan. Tag along.
What're ya up to, snoopin'
around in a place like this?!
Back at you!
A Buster Call?! Are you guys insane?!
Huh? What're you talking about?!
Ring, ring, ring...
Click.
Smoker! It's an emergency!
Bullet has appeared and taken the treasure!
He's destroyed the island and is about
to engage in battle with the Straw Hats!
So he's making his move now.
Captain! Where are you going?!
I'm clearing out, of course!
You're clearing out all those warships?!
Wow, Captain Buggy!
How positive can they be?
Just him alone is worse
than facing a Navy fleet.
It's best not to get involved...
...even if that treasure happened to be the One Piece.
You guys stay out of my way!
I'm fighting him! And you're next, Straw Hat!
I'm comin' if you aren't.
Demon Face!
Boom!
Wha—
The hell?
How pathetic! I'll finish you off
by turning you into a brat!
Gum-Gum...
Elephant Gun!
Why, you!
Don't get in my way!
Y'all are in my way!
Big Father!
Wow!
Boom, boom!
Retribution!
Go to hell!
Gum-Gum...
Red Hawk!
Stop butting in, you guys!
That's my line!
Not bad.
But it's not enough!
Training, tactics, determination...
You lack all of 'em.
I'll show you what real,
refined power looks like!
You bastard! What're you after?!
To be the world's strongest!
This is a nice, tense atmosphere.
Don't die on me too easily.
Before Luffy and Usopp come back,
I'll reduce the number of warships
and make a path!
You look after the ship!
Mistah Zoro entrusted me with a mission!
Leave it to me! I'll protect it with my life!
Now... How do we open up a path?
Aiyeeee! It's Purple Tiger!
The admiral himself!
I've come to seek on my own
what kind of justice this battle holds.
Follow Admiral Purple Tiger!
Seize all the pirates!
What do you guys want?!
Straw Hats! You must...
Please save us!
As if! Go fight yourself!
I smell Robin!
Robin!
Everyone!
I'm glad you're safe!
Thank you.
Where's he?
Well... He was suddenly alarmed
and took off somewhere.
I wonder what that was all about.
Hey, Robin, where's Law?
About that...
All right, let's split into two teams.
Chopper and Brook,
you guys go back and tell Luffy
and the others about the Buster Call.
Okay.
Robin, you come with me.
All right.
Listen, everyone! Luffy will
definitely get that treasure.
We trust in that and act accordingly.
Got it!
He's playin' around...
This is the power of the man who'll
become the Pirate King.
If your goal is to become
the Pirate King,
then I refuse to lose to you!
Gear 4:
Snake-Man!
Using your Devil Fruit power
and a full blast of Haki?
You won't last long like that.
Yeah, here goes!
Run! Python!
Gum-Gum...
Jet Culverin!
Black Mamba!
No wonder you've got a 1.5 billion bounty.
You've got some spunk!
What's the matter?! Finished already?!
Yeah! This'll finish you!
Gum-Gum...
Gimme your best shot! Straw Hat!
Show me your true power!
...King Cobra!
"Former crew member of
Pirate King overwhelmed
by the fifth Emperor, Straw Hat Luffy!"
This'll make a fine story!
Countin' on ya. This party's
just getting started.
Standby!
Brachio head! Change!
Iron Pirate!
General Franky!
Run!
Don't let them escape!
What're you all tryin' to do
teamin' up with that guy?!
That is beyond the extent of my knowledge.
Who knows whether the decision to start this
war will turn out to be worthwhile or not.
"War," you said?!
Barrier Bulls!
Blade of Beauty... Saint-Exupéry!
You think you can defeat me?!
Get 'em, Boss!
Take this! Slow-Slow Bea—
Shut the hell up!
Stop the ship!
You!
Our captain himself dove onto the front lines!
Are there only idiots?
Everyone, here goes!
Zeus Breeze Tempo!
Not bad, Straw Hat.
I like strong guys.
But you and your men...
I'll kill you all
in order to become the strongest!
Go be the strongest someplace else!
You'd better not lay another hand on my friends!
You make me sick.
This sea is a battlefield!
Power is everything!
What's that?!
This is my ship, the Catapult.
It's filled with all sorts of weapons and iron.
Union Armada!
A Devil Fruit power...
I am a combinable man
who ate the Clank-Clank Fruit!
I can combine all kinds of objects
and transform them.
In addition to my own strength,
I've got the ultimate ability!
On top of that strength,
he's a Devil Fruit power-user?
What's going to happen?
The weak can't survive in this sea...
just like that long nose from earlier.
Cut off any useless men, Straw Hat.
How can you say that?!
Then who would I have parties with?!
Are you an idiot?!
The hopeless idiot here is you!
Your so-called "friends" are just a weakness.
Even that monster geezer Whitebeard
died for his own men.
Same with Roger!
Those who died are all losers!
That's the limit of those
who cling to their "friends."
My strength exists only for me and my victory!
I won't lose to someone like that!
If you want to talk big,
why don't you take this back, kid?!
I'll tell you all before you die...
This really is Roger's treasure!
Inside this...
...is the One Piece!
One... Piece...
It ends here. Now, let me see you struggle!
Gravity Blade! Raging Tiger
1,080-Pound Phoenix!
Ultra Tiger Hunt!
We're gonna escape before
the rest of the Navy gets here!
Don't tell me...
A Warlord... What a pain...
Whatever. Pacifistas! Get the pirates!
Negative Hollow!
I'm sorry to have been born.
You're not very cute.
What's that?!
Who on earth
is blocking my path with a pirate ship?!
Hey, hey, isn't that...?
The Warlord and Pirate Empress...
Boa Hancock!
Whatever I do, the world will
always forgive my actions.
Because I am beautiful.
If they're our allies, we have
nothing to fear! Go, Warlords!
Silence! Where's Luffy?!
Look, wow!
Three current Warlords are here!
Stupid idiots! I ain't staying for this!
Even nine lives wouldn't be enough!
See ya!
The admirals and the Warlords?!
You tryin' to start a war or something?
Close, but not quite.
As expected from the Navy...
They want that treasure after all, eh?
It's over, you brats!
Kid!
This will teach you!
You guys!
Killer!
You bastard!
People can only reach this level on their own.
And on this level, the weak lose everything.
Only one person, the strongest one,
can obtain everything this sea has to offer.
An Eternal Pose to Laugh Tale?!
Such a thing exists?! It's a huge
scoop that'll flip the world!
That's right.
The treasure is a guide to the island Laugh Tale,
where the One Piece sleeps.
The shortcut to becoming the Pirate King
that dumb Roger and his
crew buried in darkness...
I found it! And with this,
I'll change the times.
I'll spark a festival of madness!
Die.
You're still fighting me!
What's all this?
Not only are you weak, but stupid, too, eh?
My captain is risking his life for me!
I can't be nappin' here!
The weaker the dog is, the stupider
he is, and the more he barks.
Festivals equal "madness."
We will plunge...
..the world into madness like no other.
Into a stampede!
We'll show ya...
Hmm... What a sight it's becoming...
Admiral! I have a report, sir!
So it came out... The Pirate King's treasure...
Seize the pirates!
We came all the way here! We ain't going down!
One! Two! Django!
Kimono Sleeve Cage!
Lock!
Don't bother with the shrimps!
We'll get Bullet!
Gimme a hand, Hina!
Smoker! Why are you dressed like that?!
Smoker!
What on earth is going on?!
HQ is keeping somethin' from us!
What?
Depending on what Roger’s treasure is,
the higher-ups may make an insane decision.
You're acting on your own again?!
Move it, Navy!
Fulfill your duty here!
No need to tell me.
Outta the way!
What the hell?!
You pirates are all... under arrest!
Buggyyyn!
You're...
What're you doin', ya flashy idiot?!
Crap! The Navy!
Wait. I'm Buggy, a Warlord!
What do you think you're doing?!
Y-You! You looked inside that
treasure chest, didn't you?!
What?!
What was the treasure?!
Who cares about that right now?!
What's important right now is our own lives!
What's the treasure?! Spit it out! Now!
I can't breathe...!
Smoker?!
Stop, I got it! I'll talk, I'll talk!
It's an Eternal Pose!
An Eternal Pose to Laugh Tale!
Say what?!
Charge! Seize the pirates!
It seems that the course of the war is
about to turn. Let us hold off our battle.
Huh?!
This is a parting gift.
Hold it right there!
What the hell?!
A meteor?!
Retreat! Retreat!
That's too huge!
The nine mountains and eight seas
constitute one world!
A thousand of them form a small chiliocosm!
And when I gather and cube that chiliocosm,
there's nothing I can't cut!
Three-Sword Style Secret Art:
The Billion-fold World...
Trichiliocosm!
Mistah Zoro!
Will I make it?!
Whaaaaat?!
Anything beyond this is outside of my contract.
Let's go, Ghost Girl.
Don't order me around!
And next time you decide to
slice a meteor, tell me first!
That scared me.
We have to hurry!
Luffy! Where are you?!
Usopp! Where are you?!
Ready! Fire!
It's time, Navy.
Now... it's showtime!
Pull out your soldiers and ships now!
He's trying to gather us and—
Too late!
Have a good taste of my awakened powers!
What's that?!
Though it's rare, Devil Fruit
powers sometimes awaken
and start affecting things other
than the users themselves.
What's that?!
What's going on?!
He's targeting the ships!
It's enormous!
What now?!
What?! Don't tell me...
He's trying to confine us on the island!
Luffy!
What're you gonna do now, Navy?
You’ve got only one choice!
Die...
The vice admirals are down in one hit?!
Run!
A mountain's gonna drop!
Ultimate... Fist!
The island split!
Twenty-four years ago,
I lost to the Navy and was imprisoned
in Impel Down. I asked myself then,
"How can I obtain power so overwhelming
that I'll never lose again?
How can I surpass Roger and
become the world's strongest?"
Fleet Admiral! The Eternal Pose
to the One Piece is right here!
Come and defeat me just like back then!
The treasure is there, eh?
What the heck's going on?!
To think that he's swallowed hundreds of
pirate ships and warships with his awakened-power...
The biggest problem is that Haki.
He's coated that gigantic body
with powerful Armament Haki.
What tremendous power...
At this rate...
He's a Devil Fruit power-user... which means...
If Luffy beats that guy,
this wall should go away!
Then we'll have to...
Uncle! What the hell's going on?!
Bullet still has the Pirate King's treasure!
And he has swallowed our warships and—
Click.
He didn't have to tell me. I can see it.
A call from the fleet admiral, sir!
I see... He's awakened, eh?
So he's built up that much power...
Borsalino.
Troublemakers are on the move, too.
Evil must be eradicated
thoroughly and completely.
He asked for it.
Commence the Buster Call!
Marvelous!
You sure are one hell of a guy, Bullet!
I was right to bet the rest of my life on you.
That bastard Roger launched
the best festival called
the "Dawn of the Great Pirate Era."
Even I, the Festival Master,
had no way to top that.
But... with you, I can create a new era.
I can destroy this stupid era.
I’ll surpass that bastard Roger completely!
C'mon, I know you can do better!
I expect more from your new fleet admiral!
He's really done it!
A Buster Call is a symbol
of the World Government.
And the great pirate Douglas Bullet
is trying to surpass it all by himself!
What an epic revenge battle! It's a huge scoop!
Now... All you underground trash...
With the key to the One Piece,
the Eternal Pose to Laugh Tale, in our hands,
we are...
...going to kill you and all the pirates!
S-Say what?!
What's he saying?!
Explain!
The era of Gold Roger will come to an end.
The Great Pirate Era that shook up
the world is now in the past!
From here on, I, Buena Festa, will create
the hysteria of a new grand war
that will rock the entire world!
If you want the treasure, take it!
Steal it from us!
Everything the world has
to offer is within our hands!
Damn you!
Are you insane?!
Anger is also...
...a form of hysteria.
See this, Roger?
I will end this dull era of treasure
hunting that you started.
The treasure is right here!
They'll fight over it and shed blood!
A festival in which only the strong win!
That's the new era I will create!
A full-scale war with us, the Navy.
And a declaration of war
on all the world's pirates.
It appears that their goal is to destroy the
order of this sea and plunge the world into a state of war.
The pirate, Douglas Bullet.
A war orphan born in the Grand Line's
militarist nation "Galzburg."
While young, he became a soldier
so great that he was called a hero.
However, he was betrayed by
the military that trained him.
That distress pushed Bullet into inciting a wide-scale
massacre that put an end to the nation itself.
After that, he took to the sea and clashed
with Gold Roger, the Pirate King
but for some reason, he joined Roger's crew
and further increased his notoriety.
Due to his brutality, Sengoku,
the admiral at the time—
Betrayed by grownups...
and betrayed by friends...
His lonesome upbringing made him
continue to fight without trusting others.
But Roger taught him defeat and took him in.
Soon, Bullet was called the "Demon Heir,"
carrying on Roger's strength.
Navy
He continued to fight, hoping to surpass him...
...but then Roger died.
Bullet lost his way and began
to destroy everything in sight.
He was a monster that lost
his goal of beating Roger.
We couldn't let him run wild,
so we ordered a Buster Call just to capture him.
We cannot sympathize with him.
We must prevent a war that will involve
the entire world at all costs.
You're right...
We must shed a lot of blood one more
time to put an end to him for good.
Or is there another way to confront
him head-on, just as Roger did?
See that, Luffy?
That bastard...
Faced with my power, he turned tail and ran.
Let's let him go...
...for today...
Don't die, Luffy!
Our journey... can't possibly...
...end here!
We can't let it end... like this!
Luffy is gonna become the Pirate King!
The Chill of the Underworld, Soul Solid!
Usopp!
You okay?!
This is bad.
I'll treat you right away!
Treat... Luffy first...
He lost... too much blood...
But, Usopp! You're also—
Please!
Okay.
Robin, let's hurry!
This place won't last long!
I found it! If we have this—
Attention!
A message from Admiral Yellow Monkey!
All units pull out!
He ordered a complete withdrawal
within five minutes!
Return immediately to the remaining ships!
Pull out!
Quickly! Return to the ships! Pull out!
What's going on?! Does he see the situation?!
Please hurry and return to the ships!
Admiral Yellow Monkey ordered a Buster Call!
Say what?!
The admiral's second fleet is on standby at sea
and will begin a barrage of cannon fire in five minutes!
In five minutes?!
You will die if you stay!
Please evacuate immediately
to the remaining ships!
Is he insane?!
Attention! Pull out completely
within five minutes!
Retreat! Pull out!
Five minutes isn't enough to reach the ships!
What's going on?! Hurry!
D-Don't push!
Finally...
A Buster Call is used to annihilate everything.
I'll completely crush it and
rise to the world's strongest!
You are next, Four Emperors!
Roger!
Smoker! We must evacuate now!
Go on ahead.
What?! I'll stay, too!
I can still fight as well!
M-Me, too.
Such a fool...
Huh?! Hina! Let me go
Vice Admiral Smoker!
Smoker!
If I take back that treasure from Bullet,
I can stop this stupid operation that
wipes out everyone, including our men.
You rotten pirate!
You think you can do whatever you want?!
Heat Haze!
I agree that we should take him down, Navy man.
But you think you can win all on your own?
You're from the Revolutionary Army!
If I remember right, you're Straw Hat's...
You know Luffy? Take it easy on him.
He's my little brother.
Don't interfere!
Retreat!
Hurry! Pull out!
Hey, look at the Navy. They're panicking.
Miss Nami!
What should we do?!
Luffy and the others will definitely come back!
Just believe in them and
think of what you can do now!
Miss Nami is so cool!
Just get a move on already!
Yes, ma'am!
Oh, Luffy, I'm worried...
Is there some kind of a clue?
Luffy's clothes?!
Luffy! Is it you, Luffy?! Hang in there!
Luffy!
Huh?
Who the hell are you?!
Chopper... Brook...
Luffy! You're awake!
We found you and Usopp half-dead
after he dragged you out of there!
What on earth happened?!
We heard their plan!
At this rate, a Buster Call will
be carried out on this island.
That guy's gotten huge and
is going wild with crazy powers.
And we still haven't gotten
a hold of the others...
Thanks, Chopper. I'm fine now.
What?
But, Luffy...
You guys head on back to the Sunny.
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
L-Luffy...
Usopp?!
Luffy...
Usopp! You saved me, thanks!
I almost got—
I'm sorry!
When it's... really important...
...I'm... useless!
I'm not strong enough at all!
Dammit!
I'm sorry... everyone!
Usopp!
Hang in there!
Hey, don't speak anymore!
Chopper, take care of Usopp.
Huh? Luffy?!
Hang in there, Usopp.
You haven't lost to him yet!
Bullet!
Considering our powers,
this fight will never end!
I don't have time to be dealin' with you!
You two! Get outta the way!
Thank you for leading the way.
Do you two know Luffy's whereabouts?!
Warlords!
What the hell?!
What are all of you guys doing here?!
Don't get so worked up.
I just want to scare him
out of his wits, that's all.
Huh?!
I've got business with the
mastermind of this festival.
Hey, hey! What're ya wastin'
time for, ya big morons?!
We'll be killed if we don't escape right away!
All of you!
What are you rambling on about?!
I asked you about Luffy's whereabouts!
What's your damage?! Get your foot off of me!
All of you, stop interfering!
We're out of time!
So our available forces are
not a unified front, eh?
Huh?!
All of you, listen to me
if you don't want to die.
I got a plan to drag him out of his giant body.
Ya flashy idiot!
We gotta run right away because we don't wanna die!
Are ya stup—
My strength... Dammit...
You've got a Sea Prism Stone?
Continue.
We'll only get one shot.
His punch can split the island.
If we fail, we die.
You're asking me to risk my life
over some pirate's dumb idea?!
You gotta be kidding!
But there's no other way.
It's out of the question!
Is that...?
Luffy!
Bullet!
So you are alive, Straw Hat...
That's what I'm talking about!
Gum-Gum...
Kong Gun!
The hell are ya doin'?!
Luffy!
Luffy! I wanted to see you!
That was a strong punch.
Are you hurt anywhere?!
Hancock! Long time no see!
How ya been?
He's worried about me more than himself!
I can die happy!
Oh, Traffy! Glad you're okay!
No need to worry about me.
Straw Hatter, I got a plan to drag him out.
Really? Let's do it!
Hey! I'm not done explaining it yet!
Sabo! Smokey!
Yo, Luffy!
All right, let's do it!
Straw Hatter! You could die if we fail!
Don't worry.
All of us here will do it together, right?
Then it'll definitely work!
I'll leave the details to you, Traffy.
I just wanna...
...defeat him!
Dammit! All right, fine!
I will follow you to the ends of the earth.
Guess there's no time to hesitate...
Let's do it!
The hell is that?!
Pirates, the Navy, Warlords,
and the Revolutionary Army?!
It'll take a lot more than a ragtag group
like that to change things!
Wait! Straw Hatter!
Luffy!
Bullet!
That idiot! He didn't even hear the plan!
So, what's the plan?
Bullet's abnormal Haki is the problem,
but I'll use my powers to
create a crack in his Haki.
You guys attack that and whittle down his body.
Then what?
The fewer things he controls,
the weaker he gets.
So we'll finish him off together
before he starts absorbing them again.
I can make the crack only once.
Why do I have to team up with these idiots?!
Gum-Gum...
You'll need more than pluck to beat me, kid!
Luffy!
That idiot! Does he ever learn?!
Dammit! He really is strong!
I can't beat him this way!
Then I'll...
You're an insignificant bunch, but fine by me.
The Navy, pirates... anyone who
dares to stand against me,
I will eradicate every last one of them!
Not even Roger could do that.
Then all will know...
...that I'm the world's strongest!
Scatter!
Follow Straw Hatter!
When I use my power, that's the sign!
I'm counting on you, Luffy's friend!
I ain't his friend!
You sure this is really gonna work?
You're taking your sweet-ass time,
you damn useless kids.
As we planned, I'll provoke his
transformation. And that's when—
Hey!
Not just once, but twice...
How dare you strike my beloved!
Unforgivable! This is unforgivable!
Damn! Every last one of 'em!
You'll die here!
Perfume Femur Magna!
His body is so tough!
I'll crush all of you in one blow!
Empresser! Good work!
Idiot!
Ground Death!
Sables!
Crocodile?!
How many decades has it been, ya heap of junk?!
Interesting! You can die here, too!
Room!
Chambres!
What?!
How pathetic.
The real fight starts here!
This is the only thing that
can surpass his power!
A petty trick like this won't stop me!
I'll just absorb all the debris
and coat myself with Haki.
That'll be the end for you!
There it is!
Now, sailor! Let's go!
Don't order me around!
White Blow!
Burning Dragon Claw Fist!
Flame Dragon King!
What?!
All right!
You little!
C'mon, don't be so angry.
You're wasting your time!
Ow, ow, ow... dammit!
The hell was all that about?
Oh, yeah! Straw Hat!
That damn rubber man!
How dare he mess with me!
Who does he think I am?!
I'm an almighty Warlord!
I'll find him and beat the crap out of—
What the hell is this?! Give me a break!
I can't die yet! I climbed all the
way up to become a Warlord!
The Great Buggy's legend has just begun!
I can't let my life end in
a place like this, dammit!
But, well, it was a pretty fun life.
Momma, thank you for
bringing me into this world.
Wait, I ain't dead yet!
What am I, a flashy idiot?!
Oh, yeah! I have my famous weapon!
Special attack! Muggy Ball!
What?!
Cipher Pol... The government's dogs!
How'd you like that taste
of my incredible power?!
The hell's going on?!
He's the one they said carried on Roger's strength!
Incredible... But I bet
it won't end this easily!
Yeah, but Luffy will be okay.
Let's hurry back to the Sunny.
Robin! Sorry, but go on ahead without me!
What?
You think you've cornered me like this?!
Crap! Run!
Even with one arm gone...
I'm sorry!
...this is enough to kill you all!
Dammit! It failed!
Not yet! Let's all attack him
one more time to trim him down!
So that Luffy can finish him off!
Straw Hatter?!
That brat...!
Luffy!
Follow Straw Hatter!
What's this?!
Bleh! That was close!
There's no way I'm stayin' for this!
Idiots! I'll just repel it, that's all!
Then how's this?!
Huh?
I can't die in a place...
like this!
How insolent!
I'll crush... everything!
The hell's going on?!
He can move in that state?!
Bullet!
This will...
...beat you for sure!
You’re just a ragtag bunch of weaklings!
Don't get so carried away!
Gum-Gum...
King, King...
Ultimate Fist!
King Kong Gun!
What?!
Lil' brat!
Nice try!
Luffy!
If you had just a bit more strength,
you would have won!
Wha...?! What the hell?!
What's going on?!
My special... Green Star: Snake Fireworks...
They're set off by a strong impact.
Assisting friends... is the role of the sniper.
Ahhhhh! Bullet!
Don't tell me my plans will be ruined
by a bunch of brats like them!
He's finally out!
I'll take that treasure.
Don't get in...
our captain's way!
Straw Hat!
Our duel starts now!
You got some guts!
Let's see who's stronger with a fistfight!
You're insanely strong!
But I'm gonna surpass you!
So that I can protect...
...what's important!
Don't make me laugh!
This sea is a battlefield!
A firm determination to believe only
in yourself and to survive alone...
That is the true source of ultimate power!
I wield that power!
I am the world's strongest man!
I am...
the Pirate King!
The Pirate King is nothing like that!
Gum-Gum...
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
King Kong...
The Strongest...
Gatling Gun!
Strike!
I can continue to win in this sea,
because I'm alone!
The world's strongest is me!
Shut up!
There isn't a single person
who lives in these seas alone!
So strong....
But someday, I swear I'll defeat you
and become the world's strongest man...
Roger!
You're strong.
I'll take you on anytime, Bullet.
We're going to gather up all our dreams
I'm the man who's gonna be the Pirate King!
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket, and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on the cruise!
We are!
We're going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket, and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on the cruise!
Luffy!
Are you all right?!
I got the treasure!
We are!
What?
We win!
We are!
This can't be... happening...
What is that, Luffy?
It's the Pirate King's treasure.
I don't know what's inside, though.
What's this?
Luffy! This is...
an Eternal Pose to Laugh Tale!
To Laugh Tale?
That's right! If you have this...
Luffy?
Hand that over, Straw Hat!
What the hell... are you doin'?!
I don't...
need this!
You're insane, Straw Hatter...
Luffy!
The Buster Call can't be stopped now!
It's my parting gift to you! Burn to ashes!
We've been watching all this time.
Festival Master...
No, the Monstrous Warmonger,
Buena Festa.
The Revolutionary Army's No. 2...
I never imagined that those guys would team up.
Was that your idea?
It was no one's.
Luffy just somehow inspired us to band together.
Fire Fist!
Straw Hat Luffy...
He draws enemies and allies together
and turns it into strong power...
He's got the potential...
to be the next Pirate King and start a new era...
I guess I teamed up with the wrong man.
Don't worry, he would never team up with you.
Thanks to Robin's map, we figured
out an escape route, but...
With the Buster Call...
...our path will be blocked!
So many of 'em!
We're like rats in a trap!
I'm gonna sink that fleet!
All of you... stay outta my way!
Those guys...
Franky! Let's go, too!
Let's go, Sunny!
Hey, you.
Can you visualize this guy?
It's no use! We're getting blocked!
Bring it on. We'll bust through!
Hey! No way!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel.
Crap! It's Yellow Monkey!
Fire Fist!
A message from Vice Admiral Smoker!
Hmm?
"Pirate King's treasure
destroyed by Straw Hat Luffy!
Many marines still on island!
Request immediate stop of Buster Call!
Repeat! Request immediate stop of Buster Call!"
A wall of flames?!
It's a path of fire!
We can escape now! Luffy!
See ya, Luffy.
Now's our chance, guys! Let's go!
Yeah!
We're setting sail on the open seas once again
Flying a flag painted with our ambition
Beyond the unknown lies ever more wonder
We'll carve a path to our intertwined future
Taking the easy way wouldn't be nearly as fun
So we'll keep taking the adventurous path!
Even when restless seas remind us of our insignificance
We won't shed a single tear until we make it through
Our blazing red flame won't ever be torn away!
As long as we draw breath, until we've made it through
We'll find the treasure we're looking for
When we realise the happiness we've found
It becomes our pride and joy
All our myriad dreams are coming together as one
Our adventure's just getting started
These intensifying feelings get our blood pumping
There may be times where we resent our fates
But even still
We'll never forget the warmth we felt every day
We've got friends we want to have the strength to be able to protect
So we can't hesitate, we have to make sure our aim is true
Be it a cruel twist of fate or the whirling seas
Each new day builds on top of all those before it
On that fateful morning we steeled our resolve
We won't shed a single tear until we make it through
Our blazing red flame won't ever be torn away!
It's still waiting for us there
As long as we draw breath, until we've made it through
We'll find the treasure we're looking for
When we realise the happiness we've found
It becomes our pride and joy
All our myriad dreams are coming together as one
Our adventure's just getting started
These intensifying feelings get our blood pumping
There may be times where we resent our fates
But even still
Even if we have to fight the entire world
We'll have each other's backs
We're free to choose, but there's a tomorrow we've just gotta see
So we can't hesitate, we have to make sure our aim is true
Let's go see (Hey!!) the places we've yet to see
Let's go see (Hey!!) all the friends we've yet to meet
Let's go see (Hey!!), Let's go see (Hey!!), Let's go see (Hey!!) more and more
Let's meet up (Hey!!) in our beloved hometown
Let's meet up (Hey!!) and party on together like we used to
Let's meet up (Hey!!) Let's meet up (Hey!!) where no-one's charted yet
What kind of joke is this?!
You recorded it to an Eternal Pose?!
We did it just in case!
If we ever need it again...
"Just in case”? We won't.
Our journey's over now.
It's not the kind of treasure that
someone who'd rely on this can obtain.
Don't you agree?
Ahh! Captain! We can't go back now!
We were too early.
The One Piece, huh?
Wonder who'll find it.
Why, my son, obviously!
You don't have one.
I'm gonna have one soon!
Whaaaat?!
You broke the Eternal Pose to Laugh Tale?!
Yeah.
What are you doing?! Are you stupid or what?!
That could've been a shortcut to the One Piece!
Well, knowing you, I thought you'd do that!
That was our big chance.
There are lots more awesome
adventures out there waiting for us!
If we took a shortcut,
we'd miss out on them all!
All right, you guys!
Let's set sail for our next adventure!
Yeah!