Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece...
head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and on their way
to the next stage—the New World—
they reached Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level, when...
The pirate boy with a straw hat!
Throw him out of this country!
A human with a straw hat on...
At Straw Hat Luffy's hands...
at his hands... Fishman Island will be...
destroyed!!
The King of Fishman Island
Neptune, the God of the Sea!
Guys! Hurry up-chin!
Quiet! Stay quiet!
We're in trouble if they notice.
Now is the chance!
Get on the ship-chin!
Everybody, grab an oar and be ready!
Fishman District, Noah
Hurry up! They'll come after us at any minute!
I'll never return to Fishman Island! Hurry up and cross the Red Line!
Damn! The Mermaid Cafe of my dreams!
I wanted to take one look at the beautiful Mermaids!
Let it go, you idiots!
Shut your mouths and just keep rowing!
Damn! What a disaster!
As soon as we got away from the sleeping Kraken,
and got 10,000 meters deep,
South Blue Pirate
"Crab-Hand" Gyro
we were surrounded by so many sea monsters.
And we couldn't even fight back!
Enlist under the Fishmen's banner or die?
I had no choice but to enlist under their banner for a while!
How absurd!
Why do we humans have to enlist under the Fishmen's banner?!
Oh, we're moving away from the Mermaid Cafe!
Stop crying and let's go, guys! We're lucky to even be alive!
Huh? They escaped?
Yes, Boss.
As soon as my back was turned.
Did they escape again-dosun?
They never learn, do they-dosun?
Humans always escape.
Should I bite off their flesh?
What a pain in the butt-ch!
No problem!
We can make them into an example as always.
New Fishman Pirates, Captain Hody Jones
Then I'll go get them-ch!
No, you won't, Ikaros.
Much, understood!
I'll go!
Huh?
Get the bubble ready!
You can't take that much at once!
That's the power drug!
Now here we are!
This is my house!
It's huge!
Welcome home, Master-sama!
Hey, that's Monsieur Pappagu!
You mean that really famous guy?!
Wow! Is it really him?
Oh, you're popular, huh?
Yeah! Are you guys surprised?!
When I'm in the water, I'm just...
a fashionable starfish, but...
on Fishman Island, I'm the president
and a very popular designer of Criminal Co.
The brand is known all over the world now
and we have stores in many countries! Even the famous Doskoi Panda is—
Oh, look over there!
What's that?
Are you listening, Straw?!
The first floor is a Criminal store.
Really?
Camie... Camie...
Let's go there!
Uh-huh!
Hey!
Listen to my story...
Whoa, Miss, that's impossible!
What is it?
The shop assistant sounds troubled.
A complaint?
As I said, the clothes here are too expensive!
They're cute but...
That must be...
So let's make it 10,000 berries.
That's too cruel, Miss!
It's less than half price!
It's her as I thought.
Hey, Nami!
Luffy!
Nami-chin!
Camie!
It's been a while!
How are you?!
Fine!
Hey, what's going on?
Oh, Monsieur Pappagu,
you came at the right time!
We have a troublesome customer.
Hey, so you own this store, huh?
Why is everything so expensive? Are you ripping me off?
Monsieur!
Well, that's what they call brand equity because I'm a popular designer...
Give me a discount!
No, you...
We're friends, aren't we?
I owe you guys big time from two years ago!
It's all free!
Take as much as you want!
Free?! Really?!
Guys! Show no mercy!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Monsieur! They took everything!
You're so merciless!
I'm happy for you, guys!
Oh? What is it?
Something's going on outside the store.
Monsieur! Th-This is serious!
What is it?
I-I-It's him!
Him?
It's him!
Look! There in the air...
He came from the palace!
Jamon! Jamon!
Jamon! Jamon! Jamon!
What is it?
A whale?
Why did he come down to the lower world?
This is the first time I've seen him in person!
What's this about?
He doesn't even have guards.
This can't be happening! He's never travelled like this!
Something wrong with the kingdom?
He doesn't bother coming down here
unless there is a problem!
Who is that old man?
Idiot, don't you know who he is? That man is...
the king of Fishman Island's Ryugu Kingdom—
Neptune-sama!
King of the Ryugu Kingdom
Neptune, God of the Sea
Neptune!
Whale!
Hoe (Pet Whale)
That's a big Merman there...
I prefer Mermaids...
Cut it out, guys!
He's a very hairy old man!
That's rude!
Get down on your knees now!
The whale's cute!
He came to see those humans?
He personally came for that?
Hey, Megalo!
Are you sure that it was these people-jamon?
Oh? We saw that shark in the water!
Yeah, the one with clothes!
He had been captured by Surume!
You Straw Hat people.
Wh-What do you want?
I'm going to...
invite you to Ryugu Palace-jamon!
What?!
Ryu-Ryu-Ryu-Ryu-Ryu-Ryugu Palace!
Ryugu Palace?
Ryugu Kingdom, Coral Hill
Madame Sharley's house
Good! Your pulse is getting back to normal.
You should be fine now.
You have to thank those two for donating blood.
Those two...
It's okay, silly!
If you want, we can give you more, silly!
I'm grateful, but I wanna forget about them.
I'm so glad!
It'd be crazy if you died from blood loss
before we found Nami and Robin!
Nami-san...
Robin-chan...
Oh no! Sanji is in danger!
Hey, come here! Splash! Splatta!
What is it?
Do you need our blood again?
If it's so, just tell us! You can have...
As much as you want!
You have to stay calm, silly!
We'll stay here and...
Take care of you!
No thank you!
Don't be shy!
Stay calm—it's bad for your health!
You two are the worst for my health!
So shy!
Stay away!
Be patient, Sanji!
Go away, fools!
Ryu-Ryu-Ryu...
Ryugu Palace?!
That's right-jamon!
What?!
I can't believe they're invited to the palace...
Who are those humans?
King Neptune came to pick them up himself...
They know Monsieur Pappagu! Maybe they're famous...
Look, there's Soul King!
You're right!
What's Ryugu Palace?
Idiot, don't you know what it is?!
I'll tell you.
It's pretty much a holy place for us citizens.
A celestial world
where ordinary people are not allowed!
Ryugu Palace is...
the place where King Neptune, the three Neptune Brothers,
and the Mermaid Princess live—it's...
The royal palace of the Ryugu Kingdom!
Oh...
Camie, again!
Hmmm... So, old man...
Don't call him that!
Is there a lot of good food at Ryugu Palace?
Straw!
Of course.
We are prepared to have a banquet-jamon.
Oh yeah? I can't wait!
I'd like to see Ryugu Palace!
My heart is filled with anticipation.
But I don't have a heart to be filled!
I wanna go too!
Ryugu Palace! I sense treasure!
I knew that'd be what you're interested in!
Okay, let's go!
Hmmm. Alright, Megalo,
give the Straw Hat people
a ride to Ryugu Palace-jamon.
Can I get on?
Wow! Cool!
Are we gonna meet the Mermaid Princess?
I can't wait!
What are you doing?
Come with us!
Huh? Well, we don't deserve to go
to Ryugu Palace... Right?
Stop grumbling and come!
Let's have a banquet!
You can't say goodbye here!
Is it okay, grandpa?
You can't say "grandpa"...
Your friends can come-jamon.
Hear that?
Grandpa, you're an understanding person!
Like I said, that person is... You guys... really... please!
Alright, let's go!
To Ryugu Palace!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Go faster-chin!
They'll come any minute!
It's hard to catch a current in the deep sea!
This is why we should've put paddle wheels on!
You know, the New World is...
Captain! Look!
There's something in front of us!
That's...
Hody Jones!
N-No way!
He found us!
What? He has...
What the... He has handcuffs on.
No way! He's gonna fight us, isn't he?
He vanished!
Where did that bastard go?!
What?! What happened?!
We've taken damage!
He's too fast!
He's here on the ship!
Take him out! He's the only enemy!
No way!
It didn't work!
I fought a Fishman before!
I've been through hell to get here!
You're only a fish!
Don't mess with humans, you fool!
Captain!
Dammit!
Boy, what we got is one hell of a thing-ch!
This power drug—Energy Steroids!
Fishmen were born to be
ten times stronger than humans.
But once we take one Energy Steroid, our physical strength doubles.
Twenty times stronger than humans.
If we take two, it'll double that!
This dream power will shorten our lives!
But we're not afraid of dying—
we just adhere to the plan!
Wh-What is he doing?!
What is he gonna do with the mast?!
Is that why he has those handcuffs!
He wants to show us that he can sink us
without even using his hands!
Humans killed Fisher Tiger and shattered Arlong's dream!
The dark and tragic history
of the Fishmen will end now...
with our help,
the New Fishman Pirates!
Take them to the New World and set them adrift.
Oh no! You didn't kill all of them, did you?
No, I need them alive.
You humans, survive with those wounds
and show the world above...
what happened to you below the sea.
And who you met.
Tell them how horrendous it was.
We'll capture the center
of the world, Fishman Island,
from the gutless God of the Sea—Neptune—
and drag you humans down into the dark depths of the sea!
You'll all learn that the Fishmen
are the supreme race!
At the invitation of Fishman Island's king, Neptune,
Luffy's group makes their way
to a banquet at Ryugu Palace.
However, Luffy's hunger gets the better of him
and as soon as he smells food,
he separates from the group.
Luffy then discovers a gigantic tower
locked with a door stuck with swords and axes!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Ryugu Palace!
Taken by the Shark that They Saved"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Ryugu Palace!
Taken by the Shark that They Saved