Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil.
--Mother-sama! --Mother-sama!
Otohime-sama!
Where are you going, Otohime-sama?
Otohime...
Trust the woman who you chose to be your wife
and the humans.
Mother-sama!
Otohime-sama!
Your Majesty! Please be careful!
Mother-sama!
"A Sudden Tragedy! A Gunshot Shuts Down the Future!"
Queen Otohime's voyage was to determine the fate of Fishman Island.
Of course, we were all worrying but it was nothing compared to
the burden of the Neptune family.
The whole Ryugu Kingdom was restless.
But all we could do was pray for the Queen's safety.
What? A Tamate Box?
Yes, Captain. I heard that they have one at the Ryugu Palace.
And it makes anyone grow older?
That's what they say.
For instance, a small brat like her...
...would become a sexy mature woman?
I think so.
Great! Problem solved!
In that case, I can get married to Shirahoshi right away, I suspect!
Go steal that Tamate Box thing now!
Wait a minute. There is no way to break in to the Ryugu Palace.
--But if you get married to Shirahoshi first... --You can go in and out as you please.
You guys are smart!
Shirahoshi is not bad-looking.
If she grows older by 10 to 20 years, she will be really hot!
But she'll get even bigger.
She'll look just fine! I like big women!
She's the legendary Mermaid Princess who can control the Sea Kings.
When I become her husband and seize that power,
our dream will come true!
It's the dream of all the ancestors of Vander Decken family!
Alright, I'll start writing an invitation to our wedding.
You have to propose to her first!
Oh, I don't have any friends!
There had been no word from the Queen for days.
WE NEED YOUR SIGNATURE FOR THE FUTURE OF THE ISLAND!
And worries kept growing.
I wanna hear her speeches again.
Please come back safe!
Hey, Boss. Where is Otohime-sama?
When will she come back?
Keep faith in her and wait.
She embarked on a voyage to make the future better for you kids.
Your Majesty, please be safe.
Mother-sama...
She will be fine-jamon.
Let's trust in her and wait-jamon.
That one week felt like 100 days.
And then...
That's...
Yeah! Otohime-sama!
Your Majesty!
We are so happy just to see you alive!
Welcome back!
Your Majesty!
After a few days of convincing, Queen Otohime finally succeeded...
...in calming down the Celestial Dragons and she brought back with her a sheet of paper...
...which held the fate of Fishman Island.
CONCHCORDE PLAZA
Everyone, the World Nobles are very influential...
...in the World Summit - the Summit of Kings.
Listen to what they wrote on this sheet of paper.
"To foster friendship between the Fishmen and humans,
we will pledge our endorsement of their duly signed petition."
That means if we can submit a petition with many signatures at the Summit,
this one sheet of paper will give us all the support we need.
We can relocate!
--The Celestial Dragons will support the petition? --I have mixed feelings about it.
So what I need now is more signatures.
All I can do is wait for you to make a decision.
Express your intention...
...to relocate to the world above and live together with the humans!
Please! Sign!
I need your signature!
You children, you aren't going to go back on your pledge after raising my hopes?
We won't! My mom said she will sign too.
Otohime-sama, this small box won't be enough.
Don't you know the population of this country?
Here, here, here! Put them in here from now on!
Those of you who support the Queen's passion, put your signature in here!
The Fishmen and humans.
We were trying to ignore the history of racism.
But the Queen took the first step herself and now we have hope.
If she can get enough signatures, the future of the island could change for real.
It would have helped Arlong if he could have understood better...
...about Queen Otohime's firm belief.
I wish Brother Tai were here to see this.
Mother! Signatures keep coming in from all over the country!
--It's going well, isn't it? --Yes, it's like a dream.
It's because of your courage!
Courage?
I got encouraged at that very moment, that this island would change for sure.
That moment?
Yes, the moment that the Sea Kings came and stared at the island.
That was surprising!
Shirahoshi called them.
What?
We Merfolk can communicate with fish and talk to them, right?
But no one can talk to those great Sea Kings.
Even your father Neptune who can talk to whales, doesn't know how to talk to them.
But according to our royal family's legend, once in several hundred years,
one with an ability to communicate with the Sea Kings, will be born.
--With those giant Sea Kings?! --And Shirahoshi is the one?
Yes, and she will meet someone who will guide her and her power in the right direction
and it will cause a major change the world.
And that is the whole story.
The world?
If it's true, there will be a major change on this island too.
Could it help what you're doing?
Yes, it could.
It's a power of love that can save thousands of lives if only the bearer wishes to.
But with the wrong intentions, that power could sink the whole world into the ocean.
It is one of the most fearsome powers in the world.
Shirahoshi doesn't know that she has that power and she doesn't know
how to control it yet.
If something were ever to shock her,
she could unintentionally drive the Sea Kings berserk.
What?
Fishman Island would be flattened like a pancake! What should we do?!
Don't worry! I can take care of it for now.
But the three of you will have to become strong warriors someday
and as her brothers and as warriors,
protect your baby sister with your lives!
--Yes! --Of course!
Thank you.
But then the unexpected happened...
Signatures were mounting up at a rapid pace.
The islanders still didn't trust humans
but they were hoping to see the beginning of a new era.
Queen Otohime!
We brought our signatures again!
That's against the rules! Each person can only vote once!
W-We're sorry...
But it means a lot to me that you did so.
Thank you so much.
Your efforts finally paid off.
Get away! Fire!
--How could the box catch fire? --Water! Water!
Put out the fire now!
I can't believe it!
The signatures we collected!
Run now!
O-Otohime-sama!
Put out the fire! We have to save the signatures!
No! It's too dangerous!
They are very important! I have to save them!
Your Majesty!
We can't let them burn! They are everyone's dream!
They are the future of Fishman Island!
Yes, ma'am!
Save the signatures now!
Yes, sir!
Please save yourself! Leave the rest up to us!
Otohime-sama has been shot!
Who did it?!
The shooter must be here somewhere! Protect the royal family!
--Mother! --Mother-sama!
It's dangerous here! Get on the gondola now!
Princes!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
--Your Majesty! --Otohime-sama!
Oh no, Princess, this is pretty serious...
--Who're you?! --Oops!
--Stay away from the Princess! --Stop!
--Mother-sama! Mother! --Mother!
M-Mother!
Dammit! Who the hell did it?!
--Didn't an emergency team arrive yet?! --Mother! Mother!
Open your eyes!
This can't be forgiven! I'll make him pay!
Mother!
Stay near me, my angels.
Don't lose your temper.
My guard was down. Because I was thrilled that everybody was signing.
I was so happy!
Prince Fukaboshi, I should be the one who is frustrated.
Your Majesty, you need treatment now!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Don't get angry on my behalf.
Don't let resentment or hatred get the better of you for my sake.
M-Mother-sama...
Shirahoshi, keep your senses.
If something were ever to shock her...
This is just like...!
Shirahoshi, no!
Hey, Shirahoshi!
Moonfish mambo! Moonfish mambo!
Look, Shirahoshi!
--It's fun! It's fun! --Shake, shake! Shake, shake!
--It's nothing! Let's sing Shirahoshi! --Moonfish mambo! Shake, shake, shake!
We three will always be there for you-la-ti-do!
Mambo dance is fun!
It's fun!
It's fun-do-re-mi-fa!
P-Princes, what are you doing?!
--Stop them! --That's not appropriate!
Mother, look, we're fine!
We will protect our baby sister like this forever-la-ti-do!
Stop it! Can't you see the Queen's situation?!
Mother-sama!
We will collect the signatures that burned away again.
We three will become great warriors like our father...
...and protect Shirahoshi with our lives as we promised!
So please...
Please don't worry!
We are almost there!
At that place under the real sun!
After Otohime's death, Fishman Island is consumed by rage.
Is this the end for her ideal?
After relating the subsequent events on Fishman Island,
and finishing his story, Jinbe again apologizes to Nami.
But Nami's reply was utterly unexpected!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Back to the Present! Hody Makes a Move!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!