Darling Darling
The clouds floating into cobalt blue
floated off-path and sent a downpour into tomorrow
Just smile before the crack of dawn
All you have to do to make your wishes come true
is cast a spell within your heart,
with all your hope...
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Accelerated premonitions,
playing rainbow-colored music notes
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Won't you come with me?
We are fallen angels
firing arrows into your dreams
Darling Darling
(Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
(
I'
m a Crazy Rainbow Star!!
)
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Shall we add some more colors
to the cobalt blue?
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!!
Smash the depressing reality in your eyes
Let us give you our warm wings
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts
Darling Darling
Wealth, fame, power...
Once there was a man who had it all,
Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
And so men set sail for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
Your father's name is...
...Monkey D. Dragon. He's a revolutionary!
What?!
Hey, guys... What are you so surprised about?
There's a power trying to bring down
the World Government directly now.
That's the Revolutionary Army.
And Dragon is the man who leads it.
Ah! I guess...
...I shouldn't have said anything about it, huh?
Well, then...
...forget what I just said!
Whaaat?!
Since you're my grandson, I decided
not to capture you on this island!
I'm gonna give the Navy that good excuse,
so stay here and rest easy!
That can't be an excuse,
so let's tell them that he got away.
I just came along with these two.
Well, take your time and talk with them.
I'm going back!
Okay! See ya!
That's too casual!
Be more reluctant to say goodbye, you idiot!
You haven't seen your grandpa in forever!
What do you want me to do?!
All you did was hit me!
Even so, I still want my grandson
to love me, you moron!
Ah...
That selfishness... You can
really tell that they're related.
Yeah.
Its Name Is the New World!
The Fate of the Grand Line
Anyway, that old man was like a storm.
I was really surprised about Dragon.
So he was special to begin
with because of his lineage.
Where's Luffy?
He's out front talking to Koby and his buddy.
Don't you have to go?
They're your friends, too, right?
It does bring back memories...
...but it was Luffy who saved Koby.
Nami isn't around either, huh?
I thought she wanted to hear
stories about the marines...
I wonder if she decided to let them talk alone...
She went to the pool with
Kokoro-san and the others.
Pool?
Yeah, to the Galley-La Company's
employee pool that's behind here.
What?! Nami-san's wearing a bathing suit?!
I'll go bring drinks or something!
Then, you guys also crossed
that mountain, huh?
That mountain? Oh, no,
we didn't cross Reverse Mountain.
Hm? But I saw in a newspaper before
that my grandpa's ship
crossed that mystery mountain
and entered the Grand Line.
Oh, that article was a lie.
Hey, Koby! You shouldn't
tell him about it so casually!
Ah...
But it's okay, since it's Luffy-san.
H-How could it be okay?!
He is a pirate, you know!
Don't worry.
Hmm... Don't just talk to each other.
Ah... Let's see... This is top secret,
but headquarters' battleships can
get through the Calm Belt, so...
What?! That's not fair!
Of course, it's not 100% reliable, though.
But how come?
There's a swarm of Sea Kings several
times larger than battleships there.
We had a terrible time there!
To tell you the truth,
at the bottom of the battleships,
they spread these stones
called Sea Prism Stones.
What about it?
Ah... That is to say...
...that Sea Prism Stones release
the same energy as the sea itself,
so to the fish in the sea, those ships are...
The sea's energy...!
Oh, I see! So even when those
ships pass by on the sea's surface,
the Sea Kings wouldn't notice them.
In that case, they don't have
to go through the trouble
of passing through Reverse Mountain,
the entrance to the Grand Line.
They can just enter as they please.
The Navy's scientists are pretty impressive.
I got some good info.
Lady! Lady! Aren't you gonna swim?!
Hey!
Hey, be quiet, Chimney!
Chances like this don't come often!
Pirate lady! This is boring! This is boring!
Quiet! I'm eavesdropping right now!
Is that something you want
to broadcast out loud?
Dig into these epoch-making technologies,
and you'll always find Dr. Vegapunk,
a Navy scientist. He's incredible!
Yeah, he's really incredible!
For example, Straw Hat,
take Devil Fruits, like the one you ate.
He's already clarified how
their powers get transmitted.
In addition, another one of his big
achievements over the past few years
is creating new tech that allows
an object to eat a Devil Fruit.
Dr. Vegapunk...
I see... There are some
amazing guys out there, huh?
Yes, the world is full of incredible people!
I realized what a small world
I lived in before I met you.
If you hadn't come out of that
barrel that day, Luffy-san...
...I bet I would still be buttering up
Alvida and doing chores for her.
That's right, you were on Alvida's ship!
That was really funny!
To start with, the reason
you were on her ship was...
What is it? I don't know anything about that.
Err... Well... Um...
You wanted to go fishing and got
on a pirate ship by mistake, right?
What the hell?! What a bungler!
Back then, I was such a coward
that I couldn't even run away.
But because I was on that ship,
I was able to meet you, Luffy-san.
So it wasn't a mistake after all!
I was doing chores on that ship
in order to meet you, I bet!
Is that how it is?
That's how it is, yep!
You've kinda become strong.
I'm being trained every day, so...
Seriously, your grandpa doesn't
know how to go easy on others.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
No, Vice Admiral Garp is a wonderful man!
He took us in when we had
nowhere to go due to an incident.
We can train in Navy Headquarters right
now all thanks to Vice Admiral Garp.
Yeah, his grueling training sure is tough...
It's tough... but I really appreciate him.
So, I'll at least become able to
return the favor first, and then...
No! I'm gonna get promoted
high enough to boss him around!
Whoa! Cool, split chin!
What'd you say?! It's not split!
I still can't get used to...
...Kokoro-san looking like that...
Pirate lady! Let's play volleyball!
What?! Are you really going back already?
Why don't you have dinner with us? Dinner!
Properly speaking, we're enemies.
We can't become close, so...
Luffy-san, do you know what the
second half of the Grand Line is called?
People call the last sea that
lies beyond the Red Line
by another name...
The New World.
The New World...
It's a sea where those who will open
the way to the next era gather.
The one who comes to conquer this sea
will indeed be the Pirate King.
Yep.
Luffy-san! Let's meet again there for sure!
Next time I see you, I'll capture you!
I'll get stronger and stronger,
and one day... I'll become a...
...N...
Navy Admiral!
Whoa... Ah... Um...
I-I-I'm sorry! I-I got too full of myself!
I'm so embarrassed! I wanna crawl under a rug!
I-I got carried away, since I saw you, and...
Koby...
You're gonna fight me, right?
Then at least get to that level.
It's obvious you'll need to.
I-It's an Admiral we're talking about...
Next time we meet, we'll be stronger!
More amazing!
Why...
As I am right now, it's such a wild dream
that just saying it almost makes me faint...
And yet, how can you
have faith in me like that?
Oh? You're still a crybaby, huh, Koby?
I'm so glad that I was able
to see you two again today!
It really is a lot of work
chasing after these people.
We'll get stronger and stronger!
Let's meet again in the New World for sure!
--Let's go!
--Ah, hey!
You guys'd better be prepared!
We'll blow you away in time!
Hey, wait up, you jerk!
All right! Let's see who
makes it to the harbor first!
Don't be silly! That's not fair!
Luffy... didn't you just
create another crazy enemy?
Koby is a man who makes
things happen. I know that much.
It was good to see that
he seemed to be doing well.
But I wonder if he realizes how the world
sees what happened in Enies Lobby...
In any event, an island directly under
the Government was annihilated...
...although I guess the news that they brought
down CP9 probably won't be made public.
Of course, it can't be made public,
since CP9 is a secret organization.
The truth is, Enies Lobby caught fire
due to the Buster Call in the first place,
and yet they claimed that Luffy-san
and the others did all of that.
With the entire military force
of Enies Lobby at our disposal...
With the power of Buster Call,
as strong as an entire country's military...
Why... Why in the hell can't we...
Why...? Why can't we take a single woman...
...from a puny little band of pirates?!
The Navy should be protecting Justice...
There's no way this is right.
So you just need to become a
big shot and change it, right?
Yeah, you're right.
Seriously, to think that he picked
a fight with the Government
in order to get just one crewmate back...
Just how stupid is he?
So you're worried about Luffy-san, too, huh?!
No, it's not like that!
I have nothing to do with him.
I'm just looking on from a distance.
Hey! What're you two doing slacking off?!
--Ahhh!
--He's here!
It's 1,000 years too early for you to fool
around in a place like this, you idiots!
No meals for either of you for a week!
Y-Yes, sir!
Nami-san! Water-water meat barbecue is ready!
Okay!
Grandma, that was amazing!
It smells good.
Right?!
Here, say "Ahh."
Ugh!
Yummy!
Yummy! Water-water meat barbecue!
Sogeking! When'd you get here?!
Okay, guys, keep eating!
Why are you crying?
Shut up! The smoke is hurting my eyes!
So how is it, Robin-chan?! You can
tell it was marinated well, right?!
Yeah, it's delicious.
Oh, there they are!
Straw Hat! We heard that you woke up!
Oh, Franky Family! Come here and eat!
Whoa! They're having barbecue!
My favorite!
Whoa! There are so many of you!
Hey, add more meat!
Ah! Sodom and Gomorrah!
I'm hungry.
Me, too.
Giants! Hey!
Hey, Straw Hat! You woke up?!
Oh, Galley-La is here, too, huh?!
What're you guys doing around the pool?
Ahh! Shameless girl! What're you...?!
This is a pool, mister.
Well... something smells good.
Iceberg-san! No! You shouldn't
see this! This woman is a perv!
Hey...
We're taking a break from building a ship!
That's right! Rejecting a party
would make me less of a man!
You'd better have a seat for me!
You'd better!
Yow!
We've been waiting for you, Bro!
Here we go! Entrant #1, Sogeking! I'll sing!
All right! Party time!
I was born on the island of snipers
I never miss my mark
Lulu lala lu
Yow! Yow!
Whether it's a mouse's eyeball, lock on!!
Here you go, sis.
--Please have these!
--Oh, thanks.
Ahhh!
Or even your heart, lock on!!
All right, guys! These are ready!
You guys, help us, too!
The man who hails from the island of snipers
Lululu, lulu lala...
Yummy!
Stay there and listen, Nico Robin.
It can't be...
Blue Pheasant...?
Why didn't you run as usual?
I'm sure you could've escaped
from CP9 alone if you'd wanted to.
I told you that it's different now.
I couldn't just stand by... and let them die.
Jaguar D. Saul, the Giant who
fought for Ohara 20 years ago,
was a close friend of mine.
Kuzan!
Can you take pride in this attack?
Can you still keep your head high?!
On that day, I let you escape
the island according to his wish.
So I'm obligated to watch
the rest of your life to the end.
But after 20 years, you seemed
to have no tree to call home.
I judged that I could no longer
ignore a dangerous bomb
that bounced around as it was chased.
Above all things, I thought
that you wanted to die.
With this whole thing, I was going
to settle everything regarding Ohara.
As a matter of course, I couldn't predict
that CP9 would be defeated at all.
So you finally found a tree to call home?
Yes...
Whether Saul letting you
live was right or wrong...
Will you show me the answer from here on?
That's what I intend to do.
Then, live strongly.
Ohara still lives on.
Blue Pheasant!
Hey! Robin! Look at this!
Robin! Look at this!
Robin!
Are you eating meat?!
That's so cool, Luffy!
You're doing that stupid
stuff again?! Cut it out!
You too! You're wearing a shirt over
a bathing suit! That looks stupid!
--Are you tryin' to be Franky?!
--Don't say that!
Hey, that way!
I heard that the pirates are having a party!
You finally found a tree to call home?
No one is born into this world to be alone!
Yeah, you're right, Saul.
Live together with them.
Yes...
Hey! Robin!
Hey! This way! This way!
Maybe... I'll try it, too.
Yeah! Do it! Do it, Robin!
Please don't do it, Robin-chan!
Whoa! You don't have to go that far...
Pardon me, but since I'm on an enemy ship,
I used a bit of intimidation.
There's something I want to discuss with you.
Whitebeard...
Please stop Ace, your second
division commander.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Shanks Makes a Move!
The Linchpin to the Reckless Era"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Shanks Makes a Move!
The Linchpin to the Reckless Era