Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Two years have passed
since the Paramount War at Marineford.
Luffy and his crew
each completed individual training,
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago.
And in order to move on
to the next stage, the New World,
they set sail for Fishman Island,
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
Hey guys, over here!
Fishman Island!
It's huge!
It's surrounded by an enormous bubble!
And there are clouds on the inside?
Maybe there's air inside.
If that's Fishman Island,
that means we're 10,000 meters deep now?
Yeah! We made it!
Hey, what are they?!
Who are they?
A pack of sea monsters!
We're dead! After we got all the way here!
They're so cool!
Sea monsters!
Somebody's riding them!
Landing at Fishman Island
Beautiful Mermaids
How can you take orders from mere humans,
Kraken?!
What are you doing, Surume?! We were almost there!
Saying that won't help!
Hang on! Don't get thrown off!
My eyes are spinning!
So are mine! But I don't have eyes!
We're right in middle of the sea monsters!
You guys are the Straw Hats, aren't you?
Wh-Who are you?
How do you know about us?
Of course I know about you.
You're the ones who crushed
the ambitions of the Arlong Pirates.
If that were all you'd done,
this would be much simpler.
But two years ago, you protected Hachi-san,
one of Arlong's former officers.
And we heard you even beat up those detestable Celestial Dragons!
Your deeds are exactly like those of our beloved Fisher Tiger, the hero of Fishman Island.
Fisher... Tiger?
New Fishman Pirates, Combatant Hammond
What are we supposed to do with you?
So, tell me, are you with us or against us?
New Fishman Pirates, Assassin Hyouzou
New Fishman Pirates, Combatant Kasagon
I'll give you an choice.
Will you submit to the New Fishman Pirates?
Or do you refuse?
If you refuse, we'll sink your ship right now!
What'd you say?!
Franky, we have to refuel!
What are you trying to do?
You know that Luffy's not going to listen to them.
But we're at a depth of 10,000 meters.
We won't even be able to fight,
which means there's no way we can win.
So we run!
Use all the remaining air for one last
Coup de Burst and shoot into Fishman Island.
Are you serious?
Otherwise, we are all gonna die
after coming this far.
You're right. That may be our only chance of survival.
Okay, I'll do the refueling.
Franky, take the wheel!
Alright, super count on me!
Looks like they're getting busy. Aren't they up to something?
They're just humans.
Whatever they do will be pointless.
So, will you become our vassals, Straw Hat Luffy?
No way!
Moooron!
You refused... the offer
of the New Fishman Pirates?!
That makes you the enemy of all Fishmen!
You're nothing but wicked humans!
Bleeeeeeah!
Why should we work for you?!
Luffy, don't make him any madder!
It's a shame, but we can't let you pass.
You're gonna sink, right here!
Sea Lion!
It's ready! Franky, do it!
Roger!
Sink them!
You wanna fight?!
Go, Franky!
The Sunny's a lion too!
We'll settle this later, Sea Lion!
Here we go! Coup de Burst!
The ship!
We're running out of air!
We're gonna get crushed!
I can't breathe! But I don't have lungs.
Endure it! Just until we get inside Fishman Island!
What's going on with that ship?!
We're going in!
I'm coming, my darling Mermaids!
The coating came off!
The giant bubble tore off our coating!
Oh, look ahead!
What is that?!
There are two layers of bubble!
In this layer of air, a normal ship would fall into the gap between them!
We're gonna hit another one! Hold on tight!
Seawater?!
The current's too strong!
Help... me...
Can't breathe...
Four of us are Devil Fruit users!
Reach...
out!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Damn! I can't swim against the current!
What a reckless way to enter the country.
They probably got themselves killed.
Shall we follow them, Hammond?
I don't know if they're still alive though.
We should check anyway.
I don't want the Neptune Army finding them before we do.
But first, let's return to the Noah
and let the boss know...
Straw Hat, the one who crushed Arlong-san's ambitions is here.
Seabed, Fishman Island
Hey.
Hey, look.
I'll look.
I won't!
Maybe I'll look.
I looked, so what?
Hey, he's moving!
He moved!
He didn't!
Maybe he moved.
He moved, so what?
Yeah, he woke up!
Luffy!
Where am I?
Oh, Luffy-chin!
I'm so glad you're all right!
How do you feel?
Camie! It's been a while!
You're prettier than ever, Camie-chwan!
You're right, it's been a long time!
I'm glad to see you again!
Camie's here—which means...
We're on Fishman Island?!
Yeah, we are!
Apparently the Mermaids saved us
when we were about to drown!
Indeed. As a matter of fact,
we only woke up a couple minutes ago too.
This is Camie-chan's home.
Here's your hat.
Oh, this is Camie's place?
I'm sorry!
I was gonna pick you guys up,
but I thought you weren't coming until next month.
Don't worry about that!
So where is everybody?
Well... it looks like we got separated.
I hope they're okay.
Is that so?
Yeah, I tried to see where they went,
but only the four of us got sent to the bottom.
Well, I'm sure they'll be fine!
I guess so.
Bones won't be much good in the water,
but Robot and Green are with him.
They should be fine.
That's right! They'll be fine, right?
I wanna see the others too.
Oh, here. You must be chilled to the bone.
I made some soup, so have some to warm you up.
Ta-dah! Cold seaweed soup!
It's delicious!
Cold... soup?
Uh-huh!
You can't warm up with cold soup!
What am I gonna do?!
What?!
I made a mistake!
It's okay, Camie-chan!
It does warm me up!
How is that possible?
Hey, Sanji! I want some too!
Your clothes are dry!
They are dry.
They aren't dry!
Maybe they are dry.
They are dry, so what?
You dried our clothes for us? Thanks!
Thank you!
By the way, who are you guys?
Oh, they're my friends.
The Rice Fish Mermaid Quintuplets.
I'm Ichika!
I'm Nika!
I'm Sanka!
I'm Yonka!
I'm Yonka Two!
Shouldn't you be Goka?
They swim really fast and they're very smart.
Oh, really?
We're at the bottom of Mermaid Cove.
This is the girls' dorm of the Mermaid Café,
so I have a lot of friends here.
What?
G... G... G... Girls' dorm?!
Oh no!
Camie-chan!
What... what... what's this Mermaid Café?
That's where I work as a waitress.
A lot of pretty Mermaids work there!
P-Pretty Mermaids?!
Would you like a coffee or...?
Sanji is...
In danger!
Dammit!
He endured!
I...
I swore that nosebleeds wouldn't make me
pass out on Fishman Island!
So, shouldn't I be allowed
to have something nice for once?
Such an earnest desire.
Oh yeah, let's go up!
I'll introduce you to my friends!
Oh, it's a turtle!
It says "Sea Turtle Elevator."
Turtle-chin, can you take us up?
These are the underwater Coral Apartments.
I'm way down at the very bottom,
but that's why my rent is cheap.
The rooms at the top get a lot more light,
so they're the most expensive.
You mean you're poor?
By the way, where are Hachi and Pappagu?
Ha-chin got really badly injured last year.
He was protecting the Sunny on Sabaody, right?
I heard he's much better now.
Ha-chin comes from the Fishman District,
so he's resting up there.
Fishman District?
That place is kinda scary.
If you'll stay with me,
I don't mind showing you around.
Let's go there later!
I want to thank Hachi in person.
Okay, got it! And about Pappagu...
He's a really famous star designer.
He has a huge mansion
in a rich area called Fishverly Hills.
I'm going there later to deliver some clams. Come with me!
He's your pet, right?
Why don't you live with him?
That area is way beyond my means.
We have better clams here, anyway.
We're almost there!
Hey, what are those tube things over there?
Oh, that's...
the Water Road, created by
the bubble craftsmen of the island.
The fish and us Merfolk ride it.
Here, watch!
Oh, that's fast!
That's amazing!
Camie-chwan, where are you going?!
We're here—on the surface!
Luffy-chin!
See? I can even swim through the sky!
Oh, that looks like fun!
Huh?
Hey, wait a minute!
More importantly, the deep sea
has a sky and clouds!
You're right! I wonder how that's possible!
Hey, Camie!
Huh? That was a woman's voice!
W-Where are you?!
Everybody!
That's...
How are your pirate friends?
They nearly drowned, didn't they?
You people didn't come in through the entrance, right?
Hello. You don't look so scary.
They came here illegally?
That's so wild! I just love pirates!
It's like a scene out of a fairy tale!
An island of coral!
The Mermaid Cove!
Sanji's crying!
You're crying harder than when you left the Baratie.
I finally found it!
This is my All Blue!
Are you really alright with that, Sanji?
I'll introduce them to you!
He's the captain—Luffy-chin.
That's me, nice to meetcha!
The crybaby is Sanji-chin.
The one with the big nose is Usopp-chin.
Nice to meet you!
The raccoon dog is Chopper-chin.
I'm a reindeer!
What's wrong? What are you crying about?
Come with me!
Let's dance together in the sea!
I see, I get it now. This can't be true.
I'm probably going to die today!
How negative!
Seriously, what happened to you
in the last two years?
Isn't this the paradise of your dreams?!
You're so funny, Sanji!
He's not trying to be funny!
Fishman District, Noah
I see.
Straw Hat Luffy...
so he's finally here?
Yes.
What are your orders, Boss?
Bring him...
to me!
At Mermaid Cove Sanji reverts to his old self
and fools around with the Mermaids.
But then the three Princes of Fishman Island arrive.
Not knowing what to expect, the group hides,
but then an unimaginable crisis occurs!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Excitement Blow-Out!
Sanji's Life Under Threat!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Excitement Blow-Out!
Sanji's Life Under Threat!