Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst of
the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil
while Zoro, Usopp and Brook get captured by Hody at the Ryugu Palace.
Get out of my way, Jinbe! You gotta let me go!
No, I won't! Leave it up to me!
You bastard!
Then I'll just beat my way past you!
I'll fight you as many times as I have to till you understand!
What did you say?!
Oh, I see some soldiers from the army!
Water Shot!
"The Battle is on! At Conchcorde Plaza!"
Captain Hody is awesome-ch!
I can't believe that he was just writhing in agony from an Energy Steroid overdose-ch!
N-Neptune's army's been beaten!
They got wiped out!
Exactly how strong is Hody?!
Minister of the Right-dono!
Minister of the Left-dono!
Neptune-sama!
King-sama!
Let's go to Conchcorde Plaza!
Oh no, Neptune-sama!
Neptune-sama!
We were almost...
...almost there!
Your efforts were expected to bear fruit at the World Summit this year!
Queen Otohime!
But then they started this all of a sudden!
Please save him!
If nothing is done, they will kill King-sama!
Please! Please save the King!
Mom!
What's gonna happen to this country?!
Captain! Hey Captain!
Captain Decken, things will start looking up soon.
You fool! I don't need you to comfort me!
You guys don't know how painful it is to be broken-hearted!
I mean, Shirahoshi was just a kid when we first met.
And I decided to marry her to fulfill my ancestors' dream!
And how did it all turn out?
You're not my type!
"Not my type" she said When the words came to my ears I felt my true love grow, I suspect.
A haiku with extra syllables. By Vander Decken IX.
She broke... She broke my heart!
I was dumped so I cut my hair!
Only the top?!
I wanted to kill her but she's still alive!
I know it because I still can throw things at her!
That Straw Hat fool must be protecting her!
Oh yeah.
What's wrong?
I got an idea!
What don't I just destroy everything altogether?!
It's gonna be great!
Let King-sama go, Hody!
Stop! Or we'll open fire!
Run, soldiers! Don't die a meaningless death-jamon!
I won't let them get away-ch! Sea Bear!
Dammit!
Finally, you're here! I got tired of waiting!
Hyouzou-san, we're here!
Don't get too close! He'll cut you!
I'm here as you wish-dokan!
You folk have nowhere to... run!
We can't get in! The entrance to Conchcorde Plaza is locked!
Neptune-sama!
Let's climb the wall! Maybe we can see inside.
Boy, he gave me a lot of trouble...
We've wasted so much time. Let's go, Princess-sama.
Okay!
Take care of Hachi, Camie!
Y-Yes.
Go, Megalo!
I thought you soldiers had to protect this country!
Soldiers...
Hody!
That soldier is up to something.
Which one?
He's gonna launch a suicide attack to kill anyone around him-bokan!
I'm gonna become a piece of dried squid if he does-ch!
Before the Princes gets here,
if I can kill at least one of their officers!
Oh no, he's gonna...
Water Shot.
What's that? How far can it go?
MERMAID COVE
--What is that? --Huh?
I hear something.
Hey, I thought the Water Shot was fairly weak, wasn't it?
I know you took a lot of Energy Steroid but still, that was great-ch!
Your hair turned white and you've gained muscle.
How do you feel, Captain?
Couldn't be better!
The soldiers...
Why didn't they wait for us?
Fukaboshi! Ryuboshi! Manboshi! Be careful!
All the sea monsters and the Fishmen have taken the drug!
I thought Neptune's army
wouldn't be beaten so easily as long as playing field was level-re-mi-fa!
We'll save you, Father!
Why don't you understand, Hody Jones?!
You folk are the weakest on this island!
The other islanders were trying to ignore the history of discrimination by humans
and to forgive the murder of their hero and queen who died at the hands of a human.
They endured their pain in order to change the future
and signed their names.
--Prince! --Fukaboshi-sama!
Why can't you appreciate the boldness and kindness of their decision?
Kindness?
It's a meaningless gesture.
You all want to be fooled by the humans?!
Merman Combat!
Spear of the Ages!
Seven Great Treasures!
Dragon Tower Gate!
Th-They beat the sea monsters!
You folk are just seeking your revenge out of your own hatred!
But I won't let you take the King's life, or the island that belongs to our citizens...
...or the Ryugu Kingdom!
They're so strong! After all, they're the strongest men in the Kingdom!
You think you win because you beat the sea monsters?
We won't lose! Because we were given the great power from above!
That power will allow us to rule the real Fishman country!
We'll beat you all and lead the way to peaceful coexistence with the humans!
If we let you have your way,
Fishmen and humans won't get another chance at friendship for hundreds of years!
Say whatever you like! But after all, this country will be ruled by...
...the winner, right?
They look strange!
Here they come!
Wh-What the...
Too slow.
Hurry up, Megalo!
Father-sama, please be safe!
He will be fine! It's going to be alright!
So that was the true power of the drug!
Attempting to free Neptune, Shirahoshi and Jinbe
but they are caught in Hody's trap.
Displaying his prisoners, Hody affirms his complete control of Fishman Island.
and reveals a surprising, long-hidden truth!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Surprising Confession! The Truth Behind the Assassination of Otohime!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!