Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
rashinban nante jyuutai no moto
compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
delirious with fever, i take the helm
hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
if the dusty treasure map has been verified,
tashikameta no nara densetsu janai
it's not a legend!
kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
when it comes to personal storms,
biorizumu nokkatte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
omoi sugoseba ii
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
poketto no koin
a coin in my pocket,
soreto You Wanna Be My Friend
and do you wanna be my friend?
We Are
we are!
You... damn caterpillar!!
Chore boy!!
Even if hundreds of weapons are built in,
he can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
At least...
...that kid doesn't have any hesitation.
Is it a survival instinct?
Or does he not fear death
because he has faith in himself?
Faith...
This is where you die!!
M-My Mighty Battle Spear is...
What the hell did you do?!
I gave it five punches.
I guess that's it for your spear.
That kid is pretty good.
He might do it...
This is bad...
I never imagined the Mighty
Battle Spear would be broken...
But he's taken that many explosions.
His body can't keep up...
The Conclusion of
the Deadly Battle!
A Spear of Blind
Determination!
Prepare yourself...
Huh?!
This is a big enough foothold.
With a foothold this size,
I can kick your ass.
What?
With the spear blade broken,
that's just a bomb on a stick.
The power is cut by half.
You think so?
Yeah, I do.
A bomb on a stick? So what of it?
Given the shape you're in, it's more
than enough force to blow you away.
With your body falling apart like that,
whatever you say sounds like just a bluff.
It's not a bluff.
Just give it up!
The moment you defied me,
you signed your death warrant!
I won't die! Bleah!
Hey! I'm over here!
That monkey!
Ooh ooh ahh!
He keeps hopping around!
It's useless!
Just how many built-in weapons does he have?
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
What's that?!
Amazing...
What the hell is that?
I see a ton of arms...
All right, chore boy!!
Get him!!
Weak!
Your punches are powerless
against this wootz Steel Armor!
You can't even make a dent in it.
Gum-Gum Pistol!!
Don!!
How impudent!!
Useless! Useless! How useless!!
This armor won't break, even with
hundreds of monkey punches!
I think I'm pretty close...
He's gone...
I'm right here!
Now listen. The ultimate force
means the strongest equipment
and the strongest power!
The strong one is the one who survives.
The strong one is!
Then, that'll be me! Gum-Gum...
Useless! Useless! It's useless!!
Even pride will only get you so far!
...Bazooka!!
No good. This is all you can do.
What?!
The strongest armor is cracking?!
But it's too late.
You're done for, anchor boy!
It's a trap! Get out!!
Chore boy!!
Is it a survival instinct?
Or does he not fear death
because he has faith in himself?
Gum-Gum...
What?!
...Bazooka!!
All right!!
Good job!!
You're the best, chore boy!!
I win!!
Don't get carried away, brat!!
Ugh! He's still alive!
Oh, no!
Can you escape?! It's a steel net!
Below us is the ocean.
The game is over, anchor boy!
I'm the one who's getting the last laugh!
All right! That's our Don!
Make him fall!
Get him!!
If I can get my arms and legs out,
the game is mine!
Why doesn't he flinch?
Why does he go that far?
What?!
This is gonna end it... for sure!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Hammer!!
Don Krieg...
Don... Don was defeated! Why?!
Dammit! Why? Why was Don...
All right, chore boy!!
Good job!!
He really did it!!
A-Amazing!!
Is this real?
This is Don Krieg we're talking about!
So strong! He's too strong!
Wh... What's all this fuss?
Oh! You've come to!!
He lost! Your Don lost!
What?!
If you have time to daydream,
go save that kid already!
Huh?
He won't be floating up to the surface!
What?!
Those with the Devil Fruit
power are hated by the sea
and lose the ability to swim.
What'd you say, you damn geezer?!
You should've told me that sooner!
What're you gonna do if it's too late?!
Where did he go?
Hey! Hang in there!!
You said you wouldn't die, right?
That's your faith, right?!
Right?!
I won't die!
I'm not gonna die here.
Really, these guys...
Zoro!!
He should give up his ambition rather than dying!
It should be easy...
to give up your ambition, right?!
They're all...
I don't know...
I don't know why, but...
...if I withdrew even a step,
I feel like those various
important things such as pledges
and promises in the past will be shattered,
and I won't be able to come
back to where I am now...
He can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
All... Blue...
Hey, chore boy! Don't you die on me!
Don! What's the matter?!
Why was Don...
Don Krieg has been defeated...
This can't be true...
He's the ruler of the East Blue...
That man is... That man is... That man is...
That man is...
Even if you say so...
Just take a look at that!
His proud armor got shattered
and he's knocked out.
He got defeated good.
You're not gonna see it?
He's the only man I admired...
I believed he was the strongest!
Hey wait, underling!
If you move around now,
the poison'll pass into your system.
Don't move around!
I'm saying this for your own good!
Hey! You're gonna die!
Chore boy! Don't die! Can you hear me?!
You still have things to do, right?!
Hey! Don't die! Chore boy!
Say... Say something!!
Chore boy! Don't die!!
You're such a...
You're really something else...
I'm the strongest!!
I win! No one defeats my force!!
Don! Please stop!
Hold him! He's not even conscious!
I'll win!!
Please stop, Don!!
I'll win! Using my force!!
I... have to win!!
I'm the strongest man!!
Don Krieg... We lost.
Chief Commander!
Let's withdraw gracefully and start afresh.
Thanks for everything, Sanji-san.
Sure. Don't ever come back!
Sanji-san, when he wakes up,
please tell him I said...
...I'll see you again in the Grand Line.
You...
When I think about it carefully,
that's the only thing I want to do...
It seems that Don Krieg's ambition
became mine as well before I knew it.
Maybe... I can live only a few more hours...
It's kind of stupid that I'm resolved
because I don't have much time left,
but this time, I want to do it with
my own will... in my own way...
Then, there'll be nowhere
for me to escape, right?
The hell with loyalty towards Don!
I've just been running away using
Don Krieg's name as a shield...
Once you're resolved,
you don't have to think about stupid things
like fearing your enemy or
how to keep from getting hurt...
I learned it from that guy.
Patty! Carne!!
Give him the boat used to go grocery shopping!
What?! Are you stupid?!
Why do we have to give our boat to pirates?!
What's gonna happen to our
grocery shopping?! You idiot!
He's right! Let those guys swim!
Just bring it out already!!
Okay, we got it...
Don't yell at us...
Okay, okay, we'll bring it out!
It's gonna sink!
Why did I hesitate?
What was I so worried about?
When I think about it, I feel stupid...
Well, then!
We gratefully accept the boat.
We don't have to return it, right?
Right. If you have the courage
to come here to return it,
try it, you small fry.
He's right! Just keep this in your brain!!
This is the sea restaurant Baratie, where cooks fight!
Yeah!!
Hmph! What a scary restaurant...
They were nice guys...
I wonder if they'll let me join them
again when I see them next time...
I wonder if I'll be able to see them again...
I wanna be free...
Belle-Mère-san...
Chisana koro ni wa takara no chizu ga
When I was little,
Atama no naka ni ukandeite
I had a vision of a treasure map
Itsudemo sagashita kiseki no basho o
and I always searched for that miraculous place
Shiranai dareka ni makenai you ni
before someone else could beat me to it
Yume sae tsukamenai mama
If the world is going to change
Moshi mo sekai ga kawaru no nara
before I can even attain my dream
Nanimo shiranai koro no watashi ni
then take me to the time when I knew nothing
Tsurete itte omoide ga iro asenai you ni
so that my memories won't fade
Now I'm free from the chores
since pops promised me.
That's right.
By the way, will you...
I'm not going. I won't become a pirate.
Okay...
Hey, you haven't given up yet!
But I'm hoping to go to the Grand Line some day.
Then let's go now.
It's not the right time yet!
Next time, on One Piece:
Set Sail!
The Seafaring Cook Sets Off With Luffy
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Set Sail!
The Seafaring Cook
Sets Off With Luffy