Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be Pirate King!
Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
BON
VO
Let that shred of courage grow
YAGE!
YAGE!
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
YAGE!
BON
VO
YAGE!
shi
ga
ra
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve your dreams aren't for naught
cious
in
my
life
i
pre
cious
in
my
life
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
See ya, fortress guy!
H-Hey! It's me!
Hey!!
Imprison him!
You should thank Robin.
I see... She thought that it'd be safer for me to be with you...
It might've been better if I didn't check into it...
To think that there's only one escape route...
Daring Luffy and Sanji!
Their Great Rescue Operation!
Among the Straw Hat Pirates
that we already captured,
there was a man wearing a uniform
who pretended to be a Navy officer.
Listen up! You can report it later!
When you see suspicious individuals,
imprison them immediately!
Yes, sir!
Did you hear?! That long-nosed guy
was a crew member of the Straw Hats!
Yeah.
But why did he take the trouble to come here?
Yeah. In the bay, there're lots of
ships that are better than this one.
They could've taken one of them and quickly escaped.
That's how stupid pirates are!
You're right!
Oh?
Are you already done for the day, Mechao-san?
Don't slave-drive an elderly man.
He says he's "elderly"!
As if!
You damn idiot! At least try to be careful!
S-Sorry.
Geez... This is such a complicated fortress!
I wonder where Zoro and Usopp are...
Well, since they got caught,
they were probably sent to jail.
Okay! Then we'll go to the jail!
Do you know where the jail is?
You don't know, Sanji?
How would I know?!
Hmmm...
I think that belly button island
is suspicious after all.
What makes you think that?
Dunno, I just do.
But in any case, that sounds about right.
It's surrounded by the sea.
On top of that, the only way to
escape is to cross that bridge.
It's a pain, but I guess we should go there.
Alrighty!
Dammit!
Going the way we came is also gonna be a pain.
Yes, sir!
This is District 4 in Block F. All clear!
Keep searching!
Yes, sir!
They're in contact with each other
using Mini Transponder Snails.
This isn't gonna be easy.
Hey, Sanji.
Hm?!
This is kinda exciting, isn't it?
Get moving already, you damn monkey!
Ouch!
Where am...?
Freeze!
Port        Entry        Records
This is strange. There're times when
no ships enter or leave. Why is that?
I'm being watched...
Hey, you! What do you think you're doing?!
Who do you think I am?!
You told us over and over on our way here.
You're Special Inspector Major Shepherd, right?
If you know that, get me out of here right now!
I have business with Commander Jonathan!
Major Shepherd?
Oh, I see!
This is the guy Robin was pretending to be!
Enough of your nonsense! There's no way
So they've mistaken him for one of us instead!
a Navy major from Headquarters would
let his ID and his coat be stolen so easily!
If that's the case...
Stop it now. It's disgraceful!
Hm?!
A man should know when to give up!
Let's not struggle...
...my comrade, Condoriano...
C-Condoriano?! What's that?!
Who the hell are you?!
Hey, hey... Stop making bad jokes...
You expect us to believe you've
forgotten my face or your own name?!
Hey! Don't come near me!
I'm not your buddy!
I don't know him! I don't know this man!
Ow, ow... What happened to you?
Oh, no... Did the impact from the fall
cause you to lose your memory?!
How sad... It's too sad!
Hey! Please! Would you let at least him out?!
He's not the same Condoriano that I knew!
That settles it.
Yeah.
There isn't even a point in interrogating him.
Wh-What do you mean, "that settles it"?
Wait! What're you going to do with me?!
Wait!
Don't you get that I'm telling you to wait?!
Condoriano!
Who's Condoriano?
Shut up already!
Nice move, Zoro!
It went well! You should thank me, Robin!
You look creepy, Usopp.
Commander...
...there still haven't been any reports of the other Straw Hats being seen.
What should we do, Commander?!
They're probably having a hard time finding the jail.
I guess we'll lead the way.
Huh?
You go ahead of them and wait.
Be sure not to act hastily.
Yes, sir!
Well, why don't we ensure our
victory by making the first move?
Ow...
What're you doing, Sanji?
Shh!
Dammit! I guess we have to
force our way through after all.
Hey, it's unguarded down there!
Let's go, Luffy! We'll head down there!
Okay!
Hello!
Reporting, sir!
The one we captured earlier
turned out to be a Straw Hat member whose name is Condoriano.
Condoriano?
Yes, sir!
He insists that he's Major Shepherd...
...but we think that it's clearly a lie.
Okay, thanks.
So there're two Shepherds, huh?
Well...
Hey, Zoro...
Don't you think this is kinda strange?
Yeah. It gives me a bad feeling.
Hm? Oh?
You're... Mechao-san...
Wh... What're you doing in a place like this?!
What am I...?
I just had a little matter to attend to.
Pull them back already!
Hmph! I see...
So, what's your business?
It's not with you! I need to talk to that long-nose held captive there.
Wha...?! Wait!
I can't let you talk to a prisoner so freely!
It won't take long. Cut me some slack!
Hey!
Ah! You're the guy from...!
Don't tell me something
happened to the Going Merry!
Don't worry. Your ship is okay... for now...
Good...
You're the one who repaired that ship, aren't you?
Hm? Oh, sort of...
The way you did it isn't acceptable.
Unless you use splices,
even if you nail the iron sheets,
it'll break in no time when
strong winds blow, you know.
Splices?
What? You don't even know what splices are?
Well, actually, I'm not a maintenance man or anything like that.
The one that did those repairs was...
Someone did them in just one night?
Yeah. That was when we were in a place called a sky island
that was 10,000 meters up in the sky, though.
Hm? 10,000, you say?
Yeah, yeah...
You probably don't believe it anyway, do you?
Come to think of it, that ship fell from the sky, didn't it?
What? You believe me?!
Since I saw it with my own eyes,
I have to believe it.
Considering the angle at which it fell,
it probably fell from a considerable height, so...
You're right!
We had a really hard time on the sky island!
There was God and there were angels...
It was really tough!
God and angels?
You talk as if you died once.
Far from just once, there were
tons of times that I thought I'd die.
There were, huh?
By the way, about what you told me earlier...
Was it foggy the night that this someone
who repaired the ship appeared?
Yeah! Exactly! How did you know that?!
Oh, do you, by any chance,know who that was?!
That could be, you know...
Uh-huh...
Wh-What're you doing?!
That's it, old man.
We're quite busy with various things.
Escort him out.
Yes, sir!
Hey, hey!
W-Wait! Hey! Tell me who that was!!
That's right.
I forgot to tell you something important!
Listen, long-nose! When you repair the ship,
pay attention to the areas that you usually don't.
Those areas are often the
ones most in need of repair!
If you treasure your ship, don't forget that!
You got that?!
Yeah! I got it, old man! Thanks!
Someone just came out!
Yeah. But that place really is fishy.
All right! Then shall we go?!
Hold on! This is a little strange.
We arrived here after we took the deserted route.
It's as if they're telling us where
Zoro and Usopp are... Which means...
I get it! The fortress guy is a nice guy!
It's a trap. A trap!
They're probably trying to save time and send us straight into jail.
Who cares?
Either way, we can't rescue Zoro and Usopp unless we go inside, right?
Idiot! Why would we want to get trapped
by our enemy so easil...?! Hm?
It's true that it'd be better than wasting
time wandering around aimlessly.
I'm also worried about Nami-san and Robin-chan.
Sanji, are you thinking it over?
No, I'm not!
You did, didn't you?!
I said I didn't!
There's nothing in here!
Never mind that, get moving already!
Alrighty!
Hey, Zoro! Usopp! Where're you guys?!
Oh? Did you hear Luffy's voice just now?
Hey!!
It's really Luffy! Hey, Luffy!
We're right here!
Sure you wanna do that?
Those guys can hear too, you know.
Luffy, don't come!
No, I changed my mind! Come get us!
Hey, what should I say?
Beats me.
Tell them to come if they want to or something.
Come if you want to!
I heard a voice!
It's this way!
Umph!
Oh, no... They came...
Be careful, Luffy!
They're here!
Hold on! I'll get you... out...
What the...?!
Oh, I see!
This is the Sea Prism Stone's doing!
We've been waiting for you!
Surrender obediently, Straw Hat!
Ha! You are making light of us, aren't you?!
You think that's enough to stop us?!
Is this still not enough?
It's all the same to me, idiots.
Now, what should I do?
For starters...!
What's he doing?!
Ha! It's painful to watch!
Those bars can't be broken unless you use a cannon or something.
Dammit! These bars sure are tough!
Cannon...? Oh, yeah!
Sanji! Hey, hey, hey...
Take what's inside my pocket!
Your pocket?!
I have an Impact Dial in there.
Use it to break these bars!
Impact Dial...
Hey, it causes pain to the user, you know!
This is no time to worry about that!
Now, take it already!
What're they talking about now?
Give up gracefully!
Well, wait a sec, gorilla man.
I'll show you something remarkable,
so keep your mouth shut.
A seashell?
It won't be my fault if you get hurt standing there.
Oh, yeah, that's right...
Here we go!
"This well-tempered snake"?
That total moron!
What's that? Are you trying to tell us that's your secret weapon?!
Shut up! Or I'll gut you!
Yipes, he's scary! A backlash!
Ah! Um, Sanji-kun, sorry!
It's actually in the other pocket.
Here. It's this side. This side... This...
Flavor... It stinks!
Th-This is...!
I-It stinks!
Who the hell stored a fart in my Flavor Dial?
I... I'm... sorry...
I guess I didn't have to ask.
Watch out! It's gonna explode! Get down!
An explosion in the jail!
It's an emergency! Hurry up!
Hey, are you okay?!
Escape... successful?
Looks like it.
Ouch!!
Help...
Geez! What a pain in the ass!
Now, there's no point staying here any longer.
Let's get out of here already!
Thank you!
Let's go, Luffy!
Alrighty! Guys, get out of here!!
Ahh! Hey, hey! Wait a sec!
Don't let Zoro go first!
It won't be my fault if we get lost!
Usopp, you jerk!
Is everyone okay?!
Y-Yes, somehow...
Okay, then!
Those who can move, come with me!
We'll go after the Straw Hats!
Those fools!
Our men should be in place outside by now!
We'll attack them from both sides and
send them to the netherworld this time!
Oh?
See?! We're lost!
Where are we?!
How can you get lost?! That's impossible!
Shut up!
Commander! I'm sorry!
I failed to catch Straw Hat!
What about the other members?
Are Roronoa and the others with him?!
Yes. Uh, well...
Witnesses told me that they didn't
see Condoriano with the others.
I see...
Lt. Commander, the bridge is guarded, right?
Y-Yes, sir!
Good! Well, don't be so discouraged.
We'll still have many opportunities to catch them.
Looks like those kids made their move.
Mirai ni mukatte, saki o isoge! Ima sugu ni
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Yume to iu mono oikakete ikou
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
Afure dashi teru subete no kotae ga kokoni
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Hashire, hashire, hiraka reta michi wo
Rush forth, rush forth, on the road opened before us
Tomaru koto naku susumou, bokura wa dekiru
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
Makenai, makenai, ookina kabe demo
We won't give in, we won't give in, even if the obstacle is big
Kowagaru koto nante nai sa, norikoerareru
It's nothing to be scared of, we can overcome it
A trap?!
Which means something fun might happen!
Well, worrying about annoying crap is annoying.
We'll see what kind of trap it is.
So you think you can escape from Navarone?
And from me?
We won't get caught! We're pirates!
Next time, on One Piece:
Enter the Hot-Blooded Special Forces!
Battle on the Bridge!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Enter the Hot-Blooded
Special Forces!
Battle on the Bridge!