Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil
and involved in an all-out war!
Surume!
So you were doing everything he says in order to save your brother's life?
I know how you feel.
Is it your younger brother or older brother?
Let me try to save his life too!
Did you forget?
I'm your friend!
Gear 2!
"The Noah Closing in! Fishman Island Facing Destruction!"
I can't believe it! That's...
...the Ship of Promise! "Noah"!
W-Why...
Why is it moving?!
Who is doing it and how?!
Th-This is no good!
What's the matter, Father?
It's a bit strange, but why are you so upset?
It's just a relic from history. It serves no purpose.
No! We can't let anything happen to that ship-jamon!
Until the proper day comes, no one is allowed to move that ship-jamon!
Captain Hody!
I thought he took a lot of Energy Steroids and became a monster!
No, look!
Straw Hat!
He's pretty tough.
We found Shirahoshi!
Over here!
Um... What do you three want?
We can't let you live!
We have to kill you!
Surume!
Surume-sama, you are very strong!
Protect Wimpyhoshi!
Straw Hat!
Do you know what Fishman Karate is?!
His head is gone!
He did it with a single blow!
It's not gonna work. Because I'm made of rubber!
Your skill is nothing compared to Jinbe's!
Of course! That's why you shouldn't depend on fake power!
Head; Hardening!
Iron Shell Squad!
Yes, sir!
You fool! Your head's gonna crack open!
Gum-Gum...
...Bell!
His head was harder than iron!
Armament: Hardening!
What?!
Shark Arrows!
He doesn't get hit at all!
Does he know when they come?!
Amazing, Luffy-sama!
That's the Observation Haki!
Gum-Gum...
...Bullet!
Captain Hody!
Luffy-sama, he is unbelievably strong!
He's great! Straw Hat Luffy!
So that's how strong the world-renowned pirate is!
What's going on?!
What is it?
What?! I-Is that...
...the Noah of the Fishman District?!
Why is the Noah in the air over the island?!
It's heading towards this plaza!
It's almost broken through the bubble around the island!
Once the bubble pops, the island is finished! We're all gonna get washed away!
--What is that?! --The Noah?!
Super big!
Once the ship hits, the whole island will be destroyed!
Who's operating it?!
I don't think it has an engine!
--What is that?! --It's gigantic!
Don't know what's happening but we're all dead!
I wonder if the sea will turn red if we all get smashed at once.
Don't say things like that! Stop it!
--Evacuate! --Get into the water off the island!
F-Folks?
It's...!
Ouch! I slipped!
You're Wadatsumi - working for Decken!
Captain Vander Decken! I fell off!
Stop the ship! I don't wanna die!
Decken?! What's going on here?
Captain Hody, are you all right?!
Um, is this one of your strategies?!
It looks like Decken is operating the ship!
Shut up, you good-for-nothings!
Damn, Straw Hat!
Huh?
How tough can he be?! I attacked him with the Armament Haki!
Did you say Decken? That crazy pirate!
This is not a part of the plan!
Shirahoshi!
Accept my love!
Did you hear me, Shirahoshi?
That must be...!
Princess Shirahoshi!
Don't tell me Decken threw the Noah like he threw those letters and axes!
I've been loving you for 10 years since you were just a little kid.
There is no one who could love you like I do in all the wide world!
It's my love! Love, love!
L-O-V-E!
Why can't you just accept it?!
Things that I throw with my Mark-Mark Fruit power...
...won't stop until they crash into something or hit their target!
Noah the giant ship! It embodies my love for you! Accept it!
And drop dead along with all of Fishman Island, Shirahoshi!
Captain Decken! What about me?!
Wadatsumi! It's too late! It's impossible for me to save you!
So I need you to become a sacrifice upon Shirahoshi's death, along with the island!
No!
This is it! The bubble is gonna pop!
We're doomed!
Hey, where did Princess Shirahoshi go?!
Oh? She's not there!
What?! Princess! Princess Shirahoshi!
What? Shirahoshi disappeared?!
N-No way!
I am over here!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
--Princess Shirahoshi! --When did she go up there?!
Wimpyhoshi...
Mermaid Princess!
Shirahoshi! Why did she do that?!
Because that ship is flying towards her!
What? Then she...
That's the girl that I love!
I thought you wanted to take just my life!
If I am the only one who you want to kill, please do not harm the other people...
...of the Ryugu Kingdom!
Come and get me!
--Princess-sama! --Princess!
Look! The Noah is changing its course!
It's heading towards Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
Shirahoshi!
Don't do this, Shirahoshi-chan!
So, that crazy Decken bastard...
He was gonna crush us all along with the island.
How dare he betray us!
Don't try to help us!
Can we do something to save her?!
How amazing!
How amazingly beautiful you are, Shirahoshi! Even your mind!
You're trying to take the matter into your own hands
in order to save the country, aren't you, Shirahoshi?!
Shirahoshi!
Shira... hoshi...
You're eligible to become Vander Decken IX's wife as I thought!
You better die while you're still beautiful and live in my heart forever!
Shirahoshi!
--Princess-sama! --How could you do that!
--Don't do that! --Run, Princess!
Damn Wimpyhoshi! I told her to stick with me!
Straw Hat! Captain Hody!
Oh? Where did Hody-san go?
Look! He's up there!
He's heading for the Noah!
Don't mess with me, Vander Decken!
But I like this idea!
That bastard! How dare he hurt Shirahoshi-chan!
Sanji, wait!
I'll go up there! You stay here and take care of the plaza!
All right!
But Luffy, the ship is in the water!
Do you think the ship is filled with water, Jinbe?
I don't know but I know Decken is a Devil Fruit user.
Which means there must be air for him!
Take this with you!
It's a coral that produces bubbles!
Thanks!
I'll be counting on you to save my beloved Shirahoshi-chan!
You ready, Luffy?!
Go ahead!
Attempting to save Fishman Island.
Shirahoshi lures the Noah away.
After Luffy follows her,
he's cornered into an underwater battle at a severe disadvantage against Hody.
Then, Shirahoshi
in order to finish things!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Hurry up, Luffy! Shirahoshi's Life in Jeopardy!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!