Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level.
Meeting Jinbe again at the Sea Forest,
Luffy learns about Fishman Island
along with Nami, Sanji, Chopper, Franky and the others.
It's okay to cry!
Don't think that we're like those stupid Celestial Dragons!
Look closely.
What?
We won't kill anybody!
We'll take her...
...to her hometown!
"The Death of the Hero! A Shocking Truth of Tiger!"
We finally got an Eternal Pose to Koala's hometown!
12 YEARS AGO - THE GRAND LINE
Nyu! Koala, you can go back to your home!
Um...
I can't believe my eyes. You've changed a lot!
KOALA (THE FORMER SLAVE GIRL)
You look like a girl now!
I don't normally wear these...
What? We bought them for you but you don't like them?
You got your hair cut, too. Your mother will be really happy.
I...
I should clean.
Nyu! You need to stop working when you don't know what to do!
This is not Mary Geoise!
Leave her alone.
She needs time.
THE SHIP'S DOCTOR OF THE SUN PIRATES ALADDIN
Trauma can't be healed that easily.
Alright.
You understand her very well, Brother Aladdin.
Because you were a slave yourself.
But wouldn't you rather kill her right now?
She's a human just like the one who owned you!
Stop it, Arlong!
Tell us the truth. What did your mother tell you?
Your parents looked down on Fishmen, didn't they?
That's how human society is!
They think that they're the best race in the world.
Their children are spoiled by watching their example.
It won't stop until somebody destroys them!
I suppose you guys have seen it enough while we were sailing these past 3 years.
Their disrespectful contemptuous look when they see us.
I don't know what I would've done to them if the Boss wasn't there.
That was only a few of them.
--The others didn't look like that. --Brother Jinbe...
Everytime I see them, they all look terrified to me.
Is it because we're pirates?
Why are you so afraid of us?
Because I don't know you folk.
If you don't know someone, you naturally fear them?
We've only known the bad sort of humans.
We don't know anything about humans yet.
So getting to know someone would change something?
Nyu. Hey, Koala.
What?
Guess which hand it's in.
Well, where is it now?
Um... This one.
Nope! It's here!
Alright, one more time.
Nyu. Get it right this time.
Uh-huh.
Where is it?
This one.
Wrong again!
Just as Koala was fitting in so well.
That's when we arrived at Foolshout Island - where she came from.
THE GRAND LINE - FOOLSHOUT ISLAND
Koala, get off of the ship.
This is your home island.
--Where is your home village? --Huh?
--I'll walk you to the entrance to the village. --Uh-huh!
Don't go, Koala! Come with us!
You're a good girl even though you're a human.
Stop crying, you guys.
I'll tell everybody in the village...
...that there are so many good Fishmen!
Thank you, everybody!
Goodbye!
Hey, take care of yourself!
I'm sure she'll grow up into a mean-spirited human like the others.
What did you just say?!
Jinbe!
Arlong, you bastard...
Brother Jinbe. You've changed a lot in last 3 years.
What?
Think about it. What's the point in her telling people that Fishmen are nice?
It's like Otohime's speeches, her voice will just ring hollow.
She's back!
He's right! Your daughter is back!
--I'm so glad! --Yeah...
Everybody!
Hurry up! She came back!
Koala? Koala!
Mom...
Koala!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
That is the captain of the Sun Pirates...
Fisher Tiger!
He's a bad man, isn't he? Because he's a Fishman...
Shh!
It must've been painful and hard being a slave!
But Mom, not everybody was like the Celestial Dragons!
What?
I thought Fishmen were all terrible but there were so many nice Fishmen!
That's because you're only a child.
No! I know it because I was with Uncle Tiger and the others all this time!
You would think so too if you'd lived with them!
Uncle!
Uncle Tiger!
Thank you for keeping your promise!
I'll never forget you - Uncle Tiger...
...and Hachi-san, Aladdin-san and all of the Sun Pirates...
...for the rest of my life!
Thank you so much!
I want to believe that when you grow up,
humans and Fishmen will...
I'm Rear Admiral Strawberry from Navy Headquarters.
Someone on this island informed us of your arrival.
The elders of this village knew there might be trouble if we stopped you
but they approved it.
On the condition that we wouldn't repossess the girl who is the rightful property
of the Celestial Dragons.
Fisher Tiger, captain of the Sun Pirates.
You are charged on two counts. I'm sure you know this already.
Assault and evasion.
What was that? I heard gunshots!
It's from the direction Boss headed!
Did something happen to him?!
Hey, look at the sea!
It's the Navy! We're surrounded-choo!
Why are they here?
We're trapped!
That brat was a ploy to lure us here!
And Big Brother and all of us took it like fools!
See?! That's what humans do!
Damn the Navy!
Boss! Boss Tai is in danger!
Arlong!
Can you handle this? We gotta go save the Boss!
Okay, Brother Jinbe!
You have to bring Big Brother back safely!
I know! Let's go!
Arlong-san, this is not good! The ship is gonna be wrecked!
Everybody, get off of the ship!
Let's hijack one of the Navy ships!
Why is he still alive?
He's been shot so many times! Why is he still standing?!
I won't forgive you...
I won't forgive you! I won't forgive you, humans!
Shoot him!
I think I heard something. Did you hear anything, Mom?
No.
Boss...
Boss!
Rear Admiral-dono! The Sun Pirates are here!
So that must be...
...Jinbe.
You all... I'm sorry!
Boss!
You're responsible for all of this?!
Everything I've done is for justice...
...and to destroy the Sun Pirates!
Damn the Navy!
I'll kill you too!
Go ahead! I'd like to see you try!
We managed to rescue Boss
and flee to sea with a Navy ship that Arlong stole.
But...
Boss!
What do you mean that you don't want a transfusion? Boss!
Don't be ridiculous!
You lost too much blood! You're gonna die if you don't get one!
The Boss' blood type is rare! No one in our crew has the same blood type!
The blood stock on this Navy ship must be...
...human blood.
That's right. But humans and we share the same blood.
So we can use human blood to save you!
Now let me do this!
No!
I'd rather die than live with their blood!
Their blood is filthy.
They never stop disrespecting us Fishmen!
Boss...
I don't wanna owe them anything!
I don't need mercy from them!
I don't wanna give in to humans!
Big Brother! Was there something... between you and the humans?!
I didn't wanna tell you this!
On my last trip, I...
It was a long trip, wasn't it?
Yeah, a lot happened.
What did you see during your trip?
I saw humans!
Soon after I set off on my trip,
--I was caught. --What?
I spent several years in Mary Geoise.
I was...
...a slave!
No!
Boss!
What I saw there was the insanity of humans!
I fled for my life but...
...I couldn't just forget about all those slaves that I saw!
Listen carefully!
I did things the way I wanted and...
...I interfered with Queen Otohime as a result.
But she is right.
Everybody wants peace, of course!
But the only people who can make a difference on that island...
...are children of the next generation like Koala who aren't prejudiced.
So, please!
Don't tell the people on the island anything!
Neither the tragedy we endured nor of our anger towards humans!
But Big Brother...
Arlong!
There are so many humans who are compassionate!
I know! But...
...it's funny - the dying leave only their resentment behind.
And even though I know that there are kind humans,
there is a devil inside of me that is...
...clouding my thoughts.
My whole body rejects their blood!
I can't...
...accept humans!
Boss! Don't say such a thing and live! I beg you!
You don't have to die!
Boss! No matter what you say,
you're the greatest benefactor to all the slaves who were freed by you!
You're a hero to all Fishmen, who accomplished such a great feat!
I'm so happy...
You're not strong enough!
What?!
You have to step further. You can't protect anybody with that punch!
Huh? Protect?!
Brother!
If there is nobody else who wants to challenge me,
I'll become the leader of the Fishman District from today!
My name is Tiger!
Since I'm your brother now, leave everything up to me.
Your life is my life!
I'll keep my men safe!
Boss!
--Boss! --Boss!
Fisher Tigers death sent ripples far and wide.
Can Fishmen and humans coexist, or must they remain separate?
As the Fishmen waver, Arlong's hatred of humans
and Jinbe's desire to preserve Otohime and Tiger's ideals
will bring their convictions into conflict!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Sun Pirates Split! Jinbe vs Arlong!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!