It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement—there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail—let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag—together, we're one
One
Piece
Ice Age...
I'm impressed that you survived as a child.
You betrayed people and ran away.
You gained people's favor and used them.
You've survived in the underworld
by being quick to switch sides.
So this is the group that you
chose as your next hideout, huh?
The organizations Nico Robin had
something to do with up until today
all got annihilated...
...except for her.
You've come across some good friends.
But you're still you, Nico Robin!
No...! I'm no longer...
Robin!
I'm...
Robin-chan!
Duel between Rubber and Ice!
Luffy vs. Blue Pheasant
You bastard!
Don't yell... She'll still live
if you defrost her carefully.
But her body has become fragile, so be careful.
If her body is broken, she'll die.
For example...
What?!
if you smash it like this...
Robin!
No!
Stop it!!
Hm?
That was close...
--Good job!
--Amazing, Usopp!
What the hell...?
Usopp! Chopper!
Run to the ship! Treat Robin and save her!
G-Got it!
Hurry up...! But gently, okay?
--It's cold!
--You idiot! Think of how cold Robin is!
Don't bother...
It'd be better for the world
not to save that woman.
Not to split hairs, but a pirate group
is a collection of people like that.
You got that right, lady.
Get out of my way, would you?
Nami-san!
--We can't...
--...just let you...
Wait, you two!
Don't interfere. I wanna fight him in a duel.
Let's you and me...
...settle this fight!
That's fine...
...but since I don't have a ship to
take you back in, I'll kill you, okay?
She... can't breathe, can she?
I think she's probably in a
state of suspended animation.
Th-Then won't she die if we don't hurry up?
But if we warm her rapidly, her body will break.
We need to restore her body
temperature from the inside.
I-Is this really gonna work?
I don't know... but this is the only way...
You can't just say you don't know!
Robin's life depends on you!!
But I've never seen a human whose
entire body got frozen like this!
Sure, Blue Pheasant said she was still alive,
but to me, it's surprising that she's still alive!
Don't whine! If you can't do anything,
then no one can save her!
You're the doctor on this ship!
I know that! Just shut your mouth for a while!
Chopper!
Ah... What?! Why?! Just the three of you?!
We'll explain it later!
We're gonna go back right away!
Do something about our frozen arm and leg!
Ahh, okay. Let's see...
We have to melt those frozen
areas with water immediately.
But we're using the shower
room for Robin right now.
Is she okay?!
It's too early to tell.
What?
So will this do?
Once you melt the ice at low temperature,
come up to the ship while
rubbing the affected parts!
Nami! Help us treat Robin!
Okay!
Why are you guys here?
Where's Luffy?! What about Blue Pheasant?!
Luffy said he wanted a duel.
A duel?! And you guys left
Luffy there by himself?!
Those were the captain's orders.
Hey! Even if it was the captain's order,
you can't just do that!
Aren't you guys a little
too cold-hearted?! Luffy is...
Shut up!
It's a duel. Can't you understand?!
Stop it! This is no time for that!
We're... in a crisis right now.
Whether this decision is his
passing whim or whatever,
if anything should happen,
be prepared to respond to that!
As I thought, you're an odd one.
Gum-Gum...
...Storm!
Ice Time...
Let's you and me...
...settle this fight!
Darn... I was tricked.
Since I accepted the duel,
this fight ends when I win.
Now I see...
If I mess with the others now,
I'd be the senseless one here...
...right, Captain?
Or...
...did you seriously intend to defeat me?
Let me say this.
In the future, Nico Robin will grow...
That woman will definitely grow
to be too much for you to handle.
You guys will no longer be able to
shoulder the burden of the brutal fate
that Nico Robin was born into.
That's what it means...
...to let her on your ship...
...Monkey D. Luffy!
Breaking you right here, right now
and killing you would be very easy,
but we owe you one.
Now I want you to cancel our debt
to you for suppressing Crocodile.
Also...
Err... Well, I guess I don't have
to talk about that idiot Smoker.
See you around!
--There he is!
--Luffy!
He didn't get broken into pieces!
Good, good...
We'll carry him!
Let's hurry to the ship!
Don't talk at the same time!
According to this island's log,
their next destination is... Hm?
Water Seven... The city of water, huh?
Oh, my, my... They're really
getting closer to our Headquarters.
Oops, sorry about that.
Both of them...
Their hearts...
...started beating!
All right!
Luffy!
--Robin-chan!
--No! You can't go in yet!
You'll make a racket, right?
Hey, Dr. Chopper. I'll make something for them.
Y-You calling me "doctor" wouldn't
make me feel happy, you jerk!
Ah, when they wake up, some drinks
that can warm them up would be good.
I'll carry them to the lounge later.
Aye-aye, sir!
Nami, are we gonna sail out?
No, we aren't, with our captain like that.
We've already got the log,
but let's stay here for today.
Hm?
What's the matter, Usopp?
Are you feeling drained?
I wonder if strong guys like him
are coming after us from now on...
All I did was get flustered.
Get some sleep, you idiot. You're exhausted.
In order for Luffy and Robin to get
some rest, the Going Merry anchored
off the uninhabited island for four days.
After that, we sailed out.
This is the third morning since
we started our voyage again.
It's a fine day today, partly spring...
...with occasional bouts of summer.
What a beautiful day!
Nami-san!
I made potato paille. Mademoiselle, if you like...
Hmm, this is good!
I'm so happy!
Shut up, you jerk. You're disturbing my sleep!
Yeah, yeah, sorry about that, cactus head.
What'd you say, you dartboard jerk?!
Dar... What'd you just say, you bastard?!
Dartboard eyebrows.
Luffy! Yeah! Luffy! All right!
Luffy! Yeah! Luffy!
At last!
Luffy!
I'm impersonating my frozen self.
Geez... I can't believe he's doing that
after he got frozen and almost died.
--Did I do a good job?
--You did! You looked exactly like that, Luffy!
Clean that up good, okay, Luffy?!
Hm? What're you eating, Nami?
It's paille, a potato dish.
Potato, huh? I'm hungry, too. Hey, Sanji!
Just how much sleep do
you need to be satisfied?!
How much sleep I get is my business!
I'll take you on if you wanna fight!
Okay, stop right there!
Hey, Sanji-kun, our captain says
that he wants to eat paille.
Okay, Nami-san!
Sanji! Potatoes! Potatoes!
Even when you're recuperating,
you're the same old Luffy, aren't you?
They said this is called paille. Yummy!
What's paille?
It's the tail meat of a huge monster Paille.
I killed it. It was at least 100 meters high.
100 meters?! That's amazing, Usopp!
Hmm, a piece of cake. I did it before breakfast.
What? You got up early and killed it?
Chopper, say my name.
What? That's, of course, C-Captain...
That's right! My name is... Captain... Usopp!
Robin!
Yoo-hoo! Robin-chan!
How are you feeling? Do you feel a chill?
I'm feeling a lot better.
Thank you, my excellent doctor!
Oh... Being called an excellent doctor
wouldn't make me feel happy, you jerk.
--He sure does look happy.
--Yeah.
Take it easy, Robin.
You might feel uneasy when you
see Luffy being as good as new
after having the same experience as you,
but you can take your time and rest, you know.
--Yay!
--That wasn't a compliment!
Robin-chan! Shall I make
something that can warm you up?
Do you have an appetite?
Then... May I have some coffee?
Okay! It's my pleasure!
Hm?
What the hell is that?
Anyway, this paille thing is so good
that we can't stop eating, isn't it?
Yeah, it's yummy!
Hey, if we sell this thing, don't you
think we can make some money?
Hey, Luffy!
A-A frog is doing the front crawl!
What?!
It went to your side, so take a look at it!
--Is that true?
--A frog... Could it be that frog?
Hey, Luffy, are you taking what
that stupid Admiral said seriously?
To start with, there's no way a frog
would do the front cra... Hey, it is!
A-A frog is doing the front crawl!
--We'll follow it, guys!
--Yeah!
Furl the sail! Stand by the oars!
Turn the ship to 2 o'clock!
--Yeah!
--Hurry up!
I don't know why, but I feel
like we have to go after it!
Sorry to keep you waiting, mademoiselles.
What the...
What?! What happened?!
Seems like the ship changed course.
Hey, you guys! Why'd you change
the course without asking me?!
Hey, Nami, you've got to hear this!
We found a huge frog
with scars all over its body!
What the heck?
We're definitely gonna roast it whole and eat it!
You're gonna eat it?!
Hey, you're right...
Hm? Is that a lighthouse?
Why is there a lighthouse in a place
like that? I wonder if someone's there...
Wh-What's the matter? Do you see an island?
No, there's a lighthouse. A Log Pose
wouldn't point to that sort of place.
What about the frog? Tell us
the direction the frog went!
Not a chance!
The frog is headed to the lighthouse.
--What?
--To cook frogs, first remove
the slime using white wine,
and then dredge them in
flour and fry them crisp.
Hey, Sanji-kun!
If our captain says we're going,
what choice do we have but to go?
Robin...!
All right! Full speed ahead!
Yeah!
What's with the solidarity?!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!...
It flew!
Don't let it get away! We'll move
ahead of it and block its course!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
We ran ashore on something!
Ahh... Nami-san, Robin-chan, are you guys okay?
Yeah, somehow...
I'm okay.
Good... Hm?
What? What's this sound?
What? What's going on?
Is this...? Don't tell me...
Why... in a place like this...?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Go back! Go back! Turn 180 degrees!
We're setting off toward the distant orange horizon
Today's winds are blowing
across the morning sea
I can't sleep
The kind of passion I saw this very morning
cannot be stifled by anyone
Hope, frustration
and much more might come our way
but for now
we can just start from scratch
Some time ago, we had a dream
in which we followed our aspirations
so we'll raise our hands high
and embrace the shining sun in our hearts
We're going to make it to that place
What the hell is that?!
A ship?! No, it's not!
Hey, it's coming this way!
--Amazing!
--It's not!
We'd better get out of here now!
Hey, that frog is headed towards it!
--Is he trying to collide with it?!
--Ahh! Wait! My meat!
That's not meat!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Dashing Sea Train
and the City of Water, Water Seven"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Dashing Sea Train
and the City of Water, Water Seven