The ocean saw the world begin,
and the ocean knows
how the world will end.
Thus, it calls us
down the path we must take.
Thus, it leads us to a just world.
It envelops all pain and suffering,
honorably and kindly
wrapping them up.
I will crush all pirates!
I will follow Z-sensei anywhere.
Grow, grow!
Get some!
My life’s devotion is
to serve Z-sensei alone!
Smash Buster!
Damn you.
Smash Blaster!
Grow!
The Sacred Yata Mirror!
Retreat! We must retreat!
Z-sensei.
Oh, long time no see, Sensei!
Why did you come here?
Borsalino!
Didn’t I warn you not to rely on
the Glint-Glint Fruit’s powers too much?!
I see you’re as strict as ever,
Zephyr-sensei!
I’ve abandoned that name! I am Z!
Those lax fools in the Navy may have
given you the title “Admiral Yellow Monkey,”
but don’t let it go to your head!
I didn’t come here to
reminisce about the old days.
How do you expect to keep up with my speed
using a bulky weapon like that?
What are you going to use
the Dyna Stones for, anyway?
You know, you and I
never really got along, did we?!
Come on, just give the
Dyna Stones back already.
They say that the Dyna Stones
rival even the ancient weapons!
How about we test their power together,
to commemorate our reunion?!
When Dyna Stones come into contact with oxygen,
they cause a massive explosion.
Here we go!
Z-sensei!
Oh my.
He completely destroyed us.
My, my, my.
What on earth is the Navy doing?
Oh, yeah!
Come on!
Come on, baby!
I am the skeleton of endless joy!
Come on!
Cherry blossoms! Cherry blossoms!
This is quite nice...
drinking and watching the flowers.
The cherry blossoms blossom, blossom cherry blossoms!
Don’t you agree, Chopper?
Yeah! Milk also goes well
with watching the flowers.
These aren’t cherry blossoms!
It’s me!
Super!
You go, Franky!
Phew! It smells like poison!
I’m a goner!
What’s wrong, Chopper?
Did you inhale something?!
Chopper!
An inhaled poison...
Of course, it’s obvious!
You’ve figured it out?
Please listen to my new song,
“Inhaled Poison”!
You figured out a song?!
Toxic, toxic, toxic poison...
Now that I think about it,
the booze tastes weird too.
Or maybe it’s just a really dry brew
that’s supposed to taste like this?
Toxic, toxic, toxic poison...
It’s dangerous, so don’t swallow it!
They’re as lively as ever.
Blossom... Blossom...
Now, all of you, keep growing
Pop Greens for me!
The great pest destroyer Usopp-sama
will protect you from insects!
Usopp!
So you’re the culprit!
Look! Chopper collapsed
because of that stuff you’re spraying around!
That’s because you’re all
standing downwind!
This is a pesticide.
It only kills pests!
If it kills you, then that must mean
that you’re a pest!
I see. Well, that’s a relief.
We’re not bugs after all.
Oh, so we’re safe?
This booze makes my tongue tingle,
but it’s still pretty good.
This is a bit bitter...
Maybe it’s meant for adults?
Let me try it!
Nasty.
I’m pretty sure that stuff’s
harmful to the human body, too.
I am the cherry blossoms.
I slowly advance northward.
Luffy-san, the cherry blossoms...
Flower viewing season
is coming to an end!
Hold it, cherry blossoms!
Hurry!
Nah, on second thought,
I’ll go south instead!
Change course!
Bastard,
why did you spill the booze?!
They’re so noisy!
Why can’t they just relax?
Hey, shut up you guys!
Sheesh.
Hey, Nami-swan!
I have brought you
my Orange Special!
Thank you, Sanji-kun.
I’d like some dessert, too.
Yes, Nami-san! With pleasure!
Hey, Sanji!
Huh?
Gimme some dessert, too!
Oh, and meat!
I want to eat some sweets, as well!
Me too!
And some cola, too!
There’s not enough booze here.
I’ll have some dessert, too!
Shut it, damn bastards!
Maybe if you asked more politely!
I was born for the ladies!
Nasty!
Hey, Usopp!
Your pesticide’s
raining down, again!
I already finished spraying!
What could this be?
It’s snow!
No, it’s too hot to be snowing.
What’s going on?
This is volcanic ash!
Volcanic ash?
This feels disgusting!
The volcanic ash
got in your fur, didn’t it?
We can take a bath together, later.
Bath?!
Together?!
Today isn’t my bathing-day...
but all right.
This is really disgusting.
And I! May I join you...
in the bath?
I mean, just look!
My face is really disgusting as well!
Don’t be offended
by your own remarks.
No.
Brook,
I don’t mind if you join in!
Chopper-san, I love you!
Hey, Nami.
Something on your mind?
One of the compass needles was pointing
in the direction that the volcanic ash came from.
Now, it’s shaking weirdly.
The movements don’t look right.
It looks like a child
who has lost their parents.
Lost child? What do you mean?
Well, if the eruption that caused
volcanic ash to rain down...
blew the entire island away...
The needle would no longer
have a magnetic field to lock on to?
That’s impossible!
This is the New World.
That’s right.
Nobody asked you.
Scatter before Nami-san’s beauty,
robo-cherry-blossom!
Nami-san,
would you like some tea?
Thank you.
In any case, we have to stay away
from the island this compass needle points to!
Speaking of which, Nami...
There is one man here
who must never see that needle.
You’re right.
It’s my job to choose the safest path,
and to ensure that nobody in the crew dies.
Hey! That needle’s moving in a really cool way!
Luffy!
Let’s go that way!
Dammit! He saw it!
I smell adventure!
W-Wait! Hang on a second, Luffy!
J-Just listen!
Nami says that the ash from before—
Hey, everyone!
I’ve settled on a course!
Get ready to go!
Luffy!
But seriously,
with the needle spinning around like that,
you don’t even know where the island—
Don’t be silly.
I’m the navigator.
Once our course is set,
I’ll get you there,
wherever it may be!
Luffy, keep watch!
Sure, leave it to me!
Hey, are you sure about this?
In the New World, choosing between the three courses
can decide whether you live or die, right?
Franky, turn the steering wheel
twenty degrees.
Turn the steering wheel
twenty degrees, aye aye!
Hey, are you listening?!
I don’t know what’ll happen next.
We just have to brace ourselves!
We don’t have a choice.
He is the captain, after all.
But I definitely don’t want to run into a volcanic explosion
or anything life-threatening like that!
Survivor spotted!
Begin rescue immediately!
Wah, he’s floating away!
I’ll handle it!
Luffy, what’s wrong?!
My powuh’th fading...
Luffy, don’t let go yet!
Sure...
Heave, ho!
Luffy, are you all right?
Yup!
Well? Is he alive?
His pulse and breathing are faint,
but he’s just unconscious.
His life is not in danger.
I see.
Are you sure you didn’t
pick up another dangerous fellow?
His body’s all rough
and covered in scars.
And then there’s this thing
attached to his right arm.
He obviously isn’t
an ordinary guy.
I knew it.
This is made of Sea Stone.
I see! So that’s why Luffy lost his strength
when he grabbed it!
A powerful weapon
made of Sea Stone...
So cool!
That’s not what I was getting at!
Sea Stone emits the
same kind of energy as the sea.
If his weapon’s made from that stuff,
then it must have been made
to take out Devil Fruit users like you.
He might be an enemy.
They say you can’t let your guard down
in the New World.
If you’re worried,
then just throw him overboard.
Idiot!
There’s no way we could do that!
I’m against it!
He might kill you
as soon as he recovers.
Even so, I’m a doctor!
I can’t abandon him!
It’s fine.
Treat his wounds, Chopper!
And if he turns on us,
I’ll send him flying!
Everyone okay with that?
Yeah! Thanks, Luffy!
Well, a warrior of the sea
can’t be afraid!
How can they always be
so optimistic?
I have a really bad feeling about this.
It’s exciting, isn’t it?!
I don’t need this kind of excitement!
Luffy, it sounds like he’s awake!
Yeah, feels like it.
Hey, crap-cook.
Oh, shut it.
I can feel him, damn moss-ball.
Would you believe it?
We’ve picked up quite the big shot.
To Chopper-kun
Are you all right?
Don’t try to get up if you don’t feel ready.
You were drifting on the sea.
Do you remember?
Yeah, I know.
I’m grateful for your skilled treatment.
You saved my life, Doctor.
I’m Chopper!
Doctor Chopper.
You are a magnificent doctor.
Praising me like that
won’t make me happy, you jerk!
You must be this ship’s captain.
You can tell?
I can. I’ve seen plenty of
young people like you.
Gauging their strength
is a specialty of mine.
I see. So what’ll you do now, Pops?
Do you want a ride to the next island?
I have a Vivre Card.
My comrades are following it,
and should be here soon.
Pops, that weapon’s really cool!
Where can I buy one?
After a lowly pirate cut off my arm,
the mad scientists at the Navy put this on me.
The Battle Smasher.
The claw is made from Sea Stone,
a Devil Fruit user’s weakness, so it saps their power...
before eliminating them
with a single blast of intense firepower.
Doctor Chopper,
I can’t recommend this heavy thing.
Awesome!
It won’t come off without using special equipment,
so if you fall into the sea, you’re in serious trouble.
You in the Navy?
No, I got too old, so I quit.
I’m doing something else now.
What?
I’m fighting to carry out
a self-given mission.
Who’re you fighting against?
This is starting to feel like
an interrogation.
Sorry!
If you were still in the Navy,
I suppose there’d be trouble between us.
Would it be bad if I was a marine?
Yeah, ‘cause we’re pirates.
I see. So you’re pirates?!
Luffy!
Nami-san, get outside!
I-I’m counting on you!
Ow... A Sea Stone punch really hurts!
Man with the straw hat.
What do you seek to accomplish
by being a pirate?
I will become the Pirate King!
Pirate King.
Did you say Pirate King?!
He’s strong!
Dammit!
B-Brook!
We have to get out of here!
Yes!
They’ve arrived.
I am Ain,
Vice Admiral of the Neo-Navy.
We, the Neo-Navy,
have your pirate ship surrounded.
Do not resist.
You will only die quicker.
No pirate would obey
a command to surrender!
There’s a fight out here, too!
Grow, grow!
What the hell is this?!
That’s...
A Devil Fruit!
Behold the power of
the Grow-Grow Fruit.
The Grow-Grow Dance
controls all plant life!
Things sound bad outside, too.
Let’s finish this quickly!
Dos Fleur!
Mosa!
Grow, grow! Grow, grow, grow!
He’s too quick!
I can’t keep track of him!
Grow, grow, grow!
Can’t breathe!
Not good!
Stay off the lawn!
Grow, grow!
No, wait!
What’s this?!
Stop it!
N-N-No!
Gust Sword!
Return-Return!
Nami!
What did you do to Nami?!
Heavy Point!
Return-Return!
Chopper-san!
Chopper!
Oh no... You... Stop it!
Ah, stay away!
No! Don’t! Don’t!
Brook!
Stop this!
Seis Fleur!
You’re a Devil Fruit user too, I see.
What did you do to Nami and Chopper?!
Robin!
Cancel the Flower-Flower Fruit’s power!
Return-Return!
I’m a reverting woman who
ate the Return-Return Fruit.
My power reverts whatever it affects
to the state it was in twelve years ago.
You’d be about eighteen years old now,
it seems.
I’m tiny!
If I touch you two more times,
you’d revert twelve years twice,
so twenty-four years...
and your very existence
would be erased.
Smash Buster!
How can you expect to become the Pirate King
when you’re this weak?
Laughable!
Should I just crush you?
What do you say, Pirate King?
Name yourself.
I’m Monkey D. Luffy.
I see.
So you’re Garp’s grandson.
Z-sensei, I’m glad you’re safe.
We will sink this pirate ship
with concentrated cannon fire from our fleet.
Luffy!
Are you all right, Luffy?
I am Z, the supreme commander
of the Neo-Navy!
Z will exterminate
every last pirate in the world!
Let’s see how long you survive,
“Pirate King”!
Dammit!
Wait!
Our fight... Our fight isn’t...
over yet!
Sunny!
Dammit!
Chopper, hurry and get these off!
This is really bad!
Luffy!
Luffy, we have to escape!
Franky!
We’re getting out of here!
Damn that bastard!
Super!
Please, Sunny!
I believe in you!
Emergency Withdrawal System...
Coup de Burst!
He’s really done it now.
The Dyna Stones were meant
to protect the End Points from pirates,
and he used them to
destroy the End Point instead!
The first End Point sunk into the ocean,
along with the Navy base protecting it.
Z’s goal is probably to destroy the three End Points,
thus annihilating the New World.
Even he couldn’t escape unscathed after
being caught in the Dyna Stones’ explosion, could he?
He’s alive.
Everyone here should know...
that he won’t die so easily.
Z... No,
former Navy Admiral,
Black Arm Zephyr.
He’s alive.
Whatever the case,
we must get the Dyna Stones back.
We may have been in his care before,
but now he is an enemy to our justice.
And even if Z himself survives,
those people who call themselves
the Neo-Navy...
must be exterminated
in the name of justice.
With all the Navy’s might,
pursue Z and the Neo-Navy!
Reclaim the Dyna Stones,
and dispense justice with extreme prejudice.
If the End Points are destroyed,
the world will end...
I thought that was just a story?
Everyone in the world knows it’s a lie.
If it was a lie,
why would we need to treat it so seriously?
We know what Z’s goal is.
It is to destroy all pirates
in the New World.
Using the End Points, he can do that.
But of course, he wouldn’t
just destroy the pirates,
but all the innocent citizens as well.
Vice Admiral Garp... Who is Z?
He was one of us once.
We were comrades.
Or I thought we were, at least.
Zephyr...
Are you really angry enough
to destroy the world?
Are you truly incapable
of forgiving us?
Luffy!
I’ll fix the Sunny up perfectly!
It’ll take a while, but you’re going after Z
in the meantime, right?
Yeah.
Take care of the Sunny.
This is the payment for using the dock,
this is for the hotel rooms, and...
I’m sorry.
I’m the one who insisted on
saving that Z guy.
Don’t apologize.
A pirate doesn’t regret
following their convictions.
It’s not your fault.
We understand.
Thank you.
Who is the Neo-Navy...
and Z?
He attacked us
as soon as he heard that we were pirates!
That Binz guy’s powers
were really annoying.
Next time,
we’ll settle the score with them.
Besides, we have to avenge the Sunny,
who fought so bravely.
If the Sunny hadn’t fought so hard,
we’d all be on the bottom of the sea
after the Neo-Navy’s barrage.
We have to find the Neo-Navy
and pay them back.
Seriously?!
I don’t wanna go near that dangerous bunch!
Let’s just stay quietly on this island
until Sunny’s been fixed!
What are you saying?!
If we don’t find them,
we can’t return my body back to normal!
I don’t wanna stay like this either!
I can’t do anything in a child’s body!
The voyage through the New World
will be tougher than anything we’ve faced before!
In order to lead the Sunny
as a navigator,
I have to get back to normal!
That’s right!
I-I don’t mean that you should
just stay like that!
I really should turn back
to normal, too.
Wait... You’ve been turned into
a spry eighteen year-old.
You’re actually happy about this,
aren’t you?
I’m sorry!
Seriously...
The ladies are having a rough time,
so stop joking around!
No, wait a second!
This means that
I’ll be able to share those precious days...
as Nami-san’s body
matures into adulthood?!
I’ll be able to see the chrysalis
grow into a butterfly!
Amazing!
Creepy.
Huh?!
I’ll fillet you, damn Mosshead!
If you’d been reverted into a kid,
I’d stomp on you!
Stupid!
Even as a kid I could beat you!
What was that?!
I’d be able to beat you
even if I was turned into a three-year-old!
Dumbass!
Huh?!
Then I’d do it even as a baby!
What?! Then I’d—
You’d what?!
This isn’t the time for petty quarrels!
Ummm...
Actually,
I was made younger as well.
What?
You don’t...
seem to have...
changed at all, though.
I was touched by that Ain lady
from the Neo-Navy, as well.
You were, now that you mention it...
but you didn’t change at all.
No, I am Dead Bones Brook!
I may have been a corpse for over fifty years,
but in that time,
I have never experienced
such a vast transformation!
I have been made
twelve years younger.
Look! My hair has regained
the shine and softness it had in my seventies!
As if we could tell!
You dyed your hair, didn’t you?!
Besides, doesn’t that mean
you’re happy to be younger?
You don’t need to go back
to normal, right?
I suppose so.
No, that will not do!
I, too, wish to return to normal!
Don’t I?
How would I know?!
If we want to return to normal,
we’ll need information on Z and the Neo-Navy.
Something you want, old man?
If it’s about our docking fee,
ask our navigator.
Z did it again, huh?
Old man, you know Z?
An awful lot of pirate ships
have been attacked lately.
They drifted to this dock afterward.
All the wounded pirates
say the same thing:
That they were attacked by Z.
These days,
all the customers that Grampa gets at the dock...
are pirates who have been
attacked by Z.
We earn a living on this island
by fixing ships and renting out the docks,
and sheltering pirate ships
that have been damaged by marines.
Grampa used to be a sailor,
so even if his customers
are pirates,
he does everything he can
to look after them.
I just like anyone who risks their life
in the New World, pursuing their dreams.
But it’s the law of the jungle
out there.
Many who have been defeated by Z
lose their spirit,
and leave the New World.
Z is taking the freedom away
from those who sail the sea.
Even if supporting them
is considered a crime,
I just can’t accept what he’s doing!
If you really meant it when you said that losing to Z
has only motivated you to stand up to him again,
then I want to give you the ultimate equipment
that those pirates left behind.
Ultimate equipment?!
Ultimate? Amazing!
Wow!
Hang on!
What is it, Nami?
It’s the ultimate we’re talking about!
Before thinking about the ultimate whatever,
we have to find Z, right?
Besides, all our clothes burned up
during Z’s attack,
so we have to replace those, too.
We can’t just stay
in these ridiculous cherry blossom party outfits.
They’ll get in the way if we find Z.
The information and clothes
comes first!
Defeating Z using this ultimate equipment
comes later!
Right, got it!
Nami-chan, you’re so small
and yet so responsible!
Oh, excuse me. Are there any big cities on this island
where we can get clothes or information?
There’s nothing on this island
besides our dock.
Why don’t you go to
the neighboring island?
It’s a popular tourist destination
because of the hot springs and volcano.
The Sea Train started going there lately, too,
so their business is really booming.
Sea Train? The Sea Train?
That’s right.
Oh right, Luffy.
And you listen, too, Mosshead and skeleton.
Your faces are too recognizable.
Leave the information gathering to me.
Right, Nami-swan? Robin-chwan?
You can’t do it either, Sanji-kun.
Whaaat?!
A hot temper is just as bad
as being too well-known.
We’ll handle the
information gathering.
But...
Together...
Resort...
Since we’re going to the hot springs,
why not soothe our bodies before the fight?
Yes, yes!
And I will put together
a fashionable ensemble for us.
It looks like they have
some wonderful brands on this island.
We’re here!
All right everyone,
make sure the Navy doesn’t find you!
Dismissed!
Yeah!
Volcanic hot spring
Now let us go, let us go!
Sheesh.
You Devil Fruit users have
so many weaknesses.
You even lose your power
in the bath?
We can more or less manage
when we’re only half-submerged.
The water feels great.
We’ve just been relaxing
in the baths for days now.
Should we really be this lax?
That’s right!
I wanna send Z flying!
Idiot.
Navy patrols are all over this island.
If someone as whimsical as you
went wandering off blindly...
you’d just cause more trouble again.
Don’t you remember
what Nami-san said?
Leave the information gathering
to Robin-chan and the others.
Fantastic! Such a lively dance.
The customers love it!
I’m glad you like it, master!
Are you going on a date, Sir?
That’s right.
So please be thorough.
Ahhh, the water soothes me
down to the bones...
Ah, I guess I’m all bones.
My bones seem to be making
a nice soup stock.
Z...
I was too impressed
by that huge weapon on his right arm.
I let my guard down.
You’re a Devil Fruit user,
so if you just charge in blindly
without thinking...
you’ll just end up being caught by
that Sea Stone arm again, and lose your strength.
You should let me
or the moss-headed swordsman handle Z.
You stay out of it!
I want to send him flying myself!
This time I’ll avoid that arm of his
and hit him with my own attacks!
I see you’re as lively as ever.
I’ve waited for you here so long
that I’ve become dizzy.
Blue Pheasant!
Why are you all so worked up?
Who might this fellow be?
He’s a marine!
Admiral Blue Pheasant,
from Navy HQ!
An Admiral?!
Hey.
Long time no see.
The Dyna Stones are in place.
I see.
When this volcano erupts,
those lax marines...
will know the strength...
of Z’s anger and hatred!
Zoro! Sanji!
Got it!
What business does an Admiral
have with us?!
Now now,
don’t get so worked up.
What do you want with us?
Don’t tell me you’re...
No, no...
there’s no reason for me to capture you now.
I’ve long since left the Navy.
You should already know
that I’m not a Navy Admiral anymore.
Then... what are you?!
What am I? I don’t feel comfortable
with a skeleton questioning my place in the world...
but now that I’m no longer
an Admiral...
An ally of justice?
No, that’s not right.
What am I?
How should we know?!
So, with things the way they are,
I have no desire to fight with you.
Besides, just think about it.
If that was my goal, why would I wait for you
in the bath, where I can’t even use my powers?
You were waiting for us?
That’s right.
Well, I’d rather not keep
boiling myself like this,
so let’s continue
this conversation outside.
Oh? You’re looking at this?
Well, how to put it...
I got into a bit of mischief.
Did you figure anything out,
Chopper?
I heard rumors that the Navy is gathering
on this island, chasing after Z,
but that’s all the
information I got.
Just rumors, huh?
There are definitely a lot more marines
showing up at the club...
but I don’t know if that’s because of Z,
or just because Robin is so popular.
It’s hard to tell.
Is Robin that popular?
Damn right! Including tips,
we’ve already made this much money!
Amazing!
We can’t just trust a rumor, right?
So what do we do?
Hmmm... All right!
Leave it to me!
What happened to your leg?
Some things shouldn’t be asked.
Keep that in mind.
All right, never mind. Then...
why’d you fight the Red Hound?
You’re friends, right?
Good grief, you really
have no tact, do you?
Again, no comment.
So what are you doing here?
You never learn, do you?
Well, I guess I can answer that.
The hot springs are curative...
...is what I’d like to say.
But it isn’t like I can relax
in the bath all day.
I’m chasing a certain man.
You people fought
a pretty remarkable fellow recently, right?
Z!
He was strong, wasn’t he?
Well, of course.
He was a Navy Admiral, after all.
Thank you for waiting!
Thanks.
You work pretty hard
for someone so young.
Mr. Marine.
Has anything interesting
happened recently?
Do you know about Z?
Miss, how do you know about—
Everyone knows!
All the adults are saying...
that the marines are here
to capture Z!
What, has the word
really spread so far?
H-Hey!
What does it matter?
So that means Z
is on this island, right?
That’s right!
We are allies of justice,
come to capture the evil Z!
So what is he after?
What is Z doing on this island?
Stop it already.
He’s trying to destroy
the End Points.
What? The End Points?!
I thought that was just
a story to scare kids!
Nope, it’s true!
That’s enough!
You’ve had too much to drink.
Stop running your mouths!
We’re sorry, Captain!
And you’re too interested in Z,
young lady.
What are you after?
Nothing! That weird man
told me to go ask about Z!
I see.
A weird man indeed.
Damn it!
Nami sent them after us!
Should we run?
Unfortunately, it seems that
the phony manager act ends here!
Okay, I have to get back to work now.
I would like you to come with us.
Let go of me!
Seis Fleur!
We have to run.
Right!
Captain, are you all right?!
This is the power of
the Flower-Flower Fruit!
That woman is Nico Robin
from the Straw Hat Pirates!
Don’t let her get away!
Yes, Sir!
We are in
the Great Age of Pirates.
Out on that sea, pirates are born and die in search of the One Piece...
and for each one that dies,
another is born.
Are pirates born because the One Piece waits
on the far side of this sea?
Or does the One Piece only exist
because pirates do?
What comes first?
The dream or the dreamers?
As long as pirates
pursue their dreams,
there will also be people
who have to grieve the loss of loved ones.
What can one do?
Is there even an answer?
Former Navy Admiral Z
forcibly gave his own answer.
“If the One Piece vanishes,
the pirates will vanish with it.”
Don’t you think he’s
jumping to conclusions?
I quit the Navy,
but I still intend to see where Z’s efforts take him.
But beyond that,
I don’t know what to do.
Straw Hat Luffy.
I’m sure you will follow your beliefs and
end up clashing with Z again.
Let me see your answer.
Later.
Z is on this island.
We went through all the effort of disguising ourselves,
but it wound up a huge mess anyway!
But we’ve got
the information we want!
Z is on this island.
We don’t know what he’s up to,
but still!
There they are!
Go on ahead!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Devil!
All right! Now let’s meet up
with Luffy and the others!
Yes!
What do you think
of the clothes I chose?
Don’t you think
they look fantastic...
on me?
Just on you?!
I feel like the ladies
will be all over me.
Shut it, Bones.
Let’s see how long you survive,
“Pirate King”!
Luffy! Luffy!
Usopp’s group is here.
Looks like they’ve got a lot of people
following them!
So things got out of hand after all.
Then we might as well have...
Hey, Luffy!
We have to ask where Z is, remember?
Leave a few of them conscious.
Luffy, we’re counting on you!
Please.
This is...
the Conqueror’s Haki.
Hey. Where is Z now?
He’s on the far side
of the island.
Our troops were sent to
ambush him in the dunes.
Iron Mass!
Your justice is useless.
Things like justice and freedom...
have to be torn down
and rebuilt from scratch!
It looks like the Dyna Stones
have woken the island.
The second End Point
has successfully been destroyed.
Grand Reboot.
That’s what destroying
all three End Points will do.
When all pirates are gone from the seas,
the world will see a magnificent new dawn!
Gum-Gum...
Rifle!
Why did you come here...
you hoodlum pirates?
Who’re you callin’ hoodlums?!
Keep spouting delirious crap like that
and I’ll fillet you, gramps!
Pops!
Return my crewmates to normal!
Ain! Binz!
Yes, Sir!
Understood.
I’ll fight the female swordsman.
Damn Mosshead,
don’t sneak ahead!
All right, there is no need
for me to join the fight!
Go get’em, you three!
Grow! Grow! Grow!
Grow, grow, grow!
Pirates just take what they want by force,
do they not?
If you want your crewmates restored,
then do it the pirate way!
Dammit, guess there’s no choice!
Usopp.
I’m going one-on-one against Z!
H-Hey, Luffy!
Z!
It’s hopeless!
We can’t get away!
Somebody, save us!
Hold it right there!
Now, my fair ladies,
take care on your way
to the Sea Train.
Thank you so much!
No regard for
who gets caught in it, huh?
Going a bit too far there,
don’t you think?
I won’t be caught by
that weapon again!
Speeding up the flow of your blood,
in order to push your body strength
beyond its limits, huh?
Gear 2!
You said you’re gonna be
the Pirate King, right?
Yeah, I’m gonna find the One Piece
and become the Pirate King!
I see.
But do you have the resolve?
Do you have the resolve
to risk your own life?!
I do!
Then what about your crew?!
Do you have the resolve to sacrifice your crew
for the sake of your ambition?
To step over their corpses
and accomplish your goals?!
Hurry!
You’re still not coming?!
We have to get moving,
or else we’ll be swallowed by the eruption!
Are they...
all right?
Return-Return!
That’s enough!
If we ever meet again,
I will finish you off for good!
My time has run out.
I take my leave!
Poof!
She got away.
Damn funny ninja!
As long as you fear the Smasher,
you’ll never be able to
land a single hit on me!
Who’s afraid?!
Fear and pain
only dulls your conviction!
Smash Tornado!
I’m rubber, so bullets...
won’t hurt me!
Is that so?
Ah... My power’s... fading.
Your body can’t move.
That bullet is made of Sea Stone.
Something of a rarity, isn’t it?
Sea Stone is not
easily malleable, after all.
The infamous pirates that infest the New World
aren’t likely to fall for this...
but when a Devil Fruit user is overconfident
and lets their guard down...
it is exceedingly effective!
You have some serious crimes
to atone for.
This straw hat has gotten old too.
I will bury it with my own hands,
along with this entire Great Age of Pirates!
Give that back!
Shanks entrusted me
with that hat!
I’ve promised to meet him
and give it back!
Give it back!
So it was Red-Hair Shanks
who led you to the life of a pirate!
He, too, has some serious crimes
to atone for.
Give it... back!
You needn’t worry.
Once my plan, Grand Reboot,
is completed,
he will be joining you!
Even that idiot, who’s become cocky
as one of the so-called Four Emperors,
will never even notice my plan...
and be powerless to stop
his own death.
Don’t mock...
Shanks!
This isn’t good!
It looks like the lava’s starting to flow!
Usopp!
How’s Luffy doing?
Luffy!
Luffy?! Luffy?!
Luffy...
There’s nothing we can do
against that.
Let’s go!
How fast is that thing moving?!
Nami said it was over
one hundred kilometers per hour!
I see!
I know!
Since we’re on a slope...
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Boaty Banana!
Get onboard!
Make this thing move faster!
You see an engine on it?!
It’s just a boat!
Look ahead! We’ll crash!
It doesn’t have a handle either!
It’s just a boat!
Everyone lean to the right!
Now it’s a crossroad!
We’re done for!
Damn it!
Hurry! Hurry up!
Quite the fireworks.
The entire island’s gone.
Sensei, what about
that man with the straw hat?
The mountain of fire
will decide his fate.
The One Piece?
All this world has to offer?
What a foolish dream!
How many needless sacrifices
have been made for that nonsense?
How much sorrow and hatred?
They call it will, freedom,
or the waves of an era...
so Z will crush all of it!
By Z’s hand...
all pirates will be wiped from this world!
Every single one will be annihilated!
I’ll make their ridiculous dreams bow down
before my infinite hatred, and then destroy them!
I, Z, will bring down the curtain...
on this Great Age of Pirates!
I have great sympathy
for what happened to him in the past.
But it’s unacceptable to use it as an excuse
to cause tragedies that even civilians get caught in.
You state your beliefs directly,
as always.
Most people aren’t as quick to draw a line
between good and evil as you are.
You know that.
Right, Sengoku?
Vice Admiral Garp.
What is it?
Z... I mean, former
Navy Admiral Zephyr.
What kind of person was he?
He believed in the Navy’s justice
more strongly than anyone.
So why is he causing these disasters?
A certain incident happened.
A certain incident?
Zephyr was a dedicated man.
Even on the battlefield,
he always stayed ahead of his men.
He fought against many enemies in that era,
and his body paid the cost.
He became an Admiral
at a young age,
and he lived a full, rich life until...
his wife and child were killed
by a pirate with a grudge against Zephyr.
Zephyr truly understood
the weight of being a Navy Admiral.
He locked the pain and sadness deep within his heart
and dedicated himself to his duties.
As the years went by...
Zephyr put his passion into
raising and training young marines.
He is the man who trained all marines.
Every officer that has made a name for themselves
was once his apprentice.
I want to raise heroes.
But another tragedy befell him.
Zephyr was leading
a squadron of new recruits on a training mission,
when a pirate with Devil Fruit
powers attacked...
and all but two of
the recruits were killed.
Zephyr, himself, was gravely injured.
The pirate cut off his right arm.
A Navy Admiral lost his arm?!
After that, the Navy’s science division equipped Zephyr
with a weapon to take out Devil Fruit users.
He formed a commando unit
with his surviving apprentices...
and hunted every pirate who’d eaten a Devil Fruit
they could find.
But he remained in the Navy.
I suppose he hadn’t entirely
lost faith in us, just yet.
But finally...
the last straw came
and Zephyr left the Navy.
That year,
the pirate who had slaughtered his students...
was recognized by the Government
as one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
And so, Zephyr left the Navy...
and only now has he shown himself again
in the New World.
He bears a deep hatred for pirates
and has lost all faith in the Navy,
so he heads his own organization,
the Neo-Navy.
The unforgiving weight of his life...
has changed that man.
You’re useless, Navy!
Why did Black Arm Zephyr
change his name to Z?
Z, huh...
Who knows?
But I can say this...
Enemies who have no doubt
are formidable.
The ocean saw the world begin,
and the ocean knows
how the world will end.
Even after I’m gone,
the all-knowing ocean will lead the way.
I must not fear,
because you are here.
I must not be timid,
because my comrades wait for me.
I always hated this song,
Sensei.
A song that cheers marines forward to their deaths...
It makes me shudder.
You liked this, right?
Yeah. This is the coolest
drink there is.
I often imitated you
and drank it myself...
because I wanted to become
a cool man.
Did you come to lecture
a hard-headed old man?
Sorry, but I’m not gonna stop.
Are you planning to die?
There’s no avoiding that,
I suppose.
But it’s for the sake of
destroying the evil known as pirates.
The Navy is incapable of
enacting true justice.
It’s starting to feel crowded here.
Let’s have a drink together
the next time we meet.
Now go!
I don’t want to kill you.
Nor I you, Zephyr-sensei.
So this is the Sea Stone bullet.
It was lodged in Luffy’s shoulder.
How long are you gonna
keep lazing about out here?
B-Blue Pheasant!
Y-Y...
W-What is the Blue Pheasant
doing here?!
It’s all right.
We already met earlier.
Former Navy HQ Admiral Z?
He has stolen the Dyna Stones
from the Navy.
The Dyna Stones?!
What are they?
Stones that are said to possess destructive power
that rivals the ancient weapons.
If you strike and expose them
to open air,
it is said that they will create
an exceptionally powerful explosion.
Due to their immensely destructive power,
the general public is strictly forbidden from possessing them.
The Navy is supposed to
keep them all locked away.
But now, Z has them?
He intends to
use the Dyna Stones...
to awaken the three End Points
that lie in the New World.
Wait a second!
What are End Points?
There are three enormous clusters of magma
beneath the New World,
which are called End Points.
When I heard the marines talking about them,
I doubted my own ears...
but they really do exist?
I still can’t believe that the sexy lady
has been reverted to a—
Are you even listening to me?!
Do the End Points really exist?
They do.
Firs Island, and Secon Island.
I’m sure that even after hearing the news
about these two islands,
most pirates would just
snort at the idea.
Many know about the legend of the End Points,
but none believe it.
But didn’t the Navy investigate it
and prove that the legend was false?
The investigation actually proved
the exact opposite.
The Government used
every trick at their disposal...
to make the world believe
that it wasn’t true.
After all, it would be a disaster
if pirates tried to take advantage of it.
Only the Government and
highest ranking Navy officers knew the truth.
Nobody could have guessed that
a former high ranking Navy officer...
would try to take advantage
of the End Points.
You have a point.
If it was just a lie,
the Navy wouldn’t be so panicked.
This is one hell of a man
we’ve gotten involved with.
Z has used the Dyna Stones
to destroy two End Points.
If the final one is destroyed,
the underground fissures connecting
all three End Points will become active.
And then?
A cataclysmic eruption will take place,
searing the entire New World.
Every last pirate in the New World
will burn to death.
But wouldn’t the same thing happen to
everyone who isn’t a pirate?
Wait a second!
He’s willing to drag ordinary citizens into this?
That’s just wrong!
Don’t speak as if
you’re any better!
You must know how much terror and damage
pirates have caused to people around the world.
Z despises them.
So much so, that he doesn’t care
if he destroys himself as well.
That doesn’t matter!
I’m going to get my hat back
and settle the score with him.
Hey, are you insane, Luffy?
The entire New World
is gonna explode!
I promised Shanks!
That I would become a great pirate
and return the hat to him.
If someone like that guy can just steal my hat,
then how could I ever become the Pirate King?!
No, like I said, the New World will...
Things like that
clearly don’t even register to our captain.
Nami, what’s our heading?
Oh, right! Umm...
I have already sworn my second life to you,
Captain Luffy.
Naturally, I will accompany you.
Let’s go.
So does that mean
we have to go along, too?
No matter how you look at it, isn’t the fate of
the entire New World too much to bear?
Oh, will you remain here?
What are you talking about,
you idiot?!
When did I ever say such a thing?!
Of course I’m going!
I’m a brave warrior of the sea!
Right, Chopper?
Of course I’ll go too!
I’m always up for a fight, you jerks!
Franky, how are the preparations
coming along?
I just finished!
The repairs are complete!
We can cast off
whenever you’re ready!
All right!
Super!
Thanks everyone!
Huh? You say that now?
Looks like it’s settled.
This is the final End Point island,
where Z is.
An Eternal Pose!
Why are you giving it to us?
Why, you ask?
Without this,
you won’t be able to find the island that Z is on!
Well yeah, but...
The Navy is heading for
the final island as well.
The Navy?!
Now that two of the End Points have been destroyed,
the Navy will be serious.
If you lose to Z,
the entire New World will be annihilated.
And even if you do beat Z, you’ll be surrounded
by the Navy’s strongest forces and annihilated.
Whatever the outcome may be,
I intend to keep an eye on you
till the end.
We just wanted to
get Nami and the others back to normal...
and now it’s turned into
a fight for the New World’s future.
Guys! Do you remember
the ultimate equipment?
Pirate ships attacked by Z
drift to this dock all the time.
The old man couldn’t bear to dispose of the equipment
left behind by pirates who abandoned their dreams.
So he held onto all of it.
What do you think?
Pretty impressive, huh?
Let’s shoulder the dreams of
the pirates who lost to Z,
and take the fight to him!
Yeah!
I’m counting on you.
Go find that damn Z who robs pirates of their dreams,
and take him down a notch!
Guys!
I wanna become a hero
when I grow up!
What do you think I should be,
a Navy Admiral or the Pirate King?
Pirates aren’t heroes.
Huh? Really?!
They’re both the same to you?
That’s right! They’re cool!
Gary!
You should be whatever you want!
Keep our course steady!
Prepare the Gaon Cannon!
Targeting the enemy command ship!
Locked on!
Fire the Gaon Cannon!
Land, ho!
It’s the final island!
Here they come!
Don’t let them reach Z-sensei!
Where is Z?!
Make way!
Go on ahead, guys!
Usopp 100-Ton Hammer!
Take this!
Oh, crap. Run!
Leave the rest to me,
Usopp!
Guard Point!
Chopper Tank,
firing at full power!
Z!
They all got lost!
Still, this is one hell of a landscape.
Return-Return!
I will not let you reach Sensei!
I will stop you!
Perfect.
I have no grudge against you,
but I want to restore my friends to normal.
I’m gonna put some spirit
into it this time!
I admit, I won’t be able to beat you
if we go all-out.
But at least I can
buy Sensei some time.
If I must die for the sake of
Z-sensei’s vision,
then that is fine by me.
Your master’s vision, huh?
You’re willing to throw
your life away for that?
But, I can see hesitation
in your technique.
Don’t act so high and mighty, pirate!
Lowly pirate!
You do not have
the right to live!
Crumble and begone,
before the glory of Z-sensei!
“Sensei” this and “Sensei” that...
What are you, five?
I’m exhausted!
Oooh,
they started without us.
We can’t let the old geezer
die all by himself,
so let’s end all of them together,
including the Straw Hat Pirates.
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Don’t let him get away!
Fire!
Return-Return!
Feel the chill of the afterlife,
in this world!
Soul Solid!
Mil Fleur!
Gigantesco Mano!
Stamp!
Take this!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Bamboo Javelin Grove!
I’ll show you the power of
the Magic Klima Takt!
Heat Ball!
Cool Ball!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Damn it Nami, you hit us too!
That made me all tingly!
Felt good, didn’t it?
Like hell it did!
Oh my, you really did take down
quite a lot of them.
Where is Luffy?
He charged ahead.
Then we must pursue—
Everyone, what is that?!
A-Aren’t those Pacifista?!
B-But they look different
from the ones we met before!
So you’ve come, kid.
The explosions that will awaken the final End Point
have already started.
I didn’t come to prevent that.
I just want my hat back!
What does this
old tattered hat mean to you?
It’s my guide.
My guide to becoming
the Pirate King!
I will not allow pirates to dream.
I will destroy these oceans
that have become infested with them!
Remember my name.
I am the destroyer of evil...
Z!
You waste your time!
Did you just give up thinking,
and come here to throw your life away?!
Oh no!
Sorry to have kept you waiting, guys!
Let’s go, partner!
Here it comes!
Iron Pirate!
General Franky!
Awesome!
Franky...
Radical Beam!
Awesome!
Grow, grow!
Sky Walk!
Diable Jambe!
Take this!
Three-Sword Style...
Blue Dragon Seal:
Water Stream!
Whatever makes you hesitate,
cut it off and leave it behind you.
Nami-san really is better sexy!
Blaze up, Sexy Fire!
Take this!
Meteor-Strike of Love!
Feel free to fall in love with me,
Nami-san.
Oh, no! Nooo!
I’m healed!
I’m back to normal!
Really?
Indeed! Oh, how I’ve missed
being in my 90s!
Zoro and Sanji did it!
Now all that’s left is Z!
Let’s go to Luffy!
Yeah!
It’s useless!
You cannot crush my justice!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Gatling!
You have some backbone,
for a pirate.
You’re not as bad as the pathetic Navy!
However...
Gear 3:
Gigant Pistol!
I am... Z!
Z!
You little brat!
Luffy!
Kid.
Why are you trying so hard
to resist me?
Even if you defeat me...
you are still a pirate.
Nobody will thank you for it.
So what?
I do what I want!
If I can’t beat you,
I can’t become the Pirate King.
Is that really it?
How childish!
You do what you want, huh?
In that case, I will do the same!
I will put my own life on the line
and crush your conviction!
Come at me! This is the end!
Black Arm Zephyr...
has returned.
I... I will do it!
I’m gonna be the Pirate King!
My name...
is Z!
Bastard!
I really have gotten old.
After so little,
my body can’t move.
What a shame.
The fun ended far too quickly.
Sheesh, that fight was cutting it
way too close.
Luffy!
Those who pursue their dreams
trample over everything in their way.
Take the hat... and my life!
I don’t want to take your life.
I’m satisfied!
If you wanna keep fighting,
I’ll humor you.
No.
I am also satisfied.
Luffy!
Are you all right, Luffy?
Guys!
Don’t you “Guys!” us!
How could you just run off
on your own again?!
Z-sensei!
Ain... Binz...
I put you through so much trouble.
Forgive me.
I...
As long as you’re safe, I...
It seems that all the actors
have gathered together.
Yellow Monkey?!
It’s disappointing that both
Straw Hat and Zephyr-sensei are close to death.
But all of you are gonna die anyway,
so I guess it doesn’t matter!
This isn’t good! Why now?!
I see that he’s brought
a whole battalion with him.
The ocean saw the world begin,
I was able to do what I wanted
at the very end.
I have to clean up my own mess...
or I won’t be able to face
all those who have gone before me.
and the ocean knows how the world will end
Straw Hat Luffy.
You have your own adventure, do you not?
I, Z, will handle this.
Pops!
Thus, it calls us down the path we must take
Sensei! Sensei, you can’t!
Kuzan.
At the very end,
you create a place for me to die, huh?
Thus, it leads us to a just world
Sensei! Sensei! Sen—
Sensei...!
It envelops all pain and suffering
honorably and kindly wrapping them up
The Sacred Yasakani Jewels!
Borsalino!
Farewell, Zephyr-sensei!
The ocean saw the world begin,
I will give you
one final training session!
and the ocean knows how the world will end
Even after I’m gone,
the all-knowing ocean will lead the way
I must not fear, because you are here
I must not be timid, because my comrades wait for me
Don’t cry!
He followed his heart
till the very end.
We must advance toward the blue horizon
That’s cool, don’t you think?
We’ll get you for this!
I’m always ready to take you on!
I am the hero of justice...
Z!
Never made it as a wise man
I couldn’t cut it as a poor man stealing
Tired of living like a blind man
I’m sick of sight without a sense of feeling
This is how you remind me
Of what I really am
It’s not like you to say sorry
I was waiting on a different story
This time I’m mistaken
For handing you a heart worth breaking
And I’ve been wrong, I’ve been down
Been to the bottom of every bottle
These five words in my head
Scream, “Are we having fun yet?”
”Are we having fun yet?”
I don’t give a damn ‘bout my reputation
You’re living in the past it’s a new generation
A girl can do what she wants to do
An’ that’s what I’m gonna do
An’ I don’t give a damn ‘bout my bad reputation
Oh no, not me
I don’t give a damn ‘bout my reputation
Never said I wanted to improve my station
An’ I’m only doin’ good when I’m havin’ fun
An’ I don’t have to please no one
An’ I don’t give a damn ‘bout my bad reputation
Oh no, not me
I don’t give a damn ‘bout my reputation
I’ve never been afraid of any deviation
An’ I don’t really care if ya think I’m strange
I ain’t gonna change
An’ I’m never gonna care ‘bout my bad reputation
Oh no, not me
I don’t give a damn ‘bout my reputation
The world’s in trouble there’s no communication
An’ everyone can say what they want to say
It never gets better anyway
So why should I care ‘bout a bad reputation
Anyway oh no, not me
Oh no, not me
I don’t give a damn ‘bout my bad reputation
You’re living in the past, it’s a new generation
An’ I only feel good when I got no pain
An’ that’s how I’m gonna stay
An’ I don’t give a damn ‘bout a bad reputation
Oh no, not me