Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
We've set off on our long journey
We'll always hold on to...
courage, love, friendship,
and a little bit of playfulness
We're all separate pieces of the world,
friends coming together one after another
As the pieces take form, I know the wind will fill our sails! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
With every tear we shed, we grow stronger
With every tear we shed, we'll gain...
more, and more, and more memories! (Yeah)
So when you feel the wind, you gotta feel it blowing!
Let's go search for the wind that dries up our tears!
We're on an adventure to find that someone
We'll never stop!
Look up ahead, my treasure, as you are waiting there for me!
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Now with Jinbe and Crocodile,
they're battling on Level 4!
There's no need to hesitate!
I'm...
...on the Government side!
I'm on Level 2.
I've just taken care of the
fools running wild here.
I blocked all the exits on this floor!
I don't know why Blackbeard
is attacking us...
--...but I already did something about it.
--Nice!
It's not something that I wanted to do but
I have no option under the circumstances!
I decided to release Shiryu against my will!
You did?!
Shiryu, how do you like
being out of the cell?
Yeah, I really learned a lesson.
The eternal boredom makes you long for death.
But you're not gonna use me as a pawn
and then ask me to go back into
the cell, are you, Magellan?
You're a condemned prisoner!
And this is a deferred sentence!
This is your only chance!
Yeah, I bet.
I'll keep that in mind!
I have the right...
...to cut you down!
A Dangerous Encounter!
Blackbeard and Shiryu of the Rain
They broke into the jailers'
room and took the keys!
Let's set more prisoners free and
let chaos free in the prison!
Then, we can divide our opponents forces and
we will have a higher chance of survival!
If you wanna run, come on and get out!
It's your chance to break out! Come with us!
Wow! Are you gonna release us?!
Go Blugori!
Go wild!
Damn, the Blugori!
Chief Guard Saldeath,
we'll leave them to you!
Blugori! Get that Queen of Queers with the gigantic face!
It's not a "gigantic face,"
it's Face Growth Synthesis!
Blugori! Get him!
Hell...
Wink!
Heehaw!
He finished off the Blugori
with a single blow!
N-No way!
I don't get it! What was that?!
Straw-boy! You can't stop running!
Leave them to us and you better keep going forward and up! Now, go!
I got it!
Thanks!
--It's the Jailer Beasts!
--There're three of them!
Finally! We got our backup!
Sadie-chan's are here!
They aren't gonna let you...
...go any further beyond this point!
Let's go, Luffy-kun! I'll assist you!
I'm not good at fighting on land though!
Yeah? You're strong enough!
Alright, let's get them, Jailer Beasts!
Gum-Gum...
Wait a minute!
We'll save you two the trouble!
Like Iva-san said, you need
to keep going, Straw-san!
We'll take care of the Jailer Beasts!
You guys?!
People call us...
...The New Kama's Six Forces!
Oh! Are they formidable?!
These babies have a lot of friends...
who got killed in the fire
and brimstone of Impel Down!
They hold grudges especially against the merciless Jailer Beasts, their commander and the chief guard!
Humph! Take care of them already!
Take this!
Even a Jailer Beast is just a big
oaf without his eyesight! Get them!
It was an eye-crusher!
Attack them at once!
Don't underestimate... mmm... these kids!
Even if they can't see you, they
still can smell you and feel you!
That's how Impel Down's...
mmm... Jailer Beasts are!
How about this?!
You can't fight back this time!
Okay, everybody, pull!
How dinky they are!
--No! They're too strong!
--Guns and cannons won't do!
--Help me!
--It's impossible! Don't fight! Get back!
--We're all gonna die!
--They're way stronger than Blugori! Run!
I can't resist! Those screams!
--Help me!
--Those Jailer Beasts are formidable!
Gear 3:
Fishman Karate:
Get them all, Jailer Beasts!
Gum-Gum...
...Gigant...
5,000 Brick...
Sables!
...Fist!
...Pistol!
--No, the poison is...
--Damn! Get back!
Dammit! We can't even get closer to it!
That turd, Magellan, he's no fool!
What should we do?!
As long as this block of poison
is here, we can't get to Level 1.
No way! Nothing will counteract
Magellan's poison!
It's impossible to break out
of Impel Down as I thought!
Shut up! We can't give
up after coming this far!
That's exactly what Magellan wants!
Have you got any insights?
Oh! Um...
Mr. 3! When we're in trouble,
we can depend on your wax!
Use your power and...
W-Wait a minute!
It's not as easy as
fooling Transponder Snails or Manticores!
Oh wait! I see!
Candle Coating!
I can cover the poison up with
wax! What was I thinking?!
You're good, Buggy! It was a great idea!
I wasn't thinking about anything!
You came up with the great idea so quickly!
You're a tower of strength!
I almost fell in love with you!
Of course! I'm not just a flashy guy!
You need to think carefully sometimes!
Do you get it, you fools?!
Now we're safe from the poison but
it's still blocking our way out!
That's true. It's not time to celebrate yet.
Don't worry! We got Captain Buggy with us!
He definitely has our next move planned!
What?!
You're right! There's no doubt about it!
What?! What?!
I mean...
Tell us!
W-Well...
--I'd do anything!
--What's next?!
--D-Don't ask me what t'do...
--"Wax'd do?"
Wax would do!
Let's use my wax power again!
We're gonna do it like when
Straw Hat beat Minotaurus!
"It?"
Ready, Straw Hat?! Candle Lock!
Alright! Gum-Gum...
...Mallet Rifle!
That was when we were in Level
3 - the Starvation Hell!
I wanted to go up but I had to go
down to Level 5 because of Straw Hat!
After that, it was a pain to
get back to Level 2 again!
Are you ready, Buggy? Candle Lock!
I-I gotta do what he did?!
I'm not ready yet...
Damn! There's no option!
Chop-Chop...
Go, Captain Buggy!
Release Wax-Wax and Candle Lock!
...Flashy Mallet!
--That's Magellan's infamous poison!
--It's like a creature!
Hey, wait! Gimme back my hand!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Oh my butt!
It didn't go like it did with
Straw Hat. That's all we had!
Damn! Magellan the turd!
Maybe you're the warden of Impel Down
- the greatest prison in the world!
But you're just a turd with the runs!
You've got no friends other
than the toilet seat!
--Buggy-san lost it at last!
--Magellan-chan, how's your seat doing?
We're stuck. No wonder!
You fools! Why can't you see it?!
Captain Buggy's not giving
up yet! He's still fighting!
Here's your bowels forecast!
He tries to fight the venom
with his venomous tongue!
As they say "Poison quells poison!"
You're gonna have loose
bowels all night long!
--What a man!
--That's the indomitable pirate spirit!
--He's a natural born captain!
--I will follow him forever!
Alright, Captain Buggy! We'll fight with you!
Poop, poop, diarrhean Magellan!
Raise the drawbridge!
Don't let them cross it!
Hurry up!
Crimson Hell
Underwater Prison Impel Down, Level 1
There's only five of them! Stop the Blackbeards!
S-Shoot!
Shoot! He's a Warlord but we're
pretty sure that he betrayed us!
Blackbeard is not on our side!
Pirates can't be on our
side in the first place.
Jail Manager Shiryu! When
did they let you out?
There are five of them...
Who's that? Here comes trouble!
Is he Magellan?!
Marshall D. Teach—Blackbeard, right?
Yes, I am! Who the hell are you?!
I blocked the exits on Level 2.
Buggy the Clown and the others are trapped.
And I know that Shiryu can
handle Blackbeard on Level 1.
That leaves us Straw Hat
and the others on Level 4.
They've got Crocodile and Jinbe with
them and have become quite a force!
In Impel Down, we won't tolerate a riot...
...let alone a break out!
I'll be there soon!
You must hold Straw Hat and others
back until I get there, Hannyabal!
Vice Warden, we have a problem!
What's wrong?
According to the report from Level 4,
the Jailer Beasts got beaten
in the blink of an eye!
Th-That can't be true! The
Jailer Beasts can't be beaten!
Don't panic, stupid! Tell
them that I'll be there soon!
I'm gonna hold them back at any
cost until the Warden gets there!
I'll definitely fulfill this
duty that the Warden left to me!
Warden!
Hey, hey, Warden! Yes, yes, Warden!
Hey, Warden! Our great Warden!
Go for it, go for it, Warden!
Hey, Warden! It for go, it for go, Warden!
Vice Warden! The crisis on
Level 4! Can we go now?!
This is it! We can't fight
them without the Jailer Beasts!
Break away! There's nothing to fear anymore!
Damn! They're multiplying, too!
Dammit!
--That's Chief Guard Sadie!
--Who cares! Push her away!
Shut up! You better call me Sadie-chan!
Manifesto of Excitement--Red Viper Whip!
How dare you...
...beat my sweet...
...minions!
Damn you!
Wait!
Vi told you to keep moving!
Heehaw!
Vi'm gonna be your match!
Don't call me "you"!
Mmm... I told you to call me Sadie-chan!
Emporio Female Hormone!
Get out of our way! Eccentric girl!
Shut up! Now you became a woman, Ivankov?!
You're just a confused anarchist!
For now, Vi...
really feel like a woman!
Level 1! What's going on?
Have you gotten Blackbeard?
Answer me! What's wrong? Answer me!
It seems like fortune favors us now!
There's no response from Level 1!
Maybe they got wiped out!
That's ridiculous!
Vice Warden told me that...
...Warden Magellan has released Jail Manager
Shiryu and let him fight Blackbeard!
Even if the enemy is one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
it's not so easy to beat Jail Manager Shiryu!
Humph! Maybe it's interesting to hear
the scream... mmm... of the Queen of Queers!
Women's weapons are not just their beauty!
These...
lithe and soft movements are weapons, too!
And maybe you don't understand it because
all you do is snap a whip but...
women care for others tenderly!
May his spirit rest in peace!
Iva-sama! Stop mourning! I'm not dead yet!
Oh no!
In addition to that, women are sometimes far stronger than any man!
Shut up! Red Viper Whip!
I will get you!
I can just pluck your head away
but then I don't get a chance to
hear your whimper so I'll wait!
I'm gonna take time and make you
suffer so let me hear you scream!
Now!
How stubborn you are! Let me hear it!
Let me hear the Queen of Queers--Ivankov's--final scream!
All of my bones shattered...
I-Iva-sama!
Oh! I can't resist this!
Or not!
Then why did you say it?!
No way! How come?!
By injecting Emporio Female Hormone,
my body got very lithe and soft!
So it absorbs any kind of shock!
How dare you!
Hey! That was too hard!
Heehaw!
Who is it?! She talks like Iva-chan!
Hurry up! We're close to
the staircase to Level 3!
I'm gonna open the door!
Alright, let's go!
Why's that?! The door's opening by itself!
Who cares? It's our luck!
Let's go up to Level 3!
This is the great fort
of hell! No one may pass!
Who are you?!
Magellan arrives on Level 4, and makes his way to Luffy and the others.
Having eliminated the forces,
Luffy and the others attempt to reach Level 3,
but Hannyabal stands before them
and finally reveals his true power.
Next time, on One Piece:
"No Price Too High!
Serious Hannyabal"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
No Price Too High!
Serious Hannyabal