A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
It's...
...a trap! A trap by the Navy!
Guys!
Usopp!
Sail on!
Impossible!
A pirate ship, coming out of the mountains?!
Old man!
Whereabouts of the
Island Treasure!
Attack of the
Zenny Pirates!
Is that...?
You did it, old man!
Hey, don't act so reckless.
His heart hasn't stopped, right?
Hey, cut that out!
Old-timer! Are you okay?!
I'm finally out at sea.
I really have become a pirate!
Yeah! This is no longer my coffin!
It's the good pirate ship Zenny!
Isn't that right?!
Way to go, old man!
We told you, don't egg him on!
He's a sick man!
What are you trying to pull,
Zenny the Moneylender?
Your profession is to extort
money from pirates, isn't it?!
I gave up lending money long ago.
Right now, I'm Zenny the Pirate!
Don't you sell the Navy short, you old geezer!
Old man, watch yourself!
He's after your treasure!
Oh? Lately, the Navy has taken to
going after treasure on the side,
in addition to capturing pirates, have they?
That's quite industrious of you.
– Nami, bring the ship over.
– Got it. Come on, everyone.
Why, you! Don't give Nami-san any orders!
Sergeant Minchy!
The Straw Hats are on the move!
Contact Captain Moore's fleet for backup!
Shut up!
I told you, I'd give you your cut of the treasure.
You understand, don't you?
We can't let the captain know.
The way I figure it...
You're keeping your men hushed
up to take on this side project.
That must cost a pretty penny, huh, Mr. Sergeant?
Why, you dotty old coot!
Don't think you won't pay for this!
Silence, boy!
You've got some nerve,
trying to swipe my treasure!
Come and take it from me, if you can!
Way to go, old man!
Show them how a pirate fights!
– There!
– You idiot!
What are you doing...?
Why, you...!
If you're a pirate, then you won't mind
it when the Navy kills you, right?!
Come to think of it, does the old
man have any sort of weapon?
Show me what you've got!
Take on my class 10-ranked abacus skills!
Get them!
His abacus and...
...the goats.
What?! Oh, no!
Old man!
That idiot! Luffy!
What are you guys, idiots?
What are you shooting at?!
You shouldn't waste your bullets like that!
I'm right here!
Let's go!
What are you doing?! They're goats!
You're taking on goats!
It's because they're goats
that I can't do it, Sergeant.
Hey! The battle has already begun!
Stop watching the goings-on from
on high, and come on down here!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
We know. Stand aside for a minute.
Relax, Chopper!
But...
The old-timer is in no physical shape
to be doing anything so crazy!
– Shoot them!
– Don't shoot!
Now you've done it!
My boys are out of control!
Charge!
Hey, look! They're waiting for us in formation!
It's strange how they don't show
any signs of movement, huh?
We have to think up a battle
plan now, while we can.
So, what shall we do?
Be the first ones to attack them?
– Don't be crazy!
– In any case...!
Right now, we have to help the old-timer!
Hurry!
By the way, did we hit something a minute ago?
– Huh? Did we?
– Never mind! Hurry!
Captain Moore, there's no response
from Sergeant Minchy's ship.
What was that sound of gunfire we heard earlier?
Shall we advance?
No, not yet. Wait for Minchy to report in.
Where did you guys go?
Enough out of you, already!
That's enough of that!
All right!
Where's all that energy you had a moment ago?
Zenny the Pirate, are you out of breath?
Hey, you've finally come forward,
you little miscreant.
You sure are a talkative bastard!
Now then, shall we get down to business?
Where is your treasure located,
Zenny the Pirate?
What, Corporal?!
Why didn't you report this sooner?!
I'm terribly sorry, Captain Moore.
What a sneaky stunt to pull!
That miserable Minchy...
So that was what he was up to!
Why don't you spit it out, already?
You don't want to die yet, do you?
I do value my own life. I cherish it.
Let me tell you, I'm penniless.
What do you want me to spit out?
I can't even manage any spittle.
Fine, then.
As dinky an island as this is,
it won't take much work to dig
it up from one end to the other.
I have no further need of you.
Why, you...!
You're through!
I seem to have broken your abacus.
Sorry about that.
What the hell are you doing?!
You think you can defy the
navy and get away with it—
Old-timer!
You guys are late! I almost died, here!
Waah! I was so worried!
Smoke Star!!
That's far enough!
Robin, this is where you were?
Old man, you can relax,
now that Captain Usopp is here—
What happened? That bump is huge!
There's no pulse!
Calm down, Chopper. I'm over here, over here.
I knew that! Here, take it easy, and lie down.
Don't you die, old-timer!
You think I would die?
How are you feeling, old man?
I feel fine, of course. I'm finally a pirate.
I don't feel like dying anymore.
We just came to the island on the sergeant's orders.
Yeah... well, I guess subordinates
can't go against their superiors.
Listen, our captain is pretty
capricious himself, you know?
You don't say.
Hey, don't go getting too chummy.
O-Old man, are you okay?
Are you okay, lad?
Good grief, there's just no helping Luffy!
Your seizure has passed, so that's a relief, huh?
Much obliged, Dr. Chopper.
Sorry about that. Old man, how's tricks?
Just fine, thanks.
Ah, right.
Listen, Gramps, you can tell us now, can't you?
About your treasure?
Hey! Don't go giving any shocks to my patients!
Old-timer, stay strong!
For the love of...
Yeah, I guess you have done a lot for me,
so maybe I can tell you.
That's more like it!
Look, the Navy knows about it, and all,
so it must be an amazing treasure, right?
I did... have a treasure...
The pirates who owed me signed over
a whole heap of treasure to me.
But then, thinking of buying a pirate ship,
and getting my pals together,
I exchanged all of it for cash.
Cash!
Thinking back on it, that's when my fate turned.
I told you last night that I was
attacked by those who had owed
money to me, and I ended up
drifting ashore on this island, right?
Well, naturally, I managed to protect the money.
After all, I'd risked my life for that
money in order to buy my dream.
When I came to, after
washing up on the beach...
– It was eaten?!
– Really?!
All of it?! They ate all of it?!
That's right.
Well, maybe they left two or three bills.
And so, like I told you,
these guys are my treasure.
All of my fortune may have been lost,
but in return, I gained my friends.
They don't betray me, or try to cheat me.
Now, I have friends at my side,
who don't do anything for selfish motives.
And so, I want to reward them for it.
I've obtained the greatest treasure in the world.
Good for you, old man.
Yeah, it is good. I'm a man that
takes advantage of every situation.
What a load of crap! Hey, Straw Hat!
This fight isn't over yet!
There's a pristine fleet over
there just waiting for you!
Don't think you're going to get away so easily!
Don't go trying to act cool
when you're rolling around.
What is he, stupid?
You're the stupid ones!
Do you think you can stand up
to a fleet of nine ships?!
I'm not running away.
Tell them that if they want a fight,
to come straight at me.
Gum-Gum...
Hey, Luffy! A little bit higher!
Okay!
...Pistol!!
Okay, direction is good.
You... disgrace to the Navy!
– Take him away!
– Yes, sir!
This is Naval Captain Moore.
I have no interest in the island,
or in this man Zenny.
My only goal is to bring you down,
in the name of justice.
To show my gratitude for turning over
this misguided member of my fleet,
I will allow you to choose where we fight.
Come, bring your ship out.
We were thinking of leaving pretty soon, too.
We'll be coming toward you right away.
Here, old man, I fixed it for you.
Oh, I should have known. Much obliged.
Don't mention it.
Everything is all set up through supper.
You just have to cook it.
Yeah, much obliged.
Then again, lads, are you sure about this?
You're facing a fleet of nine ships, right?
Don't worry about it.
I'm not just strong, I'm lucky, too.
I can't keep up with you, lad.
Old-timer, I made up a whole supply for you,
so make sure you take your medicine.
Promise me!
Yeah, all right, all right.
I'll make sure I take it, don't you worry.
– It's been fun, Gramps!
– Take care.
Guys, you take care of the old-timer!
We'll see you later, out on the seas somewhere!
Yeah! Once I finish repairs to the ship,
I'm going to be setting sail!
We'll be waiting for you, Zenny Pirates!
Now, let's head back to the island for a bit, shall we?
We have to fix the ship.
All right, everyone off. We're going back.
Age doesn't have anything to do
with becoming a pirate, huh?
My word, he knows how to get
an idea in someone's head.
Chopper is a patient one, too.
How many years will I need to
take this whole stack of medicine?
Much obliged, everyone. Very much obliged.
Thanks to you, I think I can
tough it out a little while longer.
After all, my life as a pirate has just begun!
Nice going, inviting them into
the foggy reef area, Luffy.
Sometimes, you do use your head, huh?
Huh? I do?
"I do"...? That's what I was asking you!
This is Moore's Fleet, calling any
ships sailing in this area of the sea!
This is Moore's Fleet!
Request immediate assistance!
Geez, you are such a moron!
I wish I hadn't complimented you! I take it back!
What?
It's not like he was thinking about that, huh?
Pure chance.
He was just pointing his finger wherever.
By the way, ship's doctor, how is it, really?
Gramps' condition?
That medicine controls his episodes, at best.
It won't keep him from getting any worse.
His heart was fairly weak to
begin with, and as old as he is,
sailing on a ship, let alone as a pirate...
What are you talking about?
The old man said he wanted to
be a pirate, so we should let him.
Besides, once the old man sets out to sea,
he may find an island that
has a cure for his illness.
Maybe.
We don't have to worry about it too much.
That old man isn't going to croak that easily.
His weak heart notwithstanding,
he did have plenty of guts, after all.
He's right, Chopper. We'll see him again!
Mm-hmm, sure we will.
We'll be waiting for you, Zenny Pirates!
Aa hateshinaku tsuzuiteru sora no mukou ni
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
Itsuka mita asu o ima egakihajimete iru
The future that I once saw is now starting to take shape
Jibun ni makesou ni naru hi mo aru
There are days where I almost lose to myself
Sonna toki wa
When that happened,
atataka na basho ga atta
there was someplace warm I could go
Hokoreru mono itsumo kitto
The friends I took pride in always, without fail,
Boku no senaka oshite kureta yo ne?
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Aa hoshi-tachi ga furisosogu kono sora no shita
Ah, the stars are pouring down underneath the sky
Nido to nai ima o hora
This unique moment...
An island! I see a lighthouse, too!
Then they've got something to eat!
Wow, it's incredibly tall, huh?
Is that really a lighthouse?
Never mind about that,
let's hurry and get something to eat!
Huh? Who are you, Pops?
Oh, not another weird old man!
I'm not taking care of this one!
Next time, on One Piece:
Legend of the Rainbow Mist!
Old Man Henzo of Luluka Island
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Legend of the Rainbow Mist!
Old Man Henzo of Luluka Island