Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the Paramount War against the Navy,
Luffy was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
In Order to Keep the Promise
Their Separate Departures!
Late in the day
on which the Celestial Dragon's
ship arrived at the Goa Kingdom,
at a small village somewhere
in the East Blue...
Did you see the person with
the gigantic face today?
Yeah, I've never seen someone like that!
Look, the ship is huge, too!
580... 581...
582... 583...
584...
You're late, Dragon! I got tired of waiting!
Sorry.
What happened?!
--Oh, that's very bad!
--Hey, treat him now!
Roger!
Honestly! Where have you been?!
I was watching the ceremony
for the Celestial Dragon.
How could you do that without telling me?
You attract too much attention.
M-My face, you mean?
We have to prepare as soon as
possible for what will come!
Do we have enough food?
They gave us some at the
training hall in the village.
Let's leave here! Head back to Baltigo!
Meanwhile, in the Goa Kingdom
after the observers from the
World Government left...
Here comes some junk!
People are doing exactly the
same thing they did before
accumulating another mountain of junk.
Here I come, Ace!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
What are you doing?! You're no match for me!
No matter how strong you are,
it's nothing if you can't hit a target!
Rubber is not useful in
fighting just as I thought!
Shut up!
What?! I'm telling you the truth!
All you can do is bounce back
attacks and sink like a rock!
Stop making fun of the Gum-Gum
Fruit! I'll make you cry someday!
I've been creating new attacks
stronger than the pistol!
Luffy, that was great!
Your arm stretched farther than yesterday!
Sabo! You're too easy on Luffy!
I'm stronger than yesterday as I thought!
--Don't you think so, Sabo?!
Sabo was a good brother...
What?! You mean it'd be
better if I had died?!
I didn't say that!
You meant it!
Ouch!
Sabo didn't hit me like that!
--What?!
--What?! Be nice to me!
No way!
Ouch.
"I hereby establish an independent country."
I hereby establish an independent country.
Country?!
"Me too!"
Me too!
"Ace's Kingdom"
"Luffy's Kingdom"
"Ace's Kingdom" "Luffy's Kingdom"
What do you want this time?
We need to be strong enough
to live on our own!
You guys belong to Dadan's Kingdom!
Let me use your bath sometimes.
Ace! You gotta help me! It's a bear!
I thought that you wanted
to live on your own.
Dammit!
Luffy!
Hey, anybody there in Dadan's Kingdom?!
Luffy got hurt! Please help him!
Magra! Please! Treat Luffy!
Okay, okay, come in now!
Well, well, it was no joking matter.
He might have died if the
cut was a little bit deeper.
You three fought those beasts
together, didn't you?
It's my fault!
I knew it doesn't prove that you're
strong by fighting on your own!
I'm not good enough!
I'm not good enough at all!
Ace...
I'm sorry, Luffy!
I'm sorry!
Hey, guys!
Makino came all the way bringing us sake!
How to pay respect to other people?
Uh-huh.
What's gotten into you?
Since I'm Luffy's brother,
it's my job to go see the captain
of the Red-Haired Pirates
who helped Luffy in order to thank him!
Do you have something to say?!
I'm sorry. Alright, I'll teach you how.
Okay, this would be the first one...
They didn't pay!
Stop!
Oh, we forgot to do it!
Oh yeah!
--Thank you for the meal!
Shut up, you brats! You got to pay!
I'm gonna win today!
--We did it!
Bear meat stew tonight!
"Seven tears later"
"Ace, 17 years old"
"Luffy, 14 years old"
Take care, Ace!
Yeah. See you, Luffy! I'm going now!
Uh-huh! I'll be a lot stronger
when I leave here in 3 years!
Good luck, Ace!
Take care!
Don't catch a cold!
You just wait! I'll make my name soon!
Ace, son of the Pirate King, has grown up secretly
and he quietly departed from the shore nearby Mt. Corvo.
He's gone!
Honestly! I wonder what Garp would say.
You must raise him, Dadan!
No way! Whose baby is this?
Boss!
Ace is gone!
Oh good. But I can see that
Garp will be mad at me.
He was such an useless little shit!
Oh, Ace left a message for you.
What?! He still has something to
say to me even at the last minute?!
He said "Thank you for taking care of me!"
He can't do that! That fool!
Oh? Boss, are you crying?!
I'm not crying, you fool!
I have to wait 3 years more.
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Damn! I missed it by a little.
You almost got it, Luffy!
Why don't you keep the
center of gravity lower?
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
I wanna become stronger!
"A few months later"
Luffy!
Look at the newspaper!
What is it?
Look here!
Wow! Ace made his name!
He got his own ship and crew!
He's great! Ace is great!
But I'm gonna top him!
"Three years later
Luffy, 17 years old"
Hey, guys!
I'm leaving now. You're not gonna see me off?
How annoying.
The mayor and Makino won't mind,
but the people in the Windmill
Village will be scared of us.
But...
Why don't you just go already?!
Alright. Then you guys,
thank you for everything!
Don't say it - I feel awkward!
Well, well, take care!
Yeah, okay!
Oh yeah!
Dadan, I don't like mountain bandits...
Shut up, you brat!
...but I like you guys!
Stop talking nonsense and go
away already, you bastard!
Dammit! Why am I surrounded by such fools?!
Oh, you crying?
I'm not crying!
Windmill Village at the edge of
Goa Kingdom on the Dawn Island.
Hey, why don't you take my
old fishing boat, Luffy?
That thing is gonna sink any minute!
That's a small boat...
This is fine! This is
what I wanna start with!
Sabo!
Watch over me! I'm gonna go out to sea now!
Sabo was first and Ace was second.
And I'm third but I'm gonna
top them!
Wait for me, Ace!
I'll catch up with you soon!
What are you doing screaming and mumbling?
Is it some kind of incantation?
No, it's not! It's a challenge!
--Who's Ace?
--No idea.
Alright, I'm going now!
He's finally leaving,
mayor. I'm gonna miss him.
It's a dishonor to the
village to become a pirate!
What nice day for setting sail!
Th-That's...!
Here comes our local sea monster!
You don't know who you're messing with.
Look at this technique I've
been training for 10 years!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
That will learn ya, stupid fish!
Wow! He beat the sea monster
with a single blow!
He's become quite strong!
Let's start with finding a crew!
I want at least 10 of them.
And the black flag!
Alright! Let's go!
I'm gonna become...
...the Pirate King!
And now,
Luffy mourns the loss of his brother Ace.
Luffy-kun...
The Pirate King?!
I'm...
I'm too...
...weak!!
As Garp returns to Windmill Village,
Dadan greets him in outrage.
Meanwhile, Luffy is lost in his grief
and helplessness after losing Ace.
As he watches Luffy writhe in despair,
Jinbe recalls the words of Ace...
Next time, on One Piece:
"I Wanna See Them!
Luffy's Tearful Cry"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
I Wanna See Them!
Luffy's Tearful Cry