Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has landed on Marineford
to save his brother, Ace, from execution.
At last, in their effort to reach the execution platform,
Luffy and the Whitebeards have breached the barricades.
As an all-out battle between the Navy
and Whitebeards rages at Oris Plaza,
Luffy charges toward Ace.
If you wanna see the future,
I'll show you now, Whitebeard!
Do it!
Ace!
It's no use!
Do you think that I can't stop you for doing it?!
Don't do it!!
Hey, was that...?!
Conqueror's... Haki!
Hey, come on! For real?!
That was surprising!
That brat...
The Scaffold at Last!
The Way to Ace Has Opened!!
Yeah! Ace is alive!
Hey, stay with me!
Was that Ace's brother?!
Look at this!
I almost passed out!
He used Conqueror's Haki just like Pops and Red-Haired!
Was he the one who did it?
Seems like he used it unconsciously.
I didn't know that he had such tremendous power!
He was born with it as I thought!
He uses it, too!
Back down if your heart is weak!
He is not just another rookie!
Conqueror's Haki!
But it's not surprising
because he's the son of the Revolutionary—Dragon!
Vice Admiral Doberman!
Hey, where did you get that power from?!
Huh?! What power?!
Never mind!
He's not aware of it!
So it's not ready to be used!
But it's no wonder that he attracts people!
This is why they say "blood will tell," Dragon!
Don't let him escape this battlefield!
If you do, he'll prove a formidable foe for us!
Make sure he dies!
You Navy soldiers are a bunch of cowards!
You need such strength to fight a fledgling?!
I thought you wanted to kill me!
Let's get Whitebeard first!
He's a monster but he's wounded badly!
Bring him down at any cost!
Bring it on!
We're gonna back Pops up!
Don't be afraid! Get him!
Straw-boy, now is the chance!
Don't let Straw Hat go!
Damn! Navy soldiers have started regrouping!
Pushing through by force?
I wonder how long he can hang on!
Pops!
Damn! If I could only take these off!
Pops! Don't push yourself too far, you're wounded!
You guys!
Pops?!
From now on, back Straw Hat Luffy up...
...with all your strength!
Ace's brother?!
Pops!
Take care of Straw Hat right now!
Straw-boy! Watch out!
You're...
...the allied pirate of Whitebeard—
Bohemian Knight Doma!
Nice to meet you, Vice Admiral Momonga!
The DeCalvan Brothers!
You got to fight...!
...Against us!
Thunder Lord McGuy!
I need you to fight me, Vice Admiral Doberman!
I-Is this...?!
We pirates from the New World will assist you!
Ace-chan's right there! Let's go, Straw Hat!
The allied pirates of Whitebeard are surrounding Straw Hat!
What are they doing?!
Hurry up, Ace's brother!
The Navy forces are focusing on Pops now!
This is your only chance to get beyond the admirals!
Let's break through all at once! Come with us!
This is a big deal, Straw-boy!
The world's greatest pirate is putting you to the test!
Huh?
Heehaw!
Whitebeard put all his hopes on you!
That's a big deal!
Are you ready to respond to his expectations?!
I don't know what Whitebeard wants!
But I came here for...
...only one reason, right from the start!
The pirates are gaining vigor!
They're gonna break through! We need more troops!
Vice Admiral-dono! Let's get Straw Hat first...!
Wait!
They left Whitebeard alone! Attack Whitebeard now!
If we can bring Whitebeard down,
we can stop all of them!
They think that they can beat me if they attack me all at one time!
Whitebeard! Is he invincible?!
Do it, brat!
You just stopped them
from executing Ace on my behalf!
You have the middle initial D,
so show me how the world will be in years to come!
That's...
Hawk-Eye!
Heads up, Straw-boy!
What are you...?!
It's the president's order!
We consider the Navy as our enemy for now! Go!
You're Daz Bonez, aren't you?
Straw-boy!
Crocodile!
You're sleeping too much, Mr. 1!
I got out of shape by being in prison.
I don't need you here, Straw Hat! Off you go!
Why are you standing in my way, Crocodile?
I'm not in the best mood now.
So you better watch yourself, Hawk-Eye!
Luffy!
I want to help you, too!
Shoot Monkey D. Luffy.
Boa Hancock. Friendly operative. Abort attack.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?!
You're a Warlord, aren't you, Boa Hancock?!
Why do you keep stopping the Pacifistas?!
I thought you were on the Government side!
You're such a senseless man! You don't know anything!
What?!
Let me tell you one thing.
Love is always like a hurricane!
What're you talking about?!
Damn Straw Hat!
Buggy!
Captain Buggy! How's everything going?
It doesn't look good, guys.
I appeared sensationally
in front of the whole world a while ago.
But now people are paying attention to Straw Hat
who is running to the scaffold like a fool!
Guys, who should be today's leading star?
Captain Buggy!
That's right!
I gotta do something flashier than Straw Hat one more time!
Hey, let me use the Transponder Snail!
Captain Buggy! I'm afraid that the Snail is still frozen...
What?! Defrost it right away!
It'll melt if you soak it in the seawater that is heated by Red Hound's lava!
It melted!
Good. Bring it to me!
Okay!
Here you go!
Please!
It's shrivelled up!
Oh, we shouldn't soak it in seawater!
What the hell, I think it still works.
We've taken the trouble to steal it from the Navy,
we have to take good care of it.
Transponder Snail-san,
could you wake up for a minute?
Good morning, sir!
No, he pulled in his head!
It's because of your uncanny faces!
Please excuse us, we were born this way!
Damn! Straw Hat will reach the scaffold
any minute while I'm fooling around like this!
Fire!
Not very much longer—make a path to the scaffold!
They're desperate!
You bastard!
Whitebeard!
Fishman Karate:
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Jinbe, what the hell are you doing?!
Didn't you hear that I said "back Ace's brother up?"
I don't belong to the Whitebeard Pirates so I don't have to obey your order!
Stupid!
They made a path!
The scaffold is close now, Straw-boy!
You just run straight!
Alright!
Now is our chance to do it.
I'm sorry that you must do this when you're not fully recovered.
But we need you!
It's nothing, Iva-san.
Don't worry about it.
Crab-chan!
Whoa! Wh-What is it?!
Inazuma of the Revolutionary Army! He did it!
There's a bridge! Alright!
Straw Hat is heading straight towards the scaffold!
Do something or he'll reach it!
Don't let him!
We can't! These pirates aren't letting us by!
Gah! Use guns! Fire at Straw Hat!
What?! Th-They are...
...commanders of the Whitebeards!
Ace's brother! Just run straight, don't stop!
Break through all at once!
Don't let him pass through!
Gum-Gum...
...Battle Axe!
Luffy-kun, go ahead!
Alright, thanks!
Don't let him go!
Death Wink!
No one will pass by here!
Heehaw!
Just advance, Straw-boy!
Straw Hat will make it!
Yeah! Keep going!
Yank Straw Hat down!
Go, Straw Hat!
Set Ace free!
I can't believe that you use that kid
as a trump card, Whitebeard!
But I won't let him go any further!
Whitebeard!
Why don't you stay quiet and watch?
Luffy!
I'm here, Ace!
It's Garp the Hero!
Grandpa! Move out of my way!
I'm not going to move!
Because I'm a vice admiral of the Navy!
I've been fighting against pirates since long before you were born!
Old man!
If you wanna pass through here,
you have to kill me first!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Because of the path you two...
...have chosen to live!!
Luffy runs down the path Inazuma created
intent on reaching Ace, but Garp stands in his way.
The Navy and pirates...
When a grandfather and grandson
who walk different paths meet again in battle,
what feelings are packed into the blows they exchange?
Next time, on One Piece:
"Each on Different Paths
Luffy vs. Garp!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Each on Different Paths
Luffy vs. Garp!