Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"Just a little further and I'll have the answer"
That's what I believe as I sail into this new world
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one
Linked by unshakable bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves
Meeting, saying farewell, then meeting someone new again
All under this flag...
I carry pain I don't want to forget in my heart
I carved it in there on that fateful day
I grab on tightly to the freedom nobody can take from me!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud
Stand up every time! Raise our unyielding flag
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Keep looking up!
Puff your chest out in pride!
Step up every time!
Fly over the waves!
Linking our wishes together into one,
let's head for the future!
Hands up!!
All the pirates vying for the One Piece
head for the second half of the Grand Line.
People call it the "New World."
However, the only one to ever conquer
these waters was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, the boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
venture into that very sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats reach the New World at long last,
the harshest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard—an island divided into the Burning and Frozen Lands.
After learning of the island's ruler, Caesar Clown's, true intentions,
they are now trying
to escape Netherworld.
Alongside their newfound ally, the Warlord Trafalgar Law,
they are now on the move to kidnap Caesar,
save the children, and escape from the island.
Give us the candy!
--No! --Give it to us!
No, you can't have it!
Shut up!
Just give us the candy already!
What is she thinking?!
No, spit them all out! Mocha, can you hear me?!
Mocha!!
I told you what kind of drug they are!
What?!
Straw Hat Luffy! Why are you here?!
Shoot! Shoot!
Where's Caesar?
I don't know! I-I don't know anything...
Where's Caesar?!
Brownbeard in Grief!
Luffy Lands a Furious Blow
Netherworld, the deadly gas,
is flowing into the Third Research Institute
and starting to fill up Building B, where
the Straw Hats, G-5, and the children are.
It's not this way! Go back, go back!
It's only gas - how is it outpacing me?!
Because you went the wrong way!
Keep still, you brats!
Sedate them already, G-5!
A few more to go, brother!
--Don't resist, children! --Calm down!
Hey, hurry up, raccoon dog! We don't have time...
Don't give up, Mocha!
You can make it!
Mo... Momonosuke!
W-W-Wait, Kin'emon-san!
If you go that way, you'll run into the gas!
I don't even see any soldiers, let alone my people!
What was that creepy room?!
What's this door?
I hear something...
...or not.
Master! Look!
That's Brownbeard!
I thought he was captured by Straw Hat.
--He looks okay. --Good, good.
The Video Transponder Snail is running.
That means...
Soldiers of Punk Hazard! Listen!
I know you're watching me somewhere!
You're all being fooled!
Caesar is telling you nothing but lies!
You're all gonna die if you stay here!
What is he talking about?
Has he gone crazy after being captured by the Straw Hats?
Brownbeard is on the floor below - Building R 1st floor.
But the Straw Hats and Navy soldiers will arrive there
soon according to your plan.
Should we tell Brownbeard to come up here?
I'll tell you the truth about Caesar!
No, I'll go down.
We're coming with you then.
Caesar!
Oh, my dear underling - Brownbeard!
I'm glad that you got away from Straw Hat!
Are you alright?
You look awful!
Don't touch me!
Oh? Why are you in such a bad mood?
What's wrong?
I want my people back!
We got robbed at the center of the island but they didn't die!
I'm sure they're back already!
Whoa-whoa, he's messing with Master.
Huh? Your people?
Oh yeah...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank!
M-M-Master!
Master!
What's going on?
Oh, you must be one of Brownbeard's.
Master! There are Navy soldiers at the main entrance and it's closed!
We can't get inside! Please guide us!
Oh no! That's serious!
Let me see what I can do! Wait there!
Th-Thank you very much, Master!
Master...
Master, how are you going to let them in?
Forget about it.
Netherworld will be inescapable out there soon enough.
I wonder what happened to them.
They don't even call me anymore.
If they're not here, they must be...
Are you worried? I think you are.
If they were out there, they're definitely dead because of Netherworld!
What'd you say?!
Screw you!
Hey, what're you doing, Brownbeard?!
Brownbeard?!
I can't trust your words anymore!
--What happened to him?! --What is he doing to Master?!
I'll tell you guys this
because we spent the last two years together on this island.
Leave the island now!
Do you wanna know what he called you behind your back?!
This was his special name for you!
Guinoa pags.
Guinoo pah!
Guinoa poh...
Guinoh... Guinah...
What're you trying to say, Brownbeard?!
--Speak clearly! --Is it some kind of spell?!
He's a funny guy!
Guinoh...
I don't know what you're saying!
They will keep following me thinking I'm their savior!
They don't know that I kept them alive because they're my guinea pigs!
I said "Guinea pigs"!
Why?! I got tongue-tied!
You did something, didn't you, Caesar?!
Oh, what is it this time?!
Are you putting on an act?!
Oh, are you okay? Huh?
It's a muscle relaxant.
You're losing strength around your mouth
and your whole body, aren't you?
Oh yeah, I remember now, Brownbeard.
About your former subordinates...
I let them die!
You asshole!
How dare you!
How dare you kill my people!
Oh, there is another thing that I'd like to tell you.
The chemical weapon explosion that nearly killed all
these soldiers four years ago?
I was the one who caused it!
It wasn't Vegapunk?!
This bastard did harm to everybody and pretended that he saved them?!
Hey, stop! Stop it!
Help me! Brownbeard is going crazy!
Run, everybody!
Everything that's been going on this island is all staged by Caesar!
Run, guys! He's a devil disguised as a human!
Hey, Brownbeard!
How could you do that to a person who saved you?!
Oh no! He's really dangerous!
It's too late!
I guess Straw Hat did something to him!
Brownbeard!
Shoot! Shoot him! He's gonna attack you guys!
Shoot!
Now, let me finish him off.
Gastane...
Oh?
Did we make it out of that hole?
Yeah.
You climbed that wall to the top, huh?
Shoot!
Now, let me finish him off.
Momo, stay back!
Gastane...
Master!
Oh, that was close!
It grazed my body!
Dammit! Who is it?!
It's Straw Hat...
...Luffy!
His kindness saved my life as it did to the others.
Master was our warm-hearted savior!
Return to 2nd floor, everyone!
The Straw Hats and the Navy will be here soon!
--Get ready for the experiment! --Yes, sir!
Broadcast it for the brokers!
--Let's go! --Hustle!
I assume they'll all be dead in five years.
So we need to find more kids.
Luffy! It was him!
He was the one who were talking about...
...harming those kindhearted children!
I know.
People on this island were tricked into being here, weren't they?
What is this island?!
All right.
You don't know anything so let me tell you the secret of this island.
--There's no sound! --Hurry up!
--Checking the video! --Pull the elevator up!
This island is like gas or air.
An island that doesn't seem to exist.
Do you get it?
Listen, this island shouldn't even exist.
That's why it's suitable to the work of an underground community.
It's an epicenter of evil science.
We can do unlawful experiments or get test subjects illegally as we like!
We have some powerful people backing us
and they'll cover up everything.
So no one out there would know a thing.
No matter how much you cry or scream,
no one will come to the rescue.
You don't know a damn thing about this island, Straw Hat!
If you're getting involved without taking it seriously, you'll end up dead!
Allying with Law is also not a good idea.
He wants to mess with the S.A.D.
He is using you to kidnap me because I'm
the only person who can create S.A.D.
Let me tell you about S.A.D., Straw Hat.
The most dangerous Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo owns this factory
and here, S.A.D. is processed into a fruit called "Smile."
Do you know what Smiles are?
We successfully recreated a Devil Fruit!
Smiles are Zoan-types—man-made Devil Fruit.
Anyone who wants to become powerful yearns for it.
Doflamingo is selling Smiles to big-timers in the New World.
I heard one of the Four Emperors is already on the move...
...to form an army of hundreds of Devil Fruit users with Smiles.
Doesn't it send a chill down your spine?
Do you understand what you're dealing with?
By interfering with Doflamingo's business, you'll piss so many big names off.
When they start going into action, it's gonna shake up the whole world.
And that's what Law wants.
What fools!
They're out of your league!
Catch me if you can! But I'm protected!
Doflamingo! The Four Emperors!
Do you even have balls to pick a fight with them?
I don't think so!
If you wanna run, do it now!
Get out of my face!
A fight?
Wow!
I've been...
...picking fights all along!
Undaunted by the powerful Gas Gas Fruit attacks...
...Luffy corners Caesar with his fists of rage.
But elsewhere, Smoker,
facing another powerful Haki user,
is fighting an overwhelmingly losing battle...
...and lies on the verge of death and defeat.
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Shocking Conclusion!
Smoker vs. Vergo!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The Shocking Conclusion!
Smoker vs. Vergo!