A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
Now you're all out of money.
So then... wanna bet your
pants or something, brother?
You're lucky, in a sense.
Playing with Roshio, if you had won,
he would have made you pay for it.
Sorry, but I'll be taking all your money.
Let it go. I won this money fair and square.
You cheated just now, didn't you?
Ain't that right?
What'd you say? When did I do that?
You did! You cheated!
Don't make ridiculous accusations, you punk!
Sarquiss! Sarquiss!
Hm? What?
You saw it, too, didn't you?
This guy just cheated.
Cheated?
Yeah... That's right. He cheated.
I saw it, too. What a dirty cheat!
Don't screw with me!
You don't know who you're dealing with!
Quit Dreaming!
Mock Town,
the Town of Ridicule!
Still don't see it, Usopp?
No, I don't see it yet.
This Jaya island isn't that far, right?
Yeah, since the weather has
been stable for a while now,
we should already be in the island's climate.
Then, Jaya must be a spring island.
It feels nice and warm.
Spring weather's nice.
It looks like the seagulls are enjoying it, too.
Ahhhh! They were shot!!
Oh, let's make yakitori!
Shot? I didn't hear any gunfire.
Look, I found a bullet!
Considering the direction that they were flying,
the bullets came from the
direction the ship's facing!
Are you saying that shots came from
an island that we can't even see yet?
That's impossible, Chopper.
But I was watching them the whole time.
Then what kind of eyesight, sniping skills
and rifle do you think this sniper has?
They were shot somewhere else
and just happened to fall now.
Sanji, we got seagulls!
Poor thing... He must've suffered.
I wasn't able to kill one of them instantly.
But that's also fate.
That's the result of how you lived.
Hey, you! Do you know who I am?!
Huh? I don't know, you fool!
How about I tell you, then?
I'm the Fighting Champion.
Wow! Cool!
I see a neat-looking town!
Hey, hey, doesn't it look kinda like a resort?
Resort?!
Hurry up, Merry!
Yeah, it makes me feel like
I want to stick around a bit.
But is it my imagination, or do the ships
lined up in the harbor look like pirate ships?
Silly Usopp, since when can pirate ships
just openly line up in a harbor?!
Y-You're right!
Help me! He's gonna kill me!
What's with this town?
What a weakling!
Hey, mister.
You chose the wrong guy to beat up.
Look at that symbol. He's one of Roshio's gang.
You've heard of him, right?
Roshio the Executioner,
whose bounty is 42 million Berries.
He's crazy, so you'd better be careful.
What a reckless guy!
That wasn't a bogus game.
But it's amazing that he beat up
Roshio the Executioner so easily.
Don't you know? That's Bellamy.
That guy?! Bellamy the Hyena,
the one with a 55 million-Berry
bounty on his head?!
Captain!
Who did this?!
In any case, he needs a doctor! Hurry up!
Captain, please hang on a little longer.
There're all kinds of people here.
It looks like a fun town.
There's no way...
You think those two can come
back without getting into trouble?
Well, the town looks dangerous as it is.
It's next to impossible.
That's right. They can't do that!
H-Hey, Nami!
Wait for me, Luffy! Zoro!
She went...
Well, she'll probably be okay,
since those two are with her.
What? If Nami-san's going, then I'm...
Don't you go!!
If you go, wh-what'll happen
i-i-if this ship is attacked...?!
Please don't go!!
Fine! Let go of me!
Then, guess I'll prepare
some tea and hold the fort.
Hm? Where's Robin-chan?
Oh...? She's not here.
Sanji-kun, about that tea...
Make it yourself.
In this town, I will...
...not fight. I give my word!
...not fight. I give my word.
Good. This is serious, you two.
Yeah...
What's with the weak reply?!
If you cause trouble,
we'll have to leave this town!
If that happens, we won't be
able to go to the sky, got that?!
Yeah.
Who's he?
Look, he fell from a horse.
Yeah, he did.
Looks like he's in pain.
Yeah, it does.
Hey you guys, sorry to bother you,
but please help me get up.
You're not going to get up by yourself, are you?
Luffy, get that side.
Okay.
Well, thanks... I'm on the horse now.
I was born frail.
Now, let's go, Stronger.
The horse, too?!
Geez, what a pain.
Thanks again.
This isn't much of a reward,
but would you like some?
You're too suspicious!
We don't want any, so beat it already.
Hey, apples! Thanks!
Hey, hey!
What?! What happened?!
Well, some guys were eating apples
that they got from a strange man,
and then they exploded. Five of them!
Oh, no...
Luffy! Spit it out!
Spit out the apple you just ate! Now!
I've already swallowed it.
You bastard! What's the meaning of this?!
Well, he's all right.
That's going too far!
It's a disaster inside.
If you ate a bad one,
you would've died on the first bite.
You're...
...lucky.
This is awful...
Hey, what the hell is this?
Roshio the Executioner's grave.
It looks as if a war happened here.
Did they fire a cannon or something
in the middle of the town?
Who knows?
Even people who were actually watching it said
that they couldn't tell what was happening.
All we know is that Roshio's opponent was Bellamy.
Oh, Bellamy the Hyena?
There's no doubt that he's got the power of one of the devil fruits.
Just what is up with this town?!
Well, don't be so touchy, Nami.
You almost got killed for no reason, you know!
I guess it happens sometimes.
I'll be damned if it does!
That guy again...
How many victims have there been now?
It's not like he's a famous wanted man.
Who the heck is he?
Well, I don't even wanna know.
In any case, we should stay away
from that Fighting Champion.
Champion?
Why are you trying to compete?!
Ugh... I wonder if we can really
get information in a town like this.
How about this place?
Hmm... This place seems quiet.
Or rather, this place is lovely!
So although this is a rough town,
it has a place like this.
They have a vacation house on the sea, huh?
In any case, there's no one here...
although I can smell tasty food.
E-Excuse me!
Please don't come in without permission!
Th-This Tropical Hotel is currently
chartered by Bellamy-sama and his party.
So we're asking other guests to, er... leave.
Oh, this place was a hotel?
I-If Bellamy-sama sees you, it'll be a problem,
so please kindly leave immediately.
C'mon, what's wrong with just coming in here?
Who's Bellamy?
Hey, what's going on?
Who the hell are those shabby guys?
Sarquiss-sama! Welcome back!
Well, this is just...
Never mind your excuses!
Just get rid of them already!
How much do you think we're
paying to charter this place?!
She's right. Now, go home, you dumb brat!
Hey, can I beat him up?
No!
Ha! You're going to beat me up?
What funny guys!
At any rate, those are rags you're wearing.
Here! Take this money and buy
yourselves something you like.
Sarquiss, you're wasting money
by giving it to guys like them.
Maybe I should have thrown
it down the drain instead.
Oh? Are you sure?
Let's go! This is unpleasant!
Hey, hey, I can walk on my own.
Oh? You don't want it?
Sarquiss! Lily! Don't tease them so much.
Oh, that's where you were.
They, too, worked hard in their
own way to travel here. Here.
Of course, compared to you
and Bellamy, they're trash, but...
For average guys,
they're doing better than others.
Well, they probably won't be able to survive
in the new era that is about to start, after all.
Still... I see, 30 million... for that greenhorn?
I'll show this to Bellamy.
Dammit! I'm really pissed!!
That's a shame.
Mock Town depends on pirates
who spend lots of money, after all.
So poor pirates aren't invited, huh?
Looks like there's no way of calming you down.
Here, this is on the house.
Since tough guys gather here,
there's lots of trouble.
But if you get bothered by it each time,
you can't get by in this town.
All you can do is play it safe
when dealing with people.
Here you go.
But this town is really unpleasant, you know!
That's probably how a
right-minded person would think.
But unfortunately, right-minded
people are rare in this town.
Well, the log will be stored within four days or so.
So you should leave before you get into trouble.
Four days... Then we can't stay even two days.
Hey, mister!
Hey, old guy!
Hey, buddy!
Hm? What's wrong?
This cherry pie tastes extremely bad! Hm?
This cherry pie tastes extremely good! Hm?
This drink tastes exceptionally good! Hm?
This drink tastes exceptionally bad! Hm?
Is there something wrong with your tastebuds?
Is there something wrong with your head?
Well, since I'm not the cook,
I don't care what you say.
Hey, old guy! Give me 50 steaks to go!
Buddy, give me 51 cherry pies to go!
Wait, make that 52 steaks!
Sorry, I want 53 pies!
No, 54 steaks!
55 pies!
60 steaks!
70 pies!
80!
100!
You bastard! Wanna fight?!
What the hell are you fighting about?!
Luffy, you promised, remember?!
Besides, we don't have enough
money to buy dozens of steaks!
We didn't come for shopping!
Are you a pirate?
Yeah, that's right.
What's the bounty for you?
30 million!
30 million? For you?
Can't be true! It's gotta be a lie!
I'm not lying! That's the truth!
Stop it!
Hey, no fighting in the bar!
Take this and leave now! 50 cherry pies!
Is there a pirate with a straw hat here?
Hm?
I-It's Bellamy!
So, you're the 30 million bounty,
Straw Hat Luffy!
What's this about?
Looks like he's got business with you, Luffy.
Isn't Bellamy the guy chartering that hotel?
Did you hear that?
That shorty's worth 30 million.
He is?
Is that true?
Boy, I keep running into tall guys today.
Give me your most expensive alcohol.
And give this shorty what he wants as well.
Okay.
Huh? This place is full!
What is this place? It's stinky and dirty!
And cheap-looking rum is about all they've got.
Look. They're from earlier.
You should offer us your seats, geez...
What hopeless dumbasses!
That's him, Big Knife Sarquiss, right?
Is he going to start a fight here or something?
No way...
DEER
The whole gang is here.
There's no way they just came for a drink.
Leave them be! It has nothing to do with us!
Bellamy sure is a curious one.
He sure is.
Well, have a drink.
Oh, thanks! You're actually a nice guy!
DEER
Darn! He did it!
Bellamy's nuts!
What's the meaning of this, small fry?
Why don't you tell me?
Zoro! Hold on a minute!
We haven't gotten any
information in this town yet!
Shut up! I'm just taking him up on his offer!
Hm? So you got back up!
So you're ready to take me on, huh?
Whoa! They're gonna take Bellamy on!
Go for it!
Don't get beaten!
This isn't a fight, it's a test!
C'mon! Let's see how strong you are!
Luffy, wait!
Hey, Mister! We want to go to the sky island!
Do you know anything about it?
What did that chick... just say?
She can't be serious.
Like I said, if you know how to get to the sky island...
She said "sky island"!
Give me a break!
What?!
But the Log Pose is definitely pointing to the sky!
"The Log Pose is definitely pointing to the sky!"
Log Poses get broken easily!
Hey, you got me there.
You guys believe in such an ancient
legend that there's an island in the sky?
Just which era are you from?
Unusual currents in the Grand Line
are being explained one after another.
The Knock-Up Stream is one of them.
I guess you probably don't know
something like that even exists.
The ships that fell victim to this
current are pushed up high in the sky,
and then slam into the ocean!
Without knowing this, sailors from long ago
saw the strange scene where the
ships fell, and imagined sky islands,
thinking, "There must be
another world in the sky!"
How foolish! All phenomena have reasons.
These things that people dream
about will all be explained soon!
Good grief! I thought I'd test you and
let you join my crew for the new era,
but you're such a delusional dumbass!
Listen.
The era where pirates dream about things is over!
The City of Gold, the City of Emeralds,
the big hidden treasure, One Piece...!
Those idiots who are blinded by dream treasure
don't notice the treasure around them.
In this era of oceans, those who should
be most capable of crossing the ocean
are misled by those illusions and die.
And people talk about those dead idiots, saying,
"He was happy since he lived his dream!"
That's just drivel from losers!
When I see idiots chasing after
dreams like that, I get disgusted!
Luffy!
Since there're weak pirates like you,
it even makes us strong pirates look worse.
Get outta here, you scum!
We can't enjoy our drinks!
Bellamy's right!
Get out!
Get outta this town!
Hey, Bellamy! Looks like everyone
here wants to see your show!
That's no problem.
Luffy! Zoro!
Forget the promise, beat them up already!
Zoro...
Don't take them on, no matter what happens.
Aa hateshinaku tsuzuiteru sora no mukou ni
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
Itsuka mita asu o ima egakihajimete iru
The future that I once saw is now starting to take shape
Jibun ni makesou ni naru hi mo aru
There are days where I almost lose to myself
Sonna toki wa
When that happened,
atataka na basho ga atta
there was someplace warm I could go
Hokoreru mono itsumo kitto
The friends I took pride in always, without fail,
Boku no senaka oshite kureta yo ne?
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Aa hoshi-tachi ga furisosogu kono sora no shita
Ah, the stars are pouring down underneath the sky
Nido to nai ima o hora
This unique moment...
Hey, Luffy! Zoro! What's the matter?!
It's no use. Once men decide on something,
you can't make them budge an inch.
No matter how cool they act,
it's all over if they die!
You guys come and help us!
What? Well, we also ran into a crazy guy.
Next time, on One Piece:
Distinguished Pirates!
A Man Who Talks of Dreams and the King of Undersea Search!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Distinguished Pirates!
A Man Who Talks of Dreams and
the King of Undersea Search!