Let's set sail before the break of dawn,
to meet a yet unseen tomorrow
I've made up my mind, and I have no regrets
(Oh I know what I'm supposed to do)
No matter what trials wait for us along the way,
nothing can ever stop the pounding of our hearts
There is but one place we all aim for
(Fly to the light)
The bonds that we gained at the end of the battle
I will not let anyone damage them
If we open our hands held tight,
we'll find strength within them
So let's get started!
A brand new world is calling for us
Look ahead!
Even if countless seas stand between us,
we're always supporting each other
Let's move on without any fears
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The great, wide, distant sky
that we looked up at on that day
still remains as pure as it has always been
We've come such a long way,
all carrying the vows we made within our hearts
There's nothing to fear
We carry our burdens together
The sun rises,
and it brightens everything, even my sadness
I believe,
in the future where we'll come together as one
Let's go find it together
There's nobody that can take your place
Please don't forget,
We fight together
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the Paramount War against the Navy,
Luffy made it to Maiden Island
where he was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
Luffy has been left with Dadan -
the mountain bandit of Mt. Corvo
and met 2 precocious kids named Ace and Sabo.
Leaving the Dadan Family for Good?!
The Kids' Hideout Completed!
How are you, Pochi?
Who dug a hole at the front door?!
It was Ace and the other
two - to catch boars.
This is my house! They can't just
dig a hole wherever they want!
Those brats!
Sabo, who gave you permission
to invade our territory?!
Your territory?! Ha! You
guys are so full of it!
Stop talking nonsense and bring it on!
Alright, get ready!
Ace!
Pay attention!
Dammit!
You little shit!
I made a dent!
Here comes the sheriff! Let's go!
Luffy, Hurry up! It's this way!
It's back!
Let's get a deer for dinner!
Yeah! I love venison! Let's go hunting!
Hey, wait!
We're home!
Don't come home, annoying brats!
That's for dinner.
Cook it now.
It's a mealtime!
Don't waste food!
He's gonna eat me!
Don't come out until you count up to 10,000!
Hey! Stop it!
You jerk!
Honestly!
Why do we have to do a major
housecleaning every night after dinner?!
I'm gonna kick them out at any cost!
Now it's clean!
Luffy! Wait, you bastard!
B-Boss...
Oh boy...
The only time I can relax
is when I'm in my futon.
The last training for today!
I'll win!
You'll never learn!
--Here we go!
--Okay!
Hi, fairy!
Damn!
--Luffy, are you alive?
--What a crappy floor.
You bastard!
Hey!
Should we go to sleep?
Yeah.
We gotta kick the brats out!
If nothing is done, they're gonna
take over the Dadan family!
First of all, it's ruining my health!
Easy, easy, boss.
They got control over us long ago!
Shut up! It's just I can't
look after them anymore!
Yes, I'm gonna kick them out!
Forget about the agreement with Garp!
Hey!
Garp?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry! I don't
know what made me say it!
Excuse me. I heard that Luffy is here.
Makino!
Luffy!
You look great!
It's been 6 months so we came
here to see how you're doing.
Hey, mayor!
Don't tell Garp-san.
So you're really living with the bandits...
You got a problem?
Yes, a big one! You're a bandit
- don't give me attitude!
What?! People from the
Windmill Village are all annoying?!
I have some presents for you!
I assume that Garp-san wouldn't
think about these things...
Here it is! New clothes!
Oh, great!
I'm glad that you like them.
I'll adjust the length
so... I need you guys, too.
Okay?
Oh, hey!
You, too.
I heard that Ace-kun was mischievous
but you seem like a good boy.
N-No, I'm not...
--He's so shy!
--You're blushing, Ace!
--You jerks!
--Oh hey, you can't move!
I'll show you later.
I hope you like it!
Yummy!
Meals should be good on the ship.
I'm gonna get the best cook first
thing when I go out to sea!
I'm gonna become a pirate before
you do so just forget it.
That's not fair! I'm gonna
become a pirate first!
You're still saying a crap like that?!
Can't you both understand that
you must become Navy soldiers?!
--Dadan!
--Yes, Garp-san...
Why should I get hit, too?
You're not educating the brats well!
He's Garp? He's Ace and Luffy's grandfather?
Squirt, you mentioned about
going out to sea, too...
He's not a "Squirt" - he's Sabo!
We exchanged a cup of sake and
pledged to become pirates!
He has such a big mouth...
Oh, that means now there are 3 fools
who want me to give them a real workout!
You can't get away!
Oh boy...
You must be happy, Luffy.
You have 2 older brothers now.
Wait!
Take this!
Chest!
Here, here, here!
This old man is like a monster!
That's it for today! I'm
gonna be harsher tomorrow!
You can't drop dead yet!
If nothing is done, the old
man will kill us tomorrow.
Even if we survive,
he'll keep doing it until
we give up our dream!
I don't wanna die!
We only have one choice.
It's time to make up our minds, brothers!
"We will stand on our feet."
What should we do about this?
How smart-alecky of them.
How could you not care?! They're
infamous even downtown!
Anyone will try to kill them on sight
if they aren't sheltered by us!
My vacation is over!
You gotta shape them into full-fledged
Navy men by the time I come back!
--Are you gonna leave everything to me again?!
--Huh?
Take care!
How can a bandit raise a Navy soldier?!
That geezer doesn't know what he's saying!
Easy, easy, boss.
So you are worrying about
those kids after all.
Who cares?! Come to think
of it, this is good for us.
They left voluntarily! Oh, I'm glad!
We got away successfully!
They're not coming - Dadan and the others.
It's true that "the devil's
children have the devil's luck"!
He's the devil's son!
I can tell that she feels happy now
because her troubles have gone away!
Oh no! It's pouring!
Let's stay here and hide from the rain.
This is exciting!
I've changed my mind. I don't
wanna get beaten by Garp
Go and look for the stupid brats already!
Yes, ma'am!
Guys!
Ace! Sabo!
Luffy!
Look at this!
What is it?
I designed our hideout. We can't
sleep outdoors forever, right?
So we gotta build a hideout right here!
A hideout... That's cool!
What about materials?
We've got tons you-know-where.
Awesome! Looks exactly like the design!
Great work if I say so myself!
What's wrong, Ace?
This is a hideout so we
gotta set up some traps!
Okay, I'll think about it!
Yeah!
We have a view of Gray Terminal,
the Windmill Village and
the water of the East Blue!
It's not so uncommon, is it?
It's nice to see them from here!
You're right! It's different!
Luffy, there's a tailwind! Set the sails!
Okay!
Advance to the treasure!
An enemy off the bow and starboard side!
It's Bluejam's ship! Prepare for action!
They've started shooting!
Take evasive action!
Luffy, hard aport!
Yeah, I got it!
No! You have to say "steady"
at times like this!
Oh, that's right.
Luffy, hard aport!
Hard aport! Steady!
Let's fight hand-to-hand! Lay aboard!
Wait for them to come aboard!
I got it!
Don't cry, Luffy!
Okay!
We won!
Yeah!
That'll teach you!
This is nice!
Yeah, it's great!
This is our hideout!
Here they are!
--Can't you find them yet?!
--I'm sorry!
We talked to people who saw them at Gray Terminal or in the jungle
but we couldn't find them!
It's been 2 weeks!
Maybe they were eaten by the
big tiger in the jungle!
--Boss!
--W-We found them!
Really?!
They built a hideout in the
huge tree deep in the jungle!
We can take you there!
I see!
--I'm happy for you, boss!
--You were worrying so much!
Oh crap! Are they still alive?
I can't believe that those
brats are so tenacious!
W-What?
Don't just stand around, guys!
Go get something for dinner!
Yes, ma'am!
Ace... Sabo... Wait for me...
When they're sleeping, they
look like ordinary kids.
Oh no, don't catch cold.
A trap just went off!
Someone tried to invade already?!
Oh? Maybe it was just a glitch.
Well, we made it in hurry so it could happen.
Ace...
Ouch...
Damn!
I'll never worry about them again!!
When the boys are attacked by a huge
bear, a certain old man saves them.
The man tells them
that he once fought Gold Roger.
Luffy is thrilled to hear a story
about the Pirate King that
he's never heard before!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Luffy Becomes an Apprentice?!
The Man Who Fought the Pirate King!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Luffy Becomes an Apprentice?!
The Man Who Fought the Pirate King!