Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ to rescue his brother, Ace
who is about to be executed!
Meanwhile, at Marineford,
the great war between the Navy
and the Whitebeard Pirates has begun!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
I knew that you wouldn't let me...
...strike your head that easily.
What is he doing?!
Stop this if you can!
If all three of us left our positions...
...who would cover them?!
Great Eruption!
Get away!
He lit up the place too brightly.
Why don't you light up
birthday cakes instead, you magma squirt!
Don't you want an illuminated funeral
for yourself, Whitebeard?
Descendent of the Beast!
Little Oars Jr.—Full Speed Ahead!
I didn't know that there are such giant men in this world.
He's truly a beast!
If I can have his dead body,
that means I can have the strongest zombie again!
Get to the scaffold quick!
The Giant Unit is on the move!
Don't be afraid!
They are after Little Oars Jr.!
It's our duty to...
...Stop him!
He's unbelievably big—
more than twice as big as a common Giant!
Keep shooting!
He's still a human-being
so it should work against him!
They brought such an
unthinkably powerful creature with them.
Shoot him! Shoot him up!
Oars, don't!
You're an easy target for them since you're so huge!
Ace-kun!
Here I come!
Oh no!
Stop him!
Oars opened up a space for us to get into the bay!
Invade the bay!
Damn! Fall back and tighten the defensive line!
Don't let them get to the plaza!
Wh-Where should we run?!
Stand back, Navy!
Don't get in my way!
Rear Admiral Yukimura,
the slayer of a thousand men!
What are you doing?
This is a battlefield!
We have no use for the unprepared!
I'm helpless!
I've never had to "look up" to anyone before this!
Me neither!
I must reach Ace-kun!
Don't get in my way!
I'm not gonna let you go any further!
Vice Admiral Lacroix!
Oars, he'll never change.
Brave men don't seek death!
Pops, don't stop me!
I just wanna save him!
I just wanna save Ace-kun as soon as possible!
I know that.
Everyone, help him!
Give Oars cover!
How can we defend against someone so huge?!
You cut Vice Admiral Lacroix!
You can't attack him alone! We gotta do it together!
While Oars has you distracted, we'll make our move against you!
Slave Arrow!
H-Hey, you guys!
So you're the Pirate Empress!
My body's... cracking!
Perfume Femur!
You bitch! You hit Navy soldiers, too!
I agreed to fight against Whitebeard but...
...I didn't say that I will become a part of you.
Allies or foes—men are all the same.
Except for him.
Maybe just—"I have kept my word."
What?!
Have mercy on my beauty.
Y-You!
Ace-kun!
Come on! Come on now!
Oars!
Hey, you!
I'm gonna save you now!
Oars...
Ace-kun!
Ursus Shock.
Oars!
That's enough! Stop!
You can't reach me!
Hey, Oars!
I was just wondering...
Aren't you hot?
Because you're closer to the sun?
I'm hot.
I see.
It'd be nice if you had some shade.
Captain Oars!
Can he still move?
That's great!
He's got the toughness of his ancestor!
What's this?
I learned how to make it in the Wano Kingdom.
Try it on.
Ace-san ruined two others before that one.
They burned up!
Since his body's fire, he shouldn't braid straw!
It's cool under here!
Yeah? That's good.
Fire at Oars!
Oars!
He shouldn't have gotten
off his knees! He's a ready target!
Captain Oars! Why are you staying outside?
I don't get wet in the rain.
This is very sturdy!
I love it!
I still... can't get to him!
If I could...
...get one of the Seven Warlords at least!
What's the matter, beast?
My foot...
Captain!
Captain, why are you staying outside, again?
The snow's not getting on my head.
It's not cold!
I really love this!
Thank you, Ace-...
What fun!
Oars!
H-He must be a monster!
He stepped into the plaza!
Just a little more...
Just a little more to get to Ace-kun!
Damn Doflamingo!
He cut this guy's foot off!
I already claimed his body!
Doppelman!
Get him!
Spiky Shadow Lizard!
Oars!
I'm gonna... save you now...
Ace-kun!
Oars laid his life on the line to clear a path.
The Whitebeard Pirates rush to the scaffolding,
but just when it looks like
they can rescue Ace from execution,
Sengoku is already formulating a new plan.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Justice for the Winners
Sengoku's Strategy in Action!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Justice for the Winners
Sengoku's Strategy in Action!