Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can become Pirate King!
Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
BON VOYAGE!  hito kakera no yuuki hirogete
BON VOYAGE!      Let that shred of courage grow
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
saisho wa minna BARABARA ni egaite ita chiheisen
The horizons everyone dreamed of were separate at first
ima nara hitotsu no bouenkyou de nozokeru
but now they can be seen through a single telescope
kimi no KOKORO madowasu unmei no shoppai KONPASU
A bitter compass of destiny is leading your heart astray
saka te ni kajitoru yo
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
BON VOYAGE!
SHIGARAMI mo kako mo sutete
Toss aside your bonds and your past
bokura nara sore demo waraeteru hazu
We can surely smile despite that
yume o kanaeru tame no namida naraba oshikuwanai
Tears shed trying to achieve your dreams aren't for naught
PRECIOUS IN MY LIFE
precious in my life
mirai e no SHIPPO chotto mieta yo
I caught a glimpse of the tail end to the future
The Gold and
Waver Recovery Operations!
All right, then! Here we go, guys! Ready?!
Yeah!
Wait, wait! Wait, you guys!
What's wrong, Usopp?
Geez, you guys! Are you just gonna go without thinking this over?!
This doesn't bode well at all.
Seven people running around will stand out way too much!
That's true, come to think of it.
And even though it is disguised,
I'm worried about Merry!
Yeah, given this level of quality.
They'll notice, even though it's so perfect?!
There's such a thing as worrying too much.
No one's gonna take this junky—
Don't call it junk!
Besides, that isn't the issue here!
Honestly!
I'm the only one who considers the unexpected!
There's no doubt it's gonna get sunk the next time it's spotted!
Plus... Nami!
Huh? Me?!
What happened to the Waver?!
Oh, no! I left it hidden in some grass!
See what I mean!
My bad!
Forgetful Nami-san is lovely, too!
Well, stupidity aside...
All right, men. I'll now explain the plan.
So listen good!
Tadah!
Okay, gentlemen!
I'll now explain the plan!
First, the gold recovery team!
This will consist of Luffy, Zoro, Robin, and me, Captain Usopp-sama!
And the Waver recovery team will
consist of Nami and one other!
Sanji!
Nice plan, Usopp!
Let's work hard, okay?!
Yeah, yeah.
Dumbass eyebrows.
What was that?!
Hey, Usopp!
Are you leaving me alone with the ship again?!
Don't worry!
Merry's completely disguised,
so you can almost rest easy!
Almost?!
Plus, who's gonna tend to our
injuries if something happens?!
Super Doctor!
You dummy!
Praising me won't help you, you jerk!
Listen. Here's where we are now.
The gold recovery team will avoid all regular routes
and take the shortest path along
the coast to the storage vault.
Nami.
Do you remember where you hid the Waver?
Yes.
By the bay on the eastern side of the island.
At the base of the rim... Right around here.
Almost the exact opposite side...
It'll take too long to go by land...
Yes! Right there!
Nami!
You two rush across the bay in that boat!
And we'll all meet back here, at the Going Merry!
Right!
Huh? You're still there? You can leave now...
The head chef has ordered me to stand watch
until you've eaten everything on your plate!
Even if you dine in your private quarters,
rules are rules!
You must eat every last bite!
That lousy Jessica...
You too, General!
Eh?!
We've prepared plenty for you!
Please eat up!
You don't like broccoli either, General?
No, for me, it's tomatoes and carrots...
Oh! Lieutenant Commander!
Oh, are you eating?
I'll come back later, then.
No, no! This is an exception!
You came at just the right time!
Sir?
I was just about to call for you!
O-Oh...
Commander! I apologize for letting the
Straw Hats escape three separate times!
Oh, that doesn't matter right now!
Say, have you eaten yet?
No...
That's not good! Not good at all!
You can't fight on an empty stomach!
In fact, it's your duty as a
high-ranking officer to eat first!
It's harder for lower-ranking
people to eat otherwise!
Right...
There's no need to act reserved!
Eat right up!
Tell her it was exceptionally delicious!
Understood.
I'll crush you fools and this hedgehog in no time flat!
Look forward to it, you damn commander!
正義 = Justice
It's almost time...
Looks like we'll need to reorganize our units.
So the plan is to hurry ahead of them and block their path?
Yes. General, contact each unit immediately.
Yes, sir!
Attention, all warships on standby!
Urgent orders!
Monitor the area around
the Sea Gate and the bay!
What about my unit?
Send your men to the Sea Gate
as soon as they've finished eating.
Understood!
You!
Why, hello there, Condoriano... Oh, pardon me.
I mean, Special Inspector Major Shepherd!
Commander Jonathan.
I hear you let the Straw Hat pirates escape.
Not at all.
They are likely still hiding inside this fortress.
Oh? And you can eat a leisurely meal knowing that, huh?!
You must not have a care in the world!
It's no wonder they secretly call you a peace-addict hedgehog.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, think nothing of it.
So, I assume you know what they're sneaking around for?
For the most part.
I believe they'll come back to retrieve some gold they forgot about.
Gold, huh?
Still, we've certainly declined from our former dauntless selves.
Major.
If you have any sage advice, might I ask for it?
I could put you in charge of an
especially skilled unit if you'd like...
Don't be absurd.
You know you're the most worthy to command this "skilled unit."
Incidentally, where are the men
who mistook me for a Straw Hat?
Why do you want to know that?
So I can court martial them, naturally.
It was I who gave the orders to
capture all suspicious people on sight.
All they did was follow those orders.
Am I a suspicious person?
Under those circumstances.
We seem to have a conflict of views.
I've just remembered something I need to do.
I'll return here once I'm done.
Commander. Will you be all right?!
He's a proud HQ inspector who insists that G8 is wholly unnecessary.
He would never take command of this branch base.
That wasn't what I meant!
Now, then.
Prepare to dispatch the most powerful squad in all of G8!
Not more of your jokes...
I am serious.
Those damn fools...
Hey!
The Stan Marey entered port this morning... where's its captain?!
Sir!
He's been in the infirmary this entire time!
The infirmary?! What's he doing there?!
Apparently, many of his crew were injured,
so he's probably there out of concern for them.
Call him here! Right now!
Yes, sir!
He said they're after gold...
And there's only one place in this fortress that could be!
Just you watch, you worthless commander!
I'll catch that Straw Hat myself and crush this entire fortress!
I hope everyone is all right...
I'm so lonely!
The stars! The moon!
And I'm all alone with Nami-san in a boat beneath them!
What a wonderful situation!
I feel like I'm dreaming!
The warships in the bay are moving!
What are they doing?
I have a bad feeling about this!
Sanji-kun! Go faster!
Yes! As you wish!
Oh, but row quietly!
You got it!
All clear on the left and right...
There's no telling where there could be soldiers,
so we gotta move around unnoticed!
It'll be a miracle if we don't get noticed!
Long-nose! We'll be fine for a while.
Why couldn't you say so sooner?!
What are you sleeping for?!
Get your act together, will ya?!
He has no sense of tension at all...
Commander.
Placing units all along the bay will
leave the base itself undermanned.
It can't be helped.
Against this adversary,
cautiousness amounts to nothing.
But having them prance around as
if they own the place is a bit much.
What do you say we mobilize the new recruits?
No. It's too dangerous for them.
I thought you might say that,
so I kept it quiet until now,
but many have actually
already volunteered to do it.
They are already members of our forces,
and have the same feelings of
fondness for this fortress as we do!
Is that so?
In that case, order them to observe and report only...
no getting involved.
Yes, sir! I'm sure they'll be delighted!
By the by. I have one other request for you, General...
Yes?
What?! That's insane!
The Stan Marey is crippled and
still being repaired as we speak!
That doesn't mean every ship in your fleet is out of commission.
That's true, but there are soldiers
who still can't even walk
after the storm we ran into on our way here!
Captain. Are you arguing with me,
a special inspector dispatched from HQ?
N-No, it's not like that... But...
Then gather all your men!
Half will stay with me;
the rest will board the Pinepeak
and wait for my orders!
I'm gonna show this useless fortress' fools the power of Navy HQ!
Hey! Zoro! You keepin' up?!
Just shut up, will ya?!
Robin! Are we almost there yet?
Just a little more.
Is it really there?!
There's only a door!
Yes, assuming the map is correct.
Then the vault is behind there?!
Yes. Breaking in through there
should be the shortest route!
Then it's decided!
We've got no choice but to go!
All right! Let's do this thing!
Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
All right!
Let's go, Usopp!
Eh?!
W-We're gonna crash!
Usopp. Don't get left behind.
Say, wanna do that again?!
Screw that! I'm never doing that again!
All right! No marines!
Pardon the intrusion!
Nami-san. Watch your step.
Thanks.
We can't afford to cause an uproar.
Looks like our only choice is to go along the coast now.
There's no time for us to be dealing with marines!
Sanji-kun! Let's hurry!
Okay!
We're almost there, men! Push forward!
I see it!
It's right down there!
The vault is at the end here!
All right! I'm coming for you, gold!
We made it here so easily.
Something's not right...
All right!
P-Pirates!
Y-You're not going any further!
Knock it off.
We're not plannin' to do anything crazy,
like destroy the fortress or slaughter you.
Quiet!
As disrupters of peace, you have to be punished!
We just told you, we're not gonna do anything!
Like I can really believe some pirates!
We are proud to protect these waters,
together with our commander!
In other words, you're trying to say you'll risk your life?
Obviously!
Then go eat a lot and train some damn more!
What is this?! Awesome!
That's quite heavy security.
Yeah, this is definitely the perfect place to hide gold!
I bet there's lots of other good stuff in there besides our gold!
So, what do we do?
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Sorry, Zoro.
Hey!
Sorry...
Brute strength won't open it!
With this vault, you turn these dials,
and when the numbers match,
the gears above turn, the bolts come undone,
and the door opens!
Got that, lady and gentlemen?!
That's far enough!
So they were waiting for us.
It would seem so.
You're trapped like rats!
Give yourselves up quietly!
Do so now and—
What proud, great pirates would ever give up
when there's treasure right in front of 'em?!
They're all yours now!
Hey!
Damn you pirates!
How dare you?! Fire!
Usopp! Take care of the vault!
Consider it taken care of!
Well, Long-nose? Can you handle it?
This is really Nami's specialty,
but a lock of this level is a piece of cake for me!
All right!
First one!
W-What?!
It's instant death if those hit you.
They come off?!
One slip-up, and my head could get smashed in!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Now!
Luffy! Don't stretch your arms out too much!
They'll cut 'em!
Right!
Yes! The second one!
Lt. Commander.
All ships are now at their designated locations.
Good!
Tell them to wait as-is until orders are given!
Yes, sir!
Fifty more minutes...
I surrender!
Nice, Robin!
I'm surrounded...
Treinta Fleurs!
They just keep on coming!
There's no end to 'em!
Usopp! Is it open yet?!
It's open!
Yes!
Damn you!
Whoa!
All hands, retreat!
Wow! This vault is so neat!
What?!
There's no gold at all!
I won't let you escape from Navarone so easily.
Mirai ni mukatte, saki o isoge! Ima sugu ni
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Yume to iu mono oikakete ikou
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
Afure dashi teru subete no kotae ga kokoni
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Hashire, hashire, hiraka reta michi wo
Rush forth, rush forth, on the road opened before us
Tomaru koto naku susumou, bokura wa dekiru
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
Makenai, makenai, ookina kabe demo
We won't give in, we won't give in, even if the obstacle is big
Kowagaru koto nante nai sa, norikoerareru
It's nothing to be scared of, we can overcome it
It's payback time for all your
countless insults toward me!
Oh!
My special unit from HQ will
take care of you Straw Hats!
Oh!
This is the latest portable bazooka,
the Eagle Launcher!
Oh! So cool!
Now you die!
Yeah!
Hey, you!
Next time, on One Piece:
The One Fell Swoop Plan!
Jonathan's Surefire Secret Tactic
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
The One Fell Swoop Plan!
Jonathan's Surefire
Secret Tactic