Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,--
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
Then help us!
What does he mean?
You have to help us! Please!
Please!
After being taken to a
mysterious facility by an unknown group of people,
Nami and the others encountered strange children.
Let's help these children!
What are you saying, Nami-san?!
We don't know for sure they need saving!
We just met them and we don't know what's going on here!
It's not our job to help every single person!
I understand what you're saying but...
...you can't turn your back on a child crying for help!
All right! Let's go!
I won't let you get away! Wait, you bastards!
Oh no!
That centaur again!
Boss!
The intruders are going that way! Please finish them off!
Is that the Boss?
I see a man with swords.
So is that the samurai who cut our people?
Snow! Snow! I love playing with snow!
Ta-dah! Snowmen!
It looks like me!
Oh?
Hey! Hey!
Who the hell...
What?
Whaaat?!
"A Swordplay Showdown! Brook vs. the Mysterious Torso Samurai!"
No matter how far we go, all we see is a wall of ice.
There is no point in protecting ourselves from the gas if we can't land.
Don't give up yet. Keep searching.
It's no use.
An eruption?!
Around here, it feels like...
...we are being watched by Red Hound and Blue Pheasant.
--Oh, that's scary! --Let's go back!
Stop the ship.
What happened?
There.
What?
Prepare to fire!
Fire!
Breaking the surface won't help...
There's a river!
Hey hey, that was amazing, Smo-yan!
I can't believe it!
How did you know there was a river behind there, Smo-yan?
--Yeah, Smo-yan?! --I didn't notice it at all, Smo-yan!
You can tell by looking at the sea current!
You have to pay attention!
You ought to check your own behavior too.
But it's strange.
Yeah.
The important thing is not the fact that there was a river.
It is whether the ice that was blocking the river mouth
was natural or man-made.
Do you mean somebody was hiding the river on purpose?
Who would wanna live on such an island filled with the poison gas?
That's ridiculous! No one wants to live with a mask on!
But the man on the Snail mentioned the island.
You probably misheard it, Tashigi-chan!
Not even a Transponder Snail could survive here!
That's right!
If you have time for laughing, break up more ice!
--What the hell?! --A wall of ice?!
If we collide into it, even this warship would sink!
--Oh no! --We gotta destroy it!
Shoot!
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND - THE MIDDLE LAKE LUFFY'S GROUP
They are...
Boss! Please take care of them!
Be ready!
I, Brownbeard-sama,
THE BOSS – BROWNBEARD - AN ALLIGATOR CENTAUR (A FORMER PIRATE, BOUNTY: 80 MILLION 60 THOUSAND BERRIES)
will kick your asses all the way to hell!
They're all centaurs!
I wonder if they wanna join us too!
I'm sure they don't!
They're obviously prepared to fight us!
They're colleagues of the man who sent out the emergency signal, aren't they?
Yeah, they must be!
We have to clear the air before they start to fight!
Hey!
We're here to help you people! Let's talk first!
You're lying through your teeth!
You're with the samurai!
So there's no doubt that you're intruders!
Samurai?
He's talking about you!
No, he's not a samurai - he's a swordsman!
He's a dumb meathead who picks fights without thinking sometimes but...
...he's not the one who attacked your people!
Who did you call "dumb"?!
Help! He's gonna kill me!
--I'm not gonna kill you! Stop saying that! --They're having a falling out.
What a pathetic ploy!
We can't let them go any further! Shoot them!
Understood!
THE ICE LANDS - INSIDE OF THE MYSTERIOUS FACILITY NAMI'S GROUP
This way, kids! Run if you wanna get away!
You're on fire, Chopper!
Of course!
Sanji entrusted me with the important mission of
protecting the kids and getting them out of here!
I'll do it!
I'll carry it through!
Why are those kids running?!
I'm a man! Leave it up to me!
You're amazing, raccoon dog bro!
I'm not a raccoon dog - I'm a reindeer! Hi-ya!
But where should we go?
That's something you need to figure out. Wachaa!
Boy...
Sis, are we going to be okay?
Of course! We've been though situations like this lots of times!
So just relax and follow us!
Uh-huh!
THE MYSTERIOUS FACILITY - BISCUIT ROOM SANJI'S GROUP
Weapons Left!
Super!
He has weapons all over his body!
He's the one who broke the door!
Oh? You guys wanna know more about me?
Okay! I'll spend as much time with you as you want!
Load the poison gas canisters! There are no kids in here!
Fire at will!
Why don't you take off your mask and smoke some poison gas with us.
You bastard!
Don't get so mad.
--He ripped off our masks! --He broke our air tanks too!
Don't use gas canisters!
What are they?!
Sheep?
What are you doing?
This one is different from the others!
Who is he? He's proving an able opponent!
Again, what are you talking about?
Well, that's what's going on with my torso!
IN FRONT OF THE MYSTERIOUS FACILITY BROOK
Hey! What's going on?!
Wh-Wh-Who are you?!
Where is your head and legs?!
You're scaring me! Please say something!
Shoot! Shoot!
We'll reach the end of the river soon.
I wonder what will be there!
I think I know.
Are you a ghost, by any chance?!
If so, you gotta obey the rules!
Don't come out during the day!
I didn't do anything wrong!
I just set foot on the island to make snowmen!
Oh, would you like to join me and make one, too?
We can make a snow sculpture as well...
I was just kidding!
What's wrong with him?!
How can he attack me with such precision?!
He doesn't have eyes!
Oh yeah! I don't have eyes, either!
Scary! He's strong! Scary!
What do you want?!
Can't you just tell me why you wanna fight me?!
Aubade Coup Droit!
Two-Sword Style?!
Enough already!
Scary! Scary! Gross!
Master!
Did you catch the escapees?
No, I have news about G-5.
Oh, them!
The poison gas didn't work.
Currently, they are breaking through ice floes with a cannon
and slowly forcing their way into the island.
They'll reach the laboratory in time!
Why?
Why do they want to come into the island so badly?
Do they know something?
Who is in charge?
Vice Admiral Smoker.
Smoker?
Of all others, that pain in the neck?
Conceal all the ships moored at the front.
Who's gonna deal with them?
No one's allowed to be here.
Don't let them find you at any cost.
Then you'll deal with them?
Don't be ridiculous! I can't just show myself like that!
But there is no one else who can stop them!
Do you want me to do it?
We finally made it!
I thought I was gonna die!
We've only just landed on the island. Get up!
Don't be so harsh!
We did our best so be kind to us!
Don't be such a baby!
Smoker-san?
Calm down.
I thought so.
--There is no gas. --What?
It's hard to believe but she's right.
Then why was there poison gas earlier?
Somebody who doesn't want to welcome us released it probably.
Do you really think so?
Let's find out.
Is that...
Yes, Dr. Vegapunk's laboratory.
Former laboratory, I mean.
It should be abandoned and empty.
There is still power.
Who is living here?
Hey! Come on out!
What's taking you so long?! Are you afraid of us?!
We don't have to ring a doorbell and wait!
We can just break the door with the cannon of the ship, Smo-yan...
Smoker-san...
--Hey! Answer! --Just open it!
You hear me?
No one is allowed to be here on this island!
Whoever you are, you're under arrest, fool!
Come on out now!
Ignoring us? Okay, bring the cannon here!
--Let's put a big hole in it! --Hey!
It opened!
Now you're giving up? We're the Navy!
What brought you here - to my vacation home?
Asher!
No way!
He is...
He used to be a rookie with a 440 million berry bounty and now,
he is among them...
...Hawk-Eye Mihawk, Pirate Empress Boa Hancock,
and Don Quixote Doflamingo.
Pirates backed by the World Government -
the Seven Warlords!
Trafalgar Law!
Let's go back, Smoker-san!
I don't want anything to do with him!
You know what he did!
To become a member of the Warlords...
...he delivered the hearts of one hundred pirates to the headquarters!
He's crazy!
What a creep!
Why are you here?
No one, not even pirates or Government allies,
is allowed to be here on this island, Law!
That means you people are not allowed, either!
Law stands in Smoker's way,
and neither will yield a single step.
As the situation reaches its boiling point,
the Straw Hat Pirates suddenly appear with the children in tow.
It was then that Law does something that causes
the situation to move immediately!
Next time, on One Piece:
"A Swordplay Showdown! Brook vs. the Mysterious Torso Samurai!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!