Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy hurries for Navy HQ in order
to stop his brother, Ace, from being executed.
Meanwhile, the Whitebeard Pirates have stormed Marineford, starting an all-out war with the Navy.
Oars!
Just a little more to get to Ace-kun!
Doppelman!
Spiky Shadow Lizard!
Justice for the Winners
Sengoku's Strategy in Action!
See? This is how you kill a person!
Captain Oars!
Damn you Warlord!
Captain!
Oars!
Ace-kun...
Ace-... kun...
Ace-...
...kun...
Oars!!
I'll create the most powerful zombie soldier out of his corpse!
Oars...
Your guard is down, Whitebeard!
Vice Admiral Lonz!
H-He beat the Giant—
a vice admiral of the Navy—so easily!
Oars...
Climb Oars' body and advance!
Inside Marineford bay
This is great!
Doflamingo! How could you do that to Oars!
I'll make you pay at any cost!
What's so funny?
This feeling that I'm in the center of history!
This place is the turning point now!
What are you talking about?!
That's our commander!
Doflamingo can't do anything but run now!
R-Rear Admiral Yukimura!
I can't! I can't! I can't!
I'm scared and I can't do anything!
Even those strong fighters falling one after another!
I can't take this! A loser like me!
Wait, Koby! I'm coming with you!
Get back to the battlefield!
Let me go! Please!
Admiral Red Hound! Why is he here?
I'm scared of dying
and when I think about my family,
I feel weak at the knees!
Please! I'm begging you! Please!
We Navy soldiers are...
...fighting pirates with the "justice"
of the world emblazoned on our own backs!
Anyone who turns tail and runs cannot be called a Navy soldier.
I would call him...
...a speck of dirt!
If you truly think about your family,
don't live in disgrace!
N-No! He can't kill a man who's on our side!
Admiral Sakazuki!
We are ready to proceed with the strategy.
Good! The time has come!
"The strategy?"
Ace!!
Marineford bay head
Use the space that Oars opened up!
Get into the bay!
Let's destroy the bay head to open more space!
Fire straight ahead!
Damn! Not even a scratch!
Leave it to me!
An icebreaker?!
It's "Ice Witch" Whitey Bay!
That was quite easy for us.
Alright, everyone! Let's go!
Thanks!
We must move into the bay, too!
What's the matter, 13th division commander Water Buffalo Atmos?
M-My body... What did you do, Doflamingo?!
Commander Atmos!
Don't! Stay away from me!
What's wrong?
Now!
Commander!
No!
Commander Atmos... Why?
I can't control my body!
Don't do this, Doflamingo!
Commander!
"Pirates are evil and the Navy is justice?"
That has been rewritten many times in the past!
Values are different to kids who don't know what peace is
and kids who don't have firsthand knowledge of war.
The one who ends up on top
will rewrite what's right and what's wrong.
This place is the turning point!
"Justice will prevail?"
Of course, it will!
Because the winners claim justice!
They've broken through the bay head at 2 points!
The bay will be flooded by allies of the Whitebeard Pirates!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
No problem.
Tsuru-san, let's put it into action.
Marineford bay head
It's a suitable time.
Outta our way!
If not, you'll get more than a wound!
Outta our way, old bag!
I got washed!
I got hung!
But I feel so good!
You're a million years too early to defeat me.
Connect to all ships and soldiers!
Ring, ring, ring...
He's up to something.
That cunning admiral—"Buddha" Sengoku.
His name is Gol D. Ace.
Old man!
What are you doing here? Disagree with the strategy?
No, they're pirates.
There's no room for pity!
Then...
Shut up!
It's no big deal.
I just wanna be here.
Stupid!
Ace!
What's wrong with you, old man!
"I wanna go out to sea?" I won't let you at any cost!
Don't be bossy, you're not even my father.
I don't have to listen to you, old man.
You better call me grandpa!
Old man.
You wanna get another fist of love?
Grandpa!
I'm gonna be a lot stronger and...
...I wanna go out to sea with Ace!
Ouch!
Stupid! I don't wanna hear it from you, too!
Don't hit Luffy!
Shitty old man.
Shitty?!
Hey, Ace! Come here!
Listen, to be prepared for unexpected battle,
you got to eat to the fullest when you can!
That's important for a Navy soldier!
Both of you, keep that in mind!
Navy?! You can't just decide that for us!
What?!
I'll become a pirate!
You'll join the Navy!
Pirate! Pirate! Pirate! Pirate!
Navy! Navy! Navy!
Yum-yum!
No! He ate everything!
It was good!
So quick!
I'm gonna become a pirate...
If Luffy becomes a Navy soldier,
the food stock of his ship will be gone within a day.
He would be a bigger handful than the pirates!
I have no pity for villains but...
...family is a different story.
What am I supposed to do?!
Ace, you fool!
Why didn't you lead your life as I said?!
Ace.
You two should become strong Navy soldiers.
Okay?
Become a strong Navy soldier.
Old man...
If you have your doubts at this final moment,
I take no pity on even you, Garp.
If I had doubts, I would've done something already!
Did you just hear that, Helmeppo-san? Their strategy...
Yeah...
They're gonna forget the schedule and execute Fire Fist Ace.
If they do that...
What's that?
Something's falling from the sky.
Is that a surprise attack of the Whitebeards?!
I said that you were doing it too much!
It's because of his wink!
Is it my fault, Croco?!
Doesn't matter, we're gonna die!
It's frozen all over down there!
Heehaw!
Oh! I'm a rubber man so I'll be fine!
You just care about yourself?!
Do something!
Vi don't wanna die like this!
Somebody, stop me!
I shouldn't have listened to you, Straw Hat!
Dammit!
Ace!
Luffy and his friends suddenly appear out of the sky
and drop right in the middle of the battlefield.
Luffy finally spots his brother, Ace,
and cries out to him.
The final battle to save Ace begins now!
Next time, on One Piece:
"The Straw Hat Team Arrives
Tensions Grow on the Battlefield"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Straw Hat Team Arrives
Tensions Grow on the Battlefield