Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
mirai dake shinjiteru dareka ga warattemo kamawanai
I only believe in the future, I don't care if anyone laughs
hashitteru jounetsu ga anata o kiramekaseru
that racing passion makes you shine
mabushi sugi, demo mitsumete itai
it's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
dokka "bigaku" kanjiteru
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
dare ni mo nitenai yume no senaka o
I follow, follow in the footsteps of a dream
oikakete oikaketeku
that resembles no one
doramatikku te ni ireru made
until I dramatically get it
dare ni mo mienai yume no katachi o
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
tsukamaete tsukamaeteku
of a dream no one can see
watashi wa tsuite yuku kara atsui kimochi
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
tsujitsuma awase betsu ni iranai
I don't really need everything to add up
arifureta nichijou yori mo
rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
paradaisu mezashite hashire
run for paradise instead
Wow! What a huge town!
The place used to be full of pirates
on their way to the Grand Line.
It has everything you could ever need!
Alright! I'm gonna go get equipment
for our upcoming great adventure!
Looks like I can get some good ingredients here.
Good women, too!
I got something I wanna buy, too.
Oh? How are you gonna do that?
You're flat broke, as I recall!
Alright!
I'm gonna check out the execution platform!
Huh?
I'm gonna see where the Pirate King was executed!
Hey, wait!
We still haven't decided where to meet up at!
Man, that guy...
The Pirate King was born here and died here!
He might've even walked down this very street!
Yahoo!
The Town of the
Beginning and End!
Landfall at Loguetown!
How's this?
Oh! You look wonderful, Miss!
You look so elegant, Miss!
How's this?
Elemental, Miss!
Electrical!
How's this?
Elegy!
Will you be purchasing all of these?
No, I don't want 'em.
I want something that's rougher.
Come again!
Oh! A top-quality aperitif!
Oh!
Two Poinderine champagne-like beauties!
The whole town is brimming with
the finest ingredients around!
Damn, I can't decide what to go after first!
I just found the main dish!
LOVE-LOVE
PIRATES
Awesome! What is this place?!
Everything here is a collector's dream!
Welcome!
Everything here once belonged to pirates
who returned alive from the Grand Line!
They are especially valuable goods.
Then these are all items that went
on adventures in the Grand Line?!
That's absolutely correct!
We only do business with warriors of the sea here,
so we warmly welcome
gentlemen such as yourself!
What do you say?
This was the favorite gun of the Gold Roger!
What?! Gold Roger's?!
Yes!
How about it, sir?
S-Show me more!
Thanks! Come again!
Captain Smoker! Terrible news!
A message from Headquarters!
They've received word that a
Monkey D. Luffy and his pirate crew
are headed here, to Loguetown!
He just earned a thirty-million-berry bounty in the East Blue!
Thirty million...
That's worthy of congratulation.
He's an incredibly evil villain
who even defeated Don Krieg
and Arlong the Fishman!
Quiet!
Damn your shouting.
You made it fall apart.
I'm sorry, sir!
It's not good to be tense.
I got my own pace I do things at.
Isn't that right?
Y-Yes, sir!
So... What, now?
Right! A pirate group!
Word has it they may
show up in town today, yes!
What're you so flustered for?
Have any pirates who've set
foot into this town ever escaped
since I took charge here?
N-No, sir...
Then calm the hell down.
You're gonna screw up my pace.
Yes, sir...
Reporting, sir!
We have word that pirates
have appeared at the port!
Please go there at once!
It must be Luffy's group!
They've definitely set foot into town!
30 million, huh?
I pray he puts up at least a bit of a fight.
Sir?
Just talking to myself. Forget it.
You're not going to look at this?!
"Justice"
Captain!
Please give each unit their orders!
No need.
But you need to consider how powerful he is!
You're annoying me.
Don't tell me what to do!
My apologies, sir!
Never mind that. Where's Tashigi?
Y-Yes.
She mentioned she would be gone this morning,
but that she'd show up for training.
That dumb girl.
Where the hell'd she go?
Yay! A triple-scoop ice cream!
Hold on, now!
You'll drop them if you run!
C-Captain Smoker!
M-My ice cream...
I-I'm very sorry about my daughter!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Sorry 'bout that.
My pants ate your ice cream.
Here, buy yourself five scoops.
Let's go.
Yes, sir!
Th-Thank you!
Thanks!
Loot everything there is!
Don't leave a single potato behind!
I, Gally the Crescent-sama,
will use these vital food supplies
on my way to becoming Pirate King!
Hand it all over thankfully!
Hey.
Who's in charge here?
What do you want?!
So you're Monkey D. Luffy?
I'll test you and see if you're
worthy of setting foot into my town.
Don't give me your crap!
Get 'im!
Captain Smoker?
Yeah. He's one of the toughest
guys from Navy Headquarters.
This town used to be a hangout
for pirates headed for the Grand Line.
But ever since he took over,
every single pirate who's come into town
has wound up in the slammer.
His strength is extraordinary.
He's a monster.
They even say he has Devil Fruit powers...
Devil Fruit powers?!
Incredible, Captain!
You captured Luffy's crew in no time flat!
Are your eyes just for decoration?
This guy obviously isn't Luffy.
Eh?
The world'd be ending if this
shabby fly were worth 30 million.
Th-Then, where is Luffy?
He'll show up soon enough.
The fun is just getting started.
Huh?
How did I wind up at the port? How?
Hey!
Is he one of these guys?
I don't know. I don't think so...
Perfect timing! Do you know how
to get to the execution platform?
The execution platform?
I got lost on my way...
I've never seen you around before.
Yeah! I just landed on this island!
This town sure is huge!
It's way different from Fusha Village!
Why are you looking for the execution platform?
I wanna see the place where the Pirate King died!
You don't know where? Aww...
Wait. Follow the smoke.
Oh! That way?! Thanks!
Damn, these are expensive!
Too expensive!
Lend you money? Sure!
But including interest, you'll hafta
pay me 300% of what you borrow!
I can't afford to borrow any more from that girl...
But I can't go into the Grand Line
stuck with just one sword...
What do I do?
"Monster"?! How rude!
Aww, shut up!
Our boss is behind bars all thanks to him!
Have you still not learned your lesson?!
Nope!
We ain't happy with things as they are!
We're gonna bring your corpse to him to see!
Very well. I will fight you.
You will, girlie?!
Don't make us laugh!
What can a girl possibly do?!
– Die!
– Yeah!
She did it!
You're strong, lady!
You're amazing!
Oww!
– I can't tell if she's strong or weak!
– Glasses! Glasses! Glasses!
Glasses...
Hey. Are these them?
S-Sorry to bother you!
Thank you!
My glasses!
I-I didn't mean to!
Those were expensive!
How could you do something so horrible?!
I told you, I didn't mean to...!
Pay me back for them!
Oh, man.
I was trying to get to the execution platform,
but now I'm somewhere else completely.
Oh, well. I'll get there sooner or later.
Is it this way?
Let's see...
Gold... Roger?
Do you work here, old guy?
It said "Gold Roger" on the sign outside...
Is that this place's name?
Scram.
This ain't a place for a runt like you.
Besides, we're closed for good as of today.
It went under?
It didn't go under!
I'm shutting it down myself!
Now get lost!
I was just curious about the name, that's all.
I'm lost.
I was wanting to go to the execution platform...
Can you tell me how to get there?
What's that on your table?
Oh! A skull?!
It's huge!
This is what became of a guy
once known as Killer Giant.
A villain who sent hundreds
of pirates to the afterlife.
But Gold Roger sent him to
his grave with just one blow.
Gold Roger did?!
With truly lightning speed!
This guy was famous for the
absurdly huge blade he used,
but their fight ended in the blink of an eye!
And this is the wound he received!
But he was an infamous scoundrel himself!
With his dying breath, he muttered,
"Roger... My hat's off to you...
May you have honor as the Eternal Pirate..."
So awesome! So cool!
Eric Down, the man known as King...
Silver Silver, the world's greatest gunman...
The giant Gowns Brothers...
They were all tough men who were as feared as demons.
But for Gold Roger,
they were as weak as infants.
Would ya like to hear more?
Yeah!
Very few people these days
believe this story, you know...
That's okay! Just tell me!
Hold your horses.
Gold Roger...
In those days... no, even still, I guess...
...he was the one and only man
who didn't fear the Grand Line.
Back then, the Grand Line was an unknown area,
from which not a single boat ever
returned after being swallowed up.
It was a sea of evil that people
feared and which few approached!
Old man. Give me more rum.
The whole bottle'll do.
You sure are drinking happily, Roger.
Of course I am.
I'm just about to take a
little stroll into the Grand Line.
I'm excited beyond belief.
Whoa! You're going there?!
Into that sea of evil?!
What?
Is there something wrong with that?
No, not exactly, but...
Take my advice.
Forget about going there.
No one's ever come back!
That's why I'm going.
Now, then. Give me more rum.
A whole barrel'll do.
After saying that, he drank the whole place dry,
then set sail all too casually the next morning.
When I heard he had conquered
the Grand Line a bit later,
I was more happy than I was surprised-
I was more excited than
I should have been at my age!
And then, 22 years ago today,
Roger died on the execution platform.
Ever since that day, everyone
proud of their great strength
has tossed their hat into the pirate ring.
It marked the beginning of the Great Pirate Era!
But now look! The town's full of
nothing but cowards and scum now!
Men crazy enough to challenge that
sea of evil are all but gone now!
That's why this bar is closing down for good today.
I'm going to the Grand Line, too!
Huh?!
Gold Roger's so cool...
He's how a pirate should be!
That's why I set out to sea.
I'm gonna go to the Grand Line,
find the One Piece,
and be the Pirate King!
Those're some mighty big words!
And in this bar, of all places!
I only said what I meant.
Kiddo!
If there're still patrons like you out there,
maybe I'll hold off on closing this place!
How should I know if there are?!
You're right!
Of course you wouldn't know!
I haven't been in such a good mood since then!
I'll treat you to a drink!
I don't drink alcohol.
Right! Then have this!
Let's have a toast!
To the eternal Pirate King!
You?!
That's certainly a warm hello...
...for a regular patron of yours.
Cut the crap!
You're tryin' to shut the place down!
It's wrong of you to hold a grudge against me.
I only come here as a loyal customer.
It's the pirates' fault that
they're all cowards these days.
You had a customer? How rare.
I'd like a drink of rum...
There is no alcohol for you here!
Don't be so iron-hearted.
Today's a special day.
Wouldn't you agree?
That's the stuff...
Even now, I remember that day clearly...
How Roger looked at the very end...
This is Main Street!
Did Gold Roger walk through here, too?!
Yes...
It was a humid afternoon, just like today...
His hands were shackled as
he was led down the main street
toward the town square,
where the execution platform stood...
Yet, he walked like a triumphant general.
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger had attained everything
the world has to offer...
Even though he was walking toward death,
he was literally a king of great pride...
Inherited will...
The tide of the times... People's dreams...
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Do you have any last words?!
Take this off for me.
It's itchy beyond belief.
I can't do that!
Do you think I would run away?
You sure know how to make a guy feel lonely.
All right, let's get this over with quickly.
Hey, Pirate King!
Where did you hide all the treasure you found?!
Is it in the Grand Line?!
You got it, didn't you?!
That legendary treasure!
Shut up, you!
That great treasure!
The One Piece!
My treasure?
Don't speak without permission!
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
Execution!
That's how it all began...
Hey!
A new wanted poster!
Put it up somewhere noticeable!
C-Captain Smoker!
Sorry for the rudeness, sir!
U-Umm...
That Straw Hat...
It was Monkey D. Luffy!
There it is...
So this is where the Pirate King was executed...
The place where the greatest pirate in history died...
The place where it began...
hamidashita kimochi tsunagara nakute
my overflowing feelings don't connect
kimi no te o gyutto ni girikaesu yo
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
hitori demo boku wa arukidasu kara
I'll set off by myself,
tooku made zutto mitsumeteite ne
so keep watching me intently as I go into the distance
kesa kara chotto kangaeteita
I was thinking about it a bit since this morning
doushite konna ni atsui no
why is it so hot?
itsu kara ka sonna koto bakari ga
starting from some point,
hanarenai yo
I haven't been able to get away from that
kakedashita kimochi tsukamaetakute
I want to catch those feelings that rushed off,
jibun sae mou oikoshite yuku yo
and I'm already about to overtake myself, even
tobidashita yume o dakishimetetai
I want to embrace my dreams that have jumped out
issho nara boku wa hashitte yukeru
with you, I can run there
Ahh!
This is a town for meeting pretty women!
Pretty women, indeed...
We can't relax!
The marines here are supposedly tough!
We just got here!
How about you?
Did you buy your swords?
That's the problem.
In any case, I gotta get me two more swords.
Next time, on One Piece:
Kitetsu III and Yubashiri!
Zoro's New Swords and the Woman Sergeant Major
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Kitetsu III and Yubashiri!
Zoro's New Swords and
the Woman Sergeant Major