Once there was a man who had it all,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His final words spurred people
to take to the seas in droves:
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it! I’ve left everything
this world’s got to offer there!
People now set sail
in pursuit of their dreams.
Indeed, the world is in the midst
of the Great Pirate Era!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep
If we're gonna travel through an unbelievable world,
you'll have to be tough
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner (・∀・)
Aah, freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow
I'll be the first to the One Piece, I swear
Our hearts dream beyond measure
So let's never wake them up
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... have made it this far
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us
And we won't leave anyone behind
We'll never look back, that's a vow
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still!  I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine... One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it except for Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached Fishman Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fishman Pirates who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hody's merciless plot puts Fishman Island in unprecedented danger!
What's wrong?
L-Look at that!
I can't believe it!
There is air!
"Coming to an End! The Final Decisive Battle against Hody!"
That toughness should put his worth over 100 million.
This wound...
Luffy-sama...
I won't let you interfere with my plan, Straw Hat!
You can't lay a finger on the ship!
Fishman Island is doomed to fall like this!
Gear 2!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
You're too slow, Straw Hat!
Luffy-sama...
Luffy-sama!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazooka!
Armament: Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
These fangs aren't fake!
I know you're in pain, Straw Hat!
Damn! He's pretty tough! Red Hawk worked much better a while ago.
This is the power I was granted by heaven,
to destroy you evil lowly creatures - humans!
I bet you thought you could gain the upper hand fighting where you can breathe
but it's no use.
Nobody can best this righteous power!
And nobody can stop me from getting revenge!
Hody.
I'm sure that he is now beyond his physical capacity.
But he became a real monster due to his grudge
toward humans and the Energy Steroid.
Straw Hat.
Luffy-san is losing.
Hody Jones... Is he invulnerable?
I repeat.
The giant ship - Noah is still falling toward Fishman Island
and on the deck of the Noah, Luffy-san is engaging in battle with Hody!
--The Noah is gonna crush us! --Can't we do anything?!
Straw Hat!
Did you hear that? Our captain is doing fine.
Our cause was right after all. We were chosen by heaven!
It's a one-in-a-million chance for your captain to win the fight!
No.
Like I said, I believe in him.
Our captain will never lose!
Joke around while you can!
Chopper, what do you mean you're okay?
Now, I can fight like this for 3 minutes with the Rumble Ball.
I'm not the same person that I used to be.
I won't cause you guys trouble anymore.
I can't believe it!
We can really depend on you if you can control that power!
Y-Your compliment doesn't make me happy at all, you bastard!
That's creepy!
You pissed me off-dosun!
No matter how big you get, I'll blow you away to the end of the sea-gogan!
I'm not gonna be blown away to anywhere.
Now, bring it on!
Chopper!
You fool!
Talking to a friend while fighting? You don't know your place!
You're just a burden to the Straw Hats!
I'm gonna take care of you already!
I told you I finished setting it up.
Now, bring it on! I'll put on an awesome magic show!
Much! How funny! Did you say you're gonna end this with one shot?!
Maybe the Squid Spear didn't work on you
but I have another one that will cut through anything-ch!
Emit light! Light Bright Spear!
I will beat you with one shot instead-ch!
I'm gonna cut a hole through your cockpit-ch!
That looks kind of cool but...
...it's not gonna work! You're less than an ordinary squid...
...before my ultimate weapon!
I can't fight with my bare hands. What should I do?
I won't cut a man without the fighting spirit! Go away, Froggy!
Frog?
I don't know what he is talking about.
He doesn't know that my deadly poison will kill him!
Finish this up? That's my line.
Don't think that I inflated myself just because I got taken in by you fools!
I'm gonna roll around and squash your friends in the plaza!
Are you listening?!
Sorry, I was thinking about something else.
Thinking about something else?!
Yeah, I was thinking how should I cook an unnecessarily big blowfish.
What?! Do it if you can!
Blowfish!
All right...
Luffy-sama! You are bleeding!
Can't you see it? There is nothing you can do!
You will never beat me!
Weren't you listening to what I said?
I will save Fishman Island and Shirahoshi...
Luffy-sama...
...and keep my promise to a friend.
Straw Hat...
I'll protect...
...everything!
Seems like you humans have to die in order to realize...
...how arrogant you are even though you're so weak!
Then I'm gonna make you realize!
I have no time! Let's wrap this up already!
Beat me if you can!
--Wimpyhoshi, stay away! --Y-Yes!
Fishman Jujutsu, Water Heart:
Shark Pack!
You can't get away!
Go to hell!
Luffy-sama...
Straw Hat!
Luffy-sama!
Gear 3,
Armament: Hardening!
Drop dead already!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
It's no use!
You puny humans could never stop me...
...from taking revenge!
I will stop the Noah!
Keep falling, Noah!
Kill all the pride-less Fishmen!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gatling!
This is my space, skeleton man.
If you enter this circle, I'm gonna break your bones into pieces!
What are you gonna do now?!
Okay, I'm sorry but...
...I got into the circle and cut you already.
It's going to be cold. Take care of yourself.
When did you get in?!
Scoring Song: Blizzard Slice!
Let me read a haiku.
The blood-freezing wind from the far land of the dead...
...Please, blow up some skirts!
Drop dead!
What is it?!
Green Star: Humandrake!
This plant has human-shaped roots which attack things flying over,
totally entwining them!
What is it this time?!
Green Star: Trampolia! It'll blow away all approaching enemies!
And now you're up high in the air - there's nothing you can do!
Sure-Kill Green Star...
A monster from aboveground?! I'll bite it off!
You better not.
The bulb on its nose
will release a powerful shockwave 3 meters in diameter.
Impact Wolf!
Dosun! Dogan! Bogan!
Now, get blown away to the end of the world-gadon-megagon!
Papara-Hammer!
Hoofprint: Palme!
Pi... pikon.
Squid! Squid! Squid!
Chew on this - the spear that will cut through even an undersea mountain!
Franky...
Squid! Squid! Squid!
...Radical Beam!
Dried squid!
What?!
L-Laser beam?!
Cool!!
Fishman Karate Secret Art:
Vagabond Drill!
What?!
Water blasted through his body!
The air will leak...
How do you like it up here, Balloon Blowfish!
That human is flying!
You scared the guts out of me!
Remember, over the past 2 years...
Sanji-kun!
Why did I have to go through such hell?!
He's on fire!
I want to burn those memories!
Hell Memories!
Scared the guts out of you? You saved me the trouble then.
Because when I cook blowfish,
I have to remove the toxic parts carefully.
Take these swords coated with my venom!
Cut it out, Froggy.
I'm not a frog!
I'm the best octopus Eight-Sword Style swordsman...
...on Fishman Island! My name is Hyouzou! Don't forget it!
Purgatory...
...Demon Slash!
I'm so sorry.
I thought that you were a frog. A big frog in a small pond.
He...
He did it!
This time for sure!
He beat Hody!
The Noah falls toward Fishman Island, as if inheriting Hody's grudge.
Just when the insurmountably huge mass...
...causes everyone to lose hope,
Luffy alone...
...pushes his life to the limit and stands against the Noah!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Stop, Noah! Desperate Elephant Gatling!"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!