A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
natsu-iro taiyou ga KOKORO no ho o yuraseba
When the summer sun sways the sails of my heart
atarashii sekai e no tobira o hiraku aizu
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
namima ni yureteru zetsubou o nukete
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
suiheisen no mukougawa (yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah) mezashite
We head beyond the horizon
boku wa ima sagashi hajimeta mizushibuki agete
Making a splash, I've just started on my search
hateshinaku tsudzuku sekai e
Heading towards a world without end
afuredasu jounetsu o mune ni doko made mo yuku yo
My heart bursting with enthusiasm, I'll go to the ends of the earth
mada minu HIKARI motome
In search of light yet unseen
I am... I am... the man who'll become Pirate King!
Please... stop fighting!
The battle will end...
The rain falling right now...
...will fall again as it used to...
...since our nightmares are... all over...
A Farewell to Arms!
Pirates and Different
Ideas of Justice
The nightmares are over...?
You can't be serious!
There's no way what happened
was just "nightmares"!
That's right! We saw the king attack Nanohana with our own eyes!
That's right!
Koza-san was also shot by the Royal Army!
How do you explain the Royal Army's
misconduct up until now?!
That's not good enough for
those who fell in this rebellion!
That's right! That's right!
Drop your weapons! Royal Army!
Chaka-sama!
Chaka...
Hey, what's going on?
You...
Ma-ma-ma...
You too, Rebel Army!
I... Igaram-san!
Squad Captain!
Igaram...
Igaram-san...
Let us meet safely at our motherland.
That's the old pervert from Whisky Peak!
– So he was alive!
– Uhm, who's that?
Hey, can you talk?
Yes...
That's the boy from Nanohana...
That's right... He's the kid who
was harmed by the Royal Army.
It's not true...
They weren't the ones who hurt me...
Everyone, listen! I saw it!
I just can't feel relaxed without this on!
It's vague!
That's right...
This battle was a plot from the beginning...
– Koza-san!
– Leader!
I will explain everything...
that happened to this country.
Everyone, drop your weapons!
Vivi-sama!
Where's... everyone?
Hey, walk steady.
Ahh... Well, listen... I'm coming down
with "if I walk more, I'll die" disease...
Then stay there.
What?! Well, w-wait! Whoa! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Why're you pulling me by my foot?
– Hm?
– Found him?
Who are you?
Ahh...
Thanks for carrying that guy on your back.
He's one of ours. I'll take him now.
Then you're the pirates who brought Vivi back to this country?
Who are you, old guy?
Daddy!
Everyone!
Ah, it's Vivi!
Daddy?
Vivi-chan's father?!
Are you the King?
I prepared myself to die at one point,
but he saved me...
When his body was exhausted
after the fight with Crocodile,
he carried two people and rushed above ground.
What unbelievable strength...
Then there's no more need
to worry about the poison?
Right. It should be neutralized by now.
But his injuries need to be treated...
Yours, too...
More importantly, Vivi, go already.
– What?
– Go back to the Square.
Of course! The rebellion has finally stopped.
It wouldn't be proper if the king
or princess didn't say a few words.
Yes... then I'll tell them about you, too.
Vivi-chan. You know how it is...
We're notorious.
We have no intention of
getting involved with a country.
I'm hungry.
We're going on ahead to the palace.
I'm exhausted.
Okay, understood, Captain Smoker.
Then Crocodile-san was...?
This guy was the ringleader for everything...?
Good heavens... I can't believe it...
Hey, look at that! It's the Navy!
We were told that a Baroque Works-owned
artificial rain-making ship
was discovered with dance powder on it.
Sir Crocodile, president of the
secret crime syndicate Baroque Works
and one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
Where did the gator go?!
In the name of Navy Headquarters,
an agency directly under the World Government,
I hereby strip you of your
authorization to capture enemy ships,
as well as all the titles and rights
bestowed upon you by the Government.
Just wait and see...
We've done an irreparable thing...
Leader...
I don't know what to say to them...
It's just natural to regret.
That unbearable feeling is also natural...
King...
Your Majesty...
We lost so much and gained nothing...
However, this is a step forward!
No matter who you fought against,
the battle did occur and has now ended...
King...
No one can make the past go away.
Overcome this war and survive...!
He truly is without equal...
Alabasta Kingdom!
The battle that will be engraved in history and...
...the battle that will never be told...
...have ended...
Smoker-kun! What on earth is this rain?
Don't tell me you used the Dance Powder?!
You idiot.
I do know better than to commit a crime.
The Alabasta King kept his hands off of this powder.
What's the point in me going
against his morals now?
Oh, excuse me. I apologize.
I can't believe the "White Hunter"
of all men would say something sweet.
I wonder if you've mellowed out a little...
That's none of your business.
At any rate, you're really something,
using my elite unit just to look for a ship.
Very upset... I'm upset!
We joined the Navy in the same year.
Don't say that.
You always say that. I pity Tashigi
for the troubles you put her through.
More importantly, take in
this artificial rain-making ship.
Why?
And also, Tashigi will bring Crocodile here.
So take him, too.
Give me a break!
What makes you think you can be so selfish?
Heads!
It's tails. You lose.
You're really selfish, you know that?!
You haven't changed a bit since we
joined the Navy. I'm disappointed.
That's fine. I'm well aware of it.
That's an order.
Sergeant Major!
This is a very rare opportunity!
Once they come to, we won't be able to...
I will not allow you to lay
a hand on them right now!
Wh-Why?! They're all sitting ducks right now!
O-On top of that...
Leader... Are your injuries okay?
You're not gonna die, are you?
Uhm, Toto-ojisan was... Yuba was...
Vivi... Looks like you're still
the worrywart as always...
I don't know about Yuba,
but my stubborn old man won't die,
no matter what happens.
– Leader...
– And I've got his blood in my veins.
As soon as I get treated, I'll head to Yuba.
I'll keep you updated... so don't worry.
Okay...
It's raining!
Rain!
It's raining for the first time in three years!
This rain will end the rebellion!
Our foolish sons will come back!
It's raining!
Just how long are you gonna
stay so stubborn, old man?!
Yuba is already finished.
What're you gonna do here by yourself?
Are you gonna die with the city? Old man!
Look... Koza. The rain has fallen.
Just three years... That's all.
Right... rain...?
The rain is no longer forced and
falls endlessly within the kingdom.
Vivi-sama... You're still up?
Igaram...
Can't sleep?
It's not that.
I just don't want to.
I just wanna keep watching this rain.
About Pell...
He is the most dignified and
strongest among the warriors I know.
Yes...
I wanted to say "thank you" to him...
He'd be... greatly honored by that...
Captain Smoker, Miss Hina!
Sergeant Major Tashigi has arrived.
Welcome back.
It's been a while, Tashigi.
Hina-san...
Hello... I'm... a little tired,
so I'll go get some rest...
Captain Smoker, I've just returned!
Yeah, thanks for your work.
I heard about what happened with the Straw Hats.
I'm sorry...
I helped the pirates and let our
opportunity to capture them slip away.
I know that my actions
were shameful as a marine.
Why do you apologize?
Didn't you follow your justice?
No... that's not it...
Sergeant Major...
I just... didn't have any other choice...
Losers can't speak about justice.
We're in that kind of sea.
Where did the gator go?!
Tell me!
Even when I knew where the enemy was,
all I could do was tell him where...
Even when I knew the time of the attack,
all I could do was assist them...
There was... no justice that I could follow...
Those who you thought you
were on par with up until recently
are becoming more notorious and rising rapidly.
They know that in this sea,
they'll die if they don't rise up.
Go forward or die?
Who decided to come to this sea?
Excuse me... but I'll go rest a bit.
You idiot...
If you're frustrated enough to cry,
become stronger!
I will!
I wish you guys had guts like that, too...
Now, bring them to the ship!
Yes, sir!
Captain Smoker!
You have a communication from Headquarters!
Hm?
This is Navy Headquarters.
Is this Captain Smoker?
Speaking.
In regards to your subduing Crocodile,
it's been decided that the top
officials of the Government
are going to give you and
Sergeant Major Tashigi a medal.
Subduing...? Hey, wait a sec!
It wasn't us who took Crocodile down.
Were they really listening to the report?
Furthermore, each of you will
be promoted by one rank, so...
Hey! Listen up!
The ones who've been fighting Crocodile
and his Baroque Works all this time
were the Straw Hat gang.
It's no use, Smoker-kun.
The Government is probably
going to cover up this incident.
Everyone at the Government was
outwitted with regard to Alabasta's crisis.
You think they can tell the world
that it was saved by pirates?
Therefore, we'd like both of you to
attend the medal award ceremony and...
You can't be serious!
Smoker-kun! Accept it!
If you disobey the top officials,
you don't know what'll happen to you!
We took Crocodile down?!
My subordinate is in tears
because we couldn't do it.
Hey, you... Could you tell the old
geezers at the top something for me...?
Huh?
Smoker-kun!
"Go to hell"!
Doko ni mukatte hashireba
Which direction should I run towards
Motto suteki na ashita ni aeru?
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
Kaji o totte mune ni shimatta
I took the helm and opened the
Kiseki no chizu o hirogeta
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
Sora o mezashite yume o sagashite
I aimed for the sky and sought out my dreams,
Michi ni mayotta toki mo aru
though at times I got lost
Yume ja nakute kimi to deatte
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
Suteki na jibun o mitsuketa
I discovered the wonderful person in me
Chiisana yuuki kara
With just a bit of courage,
ookina mono te ni shita
I gained something grand
"Negai" o ima koso "chikai" ni kaete
Now's the time for my "wish" to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Mirai no monogatari o egakou
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
Atarashii kaze ni subete no omoi nosete ima...
I'll put all my feelings in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
Doko made mo oikakete Shining ray
I'll chase after you wherever you go, Shining ray
Uhm, I'm Usopp, chief of the party department.
Thanks to all of you, we were able to
take down the detestable Crocodile...
Hm? Hey! Don't eat it yet!
Well, when we think of it, it was a tough battle.
Okay, okay! Well then, everyone!
Eat, drink and party like crazy for now!
Yeah!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Pirates' Banquet and
Operation Escape from Alabasta!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Pirates' Banquet and
Operation Escape
from Alabasta!