Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the Pirate King,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
rashinban nante jyuutai no moto
compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
delirious with fever, i take the helm
hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
if the dusty treasure map has been verified,
tashikameta no nara densetsu janai
it's not a legend!
kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
when it comes to personal storms,
biorizumu nokkatte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
omoi sugoseba ii
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kaki atsume
we're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashi mono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
poketto no koin
a coin in my pocket,
soreto You Wanna Be My Friend
and do you wanna be my friend?
We Are
we are!
Big Bro!
Even if it's an injury that kills
ordinary people, I must not die!
Dragon Twister!!
I have to hurry up and rescue Luffy...
Such an idiot!
Sorry. This is all we can do right now.
I see.
That means that if I kick and break that rock...
Realize... that you all are mere humans!
Proud Warriors!
Sanji and Usopp's
Fierce Battles
Hmph! A man from Cocoyashi Village...
You're wasting your time...
Dammit! He found me!
What's the point of extending his life like that?!
I'll sink you as well!
No way I'll let you!
You damn human!
Are you seriously trying
to fight me in the water?!
You're an inferior species that has
to worry about holding your breath!
Okay, I'll fight.
Fishman Karate! Duelling Hair Tether!
You son of a...
What's that?
The power of your kick dropped in half.
That's the limit for humans.
But Fishman Karate's power
doesn't drop even in the water!
Rather, depending on the technique, the power doubles.
Fishman Karate! Instant Undersea...
...Bowel Buster!!
Fishman Karate!
Flaming Axe Kick!
Back Foot Jawbreaker!
Special Attack!
Guffaw Palm Bomb!!
Yeah!
Air! Air! Air! Air! Oxygen! Air!
I let out too much air! I can't breathe!
Where're you going?
Dammit! Let me through.
I need air! Let me breathe!
Seriously, what amazing strength...
I can't believe he's human.
Let me breathe...
If I remember correctly,
you said that those who harm a lady are crap.
But look how it's turning out.
This is the outcome of your cheap chivalry.
You won't be able to escape
from me and will die.
That policeman and the rubber man will also die.
Zoro, that long-nose man and the
rebel villagers... They'll all be killed.
With all that's happened,
Nami won't get away with betraying us!
Do you get it?
With your superficial chivalry,
you can't protect anyone,
let alone Nami, after all!!
Even if you're kinda strong,
that's just silly talk by a helpless human.
You humans can't handle a sudden
change in water pressure, right?
In other words, if you rapidly dive into the abyss...
your organs will burst out of your body.
Pulverizing Pressure Plunge!!
I'm not gonna let him get away with this!
I can't protect anyone?!
This man won't die yet?
Then, I'll give you that attack as you wish!!
They use pulmonary respiration on land
but switch to branchial respiration in water.
Which means that he's just
a talking fish right now.
Can you bear a second time?
A fish'll die if air is shot into its branchia.
If you're also a fish, you'll feel the same pain!
Hm?
You...
Hey...
Don't worry. He's okay.
Really?!
Yeah, sort of.
Sort of?
I'll explain it later.
Anyhow, come out of the water,
you damn fish! Let's settle this!
You still don't get it, do you?
Whether it's in the water or
on the ground, it's the same.
I'm really angry!
I'll make you experience the
essence of Fishman Karate!
The earlier attack I used to send you
flying was the Hundred-Brick Fist!
But my ultimate attack
is the Thousand-Brick Fist!
Your survival probability is... zero!!
Collier!
My chivalry is naive?
Epaule!
I can't protect anyone, you said?
Cotelette! Selle! Poitrine!
Gigot!
You...
Son of a bitch!
Ultimate Fist! Thousand-Brick!
Mouton... Shot!!
I guess...
...he doesn't want dessert?
What was that?! What's happening?!
Kuroobi...
Hachi...
They're small fish, after all.
It's a million and fifty thousand years
too early for them to go against a cook.
We win this game.
How dare you bastards beat my
dear brothers one after another...?
Aren't you getting a little too carried away?!
Hey, what do you mean
by Luffy being sort of okay?
It means that he won't die for the time being.
But to revive him, I have to go
into the sea one more time...
...though it doesn't seem like
that guy's gonna let me...
Amazing... They're really amazing!
They beat two of the Arlong Pirates' leaders!
This is it. I can no longer hold my breath!
Gen-san, take my place.
I'll go in this time.
His color has improved considerably.
He spit out quite a bit of water.
What's going on over there?
Don't worry. Everyone's still alive.
In fact...
...although it's hard to believe,
this fight is giving me hope...
the hope that I've been holding back...!
Geez... Causing me all these troubles...
What amazing ability to run away!
But that was too easy...
He died instantly with a shot of my Squirt Gun.
Hmph! I guess I should head back.
The others should be done by now.
I'm saved! It worked!
I'm so glad I made Ketchup Star for times like this.
He thinks his Squirt Gun or whatever
actually hit me. Go back already!
Seriously... What a scary species they are...
They turned the houses in town upside down...
Well, I feel sorry for Nami and
I really want to help her, but...
Hm?
I guess it was just my imagination.
I think I'll pass on dying.
B... But actually, although I'm covered in fake blood,
I want something that shows
a trace of deadly combat.
Oh, yeah. If I show up with my body all
covered in mud, it may look that way.
I'd say something like, "Ahh, sorry. I lost."
Hmmm.
I wonder if, "Well, I let that bastard slip away,
though I was this close," is better...
Or that may not be quite convincing...
We're friends now, aren't we?
"Well, don't cry, Nami.
We only did what was right."
I'd rather die than lose.
"Well, we all fought very well."
He's 100 times better than a
damn gang that'd hurt a lady.
"Well, it certainly was a deadly combat."
It's for my business!
This was my only choice!
"Well, my injuries aren't that bad."
Big Sis Nami was crying.
Do they need any more reason than
that to put their lives on the line?
Nami was only ten.
Do you know how painful of a choice it was?
Let's fight!!
"Well, the way... I fought... was really..."
How...
How shameful...!
How... shameful I am!
Hold it, you damn fish!!
Oh? You're still alive?
Of course! No way that staggering
shots by a half-fish would hit me!
The moment I left my village,
I gave up on things...
...like peace and safety...
Because they live risking their lives everyday, they laugh so happily!
That's why I decided to set out to the sea.
I wanted to laugh from the bottom of my heart, too!
If I don't fight with all my might here,
I won't have the right to be
on board the same ship as them.
I won't have the right to laugh from
the bottom of my heart with them!!
Are you an idiot?
You should've just pretended to be dead...
Even your brain is inferior...
I'm done...
Yeah, you're right!
You're already done for!
I'm done!
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Rubberband of Doom!
Ahhh! Dammit!
What a stupid trap I fell into!
That son of a bitch...!
– Special Attack! Lead Star!
– Alcohol?
How dare you do all these
impudent things, you feeble species!
No matter where you hide, I'll blow
you away using this rice field water!
Impudent or whatever... It doesn't matter.
At any rate, as a man,
I can't run away from this fight.
Yeah, if I lose, I'll die.
But I'm already a pirate!
Squirt Cannon!
Oh, my... What power...!
Why do I have to fight
against an idiot like that?
He's completely exposing himself!
You're gonna be swiss cheese!
Squirt Machine Gun!
Ahhh!
H-How did he figure out where I was?!
Dammit! Dammit!
Just watch me, Usopp Pirates, Kaya!
I set off to the sea and became a pirate!!
I'll fight! In order to become a real,
brave sea warrior, not a fake one!
I'm done pretending to be a pirate!
What'd you say's done?
This fight!
You know, alcohol catches fire!
Special Attack! Fire Star!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Water! Water!
Water! Water! Water! Water!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
This isn't good!
Water, water, water! Water!
Usopp Hammer!!
You son of a bitch...!
Ugh! Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Rubberband of Doom!
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!!
I win! I beat a Fishman!
It serves you right!
I can do it, too, if I try!
Did you see that?!
Don't make light of me, you bastards!!
Please... come back to life!
Come back to life quick!
Or it'll be too late!
Your friends are... Your friends are...!
I thought that they had a chance in this fight.
Was it just a dream...?
What did that damn shark do?
I don't know.
As soon as he shot water,
they both vomited blood and flew...
I can kill humans like you
without even directly touching
you if I have some water.
That's the difference between Fishmen and humans.
Give me a break!
This isn't funny...
Just a water shooting game to him
is like a shotgun shot to us...
So this is the power of a shark...
And he's in a class by himself among Fishmen...
He's in another league...
Die already.
Your lives are not worth that much.
Arlong!!
Big Sis Nami!
Nami-san!
Nacchan...
Hey, Nami!
I was about to crush some pirates just now.
What did you come here for?
To kill you...
hamidashita kimochi tsunagara nakute
my overflowing feelings don't connect
kimi no te o gyutto ni girikaesu yo
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
hitori demo boku wa arukidasu kara
I'll set off by myself,
tooku made zutto mitsumeteite ne
so keep watching me intently as I go into the distance
kesa kara chotto kangaeteita
I was thinking about it a bit since this morning
doushite konna ni atsui no
why is it so hot?
itsu kara ka sonna koto bakari ga
starting from some point,
hanarenai yo
I haven't been able to get away from that
kakedashita kimochi tsukamaetakute
I want to catch those feelings that rushed off,
jibun sae mou oikoshite yuku yo
and I'm already about to overtake myself, even
tobidashita yume o dakishimetetai
I want to embrace my dreams that have jumped out
issho nara boku wa hashitte yukeru
with you, I can run there
I'll hold back that half-fish bastard.
You go into the sea!
Yeah! Leave Luffy to me!
All right! I've got your back!
Hey! You've got my back from that far?!
Ahh... My "Do Not Fight Arlong" disease is...
That's a lie, isn't it?
Ahh! I'm saved!
Next time, on One Piece:
Luffy at Full Power!
Nami's Determination and the Straw Hat
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Luffy at Full Power!
Nami's Determination
and the Straw Hat