Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has rushed to Marineford,
scene of a battle between
the Whitebeard Pirates and the Navy...
...to rescue his brother, Ace!
Attention, all ships and soldiers!
When you are all set,
we move the schedule forward...
...and execute Ace immediately. That's all.
Luffy-kun...
Let's move!
Let's go!
H-Hey!
No! That's not the side!
Ace!!
H-Hey, don't tell me that's...!
Crocodile!
That's not all! Who is in that lineup?!
All forces are here on both sides! There are a lot of big names!
The world's got to be ready for it!
Ace, we're coming to rescue you!
We're here for you!
Garp! It's your family again!
Luffy!
Grandson of the "Hero of the Marines"—Garp—
and son of the Revolutionary—Dragon.
I'll take care of him for good!
Where's Croco-boy?
Oh? I think he chickened out and...
There he is!
He went ahead of me!
Long time no see, Whitebeard.
You never learn.
Now that we are here,
our agreement has been fulfilled.
Why do you want to protect Whitebeard?!
As I thought—this old man is Whitebeard.
Then leave him alone! Ace likes this old man!
Ace's brother is quite a fighter.
You came here to rescue your brother?
Yeah.
Do you know who you're messing with?!
A squirt like you will be dead meat!
Shut up! That's not up to you to decide!
I know what you're up to!
You wanna become the Pirate King, right?!
But I'm the one who'll become the King!
How saucy you are!
I won't forgive you
if you cause me trouble, spoiled brat!
I'm gonna do as I like!
I'm gonna rescue Ace!
Even If It Means Death
Luffy vs. the Navy; The Battle Starts
He's the... rookie—Straw Hat!
How does he know Whitebeard?
I don't get it!
He should hide after breaking out
of the great prison!
Why bother coming to this living hell?!
Because he is Luffy-san.
Huh?
That's the way he is!
Pops! Luffy!
So he is Straw Hat.
Old man.
Hmmm?
I heard while on a Navy ship that...
He's such a bonehead!
I wish he'd just get his ass kicked already! Stupid!
How brave he is! Only his son could do it.
So they're gonna execute Ace immediately?
Are you sure?
They said they would after getting "all set" for something...
...but they were using codes so I couldn't understand.
I know that you wanna rescue Ace, too, so I wanted to share that with you!
I see. That was important information.
Thank you.
No problem.
How can he talk on equal terms with Whitebeard?!
Okay! Ace, I'm coming now!
Why is he so confident?
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Get outta my way!
So he is Ace's brother.
Keep up with the boy! Let's go, 3rd division!
We should go, too!
Wh-Wh-What?!
Really?!
14th division, let's charge ahead!
Yes, Commander Jill!
Luffy...
They're so encouraged by just one daredevil?
But our strategy is airtight.
Don't hesitate! Do as I said!
Damn Sengoku!
I bet he thinks that he doesn't need
to stick to the schedule
for the execution of a mere pirate.
The key is—after they're "all set" for what?
Pops! I heard that they're moving
Ace's execution forward!
I heard. How're Squard and the others doing?
They're tied up with the vice admirals
at the bay head. I'm gonna fly there and help...
No, wait.
I bet it must be a part of his plan that we'd get some leaked information and advance.
Sengoku wouldn't let his enemy know his strategy so easily.
He's not that foolish.
Keep going!
A kick at the speed of light?!
Don't push your luck.
I won't let you invade that easily.
It's Admiral Yellow Monkey!
You're the guy from Sabaody!
Yes, I was gonna ruin you there
because the Celestial Dragons wanted it.
Straw Hat Luffy.
S-Straw Hat is dead!
Death...
...Wink!
No! I wanna go home!
What, Captain Buggy?!
I can't believe what you just said!
You mean you wanna destroy
Yellow Monkey quickly so you can rush home?
Only a legendary pirate
could face Admiral Yellow Monkey without fear!
You guys are too positive!
Straw-boy, are you okay?
That was close! Thanks, Iva-chan!
My only mission is to save you!
Yellow Monkey, again!
Huh? No, it's not! That's...
Kuma!
He's the bear-like guy who blew us all away!
Rolling Spa!
Bartholomew Kuma!
How despicable you are!
I know that you have a role as a Warlord but...
...we've known each other so long. How can you just fire a laser at me?!
Hey, how could you...
A hole!
Iva-chan!
Don't worry about me!
Leave this to me and just go ahead!
Okay!
Let's do this!
It's so unlucky of you to run into us!
Straw Hat, you're gonna die here!
Huh? Who are you?
I'm Fullbody!
You gotta pay for what happened
at the on-the-sea restaurant—Baratie!
Oh, Sanji beat you there.
You should remember this chakram.
You're the hypnotist
from Usopp's village. Why're you here?
I honed my skill in the Navy.
With two chakrams, it's twice as effective.
When I say "one, two, Django," you're gonna get tired.
One, two...
...Django!
What are you two doing?
Hina disappointed.
I know you from Alabasta, don't I?
I have no time to play with you people now!
I won't let you get away! Kimono Sleeve Cage!
I will bind anyone who passes through me!
That's her signature phrase!
Miss Hina is so captivating!
I'm sick of being in bars! Gear 2!
Th-That was fast! I couldn't see him!
Hina failed!
We failed, too!
We're bound by Miss Hina—body and soul!
Marineford bay head
Don't fight the vice admirals alone!
They'll defeat you!
Captain Squard! It's getting frantic inside the bay!
I know!
I gotta hurry up and get to Ace.
The wall that Oars broke.
If I sneak in from here, maybe I can outsmart them.
You are...!
Stop!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
They're all strong!
Straw Hat! He's high-spirited as usual!
Oh yeah! I'll cut his shadow off and implant it in Oars again!
Come on, zombie soldiers!
Alright, zombie soldiers!
Go ahead and capture Straw Hat!
Moria! I don't wanna deal with him now!
Take your bullets back!
They're multiplying!
Yes, because this is a battlefield
and all the corpses provide fresh zombies!
Capture Straw Hat!
He's the main suspect of the escape!
Keep going!
He's got to fight all these officers!
I wonder how long he can hang on!
Luffy!
Stay away, Luffy!
I know that you know it!
We're both pirates!
We both sailed on the sea as we liked!
I have my own adventures!
I have my own friends!
Ace!
I want you to...
...keep your hands off of them!
A wimp like you wants to save me?!
Outta my way!
You think that I'll allow you to do that?!
It's so humiliating!
Go back, Luffy! Why did you come here?!
I beg you, Luffy! I don't want you to share my fate!
This is all my fault!
I'm...
...your brother!
Did you know?
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
From now on, we're brothers!
Did he just say "I'm your brother?"
He's also a son of Roger?
When Ace was born, both of
his parents died. That's impossible!
I don't give a damn about...
...the rules of pirates!
You hardhead!
Go, zombie soldiers!
S-Seawater?
Jinbe!
If I remember correctly, Moria, your zombie soldiers can't take salt.
Luffy-kun, let me handle them!
Great!
First Son of the Sea Jinbe!
The former Warlord.
What are you doing?!
Don't let this rookie take control of the war!
Move out of the way!
I'm gonna crush him up!
He's also a loose cannon!
He grew up together with Ace as his step-brother
and he's a biological son
of the Revolutionary Dragon!
The Revolutionary Dragon?!
The worst criminal in history?!
Sounds very familiar!
His daddy's got such a big name!
He revealed it!
Luffy-san...!
Luffy...
I couldn't care less even if you were the devil's son!
I didn't know that!
That explains everything!
You bastard! Gum-Gum Pistol!
I finally understand what happened at Loguetown!
That's why Dragon saved Luffy.
Did you hear that?
They mean that Dragon?!
Head Office! I'm calling from Sabaody!
We've got big news!
Spread this all over the world!
We can't allow him to live!
Kill him at any cost!
Who cares? There's no need to hide it anyway.
That label won't hurt him
because Luffy is already a notorious outlaw.
You brothers are both fools.
Gear 3:
Gum-Gum...
...Gigant...
...Rifle!
Ace!
You can say whatever you want!
I'm gonna save you even if it means death!
That brat!
We all feel the same way!
We're Ace's family, too!
We're gonna save him at any cost!
Marco, we can't let that kid die.
Alright.
Luffy!
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates
continue to run forward.
As he watches his friends face off against foes with awesome powers,
Ace comes to a decision.
Meanwhile, the Navy enacts a new plan.
Next time, on One Piece:
"Hard Battles, One After Another!
Devil Fruit Users vs. Devil Fruit Users"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Hard Battles, One After Another!
Devil Fruit Users vs. Devil Fruit Users