Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was still a crybaby
Desperately chasing after someone's back,
thinking "I want to become stronger"
Now my "Thank you" has disappeared into the wind
Am I becoming stronger?
I can't find my answer
So I'll keep on moving forward
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
I can hear the voice inside my head
Always, always lifting me up
Even when the mischievous rain gets in my way,
I won't try to run away
Come on, let's go,
and keep moving no matter what
So that the flow of time won't get the better of us
We'll keep getting up, again and again
Because we don't want to lose what's important to us
Let's head toward the future we believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, the Pirate King.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea
to become the next Pirate King.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less
able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace, who was to be executed!
Blackbeard who acquired
Whitebeard's power now is in a standoff
with the Navy at the plaza!
Meanwhile, Luffy has collapsed after Ace's death and...
...Jinbe rushes to the bay head in order to help him escape!
Let's start with sinking Marineford into the water!
Shock Wave!
A building can easily be rebuilt!
But the island of Marineford
is the hub of the world!
To all the citizens of the world,
who fear the villains that roam the seas,
it is important that we are here!
Justice and righteousness will never perish!
Don't you dare speak lightly of sinking this island,
you little punk!
Well, then:
defend this place—if you can!
Destroy them!
Destroy them!!
What is this?!
I'll have an advantage once we get
to the sea! I can outrun him!
Oh no! It's frozen!
Sables!
You gotta protect the one you wanna protect!
Don't let them have their way!
What is that?! A ship came out of the water!
That's a submarine!
Whose ship is that?
Put Straw Hatter on my ship!
"Straw Hatter"?
That sure is a strange way to call somebody!
Who the hell are you, brat?!
I'll help him escape! Leave him to me!
W-What?!
I'm a doctor!
A Desperate Scream
The Fateful Moment of Courage
Are you kidding me?! Doctors don't carry swords!
Do you visit your patients by submarine?!
What's wrong?! Who is it?!
Trafalgar Law, a rookie from the North Blue!
What?!
That rookie must be
Straw Hat Luffy's accomplice
whom we weren't able to catch when they had trouble with...
...the Celestial Dragons on Sabaody Archipelago!
He came to save Luffy by submarine!
You're too slow! Hand him over already!
I said who the hell are you?!
Captain Law! Navy ships
are approaching off the stern!
Hurry up! Put those two on this ship!
I said "move out of my way"!
It's amazing that such
rascal pirates like you guys...
...are risking your lives to protect the son
of the worst criminal—the Revolutionary, Dragon!
Stop undermining the wheels of justice!
Hound Blaze!
Stop Red Hound here!
I won't let him lay a finger on Ace's brother again!
Listen all Navy soldiers!
Divide into two forces! Pursue the Whitebeards
and intercept the Blackbeards!
Navy soldiers are coming up from underground!
There's tunnels?!
We have backup! Great!
Let's get them at once!
Hey, Coby?! Are you alright?!
You're acting weird!
Only the man reigning over
the Navy could do that!
Sengoku the Buddha, very impressive.
But that's not enough
to defend this island against me!
Shut your big mouth already! And be gone from Marineford!
B-Blackbeard has...
...Stopped the shock wave of the Fleet Admiral!
Let me give you a hand, Captain!
W-What was that?!
Garp!
I'm a Navy soldier, too.
I have a duty to defend Marineford!
You washed-up old farts!
Take a good look!
Captain, we'll soon be in range of the Navy ships!
Do something, Bepo!
What?! Don't act like you're the captain, darn newcomer!
They're coming on this side too!
Finish them off with a barrage!
Fire! Fire!
Wh-What is this?!
This is...!
Blackbeard is using the power of the Tremor-Tremor Fruit
that he stole from Whitebeard!
But it's way more powerful compared to
when he destroyed the HQ building!
Not only the ground!
The sky and the sea... Everything is shaking!
What wonderful power!
I won't let you get away!
We're not letting you any further!
Not again!
Stop the Navy soldiers right here!
Let as many of our people escape as possible!
No way! We won't let even one of you get away!
You just put on another great show!
But I can't control this power very well yet!
Hey, Captain! If you aren't careful,
we'll lose the ground we're standing on, too!
Blackbeard, you bastard!
Whitebeard would be horrified
to know this punk is using his power!
How do you like that,
"Buddha" Sengoku and "Hero" Garp?!
Do you think you can stop me?!
Your time ended with Whitebeard's death!
What will Blackbeard do next?!
I'm scared!
He's terrifying!
Urgent! After the earthquake that hit Marineford,
a tsunami warning has been issued
for the south shore of Sabaody Archipelago.
We assure you there's no cause for panic, please remain calm.
Run!
Please evacuate to the north side—
the elevated areas of Grove 40 or 50.
Move! What are you doing?!
I'm a nobleman! I'll pay you to let me go first!
Everybody, please remain calm.
The Pacifistas are getting over the crack in the plaza!
Follow the Pacifistas!
Don't let the pirates get away! Go!
H-Hey!
You guys should go ahead and get on a ship!
But...
Did you forget Pops' order?!
We gotta get back to the New World
with as many alive as we can!
I got it!
Alright, stay with me!
We won't let you go! None of you will survive!
Pops, I'm sorry! I'm gonna disobey your order for the first time!
I'm gonna die here!
Me, too! I'm gonna follow Pops to heaven!
Finally, it stopped shaking!
What's the matter with you?!
I don't know! I feel sad!
Sad?!
I can hear voices in my head disappearing one by one!
Huh? Voices?
We'll show you the justice of the Navy!
Is this what you call "justice"?!
Stop the Navy soldiers here!
No way! Destroy the pirates!
That's for my friend who died in the war!
Damn pirates! Go to hell...
Let's teach them!
We're the ones that will
conquer the world, not the pirates!
I got one!
What are you talking about?!
Are you losing your mind?! Get ahold of yourself!
H-Help me!
Run!
Coby! H-Hey! Where are you going?!
Let as many of our people escape as possible!
Stay with me! He's alive! Let's get him treated!
I-I don't wanna die!
Forget about him! The war is not over yet.
But...
Now is our chance to show them
the power of our justice!
There's no time to help the wounded! Go!
Y-Yes, sir!
Corner the pirates! Destroy them—every last man!
Somebody, give me a hand! Somebody!
Destroy all the damn pirates!
The Navy soldiers are still motivated even though we achieved our goal!
Guns don't work!
Run!
Chase them!
Damn villains!
Something is not right—with either side!
We're not content even though we won!
Damn!
Listen, guys!
As long as you're a Navy soldier,
you can't forgive those thugs, the pirates!
Curiel!
Admiral Sakazuki!
Hey, are you alright?!
H-Hey!
No one can stop me!
I'm gonna destroy everything—devour everything!
B-Blackbeard! He's pretty scary!
I gotta leave here as soon as possible!
Why don't you leave Straw Hat Luffy here?
Ugh! It's...!
It's Yellow Monkey!
Get them on the ship!
Alright, I leave them to you, Whoever You Are!
Do your best!
Catch them, Jean Bart!
Yeah, that's it!
Submerge!
How dare you get away
from us at Sabaody, Trafalgar Law?
He's severely wounded! Is he alive?!
Let's hurry!
Dammit!
Give it up!
That's enough!
A Navy soldier?
Coby!
Let's end this now!
Let's not fight anymore!
What is he doing?
S-Somebody...
H-Help me!
We're throwing away people's lives!
Every single soldier has a family
that's waiting for them to come home!
We've accomplished our goal already
but we're still chasing the pirates who don't have any will to fight!
We could stop but we're coveting more!
We're giving up on our soldiers,
who could be saved
if we treated their wounds right away!
But still, we keep multiplying the number of victims!
Soldiers who die from here on...
Is that Coby?
They're just fools who will die for nothing!
Huh? Who are you?!
You've wasted my time!
We have no use for a soldier who doesn't believe in justice!
Oh no, I'm going to die!
But I said it! I said what I had to say!
I have no regret!
Coby!
Good job, young Navy soldier.
That moment of courage,
you risked your life for,
will have a massive impact...
on the destiny of the world,
be that for better or worse.
Hurry up! Bring him inside!
Not a chance!
Don't do anything, Yellow Monkey!
Oops, you're Benn Beckman!
Huh? That's...! That ship is...!
Let's go!
Why is one of the Four Emperors of the New World here?!
Red-Haired Shanks!
I'm here to...
...end this war!
The Red-Haired Pirates
have appeared out of the blue!
Law tries to give Luffy a chance
to escape while the Navy catches their breath,
but the three admirals attack relentlessly.
Then Shanks reveals his real reason for appearing on the battlefield...
Next time, on One Piece:
"Here Comes Shanks!
The Paramount War is Finally Over"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!!
Here Comes Shanks!
The Paramount War is Finally Over